<text id="SE3Y">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:32</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-20</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0192 S0227</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In Dad's car between homes</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Phones, change in the area, speed cameras &amp; licenses, work, sickness, moving to Brighton, family, trip to Tanzania, putting on weight, racism, suicide, TV, board games, Game of Thrones, remembering the recording, flights</topics>
		<activity>Seeing dad for the first time in two years</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, requesting, anecdote telling, making arrangements, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T03</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0192">
				<exactage>28</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bedford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>English Language Instructor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2>Spanish</l2>
				<fls>Korean -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0227">
				<exactage>54</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Crayford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>9</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>customer services agent</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate; Spanish -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0227">my brick?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0192">yeah no this isn't a phone this is the er</u>
<u n="3" who="S0227">oh it's a</u>
<u n="4" who="S0192">the recorder</u>
<u n="5" who="S0227">what is it? oh the right</u>
<u n="6" who="S0192">this is the phone</u>
<u n="7" who="S0227">oh right I thought it was a phone I had a quick look and thought it</u>
<u n="8" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh no the phone is back there</u>
<u n="9" who="S0227">had a quick look and thought that that was your phone</u>
<u n="10" who="S0192">nope a recorder</u>
<u n="11" who="S0227">they all look similar nowadays</u>
<u n="12" who="S0192">my one's kind of bigger than that</u>
<u n="13" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="14" who="S0192">it's a touch screen one that mum gave me</u>
<u n="15" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="16" who="S0192">so you've got my mobile number now</u>
<u n="17" who="S0227">yes it's all logged into my little phone I I don't have my own phone that's that's it</u>
<u n="18" who="S0192">that's your work phone yeah?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0227">that's the work phone yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0192">yeah when you're not at work it's off</u>
<u n="21" who="S0227">exactly yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0192">yeah I can't believe two years have gone</u>
<u n="23" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="24" who="S0192">that's flown by hasn't it?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0227">did I have this when you were?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0192">you just got it just before I left</u>
<u n="27" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0192">I think I went in it once</u>
<u n="29" who="S0227">oh right yeah it's it's two years old now</u>
<u n="30" who="S0192">yeah still looking pretty new</u>
<u n="31" who="S0227">yeah it's not bad</u>
<u n="32" who="S0192">really new</u>
<u n="33" who="S0227">it needs a clean it's dirty</u>
<u n="34" who="S0192">have you seen the school they've built up here?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0227">er no but I know they've erm built a lot of stuff since you've gone on the er</u>
<u n="36" who="S0192">if you go down up to <anon type="place"/> there's a school</u>
<u n="37" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0192">there up there now</u>
<u n="39" who="S0227">I do tend to go up that way a bit</u>
<u n="40" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0227">but I don't erm take much notice and that if I was plopped further down there at that roundabout and I just was just woke up so that they said where are you know I'd know it now but if someone had said done that to me where I'd just been away when before it was all built and they just put me there I wouldn't know where I was</u>
<u n="42" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="43" who="S0227">and I was only a few yards away from a few hundred metres away from where I used to live</u>
<u n="44" who="S0192">yeah definitely when I was erm coming back from the airport <pause dur="short"/> mum was like oh there's a school that's been built around here now and I kind of had to double take and it took me a few moments to really really register where I was at that point</u>
<u n="45" who="S0227" trans="overlap">that's right yeah <pause dur="short"/> where you were yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0192">it's a bit weird <pause dur="short"/> and it's changed quite a lot around this way</u>
<u n="47" who="S0227">it is</u>
<u n="48" who="S0192">you go further into <anon type="place"/> there's no change at all</u>
<u n="49" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="50" who="S0192">but this was the rich area wasn't it</u>
<u n="51" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0192">it was on the cusp</u>
<u n="53" who="S0227">this was <pause dur="short"/> they're about to build on the inside of the <trunc>bar</trunc> bypass</u>
<u n="54" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0227">so this is what they've done and they're building all over here <pause dur="short"/> if I <unclear/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean they're not they're not bad houses</u>
<u n="57" who="S0227">oh no they're very nice</u>
<u n="58" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they're all quite nice yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0227">yeah they're very nice and they're well thought out and spaced around so <unclear>it's sort of</unclear></u>
<u n="60" who="S0192">so does it kind of up the area a little bit or?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0227">erm well it's not downgraded it but <unclear/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0192">no cos I was worried when they were gonna build it was all gonna get more scummy round here or something but</u>
<u n="63" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well I think we should build some social housing but I don't know well I think they probably have to build some social housing</u>
<u n="64" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0227">but erm</u>
<u n="66" who="S0192">some of that housing is <pause dur="short"/> cos it's quite nice</u>
<u n="67" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but erm but the architects er of of today seem to put more thought into design</u>
<u n="68" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0227">they don't they don't look like all erm erm all rabbit hutches or <unclear/> design</u>
<u n="70" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no there's a block there</u>
<u n="71" who="S0227">through through the haze of bong smoke or something and they were all all on crack</u>
<u n="72" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0227">at the time cos back in the sixties</u>
<u n="74" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0227">you wouldn't get the architecture of the sixties and seventies</u>
<u n="76" who="S0192">is terrible isn't it</u>
<u n="77" who="S0227">yeah it's awful</u>
<u n="78" who="S0192">almost communist or something isn't it</u>
<u n="79" who="S0227" trans="overlap">the the <trunc>tow</trunc> the town hall not the original town hall but the town hall I was in <pause dur="short"/> that mum was in</u>
<u n="80" who="S0192">that grey big it's a monstrous grey building yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0227" trans="overlap">is <unclear/> completely demolished</u>
<u n="82" who="S0192">oh good why is that?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0227">the flats have gone in <anon type="place"/> throughout yeah the town</u>
<u n="84" who="S0192">yes</u>
<u n="85" who="S0227"><unclear/> the bus station</u>
<u n="86" who="S0192">not all of them but some of them</u>
<u n="87" who="S0227">yeah some of them are gone</u>
<u n="88" who="S0192">I did notice that that had changed</u>
<u n="89" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0192">that was a bit strange</u>
<u n="91" who="S0227">they've got <trunc>s</trunc> average speed cameras down here not so you have to watch your speed as you go down here</u>
<u n="92" who="S0192">oh fair enough</u>
<u n="93" who="S0227"><unclear/> average ones and they've got er average ones in <anon type="place"/> as well</u>
<u n="94" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0227">just coming up to the average ones here</u>
<u n="96" who="S0192">does it mean average speed?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0227">yeah so you erm it</u>
<u n="98" who="S0192">never heard of that</u>
<u n="99" who="S0227">so you clock er down so he'll er er this camera this camera erm coming up on the right</u>
<u n="100" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0227">will clock our speed going and the one at the end will clock and take an average if we're over thirty odd it will get a speeding ticket</u>
<u n="102" who="S0192">oh fair so you get er two</u>
<u n="103" who="S0227">yeah so that one there <pause dur="short"/> and then you've got another one at the other end</u>
<u n="104" who="S0192">seems a bit slow for this road</u>
<u n="105" who="S0227">well it was a forty</u>
<u n="106" who="S0192">thirty?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0227">it was a forty</u>
<u n="108" who="S0192">oh a forty down to a thirty</u>
<u n="109" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah they've erm changed changed it</u>
<u n="110" who="S0192">why? doesn't there's no schools here is there</u>
<u n="111" who="S0227">er I don't know maybe someone was killed along here</u>
<u n="112" who="S0192">right</u>
<u n="113" who="S0227">normally there</u>
<u n="114" who="S0192">not very residential</u>
<u n="115" who="S0227">there's normally a fatality or something</u>
<u n="116" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0227">tends to er change it</u>
<u n="118" who="S0192">it's not a money maker then? I take it that if you get a ticket it's got nothing to do with making money it's not a <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="119" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="120" who="S0192">not a monetary fine it would be</u>
<u n="121" who="S0227">yeah it's a definite monetary fine it's a system to make money yeah sure</u>
<u n="122" who="S0192">at thirty I mean this is ridiculous you</u>
<u n="123" who="S0227">yeah <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0192">you might as well automate this there's no point in driving is there?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0227">but it ha</u>
<u n="126" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0227">they erm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0227">they can't really take it down to twenty cos twenty you know and get speed there are twenty</u>
<u n="130" who="S0192">you could</u>
<u n="131" who="S0227">they've got twenty zones</u>
<u n="132" who="S0192">you could cycle at twenty</u>
<u n="133" who="S0227">yep there are twenty zones but I don't think they'd ever ticket for going over twenty cos er to be honest you'd be <trunc>o</trunc> being overtaken by bicycles</u>
<u n="134" who="S0192">yeah it's difficult to stay at twenty isn't it</u>
<u n="135" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it would be a bit ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="137" who="S0227">so thirty is the is the <unclear/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0192">yeah fair enough</u>
<u n="139" who="S0227">now the camera is back there I think</u>
<u n="140" who="S0192">so you can speed up a bit</u>
<u n="141" who="S0227" trans="overlap">so I mean it's never one <anon type="place"/> I don't I got shot when I got in <anon type="place"/> once because I'd heard there was cameras going in I didn't question where they were cos I me of all people should know where the well I I work with the highways and I got up not the last Christmas but the Christmas before that</u>
<u n="142" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0227">and the one thing one of the guys um and er as we were driving through as I was driving through <anon type="place"/> he goes you know slow down mate there's average cameras I went what? he goes average cameras I said crap this was like the end of January when did they come in? he said I think I think it was about the beginning of January I thought oh my god <pause dur="short"/> I'd have been going home every day <pause dur="short"/> I I didn't come this way to work but cos I go through <unclear/> because it's not the school holiday er</u>
<u n="144" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0227">school term but I was coming home this way every time and I was thinking Jesus Christ you get so used to the route every day you don't think about it you know where the Gatso camera is</u>
<u n="146" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0227">well so you didn't take any notice I think additional signing and that but fortunately I never got caught so I'm alright</u>
<u n="148" who="S0192">you obviously drive well enough regardless of knowing that the cameras were there</u>
<u n="149" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> I was thinking I could I could have potentially up to about ten tickets which <unclear/> <trunc>wh</trunc><trunc>wh</trunc>which <trunc>f</trunc>four would put me up would ban me</u>
<u n="150" who="S0192" trans="overlap">coming through the post <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah it would wouldn't it</u>
<u n="151" who="S0227">I was um I know they've gotta arrive within fourteen days of of it being done</u>
<u n="152" who="S0192">so you're alright</u>
<u n="153" who="S0227">so every day after that I er was sweated in February</u>
<u n="154" who="S0192">oh yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0227">that year I didn't get one but I sweated</u>
<u n="156" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0227">yeah fucking hell</u>
<u n="158" who="S0192">not a good situation to be in</u>
<u n="159" who="S0227">no because you're thinking oh my god</u>
<u n="160" who="S0192">you lose your licence you lose your job don't you? I mean what do they do?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="162" who="S0192">you need to drive for your job</u>
<u n="163" who="S0227">I need to drive yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0192">what would happen in that that situation?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I think if I'd lost my licence I'd just go off and stress and they wouldn't even know about it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0192">no yeah don't tell them</u>
<u n="167" who="S0227">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0192">really really stressed</u>
<u n="169" who="S0227">yeah just go off and then</u>
<u n="170" who="S0192">cos I lost my licence</u>
<u n="171" who="S0227">go off</u>
<u n="172" who="S0192">you lose your licence for a little while though don't you?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0227">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0192">a year or?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><unclear/> you'd lose it for a year yep</u>
<u n="176" who="S0192">you can't stress er off on stress free?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0227">yeah well er <trunc>ironic</trunc> I'm not ironically but in coincidentally um I've been back to work a year yesterday</u>
<u n="178" who="S0192">oh yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0227">and that it's gone very er very fast</u>
<u n="180" who="S0192">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0227">I can't believe it a year has gone <unclear/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0192" trans="overlap">how long were you off for?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0227">twelve weeks</u>
<u n="184" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0227">twelve weeks <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>met</trunc> I stayed longer and made them suffer I made I punished them for the stupidity <pause dur="short"/> a stupid decision</u>
<u n="186" who="S0192">yeah that was when they tried piling you up with much too much work</u>
<u n="187" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0192">and ridiculously terrible time</u>
<u n="189" who="S0227">yeah I mean and redundancy straight redundancy as well so it was all kind of er and then was allowed to do I was still responsible for my tidying up the loose ends of my old job</u>
<u n="190" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0227">which was where the other people were starting new jobs with clean slates I wasn't I was thrown into <unclear/> an area that had been sadly neglected <trunc>har</trunc> er increased fifty per cent in size and that fifty per cent came from the other area that was neglected me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0192">so it needed a lot of work</u>
<u n="193" who="S0227">me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got thrown in there <pause dur="short"/> and yeah with that and er and especially <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> going blind was very erm was quite <trunc>stre</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I could have handled the work</u>
<u n="194" who="S0192">it doesn't get much more stressful does it <unclear/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah I could have handled the work if the if the work hadn't changed</u>
<u n="196" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0227">cos I did before erm because I had a solid you know you you stand on two feet and you kick one away you can potentially stand on one but if you kick both legs away</u>
<u n="198" who="S0192">yeah you fall over</u>
<u n="199" who="S0227" trans="overlap">you've got no leg to stand on like er no er rudder no <unclear/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0192">and you're still not sleeping great?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0227">er yeah I sleep fine as long as erm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0192">you're exhausted</u>
<u n="203" who="S0227">as long as I it's it's a mental thing <pause dur="short"/> I'll Sunday night I'll go into <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s room and then I'll stay in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s room until well I've I've slightly progressed <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> come I've been guiding <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to come in on a Thursday so he stays in his room which I could go in the front room but I don't I'm pretty tired but if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was to come sooner I'd be er and like by Monday if he came Monday I'd be going I'm not <unclear/> near tired tired enough I'd have to go and sleep in the front room which I don't particularly wanna do</u>
<u n="204" who="S0192">no yeah fine</u>
<u n="205" who="S0227">so</u>
<u n="206" who="S0192">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is moving out soon is he?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0227">he's moving out Friday</u>
<u n="208" who="S0192">okay so</u>
<u n="209" who="S0227">all his stuff's packed up <pause dur="short"/> he's got stuff to come from other places and he's so all all</u>
<u n="210" who="S0192">so this weekend?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0227">yeah all his stuff is</u>
<u n="212" who="S0192">so it wasn't the same weekend that we're moving out?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="214" who="S0192">yeah I was confused about that</u>
<u n="215" who="S0227" trans="overlap">all his stuff all his er his er er he wouldn't have got the van anyway because the van's not big enough for him he's gotta get he's got a fridge freeze which has to be moved upright <pause dur="short"/> wouldn't have gone in the van</u>
<u n="216" who="S0192">no okay <pause dur="short"/> ah so it didn't matter anyway</u>
<u n="217" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="218" who="S0192">what kind of van are we looking at here? like a transit van or?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0227">yes a transit van yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0192">you know if you see one as we go past</u>
<u n="221" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0192">the same kind of dimension the same kind of size point it out to me</u>
<u n="223" who="S0227">I I I think it's a normal standard transit van <pause dur="short"/> erm it's one of the ones they're selling <pause dur="short"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said it should <trunc>b</trunc>bar an incidents and <trunc>a</trunc>and then nothing goes wrong with with the any of the work</u>
<u n="224" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that kind of thing?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0227">like yeah like that</u>
<u n="226" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="227" who="S0227">with the with the <unclear/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0192">like that</u>
<u n="229" who="S0227">no no not</u>
<u n="230" who="S0192">not a truck a flatbed no?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0227">no no erm he said barring incidents and accidents he said you know that suddenly I's only pull the van if like the ones they're using broke down at the last minute and they needed it otherwise we're selling it</u>
<u n="232" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0227">it's had erm you know a new engine put in it it's er they've decided to launch it</u>
<u n="234" who="S0192">so it should be running fine</u>
<u n="235" who="S0227">well hopefully it's had a <trunc>re</trunc>rebuild on it so</u>
<u n="236" who="S0192">um</u>
<u n="237" who="S0227">they said it's burning a bit of oil</u>
<u n="238" who="S0192">do you have to pay for that?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0227">no <pause dur="short"/> it's just the just the fuel</u>
<u n="240" who="S0192">just the fuel costs</u>
<u n="241" who="S0227">just the just the fuel</u>
<u n="242" who="S0192">and you're happy for me not to come back up?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0227">well no I'll take <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos it'll be a day out for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> er otherwise you've gotta spend money and get all or get your arse back up here again to go back down again where</u>
<u n="244" who="S0192">I mean it's not a cost thing if you're worried about like cos it's</u>
<u n="245" who="S0227">no it's no no</u>
<u n="246" who="S0192">for some reason it's thirty-five pound one way</u>
<u n="247" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0192">or forty pound return</u>
<u n="249" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0192">so it's only like five pound more</u>
<u n="251" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0192">I've already spent thirty-five quid so</u>
<u n="253" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0192">if you need me to come up I can</u>
<u n="255" who="S0227">no it it it was good for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0192" trans="overlap">if you don't then it's it's probably worked out</u>
<u n="257" who="S0227">because it gave <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> an opportunity to see where you were</u>
<u n="258" who="S0192">yep</u>
<u n="259" who="S0227">and er it's a <unclear/> for him cos he's he's not doing anything he's just</u>
<u n="260" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean if you leave fairly early then cos you'll have the van the day before I presume on Friday?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0227">er I don't</u>
<u n="262" who="S0192">Friday night</u>
<u n="263" who="S0227">I'll have to I'll have to <trunc>fin</trunc> I'll have to know that cos I'll be picking it up from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0192">yeah I don't know</u>
<u n="265" who="S0227">so I</u>
<u n="266" who="S0192">is that close?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0227">I'm not sure how I erm there's a barrier to take it's not it's not an industrial estate where they they've got the company</u>
<u n="268" who="S0192">oh right</u>
<u n="269" who="S0227">erm so erm I've gotta nail it with with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> how how I'm gonna pick the van up <pause dur="short"/> and then what we'll do is we'll we'll um well we can go out for something to eat</u>
<u n="270" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I'm saying if you come down</u>
<u n="271" who="S0227">and then we'll come back Saturday night</u>
<u n="272" who="S0192">yep if you come fairly early then we can have food then</u>
<u n="273" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0192">maybe even lunch and dinner</u>
<u n="275" who="S0227" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> yeah cos it's er ironically now this this is ironic is that when I come to you a year before I was there in Brighton on a stag weekend</u>
<u n="276" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="277" who="S0227">we were at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s wedding</u>
<u n="278" who="S0192">had the</u>
<u n="279" who="S0227" trans="overlap">we had yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s stag weekend</u>
<u n="280" who="S0192">oh <pause dur="short"/> is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> around?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0227">er he will be round on Friday</u>
<u n="282" who="S0192">cool</u>
<u n="283" who="S0227">because er he's helping with the erm with the move</u>
<u n="284" who="S0192">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is still in obviously</u>
<u n="285" who="S0227">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is in <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0192">he'll be there for dinner?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0227">er probably not tonight no I think he's doing something else</u>
<u n="288" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="289" who="S0227">he's not for the past while he's not been in for many meals and plus he's had like he's on some kind of a <trunc>str</trunc>strange diet and him and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> keep chopping and changing what they're eating</u>
<u n="290" who="S0192"><unclear/> thing or whatever it is er</u>
<u n="291" who="S0227">I don't know what er I've lost I've lost track</u>
<u n="292" who="S0192">ha</u>
<u n="293" who="S0227">other that the diets and them moving on but I mean he does er he's only fat in his head</u>
<u n="294" who="S0192">does he think he's fat then?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0227">yeah cos you know he's fat in his head he's not fat anywhere else</u>
<u n="296" who="S0192">does he still doing his like refereeing or whatever?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0227">yeah he still does that he's he's getting stuff <unclear/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0192">is he getting paid for that?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0227">yeah er but he doesn't do it as regularly as he used to <pause dur="short"/> he's still supposed to be going to Tanzania to do this cycle thing</u>
<u n="300" who="S0192">oh yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0227">so er</u>
<u n="302" who="S0192">yeah when's that?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0227">er er October</u>
<u n="304" who="S0192">oh so it's definitely going ahead</u>
<u n="305" who="S0227">yeah I don't think he'll be fit enough for it but he hasn't trained so he's not going to be used to the altitude or the heat</u>
<u n="306" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="307" who="S0227">not in Tanzania it's about five five degrees off the equator and it's at altitude <pause dur="short"/> that's gonna <trunc>no</trunc> you'd notice that when um</u>
<u n="308" who="S0192">how much altitude? do you know?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0227">it's probably about four five six thousand feet <pause dur="short"/> a lot higher than here</u>
<u n="310" who="S0192">feet into metres?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0227">er er metres divide it by three</u>
<u n="312" who="S0192">oh so about two thousand metres</u>
<u n="313" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0192">so ha it might not be too bad actually I mean the altitude at two thousand metres isn't enough to</u>
<u n="315" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="316" who="S0192">make you really short of breath</u>
<u n="317" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="318" who="S0192">and it will probably just take the heat off from</u>
<u n="319" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0192">the being on the equator <pause dur="short"/> I mean I've been about two thousand metres in the equator it's a comfortable twenty-three</u>
<u n="321" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0192">twenty to twenty-five degrees</u>
<u n="323" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0192">kind of like a nice hot <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="325" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0192">summer's day in England</u>
<u n="327" who="S0227">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah so obviously the higher you er it starts heating up yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0192" trans="overlap">as you come down It will get it will get so it might be okay</u>
<u n="329" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0192">it might be</u>
<u n="331" who="S0227">I've just guessed the altitude all I know is it's a damn site higher than here</u>
<u n="332" who="S0192">I mean I know Kilimanjaro is there isn't it</u>
<u n="333" who="S0227">yeah that's</u>
<u n="334" who="S0192">and that that goes up to about six thousand metres so</u>
<u n="335" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0192">obviously there's some pretty big elevation</u>
<u n="337" who="S0227">and</u>
<u n="338" who="S0192">I wanna go there myself</u>
<u n="339" who="S0227">right they're doing some they're I think they're um cycling something like about <trunc>s</trunc> five hundred miles in about <trunc>f</trunc> six days or something</u>
<u n="340" who="S0192">oh wow</u>
<u n="341" who="S0227">day after day after day after day and he hasn't done that kind of</u>
<u n="342" who="S0192">no yeah I'm not</u>
<u n="343" who="S0227">stamina training</u>
<u n="344" who="S0192">that might be a bit</u>
<u n="345" who="S0227">yeah I mean I cycle just under three miles I haven't done as much <pause dur="short"/> I've done more this year than I've done for the year before definitely and the year before that combined</u>
<u n="346" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0227">and I'm a bit <unclear/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0192">hey you don't look er you don't look fat</u>
<u n="349" who="S0227">oh no not physically</u>
<u n="350" who="S0192" trans="overlap">have you been losing it lately?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0227">erm I got up to just under two just over two hundred pounds which is about fifteen stone roughly</u>
<u n="352" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0227">but er</u>
<u n="354" who="S0192">what's that in kilos? sorry I work in kilos now</u>
<u n="355" who="S0227">er er yeah you work in kilos don't you yeah about erm</u>
<u n="356" who="S0192">a hundred kilos?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0227">no no not er that it'd be two hundred and twenty pounds about ninety kilos</u>
<u n="358" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0227">but erm</u>
<u n="360" who="S0192">so it's two point two pounds</u>
<u n="361" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0192">to the kilo <pause dur="short"/> yep no you look fine</u>
<u n="363" who="S0227">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0192">you don't look too big</u>
<u n="365" who="S0227">I don't think I've lost any more hair since you were last here</u>
<u n="366" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no I'm not sure if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is gonna make it looks like it's going grey actually</u>
<u n="367" who="S0227">yes I think it er at the sides it's well it might be going grey</u>
<u n="368" who="S0192">yeah definitely that's alright</u>
<u n="369" who="S0227">I saw your mum the other day</u>
<u n="370" who="S0192">oh yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0227">and er er she obviously looked at me and thinks the same thing but I looked at her again you'll probably notice this yourself cos you don't see like us for a a length of time</u>
<u n="372" who="S0192">and she looks older</u>
<u n="373" who="S0227">and I thought round her eyes she's aged</u>
<u n="374" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think we're all looking older</u>
<u n="375" who="S0227">she couldn't see my eyes cos I had these on</u>
<u n="376" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> keep them hidden</u>
<u n="378" who="S0227">but er yeah yeah I thought oh I thought er er you've aged</u>
<u n="379" who="S0192">I think we're all looking a little older now</u>
<u n="380" who="S0227">well we the the we all all getting</u>
<u n="381" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> thought I looked older</u>
<u n="382" who="S0227">really?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has ballooned</u>
<u n="384" who="S0227">has she?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0192">yeah she's gotten bigger <unclear/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I dunno she used to be quite <trunc>s</trunc> er <trunc>s</trunc> when she was young she was quite slim</u>
<u n="387" who="S0192">yeah she's not slim now</u>
<u n="388" who="S0227">what's she now?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0192">she's like a Humpty Dumpty or something</u>
<u n="390" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0192">she's this little round thing</u>
<u n="392" who="S0227">that big</u>
<u n="393" who="S0192">she'll lose it again apparently but</u>
<u n="394" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0192">she's she's ballooned since I last seen her</u>
<u n="396" who="S0227">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's also erm erm what's this called erm <event desc="sound of clicking fingers"/> the menopause</u>
<u n="397" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0227">you know it makes makes women barrel bodied</u>
<u n="399" who="S0192">they're having a lot of problems with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I don't know if you've heard about anything or</u>
<u n="400" who="S0227">I've heard something about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but erm</u>
<u n="401" who="S0192">or heard from him or?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0227">I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> kind of erm removed himself from from the moral high ground where he was sitting comfortably he decided to erm I er according to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's not really shaping up as much as er of a grandfather</u>
<u n="403" who="S0192">no he's he doesn't he doesn't talk to the cousins or their children basically at all</u>
<u n="404" who="S0227">it's you mean his own children?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0192">his own children yeah pretty much at all</u>
<u n="406" who="S0227">has he like disassociated himself with them?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0192">he's er yeah I mean she er like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> saw him in Lidl's the other day and like called out to him and he completely ignored her</u>
<u n="408" who="S0227"><unclear/></u>
<u n="409" who="S0192">so er just er they've had a falling out <pause dur="short"/> he er basically who he's with now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or something doesn't really want anything to do with his children and has made him kind of make a decision and he's decided her</u>
<u n="410" who="S0227">her or them?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0192">over the children yeah <pause dur="short"/> effectively</u>
<u n="412" who="S0227">yeah <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="413" who="S0192">so they're they're all quite annoyed about that</u>
<u n="414" who="S0227">it's a it's a poor choice and and a bad choice when you put erm sex over <trunc>y</trunc> erm over kin</u>
<u n="415" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it happens</u>
<u n="416" who="S0227">obviously he's</u>
<u n="417" who="S0192">I guess he's a bit black and white</u>
<u n="418" who="S0227">he's</u>
<u n="419" who="S0192">thinks well I've done my duty and</u>
<u n="420" who="S0227">yeah he's he's he's a bit hurt but then again he er he he <trunc>sh</trunc> you know his his daughters did <trunc>f</trunc> erm I can't speak for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were firmly behind him and not behind their mother</u>
<u n="421" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0227">so they didn't have some support so I don't know <trunc>wha</trunc> you know sometimes er erm men are influenced by their partners <pause dur="short"/> your grandfather <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was he was a closet racist</u>
<u n="423" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0227">but erm when he married</u>
<u n="425" who="S0192">it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who was</u>
<u n="426" who="S0227">was er <trunc>on</trunc>once you got them together they <trunc>f</trunc>fed off each other's <trunc>prejudi</trunc>prejudice and they were basically totally yeah if if she had've if she hadn't have been like that and she was not not had a problem with it she'd have probably have said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> don't be so stupid it's your it's your grandchildren but she was racist too</u>
<u n="427" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0227">that was all that he needed and perhaps <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was at a crossroads where he was thinking do I stick with this or not? but it's it's erm it's erm I it's a wrong decision if you ask me because</u>
<u n="429" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="430" who="S0227">it's his children and his grandchildren <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> they will probably forgive him in time because it the there is a dynamic that <trunc>y</trunc> <trunc>y</trunc> erm you can treat your <trunc>chil</trunc>children like shit and they'll just keep coming back for more</u>
<u n="431" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0227">they want acceptance but erm it's a risk it's a risky game and and if it it it doesn't pan out with this woman <pause dur="short"/> or something was to happen to her he's got a lot of ground to make up because</u>
<u n="433" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0227">he's given it all back to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> if she's there for them now they'll forget her her erm</u>
<u n="435" who="S0192">past indiscretions</u>
<u n="436" who="S0227">her past indiscretions yeah because she's there</u>
<u n="437" who="S0192">yeah I think they pretty much have by the <trunc>look</trunc>by the looks of it now</u>
<u n="438" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah but er yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0192">they're much more on her side</u>
<u n="440" who="S0227" trans="overlap">he had the position and the er he just <trunc>thr</trunc> gave it away just traded with her</u>
<u n="441" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0227">now he's the <vocal desc="laugh"/> villain of the piece</u>
<u n="443" who="S0192">yeah I dunno why he's done that</u>
<u n="444" who="S0227">no I I they said like no reason to I I didn't go and see him I well I I kind of I've tied all my all my ties are tied off</u>
<u n="445" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> said I went and saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's living in some tiny little house you know</u>
<u n="446" who="S0227">is she? I hear she's gone back to erm I think she must have been watching er erm Spartacus</u>
<u n="447" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0227">where they are kind of er to you to paraphrase those words cock or cunt</u>
<u n="449" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0227">and erm I think she's gone back to the former rather than the latter but I may there may be an update on that</u>
<u n="451" who="S0192">no I think she just swings whichever way she wants to <unclear/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0227">do you mind if I wind the window down? is she living with someone or by herself?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0192">I think she's living by herself as far as I can tell <pause dur="short"/> I think this weekend I'm gonna see the cousins <pause dur="short"/> I'll go out with them</u>
<u n="454" who="S0227" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="455" who="S0192">she's going down er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is going down to Devon of course she doesn't speak with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> now at all</u>
<u n="456" who="S0227">she doesn't? why?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> erm she blamed him because when she decided she was a lesbian apparently he just cut off from her but what I can gather from mum they just both cut off from each other it wasn't</u>
<u n="458" who="S0227">yeah I've</u>
<u n="459" who="S0192">that he said anything to her or did anything they both used it as an excuse to</u>
<u n="460" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="461" who="S0192">not really communicate any more after that</u>
<u n="462" who="S0227">I don't think erm</u>
<u n="463" who="S0192">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> too she doesn't see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or talk to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at all but mum does</u>
<u n="464" who="S0227">yes well there was always a connection between your mum and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> there was a a bond not blood but a bond</u>
<u n="465" who="S0192">they lived together didn't they</u>
<u n="466" who="S0227">erm er no they never actually lived together but they <trunc>s</trunc> erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was very young</u>
<u n="467" who="S0192">did you hear about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0227">yes I did</u>
<u n="469" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0227">yeah that was um yeah that was a bit sad</u>
<u n="471" who="S0192">did you hear about erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s old friend as well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0227">erm no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I remember big goal guy <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah massive guy</u>
<u n="474" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0192">he erm hung himself while his child was he was with his child he said I'm just going out to the garage to get something <pause dur="short"/> his child went out to see where he was about ten minutes later</u>
<u n="476" who="S0227" trans="overlap">and found him</u>
<u n="477" who="S0192">and found him still alive like</u>
<u n="478" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="479" who="S0192">squirming on the on the the hangman's noose and er ran screaming to help people but when people came it was too late</u>
<u n="480" who="S0227">no it's a terrible thing yeah</u>
<u n="481" who="S0192">what a horrific thing to do</u>
<u n="482" who="S0227">yes that would erm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0192">I mean <trunc>f</trunc> er if life really is that bad okay <pause dur="short"/> disappear somewhere tell your family you're going on holiday and then just disappear or something</u>
<u n="484" who="S0227">just disappear yeah yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0192">you know what I mean? don't do it in front of them</u>
<u n="486" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="487" who="S0192">and you could even do it in such a way where they're not sure if you've if you've done it or not</u>
<u n="488" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0192">maybe you just died or er something happened</u>
<u n="490" who="S0227" trans="overlap">must must have been a botch job because um hanging someone is I mean hanging er properly so that their neck breaks um you have to have to know you have to know what they weigh</u>
<u n="491" who="S0192">tie the knot correctly</u>
<u n="492" who="S0227">and yeah and calculate the length of drop because otherwise if you get it wrong there's a good and the drop's too long there's a good chance the head literally comes off</u>
<u n="493" who="S0192">oh my god</u>
<u n="494" who="S0227">which happened with one of Saddam when they were</u>
<u n="495" who="S0192">Saddam yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0227">when they were executing Saddam's lot</u>
<u n="497" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0227">they did that to one of them <pause dur="short"/> erm if you get it wrong the other way they don't die by er C2 snapping they die by <trunc>str</trunc> slowly by strangulation so obviously cos he's a big guy</u>
<u n="499" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that's how I think he died yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0227">he was a big guy he obviously it should have snapped his neck <pause dur="short"/> but it didn't so he was then suffocating</u>
<u n="501" who="S0192">maybe it did snap his neck and he was just jerking I mean afterwards or something</u>
<u n="502" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it would <unclear/> no if it was C2 it would have paralysed him from the neck downward he wouldn't be able to move</u>
<u n="503" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so no movement whatsoever</u>
<u n="504" who="S0227">yeah he wouldn't be able to move</u>
<u n="505" who="S0192">is there no muscle reflex?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I think you would have seen that in erm in Hannibal the second he where that guy erm was</u>
<u n="507" who="S0192">it was pretty dark <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0227">probably was eating his own face</u>
<u n="509" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="510" who="S0227">he snapped his neck</u>
<u n="511" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0227">he he did kill him</u>
<u n="513" who="S0192">that's pretty dark</u>
<u n="514" who="S0227">yeah I liked Hannibal</u>
<u n="515" who="S0192">yeah it is good</u>
<u n="516" who="S0227">I liked Mads Mikkelsen who plays him because we've</u>
<u n="517" who="S0192">he was in James Bond wasn't he?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0227">yes he was Le Chiffre in erm</u>
<u n="519" who="S0192">the guy that bled</u>
<u n="520" who="S0227">Casino Royale</u>
<u n="521" who="S0192">out of his eyes wasn't it?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0227">yeah Casino Royale Le Chiffre erm with the original with played by erm Anthony Hopkins you just see Hannibal as a as a intelligent manipulating erm person <pause dur="short"/> you don't see him being charming</u>
<u n="523" who="S0192">no where is the psychology <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0227">whereas Mads Mikkelsen comes over as being very charming very well you know he's not but</u>
<u n="525" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0227">he comes over as being incredibly er sane not insane</u>
<u n="527" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="528" who="S0227">yeah so he plays the part well</u>
<u n="529" who="S0192" trans="overlap">too sane mm <pause dur="short"/> very flamboyant in his eating his culinary desires</u>
<u n="530" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well yes and his presentation immaculately dressed</u>
<u n="531" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="532" who="S0227">his cooking skills you know he has has passion in his work</u>
<u n="533" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no it's good I liked it</u>
<u n="534" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="535" who="S0192">it's quite dark</u>
<u n="536" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="537" who="S0192">and interestingly filmed as well</u>
<u n="538" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="539" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="540" who="S0227">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I I did like that</u>
<u n="541" who="S0192">can you watch that one quick?</u>
<u n="542" who="S0227">did you watch? yes I did yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wasn't into it</u>
<u n="543" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="544" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="545" who="S0192">I didn't think she would be</u>
<u n="546" who="S0227" trans="overlap">if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can draw a conclusion very quickly and she her mind won't change</u>
<u n="547" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="548" who="S0227">I can start off with something and go mm and then I think</u>
<u n="549" who="S0192">give it time</u>
<u n="550" who="S0227">give it give it <trunc>t</trunc>time for characters to develop and stuff like that and then er erm</u>
<u n="551" who="S0192">it's too graphic for her I would imagine</u>
<u n="552" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="553" who="S0192">would she um be up for playing a game? I know she probably doesn't like Battlestar Galactica but she likes board games though</u>
<u n="554" who="S0227">she likes board games she'll give it a I guess she'll give it a go</u>
<u n="555" who="S0192">yeah if there's the four of us tomorrow</u>
<u n="556" who="S0227">yes okay</u>
<u n="557" who="S0192">it's a good four player game</u>
<u n="558" who="S0227">okay er erm</u>
<u n="559" who="S0192">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has told you about it I guess</u>
<u n="560" who="S0227">no he hasn't</u>
<u n="561" who="S0192">cos I said to him</u>
<u n="562" who="S0227">no cos</u>
<u n="563" who="S0192">oh I though he said he mentioned it</u>
<u n="564" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><unclear/> no</u>
<u n="565" who="S0192">I've got a a friend's bought me a board game Battlestar Galactica</u>
<u n="566" who="S0227">no he didn't mention that</u>
<u n="567" who="S0192">you play on the on the Battlestar and you move around and do different things</u>
<u n="568" who="S0227">okay</u>
<u n="569" who="S0192">and one person is the Cylon but he's undercover so you don't know who the Cylon is</u>
<u n="570" who="S0227">oh right okay</u>
<u n="571" who="S0192"><unclear>and a lot of undercover stuff</unclear> it's quite good <pause dur="short"/> it takes a few hours to play though</u>
<u n="572" who="S0227">okay</u>
<u n="573" who="S0192">like a good like three hours I'd say <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to play it so</u>
<u n="574" who="S0227">okay did you watch erm Game of Thrones?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0192">yes yeah</u>
<u n="576" who="S0227">I'm on series four</u>
<u n="577" who="S0192">you're not finished it yet?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="579" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="580" who="S0227">I like Tyrion he's very good that little <unclear/> is very good</u>
<u n="581" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah yeah Peter Dinklage his name is</u>
<u n="582" who="S0227">he's good the I think he was in erm erm the film with erm <event desc="sound of tapping"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>bru</trunc> I think it's called Bruges</u>
<u n="583" who="S0192" trans="overlap">Bruges In Bruges yeah</u>
<u n="584" who="S0227">and he was and erm erm what's he called? Collin Farrell gave him a karate chop <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0192">yeah I think you're right I've known about that in retrospect but I haven't actually seen it again</u>
<u n="586" who="S0227">yeah yeah he's a he's a good actor</u>
<u n="587" who="S0192">yeah he is good <pause dur="short"/> have you seen the scene where he's in court?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="589" who="S0192">no he's really good in that you'll see</u>
<u n="590" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah no I haven't seen it he has comes out with some great lines and given great lines to work with</u>
<u n="591" who="S0192">yeah it's directly from the book</u>
<u n="592" who="S0227">oh okay</u>
<u n="593" who="S0192">I was very surprised when I read the book thinking how quotable it was pretty much all of the dialogue in the</u>
<u n="594" who="S0227">is <unclear/></u>
<u n="595" who="S0192">especially in the third season's book</u>
<u n="596" who="S0227">oh</u>
<u n="597" who="S0192">the fourth season they started to deviate a bit</u>
<u n="598" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="599" who="S0192">now they still use stuff from the book</u>
<u n="600" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0192">but they've made more of their own stuff</u>
<u n="602" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="603" who="S0192">but like the first two three seasons pretty much directly everything they said was directly from the book</u>
<u n="604" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yes yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't like it cos of the profanity</u>
<u n="605" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="606" who="S0227">and and in er series four it's really quite profane</u>
<u n="607" who="S0192">yeah well</u>
<u n="608" who="S0227">the the language got worse as the series went on</u>
<u n="609" who="S0192">well it's I think because they've deviated</u>
<u n="610" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="611" who="S0192">more from him</u>
<u n="612" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="613" who="S0192">they were adding some I don't know what they're doing with the season actually because they've come to the point now I've read all of his books</u>
<u n="614" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="615" who="S0192">there's about six thousand <trunc>wor</trunc> er pages it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="616" who="S0227" trans="overlap">right right</u>
<u n="617" who="S0192">he's got two more books to come out</u>
<u n="618" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="619" who="S0192">and he hasn't finished them and it takes him about five or six years to write a book</u>
<u n="620" who="S0227" trans="overlap">mm mm yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0192">so at the minute he does as you can tell in the series they have different stories you follow different characters</u>
<u n="622" who="S0227">but they're all threaded aren't they</u>
<u n="623" who="S0192">yeah they're all threaded together</u>
<u n="624" who="S0227">that's the clever part about it is they</u>
<u n="625" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="626" who="S0227">er they're all heading to a a a point of of convergence</u>
<u n="627" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0227">that's the good thing I like about it is that there's I wish I'd thought of it there's sort of all separate plots</u>
<u n="629" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="630" who="S0227">but you know they're all tied by a single theme and a single they're all gonna end or meet <trunc>a</trunc><trunc>a</trunc>at a single point</u>
<u n="631" who="S0192">at a head point yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0227">further in time <pause dur="short"/> you know that's gonna happen</u>
<u n="633" who="S0192" trans="overlap">although quite a few of them die</u>
<u n="634" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="635" who="S0192">don't they yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> there's a theory that fans believe I don't know if you've come across it but <trunc>the</trunc> they claim that John Snow is actually the air to the throne and he wasn't Ed Stark's son <pause dur="short"/> he was the son of sorry Ned Stark he was the son of Ned Stark's sister</u>
<u n="636" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="637" who="S0192">Elina Stark or something married to the old Targaryen king</u>
<u n="638" who="S0227">okay</u>
<u n="639" who="S0192">and Ned er has been keeping this promise by hiding this son amongst</u>
<u n="640" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="641" who="S0192">his own prodigy</u>
<u n="642" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="643" who="S0192">erm when in fact he's not actually his son so that's</u>
<u n="644" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="645" who="S0192">and George R R Martin has recently said that fans have actually got his ending correct</u>
<u n="646" who="S0227">oh alright</u>
<u n="647" who="S0192">but he hasn't said which fan theory it is</u>
<u n="648" who="S0227" trans="overlap">which <pause dur="short"/> yeah yes</u>
<u n="649" who="S0192">but he's grappling with whether or not he should change what happens in the book</u>
<u n="650" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="651" who="S0192">because he's apparently he's been been putting lots of subtle clues in about what where it's going</u>
<u n="652" who="S0227" trans="overlap">right <unclear/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0192">and so his fans have picked up a lot</u>
<u n="654" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="655" who="S0192">the evidence and put it at that as the end or something</u>
<u n="656" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I said it's it's very it's very good I wish I'd written that those books <unclear/></u>
<u n="657" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="658" who="S0192">oh yeah</u>
<u n="659" who="S0227">oh god they might be from</u>
<u n="660" who="S0192">it's quite historically based as well</u>
<u n="661" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0192">he um bases a lot of his characters on real people from</u>
<u n="663" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="664" who="S0192">you know history</u>
<u n="665" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="666" who="S0192">erm and I do like it but what I was saying about it I don't know what's gonna happen next <pause dur="short"/> so he's already written five books</u>
<u n="667" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="668" who="S0192">he's got two more <pause dur="short"/> no he's already written six books</u>
<u n="669" who="S0227">so is there so is there a series five to come?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0192" trans="overlap">he's got two more <pause dur="short"/> there's well this is the thing</u>
<u n="671" who="S0227">so I I</u>
<u n="672" who="S0192">some of their stories</u>
<u n="673" who="S0227">I'm about four <trunc>ep</trunc> er five episodes into series four</u>
<u n="674" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what they're gonna do because there's two more books <pause dur="short"/> they've got all these characters some of the characters for example Sansa and Bran and these kind of characters</u>
<u n="675" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="676" who="S0192">they've reached the end of their story</u>
<u n="677" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="678" who="S0192">and I can go I've read as far as they as he's written</u>
<u n="679" who="S0227">yeah they haven't</u>
<u n="680" who="S0192">they have no</u>
<u n="681" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0192">no further to go</u>
<u n="683" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="684" who="S0192">whereas Aria and a bunch of other people John they have quite a bit more story left to do</u>
<u n="685" who="S0227">there's more mileage</u>
<u n="686" who="S0192">so they haven't been running it the same as the books</u>
<u n="687" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="688" who="S0192">the books were all inter-threaded chronologically</u>
<u n="689" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="690" who="S0192">but they focused on some stories and</u>
<u n="691" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="692" who="S0192">and sped others up so</u>
<u n="693" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that woman that actress who plays the um who you know they the king slayer who <trunc>wh</trunc>what took him in</u>
<u n="694" who="S0192">Brienne of Tarth?</u>
<u n="695" who="S0227">yeah the</u>
<u n="696" who="S0192">the big woman?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="698" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="699" who="S0227">Jesus she's a big woman</u>
<u n="700" who="S0192">yeah she's massive she is yeah</u>
<u n="701" who="S0227">Christ she's big woman she must be about six foot four</u>
<u n="702" who="S0192">yeah she is big</u>
<u n="703" who="S0227">I mean er er put her</u>
<u n="704" who="S0192">er yeah have you met the Mountain yet or no</u>
<u n="705" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="706" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="707" who="S0227">you put her in a</u>
<u n="708" who="S0192">he's huge</u>
<u n="709" who="S0227">you put her in a pair of stilettos <vocal desc="laugh"/> she's gonna be absolutely huge</u>
<u n="710" who="S0192">she'd break them</u>
<u n="711" who="S0227">yes she probably would</u>
<u n="712" who="S0192">the mountain that comes in now is this <trunc>ice</trunc>Icelandic guy who's you know the Hound? erm Gregor Clegane</u>
<u n="713" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="714" who="S0192">he's with Aria</u>
<u n="715" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="716" who="S0192">erm you know the Hound he's got the big burn mark on his face</u>
<u n="717" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="718" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="719" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="720" who="S0192">he's cool</u>
<u n="721" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="722" who="S0192">I like his character <pause dur="short"/> erm his brother is even bigger than he is</u>
<u n="723" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="724" who="S0192">the Mountain and he's gonna fight with Oberyn Martell</u>
<u n="725" who="S0227">oh</u>
<u n="726" who="S0192">the Snake <pause dur="short"/> erm later in it you'll see</u>
<u n="727" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="728" who="S0192">he's humongous the guy is like he weighs like <vocal desc="laugh"/> I will shit you not like two hundred kilos or something</u>
<u n="729" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="730" who="S0192">the guy is ridiculously big <pause dur="short"/> he's this he was he came second in the world's strongest man</u>
<u n="731" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="732" who="S0192">he was actually in it you may have even seen him there</u>
<u n="733" who="S0227">oh right I'll probably <trunc>rec</trunc></u>
<u n="734" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="735" who="S0227">oh if that's the case then I'll see I'll recognise him</u>
<u n="736" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's an Icelandic guy</u>
<u n="737" who="S0227">because I I watch it every um Christmas just because it's on at Christmas</u>
<u n="738" who="S0192">yeah I remembered you watched it</u>
<u n="739" who="S0227">and yeah I do watch it</u>
<u n="740" who="S0192">he was the second Icelandic guy</u>
<u n="741" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="742" who="S0192">a massive guy</u>
<u n="743" who="S0227">right yeah</u>
<u n="744" who="S0192">and um</u>
<u n="745" who="S0227">way don't be rolling back and hit my car</u>
<u n="746" who="S0192">not in this <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> do you think if I just keep recording <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will mind? or should I stop this now</u>
<u n="747" who="S0227">are you recording?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0192">and ask for her permission?</u>
<u n="749" who="S0227">I I <trunc>th</trunc> I I'd no erm well you can <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I I don't even remember you actually erm oh crap the stuff about your mum</u>
<u n="750" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="751" who="S0227">it's all I was just quoting myself</u>
<u n="752" who="S0192">she's not gonna hear it is she</u>
<u n="753" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I forgot that was on</u>
<u n="754" who="S0192">it's all good <pause dur="short"/> well we've done half an hour</u>
<u n="755" who="S0227">god</u>
<u n="756" who="S0192">so if I stop it now then I can <unclear/> so</u>
<u n="757" who="S0227">oh yeah I'd completely forgot that that was on</u>
<u n="758" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="759" who="S0227">I in fact I once</u>
<u n="760" who="S0192">you do don't you quickly</u>
<u n="761" who="S0227">yes I</u>
<u n="762" who="S0192">yeah very quickly</u>
<u n="763" who="S0227">I didn't I didn't pay any attention to it</u>
<u n="764" who="S0192">where did they leave the bag then?</u>
<u n="765" who="S0227">er</u>
<u n="766" who="S0192">you <trunc>s</trunc> did they leave it on the <unclear/></u>
<u n="767" who="S0227" trans="overlap">they they were here <pause dur="short"/> no they er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was still here when it arrived</u>
<u n="768" who="S0192">oh that's good what time did it arrive?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0227">so</u>
<u n="770" who="S0192">something like four o'clock or something</u>
<u n="771" who="S0227" trans="overlap">er just before they went</u>
<u n="772" who="S0192">oh just before right</u>
<u n="773" who="S0227">just before they were going and so erm yeah I've carried it up to the front bedroom so it's up there</u>
<u n="774" who="S0192">good stuff thank you <pause dur="short"/> kind of heavy was it?</u>
<u n="775" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yes it it's got a few it weighs a few kilos and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you didn't try picking this up did you?</u>
<u n="776" who="S0192">it's really just suits and erm <pause dur="short"/> there's really not much in it</u>
<u n="777" who="S0227">no?</u>
<u n="778" who="S0192">and having that luggage allowance really I don't think it's an adequate enough luggage allowance</u>
<u n="779" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="780" who="S0192">basically twenty kilos</u>
<u n="781" who="S0227">what was your flight like back?</u>
<u n="782" who="S0192">yeah tiring because we erm we flew with the sun all day</u>
<u n="783" who="S0227"><unclear>oh okay</unclear></u>
<u n="784" who="S0192">so even though it was like seven o'clock in the morning my time in Korea</u>
<u n="785" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="786" who="S0192">it was erm</u>
<u n="787" who="S0227">I sent it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> never responded and I did copy your mum in there was there's some software it's very clever that um it's called <trunc>f</trunc> um Flight Radar um <trunc>f</trunc> Twenty-four erm dot com where you you'd see the screen and you're like over Europe or whatever and you can see the planes moving in in in real time</u>
<u n="788" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="789" who="S0227">and what you do is you double click on it and it'll tell you what that flight is and where it's going and where it's come from</u>
<u n="790" who="S0192">so you can trace people or?</u>
<u n="791" who="S0227">yes but I didn't know if your flight numbers had changed because the info you gave me</u>
<u n="792" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="793" who="S0227">I couldn't find I couldn't <trunc>fi</trunc> I'll I'll show you <unclear/></u>
<u n="794" who="S0192">who's doing the <unclear>gardening</unclear>?</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
