<text id="SE58">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:09:47</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-12-11</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0326 S0327</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>university, family members, art, travel plans, books, exhibitions </topics>
		<activity>Two family members catching up over lunch </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0326">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>12</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0327">
				<exactage>76</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Vienna</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Italy</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Austria</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>74</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Artist</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0327">which is together with talent which is very important</u>
<u n="2" who="S0326">yeah so when I write the essays I really just it takes me sort of three and a half days of solid work</u>
<u n="3" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="4" who="S0326">and then I go come to <anon type="place"/> for a few days</u>
<u n="5" who="S0327">okay</u>
<u n="6" who="S0326">for the weekend</u>
<u n="7" who="S0327">and what are the subjects now?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0326">erm now I'm mainly doing er Greek and Latin literature and philosophy and art history</u>
<u n="9" who="S0327">gosh so it's gonna be quite demanding isn't it? art history from what period?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0326">erm it's from from Archaic Greek to Late Antiquity so it's sort of eight hundred BC to six hundred AD</u>
<u n="11" who="S0327">so er at some point you'll cross over with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a little bit won't you?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0326">yeah she always said that she was doing a lot of Roman Britain art</u>
<u n="13" who="S0327">I mean I do she sends me her essays to read sometimes to read through for you know typos and so on and I mean it's so academic what she's doing</u>
<u n="14" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0327">I do really admire her I mean I actually think your subjects are more interesting in a way</u>
<u n="16" who="S0326">well she's doing erm archaeology it's it's gonna be a bit like that</u>
<u n="17" who="S0327">but she doesn't seem to mind I haven't mentioned that I found it find it a bit boring it's heavy</u>
<u n="18" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0327">I mean so is yours so are your subjects erm so it's of course it's ancient Greek philosophy and everything</u>
<u n="20" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah I mean what I liked about the <trunc>w</trunc> erm work I've done this year I'm just I tried basically hard to just have my own ideas I don't do <trunc>t</trunc>too much secondary reading I just look at the text</u>
<u n="21" who="S0327">that's that's very demanding that's er that's interesting cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> told me that she er <trunc>th</trunc> was told that they're looking for er you know originality and I thought how do you do that with archaeology? you know it's almost impossible to have an original view</u>
<u n="22" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0327">on subjects that have been beaten to death</u>
<u n="24" who="S0326" trans="overlap">although although it's it's surprisingly people there's a famous example or famous in terms of archaeology where they had these coins sort of Persian coins and no one could understand what was shown on the coin they came up with all these different ideas and then a student at university girl at university <unclear>got to say</unclear> it's quite obvious that this is a map of Persia and no one had noticed</u>
<u n="25" who="S0327">good lord is that right? well of course one forgets that even the cleverest people are mostly silly as well</u>
<u n="26" who="S0326">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0327">it's worth bearing in mind <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I've never met anybody clever all the way through</u>
<u n="28" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0327">either they're clever intellectually stupid emotionally or they're clever emotionally and da da da da erm that's just how it is <unclear/> coffee and actually the pizza's ready so we might as well are you hungry enough for a pizza?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0326">yeah I am quite hungry</u>
<u n="31" who="S0327">good</u>
<u n="32" who="S0326">I didn't eat yet</u>
<u n="33" who="S0327">okay erm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0326">I see you've got your pease pudding stashed up <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0327">well I bought quite a lot them and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said whatever however much you bought she said double it</u>
<u n="36" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0327">so I went out and bought a a whole lot more <unclear>here's your</unclear> milk</u>
<u n="38" who="S0326">thank you</u>
<u n="39" who="S0327">tell you what you help yourself to milk erm and what haven't I got? I need to put the kettle on for me <pause dur="short"/> I have erm and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because I I did have a brief email from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> which was nice not very communicative I have to say</u>
<u n="40" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0327">erm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0326">did you get one sentence?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0327">I think I got one and a half sentences which was not bad but it sounded as though he was okay</u>
<u n="44" who="S0326">yeah I I <trunc>s</trunc> I ran into him in at home in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0327">er <trunc>d</trunc>did you? by chance? <unclear/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> by chance cos no one's really in that house so ran into him and he seems to yeah he he likes <anon type="place"/> a lot</u>
<u n="47" who="S0327">oh well that's good oh well <unclear>you'll</unclear></u>
<u n="48" who="S0326" trans="overlap">he likes the sort of like the <trunc>pe</trunc> lots of friends that he met <unclear>interesting</unclear></u>
<u n="49" who="S0327" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0326">or people he likes</u>
<u n="51" who="S0327">cos you haven't <trunc>ha</trunc> or have you now?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0326">well yeah not I mean</u>
<u n="53" who="S0327">not to not to match your <anon type="place"/> friends?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0326">not no not not at all</u>
<u n="55" who="S0327">nor has <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> oh I'm glad at least erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has why? why is that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0326">erm I dunno it's probably the mm sort of er not so much the people at university it's the way that me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are and the way that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is</u>
<u n="57" who="S0327">so you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are rather snooty? and your friends have to live up to certain standards</u>
<u n="58" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0327">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is a bit more open is that what it is?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0326">well or I dunno <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s always had his friends have always been in his peer group whereas my friends have not really er they've always been sort of <pause dur="short"/> even at school my friends were <trunc>n</trunc> lots not lots of them were not in school <unclear/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0327" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="62" who="S0326">but all <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s friends have always he's always been er accustomed to be friends with the people who <unclear/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0327">does that mean that you feel a bit isolated down there?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0326">erm not really I don't really not really because I'm either in <anon type="place"/> or I'm doing the work or I or I am in <anon type="place"/> with my friends that I do have <unclear>there</unclear></u>
<u n="65" who="S0327">right <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to have a bit of leftover extremely boring noodles</u>
<u n="66" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0327">that somebody has to finish <unclear>I've given you a few</unclear> there erm and do you have any more ideas as to what you might do later? or not?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0326">mm I wanna do er <trunc>someth</trunc> like as little as possible really</u>
<u n="69" who="S0327"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what does that mean?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0326">I mean I don't wanna have I wanna be able to think I er wanna I liked I thought very I felt like I was thinking very clearly when I had a year out so I think it's like er it's maybe do some jobs and get some money and go somewhere and do some work or something go somewhere cheaper to live</u>
<u n="71" who="S0327">do you mean write? <unclear>or something</unclear>?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0326"><trunc>ma</trunc> yeah or <trunc>s</trunc> or <trunc>s</trunc> yeah or or or just like <trunc>thi</trunc> also think about what to do</u>
<u n="73" who="S0327">right <pause dur="short"/> erm I assume you don't want bread with that but if you want some?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0326">no I'm I'm fine thank you</u>
<u n="75" who="S0327">you're alright? erm <pause dur="short"/> okay well er you know if you're willing to work you can actually on that subject I don't suppose you've got a couple of mornings you can work for me have you?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0326">definitely I mean I just</u>
<u n="77" who="S0327" trans="overlap">oh that would be really wonderful</u>
<u n="78" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I should do I just I've just <trunc>en</trunc> like asked about a job but if that doesn't happen then I would be able to do those mornings</u>
<u n="79" who="S0327">I mean I it's just I need to it's a question of sort of putting down boards that I haven't got the strength for</u>
<u n="80" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0327">well we'll look at the dates probably be in a few days' time er knives and forks</u>
<u n="82" who="S0326">before Christmas?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0327">before Christmas</u>
<u n="84" who="S0326">cos I'm going away</u>
<u n="85" who="S0327">I'll look er I'll look at the <vocal desc="cough"/> my diary and I'll look at the work and see if you can <unclear>I'll</unclear> probably need the car tomorrow maybe Sunday or Monday that would be that would be really good <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> fifteen pounds an hour?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0326">that's a lot <unclear>really</unclear></u>
<u n="87" who="S0327">that's what I pay the professions so probably a <unclear>good</unclear> week's work if if you want to do other stuff</u>
<u n="88" who="S0326">yeah that's good <unclear>I've been</unclear></u>
<u n="89" who="S0327" trans="overlap">right that's that that's</u>
<u n="90" who="S0326">trying to make money</u>
<u n="91" who="S0327">well I suppose you have to erm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0326">yeah I've been I've been I was been working in a in a bakery</u>
<u n="93" who="S0327">oh have you?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0327">doing what?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0326">erm mostly erm making coffee and cutting pieces of cake <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0327">well that's quite good that you got that</u>
<u n="98" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0327">is that in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0326">erm yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0327">and how much do you get there? six pounds fifty?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0326">eight</u>
<u n="103" who="S0327">eight pounds? okay well you're not gonna become a millionaire with that</u>
<u n="104" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0327">it's better than better than nothing erm and I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got a job</u>
<u n="106" who="S0326">yeah I bumped into him in his dishwashing</u>
<u n="107" who="S0327">oh yes</u>
<u n="108" who="S0326">on the street <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0327">I think he's quite enjoying it from what I gather</u>
<u n="110" who="S0326">yeah I think he would do I mean if cos what I don't know what he's been doing before since up to then</u>
<u n="111" who="S0327">I mean the thing is those jobs are fine and fun oh I I want you to help me change some text on my computer</u>
<u n="112" who="S0326">okay</u>
<u n="113" who="S0327">as long as you er as long as it's not for life</u>
<u n="114" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0327">don't you think? you don't want to do dishwashing have salad if you want erm what's that like that <trunc>be</trunc> that deep one? I thought that might be</u>
<u n="116" who="S0326">it's good</u>
<u n="117" who="S0327">is it? Co-op</u>
<u n="118" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0327">now I don't have to go anywhere for the things</u>
<u n="120" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0327">erm remind me also to give you a copy of my new book</u>
<u n="122" who="S0326">oh yeah <unclear/> is that the bigger one?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0327">no it's the little one</u>
<u n="124" who="S0326">like is it the that one there?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0327">mm have you seen it? I <trunc>s</trunc>I sent your mum one that as er of the well the she was sent one of the TLS <pause dur="short"/> it's all about the family really so it's a bit of your history</u>
<u n="126" who="S0326"><unclear/> yeah cool</u>
<u n="127" who="S0327">yes well spotted</u>
<u n="128" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0327">I had my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was here the other day and he had the book in his hand he was standing like this and he said well where is this blue cupboard?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you should have sent him looking for it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0327">exactly he's been here several times before some people just don't notice it erm okay what else? erm <pause dur="short"/> do you see any of your tutors out of hours?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0326">erm no</u>
<u n="133" who="S0327">you don't?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0326">they're all very old</u>
<u n="135" who="S0327">are they? what? like fifty?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0326">no like like <trunc>fi</trunc> well <trunc>o</trunc> er <trunc>o</trunc> that and above one's a bit younger but he's still pushing forty</u>
<u n="137" who="S0327" trans="overlap">even old people have a mind sometimes <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I'm not gonna see them in a in a club</u>
<u n="139" who="S0327">no you're not gonna no quite</u>
<u n="140" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0327">course you're not <pause dur="short"/> and the level of of lectures and everything is really top notch is it?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0327">well that's what you're supposed to think isn't it? mm <anon type="place"/> which is nice <pause dur="short"/> do you still have good food there and everything?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0326">erm yeah the food in the hall is is good and I get a bursary so it's basically free</u>
<u n="145" who="S0327">how come you get a bursary?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0326">cos the house only covers <unclear>loan</unclear></u>
<u n="147" who="S0327">oh that's handy</u>
<u n="148" who="S0326" trans="overlap">er for their standards yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0327">that's very handy and you get help from your dad?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0326">yeah a bit</u>
<u n="151" who="S0327">okay that's nice well he must be pleased with what what you're doing</u>
<u n="152" who="S0326">yeah and when I I send him the philosophy essays that I write</u>
<u n="153" who="S0327">do you? <pause dur="short"/> and does he does he criticise them? does he? or does he just?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0326">erm</u>
<u n="155" who="S0327">does he help you?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0326">he can try and criticise them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0327">do you argue with him? <unclear/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0326">well he I think I <trunc>kn</trunc> he doesn't really know this this this branch of philosophy as well as I do almost</u>
<u n="159" who="S0327">right</u>
<u n="160" who="S0326">erm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0327">what was his his what is his period?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0326">I don't know but it's definitely not pre Socratic</u>
<u n="163" who="S0327">you're doing pre Socratic philosophy?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0326">yeah and also</u>
<u n="165" who="S0327">Plato?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0326">no Plato's</u>
<u n="167" who="S0327">Plato's after?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0326">yeah it's</u>
<u n="169" who="S0327">so who is <trunc>pre</trunc>pre Socratic?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0326">it's people the <trunc>fa</trunc>famous people is people like Heraclitus</u>
<u n="171" who="S0327">oh right yes okay</u>
<u n="172" who="S0326">erm Parmenides</u>
<u n="173" who="S0327">oh right they're before?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0326">they're very and <trunc>m</trunc>and more interesting I think cos they're all sort of mystics in a way</u>
<u n="175" who="S0327">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0326">mm and their <trunc>ph</trunc>their their philosophy is collected from so so one might just have sort of forty-one liners left or they write it in a poem</u>
<u n="177" who="S0327">actually it's astonishing isn't it that it's left er that er that we still have it it's absolutely startling when you think about it</u>
<u n="178" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0327">you know when I think of stuff that I've lost from not only my own parents or grandparents but my own early life forty fifty-sixty years ago and then we have oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you've got a you've got a tattoo?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0326">oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0327">a leaf okay that's not very daring but it's very pretty</u>
<u n="182" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0327">does it symbolise anything?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0326">erm I got a <trunc>symmet</trunc> I got matching tattoos</u>
<u n="185" who="S0327">oh where's the other?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0326">no with er someone else</u>
<u n="187" who="S0327">oh I see</u>
<u n="188" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0327">a girl?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0326">with a girl yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0327">have you got a girlfriend?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0327">you've got a girlfriend? and is she in <anon type="place"/> or in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0326">she's in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0327">oh the girl who <unclear/> in a cake shop? still the same one?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0326">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0327">excellent what's her name?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0326">er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0327"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes useful <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0327">terribly useful my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> all her up to a certain point all her boyfriends were called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0327">and so we we all said it's very convenient we'd just say how's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? and it didn't matter we'd got it right</u>
<u n="204" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0327">fancy that and is that her profession working in the cake shop?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0326">yeah she owns erm bakeries she owns</u>
<u n="207" who="S0327">mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0326">she owns one in <anon type="place"/> and she owns <trunc>o</trunc>one in <anon type="place"/> and some in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0327">I see you're you're going out with erm how does one put it? a proper business</u>
<u n="210" who="S0326">yeah she's a businesswoman</u>
<u n="211" who="S0327">a businesswoman well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that's probably very good for you I would imagine because there must be a touch of real life there</u>
<u n="212" who="S0326">well sort of</u>
<u n="213" who="S0327">not not just ancient Greece and you get cakes to match?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0327">mm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0327">some people have fallen on good times haven't they?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0327">well that sounds brilliant <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't know whether I should ask you about your mum's new boyfriend <trunc>sh</trunc> cos she I haven't heard anything from her <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0326" trans="overlap">well he's called he's called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0327">he's called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? yes that's also handy yep</u>
<u n="222" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm</u>
<u n="223" who="S0327">and is he nice?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0326">yeah he <trunc>seem</trunc> yeah he's nice I I don't know him that well but he seems nice</u>
<u n="225" who="S0327">he's a painter?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0326">yeah he's an artist</u>
<u n="227" who="S0327">what kind of?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0326">what kind of?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0327">mm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0326">erm <pause dur="short"/> you'd have to you'd have to have a look erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came round and saw some of his paintings on the wall he liked them erm it's sort of abstract paintings</u>
<u n="231" who="S0327">and why does he not sort of show or anything?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0326">I don't know I don't know what he seems to I don't know what they erm he does with his time really <trunc>i</trunc>if he's <unclear/> like if he's working towards a show or</u>
<u n="233" who="S0327">anyhow your mum's happy?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0327">that's the main thing and he's a proper age not a child</u>
<u n="236" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0327">oh well that's all excellent</u>
<u n="238" who="S0326">child <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0327">well don't forget from where I stand <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> er anybody under fifty's a child and as I have yet to meet meet a grown up man in my life erm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0327">I'm certainly I have yet to meet a grown up artist</u>
<u n="242" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0327">yeah there was a big meeting at the <anon type="place"/> yesterday which was a general assembly and I actually didn't sit it out cos I can't sit there for sort of six hours or you know but I know that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm was going to bring up the fact that he's very upset that the <anon type="place"/> accepts money from the tobacco companies which is true we get apparently four four and a half million from them and I you know I I left messages to be read out at the meeting after I left whether or not they were but bit sarcastic I said first of all you know will you thank <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for drawing our attention to the fact that smoking's not good for you erm</u>
<u n="244" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0327">and secondly erm <pause dur="short"/> if we turn down the money from tobacco companies then surely we should turn down all money because where is clean money? what is it <trunc>w</trunc>what is clean money? and can he suggest some? because if he can suggest some I'd like some myself</u>
<u n="246" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0327">erm and that most money that any of us touch er certainly through the banks comes through armaments one way or the other cos it's the biggest world trade we have isn't it?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="249" who="S0327">I think so I haven't heard any he doesn't get up till late so I hope he's not too cross with me</u>
<u n="250" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0327">just thought it was a silly thing to do</u>
<u n="252" who="S0326">should get try and get some free fags out of them</u>
<u n="253" who="S0327"><vocal desc="laugh"/> now that hadn't occurred to me I don't know how you do that</u>
<u n="254" who="S0326">be like</u>
<u n="255" who="S0327">write to them and say look I've been defending you I mean I'm not defending I'm not defending smoking</u>
<u n="256" who="S0326" trans="overlap">you could be their you could be their erm sort of lobbyist in there</u>
<u n="257" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0327">I'm not going that far I mean I you know you do have to be an idiot to smoke <pause dur="short"/> it's not a good thing on the other hand and you know you can get lung cancer but all drugs have side effects and because smoking's so dangerous the side effects are good I hope you don't smoke <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0326">not properly</u>
<u n="260" who="S0327">no try not to because you it's very easy to get addicted like me quite apart from anything else the cost is horrendous</u>
<u n="261" who="S0326">yeah I smoke roll ups <unclear>if I do</unclear></u>
<u n="262" who="S0327">but you know they're going they're going to erm give their four and a half million to somebody else if they don't give it to the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="263" who="S0326">what are they giving it for? what do they get back?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0327">acknowledgement</u>
<u n="265" who="S0326">so you put it in er?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0327">they put it in like you know erm advertising exhibitions and things like that <pause dur="short"/> I mean the <anon type="place"/>'s <trunc>g</trunc> a big establishment now I mean actually I'm organising an exhibition for them which might interest you a bit erm not until the new building is built which'll be maybe not for three or four years so who knows? maybe I won't be alive in three or four years or with a Zimmer frame or whatever so I'm trying to get it organised now but I'm picking out great works er that is to say great drawings from the great artists from the past and connecting them to contemporary stuff that's been now being done now</u>
<u n="267" who="S0326">er <trunc>j</trunc>just <trunc>conte</trunc> any sort of contemporary art? or just drawings?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0327">erm no anything erm but I'm also basing it in erm ideas of geometry and proportion erm and measurement dimension so I'm trying to make these connections between the past and the and the present so it connects a little bit to you know to <trunc>w</trunc>to what you're doing</u>
<u n="269" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0327">cos all those initial ideas of proportion came from the Greeks didn't they?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0326">yeah and Plato had above his school mm don't come in unless you know the geometry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0327">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but he must have been a very er disagreeable person to work with if you if you were an artist of any sort</u>
<u n="273" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0327">he was so against art <pause dur="short"/> or have we misinterpreted that?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0326">no he is more or less more or less against it <pause dur="short"/> he just er he thinks cos he can't free it from er it's always gonna be <trunc>di</trunc> sort of er I mean the two problems he has with it is sort of the sort of <pause dur="short"/> unreliability of sort of phenomenal world or what you can see with your eyes so that's anything you can see with your eyes only has a limited amount of value anyway erm and then he thinks if he can't really separate it from it having a didactic purpose so if you have all these myths about gods castrating their fathers he was <trunc>qui</trunc> they shouldn't tell that to children <pause dur="short"/> but that's I don't I suppose he would he would be he if if he believed that erm through art you could get closer to understanding other forms then he could see a a purpose for it which is more or less what I think artists are trying to do in some way point towards something that you can't express</u>
<u n="276" who="S0327">well what I'm trying to look at I mean I'm only <unclear/> really so that I can find out myself I'm not it's not academic in the sense that I know something I'm trying to teach it's that I'm <trunc>try</trunc> <vocal desc="sigh"/> basically I'm trying to understand what I've been doing for the last fifty years erm but what I don't understand about the little bit I know about what he said is why he doesn't understand that that is a fundamental it is a <trunc>fun</trunc> creativity is a <trunc>funda</trunc>fundamental part of human nature whatever form it takes I'm just reading this book actually which I won't lend you because I keep referring to it's really really interesting called The Art Instinct</u>
<u n="277" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="278" who="S0327">erm he you know he puts up er puts a very good argument up for the fact that it is more to do with the heart than the head</u>
<u n="279" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0327">which is what I certainly believe and that it is inbuilt</u>
<u n="281" who="S0326">it's very it's interesting when erm when people look at the differences between Homo sapien and Neanderthal societies the only real difference is that <trunc>Neanderth</trunc>Neanderthals didn't erm have a sort of culture of figurative art or symbolic thought they didn't do any like cave paintings</u>
<u n="282" who="S0327">did they not?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0326">no and so and <trunc>s</trunc> people just can't <trunc>w</trunc>can't work out why er that should make a difference but it seems to have made some sort of difference to survival</u>
<u n="284" who="S0327" trans="overlap">but but cave painting started I mean we we know of cave paintings at least thirty thousand years ago so who were they?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah but there there was erm that's they er they existed together at the same time</u>
<u n="286" who="S0327">I think I read about that somewhere so these two kinds of human species</u>
<u n="287" who="S0326">yeah er protohuman species</u>
<u n="288" who="S0327">they don't really know do they? I mean er</u>
<u n="289" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0327">they don't know how we appeared I mean from everything I've read it's just almost as though we appeared ready made and I know quite <unclear>honestly</unclear> how that fits in with Darwinian</u>
<u n="291" who="S0326">yeah well especially when you think about a hundred thousand years ago it's not that long</u>
<u n="292" who="S0327">it's not that long <pause dur="short"/> it's amazing</u>
<u n="293" who="S0326">yeah everything that's happened in the <trunc>t</trunc> last two thousand five hundred years</u>
<u n="294" who="S0327">yeah but you see if you look at some of those cave paintings and I've been to Lascaux the sophistication is so great <pause dur="short"/> the intuitive sophistication they had that one has to think that they weren't really all that different that the only thing that's changed is technology and our learning but the actual way they were constituted as human beings wasn't that different</u>
<u n="295" who="S0326">and so he's and <trunc>h</trunc> this book is about the sort of natural drive?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0327">it's about the natural drive</u>
<u n="297" who="S0326"><unclear/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0327">and erm <pause dur="short"/> I actually read it before but my memory now my memory is just unbelievably bad which is useful it means I can read books again and erm you know it goes into you know the meaning of aesthetic values and aesthetic problems and erm forgery erm uses of fiction I see I've marked a few things natural selection I mean <trunc>ba</trunc>basically what he's arguing <unclear/> is a kind of <trunc>n</trunc>natural selection in art as well erm I mean I can only read it rather slowly and carefully but you might you might just find it interesting but I mean who who were those human beings who first measured a pillar?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0326">yes I mean there's this there's a good erm do you know that woman Camille Paglia?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0327">yes yes I remember her</u>
<u n="301" who="S0326">she like yeah she writes a lot of like nonsense some of the time but there's a she has a book called Sexual Personae a sort of art history book goes from ancient Egypt to Emily Dickinson and the first chapter is <trunc>r</trunc> it's really good about sort of thinking about where art came from and why people make art erm it's sort of like a reaction to a sort of primal <trunc>a</trunc>anxiety about nature and what they can't know in the dark and so she has ideas about why people have pillars and pyramids and a straight line a straight line is erm sort of a symbol of man's trying to er emancipate himself from from nature erm and yeah she looks at like er she compares Egyptian free standing statues to their do you know the Venus of Willendorf sculpture? that sort of bulbous yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0327" trans="overlap">yes yes I know yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0326">and sort of the <trunc>r</trunc> this is erm sort of chthonic primal art and then the birth of the western eye is what you see when er in in Egyptian culture</u>
<u n="304" who="S0327">I do remember reading some stuff of hers which was simply over the top</u>
<u n="305" who="S0326">yeah she <trunc>g</trunc> I mean she goes on she's</u>
<u n="306" who="S0327"><unclear/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0326">she'll er she'll like go on and on saying a lot of things that without stopping to like</u>
<u n="308" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="309" who="S0326">about without an argument</u>
<u n="310" who="S0327"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> adored her work when it first came out I actually couldn't cope with it erm it's too much like a rant to me</u>
<u n="311" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="312" who="S0327">erm I mean what I'm in fact I might</u>
<u n="313" who="S0326">well the it's just the <trunc>f</trunc>the first chapter is good er the first three chapters of that book are are <trunc>goo</trunc> are interesting at least</u>
<u n="314" who="S0327">yes <pause dur="short"/> er well what I'm trying to do in this exhibition erm I might even let <unclear/> give you the draft of the mm the introduction <unclear/> would you be able to do that for me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="316" who="S0327">at some point? it's not long it's a couple of thousand words <trunc>i</trunc> er well it's partly I mean this none of this is original but you know is to is to talk about all the dimension coming from the body that even even the most abstract artist it has to come from us because this is the only tool we have really</u>
<u n="317" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0327">to measure things and you you see it very clearly in art</u>
<u n="319" who="S0326">oh right</u>
<u n="320" who="S0327">erm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0326">I did actually write an essay last time about erm the naked male body in art and I spent most of it trying to work out why people was er fixated by using the <trunc>n</trunc>naked male body in Greece <pause dur="short"/> and but people do say about columns <trunc>s</trunc>sort of Doric columns and er Ionic columns and <trunc>Vitru</trunc> like the sort of Vitruvian theory about male Doric columns and and based on the male body er</u>
<u n="322" who="S0327" trans="overlap"><unclear>well I mean er</unclear> those are all good theories I mean well I don't suppose we'll ever know erm but it seems to me perfectly obvious that that this is the way any creature relates the <trunc>worl</trunc> relates to the world you know if you're an ant presumably you have a very different understanding of the world of the size and the scale erm assuming they have brains and things like that which I dare say they don't erm you know and if we were if we were giants we would see it all scale is incredibly important I don't mean size</u>
<u n="323" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0327">I actually mean scale which is the relationship of large and small erm Jacquetta Hawkes I seem to remember in a book one of those first books that came out in the fifties or sixties don't eat too much cos I've got a big pudding for you</u>
<u n="325" who="S0326">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0327">erm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0326">it's nice the salad though</u>
<u n="328" who="S0327">it's delicious isn't it? I eat this every day and I er I I think it's very very good to eat it's just pickled vegetables I just shove in whatever I erm whatever I can get hold of er <unclear>there are</unclear> images I seem to remember of sheaves of corn so when you've got the corn tied together and then it springs out at the top and the that was originally how the dwellings were were erm constructed and so it was just their theory I seem to remember I can't remember it's a very famous book that I remember giving to my father for Christmas erm fifties er in the fifties I would've thought erm what was it called? Jacquetta Hawkes and</u>
<u n="329" who="S0326">not a novel?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0327">no no no it's an <trunc>ar</trunc> a book on archaeology erm and so er you know they made the same things except in stone and so they gradually they gradually emerged <pause dur="short"/> but I suppose they will <unclear/> and of course the Egyptians did come first didn't they?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0326">yeah what is very strange about only about the Egyptian sort of visual culture that it doesn't change really once it's there it <trunc>st</trunc>stays the same for three thousand years</u>
<u n="332" who="S0327">that is interesting isn't it?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0326" trans="overlap">when you look at Greek visual culture within two hundred years it's totally transformed</u>
<u n="334" who="S0327">yeah well it's the same er thing with Islamic art actually you know that they won't allow that to change erm I noticed when I was in Morocco that you know it's well it's really been downhill all the way since about eleventh or twelfth century I remember in in Marrakesh there's a <trunc>f</trunc> a wonderful building I can't remember what it's called now erm all that's left is just stone one portion and bit by bit you know the Ottoman's came and that was lovely all that stuff</u>
<u n="335" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0327">er and now they don't know er of course they haven't a clue what to do now now modernism has taken over erm they're still not supposed to do anything figurative everything's held back <pause dur="short"/> so those cultural comparisons are are terribly interesting <pause dur="short"/> but I know that you know I think I'm not one that's always asking myself what is it one's trying to do? cos as an artist you never really honestly know because as I said</u>
<u n="337" who="S0326">thank you</u>
<u n="338" who="S0327">I don't believe the brain has much to do with it erm and so I think a lot of a lot quite a lot of art is always trying to go back to to the origin where you know where it all came from it looks a bit different because we're all creatures of circumstance and we can't escape our time now I've got <unclear/> but I <unclear/> too fussy <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0326">I haven't showed this tattoo yet to my mum <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0327">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what do you think she's going to say?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0326">she won't mind I just haven't <trunc>hav</trunc>haven't actually worn a T shirt that's why probably</u>
<u n="342" who="S0327"><unclear/> have another look I need to find my glasses <unclear/> where did you get it done?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0326">erm some place in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0327">it's very pretty actually</u>
<u n="345" who="S0326">it's cos erm</u>
<u n="346" who="S0327">it's quite delicate</u>
<u n="347" who="S0326">er we have erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I were we had we made up in the summer played a lot of pool erm and we made a pool team called <trunc>Au</trunc> er Autumn Leaf I can't remember why so that's what it's</u>
<u n="348" who="S0327">called what?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0326">Autumn Leaf <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0327">Autumn Leaf <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> how nice and romantic how's the other <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are you still friends with her?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0326">erm yeah I mean she emailed me the other week I wrote back</u>
<u n="352" who="S0327">is she over <trunc>he</trunc>over here?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0326">she's no she's in erm <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="354" who="S0327">she's in <anon type="place"/> now?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0326">yeah at the at <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> liberal sort of arts college</u>
<u n="356" who="S0327">oh really?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0326" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0327">doing what?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0326">liberal arts</u>
<u n="360" who="S0327">what er what are liberal arts? <unclear/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0326" trans="overlap">liberal arts is an American humanities degree I told her that she <trunc>sh</trunc> probably shouldn't go to that school erm in her email she said you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you were right about my school it's kind of crap erm but I just wrote back saying it doesn't matter what school you go to they're all kind of crap</u>
<u n="362" who="S0327">they aren't you know are they all <unclear>crap</unclear>?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0326" trans="overlap">well in to some er er some extent yeah they're not gonna</u>
<u n="364" who="S0327">they weren't in my day</u>
<u n="365" who="S0326">well I think they're all they're gonna be crap if you're er if <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="366" who="S0327">I'm mean you're not saying <anon type="place"/> is crap are you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0326">no but it's not you know it's there's things about it that I'd rather that are er <trunc>n</trunc>not perfect</u>
<u n="368" who="S0327">like what?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0326">well like the <trunc>t</trunc> the the <trunc>ed</trunc> the teaching and er learning is not is not crap but the <trunc>s</trunc> town is the <trunc>s</trunc> the sort of the culture maybe of people there</u>
<u n="370" who="S0327">the culture of what? which people? the teachers?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0326" trans="overlap">for the the students</u>
<u n="372" who="S0327">the students?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0327">oh well I mean there's nothing the <trunc>u</trunc>the university can do about that</u>
<u n="375" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah I know yeah I know well er there is probably but you know there's <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="376" who="S0327">this is crème fraîche I think erm</u>
<u n="377" who="S0326">but also I suppose er like if you we're <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and you've just spent a year being like a successful model then it'd be boring to go to school</u>
<u n="378" who="S0327">but being a model is terribly boring</u>
<u n="379" who="S0326">yeah but not she was <trunc>qu</trunc>quite like she wasn't it wasn't I don't think it was very boring for her cos she was working with all the best people and getting to er you know they were photographers who are really artists and she didn't have to <trunc>d</trunc> work that <trunc>har</trunc> she was just doing a few things for lots of money</u>
<u n="380" who="S0327"><unclear>right</unclear> <unclear/> lots of money <unclear/> but she has a brain it's a bit of a pity not to use it well maybe your standards are a little bit high or perhaps you're interested in a broader range of things than some of your peer group is do you think it's that?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0326">what? are you talking about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I? or?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0327">er no er <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0326">well maybe er I dunno I guess it's probably just like sort of the from the age of like fifteen er it was I <trunc>ha</trunc> like my life has been unusual compared to other people's my age</u>
<u n="384" who="S0327">in what way? because you've travelled more?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0326">just because the because of growing up in in <anon type="place"/> area in <anon type="place"/> and <trunc>ha</trunc>having friends that was older</u>
<u n="386" who="S0327"><vocal desc="cough"/> sorry it's a bit of ginger my god that's hot <vocal desc="cough"/> oh dear <pause dur="short"/> because of it being <anon type="place"/>? because of it being working class? because of being racially mixed?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0326" trans="overlap">no because er no because erm cos of what that's going on there all sort of the interesting thing's like er parties that are erm the things to go to and the people to meet and then <trunc>tr</trunc>and then travelling more</u>
<u n="388" who="S0327">so do you do you think that most of them have more conventional backgrounds than you? I suppose yes er you know your parents are not straightforward middle class working in a bank kind of parents erm <trunc>s</trunc> is it partly class then?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="390" who="S0327">that you have a broader view of things</u>
<u n="391" who="S0326">yeah probably I mean not like no one very few people went to schools like <anon type="place"/> I mean it's not most people who went to <trunc>s</trunc> like sort of the people from <anon type="place"/> they er <trunc>t</trunc>tend to be from like <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0327">right <pause dur="short"/> and yet from what I understood about <anon type="place"/> when you were there is that it was er er relatively old fashioned values in terms of discipline and so on</u>
<u n="393" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="394" who="S0327">cos I know when you know erm when I heard <trunc>w</trunc> er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> complain about things well the discipline that he complained about was what was absolutely normal for my generation</u>
<u n="395" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0327">you know and you walked down the corridor and you er in single file and there's no big deal and you just did that and</u>
<u n="397" who="S0326">it's it's</u>
<u n="398" who="S0327">and you weren't supposed to make a a noise in class and you weren't supposed to you didn't have mobiles to listen to in <trunc>cl</trunc> all those things</u>
<u n="399" who="S0326">yeah no but</u>
<u n="400" who="S0327">of course they can't teach now if if they're all if there's all that disruption</u>
<u n="401" who="S0326">yeah but it was er it was a bit shit like if you forgot your pencil and you had a teacher that didn't like you you'd get an <trunc>hou</trunc> you know you'd stay after school for an hour</u>
<u n="402" who="S0327">right</u>
<u n="403" who="S0326">that kind of thing that was a bit was what <trunc>upse</trunc> er annoyed people I think</u>
<u n="404" who="S0327">yeah so you <unclear>we didn't have <trunc>tha</trunc> even that</unclear> well I mean as you know he's now a big deal <vocal desc="cough"/> he's a big cheese now</u>
<u n="405" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0327">er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I've read people complaining about him but I must say I rather admire him</u>
<u n="407" who="S0326">yeah I think he <trunc>di</trunc> is good</u>
<u n="408" who="S0327">from you know from what I've heard he's er does he stands up for standards mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0326">he also put Latin into <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0327">yep <pause dur="short"/> well I think you lot were incredibly lucky to go to <anon type="place"/> at that period cos who was it? was it either <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? told me that er you know it isn't so good anymore that now apparently there's some head teacher who's over the top disciplinarian</u>
<u n="411" who="S0326">yeah that's erm er yeah I remember him he was here when I was there</u>
<u n="412" who="S0327">was he?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0326">yeah I mean he was like he seems like a sort of sadist you know</u>
<u n="414" who="S0327">oh really? okay well you'll always get those you know wherever you are <unclear/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0326">I'm just gonna get some water would you like some?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0327">er no help yourself there's a glass a glass there <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0326">but whilst their their project er <anon type="place"/>'s a bit more it's not not so coherent anymore because er because the school became <trunc>fam</trunc> a <trunc>fam</trunc>a famously a good school</u>
<u n="418" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="419" who="S0326">so people go er like wanna go there don't cause the same kind of problems as the <trunc>t</trunc> kids that went there five years ago</u>
<u n="420" who="S0327">oh really?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0326">well it's in the in the general gentrification like one of the reasons why</u>
<u n="422" who="S0327" trans="overlap">yes of course</u>
<u n="423" who="S0326">that whole area's been gentrified</u>
<u n="424" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="425" who="S0326">is cos there's good schools there</u>
<u n="426" who="S0327">that's right of course yep I know I mean I've heard this that in fact last time I saw your mum which was a very long time ago she was we went up for lunch up the road here and she said there are no restaurants like this anymore in <anon type="place"/> she said that you have to sit down and have a menu now you know it was just a kebab place</u>
<u n="427" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="428" who="S0327">but a very nice one which is I find absolutely incredible it's happened so fast and all the houses and</u>
<u n="429" who="S0326">yeah all the erm Turkish you have er sit down and have a menu and everything's like eleven pounds</u>
<u n="430" who="S0327">it's incredible <unclear/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0326">whereas er</u>
<u n="432" who="S0327">you can get a perfectly good lunch for six pounds <unclear/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0326">yeah I know I remember when we moved there and we we ate in the Turkish every night cos we didn't have a proper kitchen it was like you'd just sit down and er I think it was like four pounds for</u>
<u n="434" who="S0327">yes and all that's changed gosh it happens fast <pause dur="long"/> I dunno where people live now I mean if they haven't got any money I think it's really really really difficult</u>
<u n="435" who="S0326">they don't though they're <trunc>mo</trunc> I mean they're moving more and more outside of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0327">yes but</u>
<u n="437" who="S0326">I don't particularly wanna live in <anon type="place"/> after I <trunc>fin</trunc> like it seems too difficult and not worth it</u>
<u n="438" who="S0327">I think it is difficult now for for <unclear/></u>
<u n="439" who="S0326" trans="overlap">you can't live anywhere for er er that close for sort of less than six hundred pounds a month</u>
<u n="440" who="S0327">no I mean I'd miss <unclear/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0326" trans="overlap">and like all all my friends who are thirty and er they none of them have their own place</u>
<u n="442" who="S0327">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0326">they all they're all living with their friends because they <trunc>c</trunc> you you know <trunc>c</trunc> no one can afford it</u>
<u n="444" who="S0327">no the only way people can get somewhere to live is er is if their parents die and leave them somewhere to live <pause dur="short"/> and as your grandparents are still alive you can't really hold you breath for your parents to die just yet</u>
<u n="445" who="S0326">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0327">how is your other granny by the way?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0326">as far as I know she's fine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="448" who="S0327">er how old is she now?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0326">mm ninety-five I think</u>
<u n="450" who="S0327">that's pretty impressive well you may have a very long life ahead of you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0326">yeah I wouldn't be <trunc>surpri</trunc> I <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="452" who="S0327" trans="overlap">even your dad is not that young anymore how old is your dad?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0326">sixty-three</u>
<u n="454" who="S0327">sixty-three? mm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0326">yeah I wouldn't be surprised if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> lived to be like a hundred and ten <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0327">er <trunc>th</trunc>that's asking quite a lot</u>
<u n="457" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="458" who="S0327">there are not very many people that make a hundred and ten</u>
<u n="459" who="S0326">I know but it's just seems like she seems you know a machine</u>
<u n="460" who="S0327">she is <unclear/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="462" who="S0327">although as my dear friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said the other day when I said something about dying he said oh we'll have to shoot you</u>
<u n="463" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0327">and your dad lives still mostly in America?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0326">erm yeah he's in <anon type="place"/> still</u>
<u n="466" who="S0327">and why are you going to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0326">erm I don't really know just</u>
<u n="468" who="S0327">you don't know you just want to see it?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0326">just for the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wanted to go somewhere</u>
<u n="470" who="S0327">oh you're going together? right</u>
<u n="471" who="S0326">yeah we're flying to <anon type="place"/> on Christmas Day and then stay there hang out there for a few days and then to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0327">what's the climate in <anon type="place"/> this time of year?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0326">it's hot</u>
<u n="474" who="S0327">oh it'll be nice</u>
<u n="475" who="S0326">it's it the country seems quite <unclear/> it kinda <trunc>depe</trunc>depends quite a lot on where you are</u>
<u n="476" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="477" who="S0326">but it's in it's like holiday season it's like good weather it's not the rainy season</u>
<u n="478" who="S0327"><unclear/> and I don't know anything about <anon type="place"/> actually be careful <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> young men and young women in er you know it does sound as though it's an incredibly criminalised society don't take any risks</u>
<u n="479" who="S0326">mm it's <trunc>c</trunc> it's a dangerous country but also it's pretty it's relatively safe</u>
<u n="480" who="S0327">I would quite like to go somewhere like not anymore but I would have like somewhere like Peru erm Mexican art doesn't er pre Columbian art I like <unclear/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0326">yeah most of <trunc>l</trunc> <trunc>m</trunc> <trunc>m</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> two of my favourite things in books are set in <anon type="place"/> erm the er there's that book Under the Volcano</u>
<u n="482" who="S0327">oh yes you've mentioned that before they'd obviously made a big impression on you</u>
<u n="483" who="S0326">yeah I know I'm reading it again now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="484" who="S0327">are you? I never managed it</u>
<u n="485" who="S0326" trans="overlap">er the fourth time so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0327">really? do you think I should try give it a try?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0326">I dunno it depends er it's like the slower you read it the better it is and like the more you read it cos you it's a <trunc>comp</trunc> it's like it's a complicated book and things you er won't won't notice even on like a third go erm there's a really good thing online a companion someone some sort of Malcolm Lowry fanatic has made it he's quite it's a really good document like basically every sort of line he has explains the reference or if they talk about a brand of cigarettes they're smoking in <anon type="place"/> it'll have a picture</u>
<u n="488" who="S0327" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="489" who="S0326">of the box of cigarettes</u>
<u n="490" who="S0327">right</u>
<u n="491" who="S0326">so <trunc>n</trunc> it's nice er it's fun to read it with that going through with that to explain you can understand everything</u>
<u n="492" who="S0327" trans="overlap">yes I've got a in my book I've got a picture of cigarettes that my mother used to smoke erm I'll get you <unclear>er another</unclear> coffee mm <pause dur="long"/> page sixty-one very proud of this actually because I</u>
<u n="493" who="S0326">yeah it looks nice</u>
<u n="494" who="S0327">it's easy to read you know it's it's not it's quite <unclear>distinctive</unclear> <unclear/> it's about your various grandparents and things no great-<trunc>gran</trunc> look I was</u>
<u n="495" who="S0326" trans="overlap">called Passing Clouds?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0327">yes they were called Passing Clouds and I was so that is the only one I could find the only packet I bought it for two pounds fifty from Ebay</u>
<u n="497" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="498" who="S0327">and that was the only answer I had so I probably have the last</u>
<u n="499" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0327">the last cover of Passing Clouds and then there's one that you I hope you'll find interesting <pause dur="long"/> which is the</u>
<u n="501" who="S0326">oh yeah the stamp</u>
<u n="502" who="S0327">the stamp which I've got there <unclear>exit permit</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0326">okay <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0327">erm shall I dedicate it to you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0326">er why not <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="506" who="S0327">why not huh? <pause dur="short"/> everybody else had my name and you can have</u>
<u n="507" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0327">granny instead <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> wrapping yes well I need to go to evening classes in unwrapping <unclear>things</unclear></u>
<u n="509" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0327"><vocal desc="cough"/> <pause dur="long"/> I'm so exhausted didn't sleep well er last night <unclear>no wonder</unclear> I'm so tired <pause dur="short"/> and you' get a free bookmark with it</u>
<u n="511" who="S0326">oh thank you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="512" who="S0327">that's what you get if you buy them from the <anon type="place"/> if you get them from Amazon you don't get the free bookmark</u>
<u n="513" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what's on at the <anon type="place"/> at the moment?</u>
<u n="514" who="S0327">well there is a Kiefer you might be interested in you know Kiefer?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0326">I don't think so</u>
<u n="516" who="S0327">Kiefer is this wildly successful er German artist erm rather Wagnerian did I have a? here absolutely massive work <trunc>unbeliev</trunc> wouldn't fit in anywhere in this house</u>
<u n="517" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0327">erm I have a lot of reservations I mean one cannot but admire what he does erm <pause dur="short"/> you know I mean that is something like thirty feet wide and er thirty <trunc>f</trunc> twenty feet high or whatever have a look in here</u>
<u n="519" who="S0326">and <trunc>w</trunc>what erm what years?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0327">he's er he's alive now</u>
<u n="521" who="S0326">he's alive now</u>
<u n="522" who="S0327">he's just he's probably a bit younger than me <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0326">yeah it's the kind of thing people go for</u>
<u n="524" who="S0327">they do I mean the thing is <vocal desc="sigh"/> his studio apparently is about ten acres he has er all this amazing amount of space and erm I mean it is big beyond the whole thing is big beyond belief and he's er as he's so gone for it erm one has to admire that <vocal desc="cough"/> it doesn't touch the heart with me erm it's too big it's too <trunc>gi</trunc> it's such <trunc>gigant</trunc> the ego is</u>
<u n="525" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0327">is almost impossible to understand actually erm I think it'd be worth your going if you wanted to go <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and you could go on a Friday morning at nine o'clock I can probably always get you in free</u>
<u n="527" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="528" who="S0327">er as a <trunc>ma</trunc> I don't er tomorrow in fact I've got to go into the <anon type="place"/> if you could go to <trunc>tom</trunc> wanted to go tomorrow I'll be there most of the morning and I can leave a ticket or something</u>
<u n="529" who="S0326">yeah maybe</u>
<u n="530" who="S0327">let me know before I'm probably gonna be leaving here at half past nine tomorrow morning cos I'm gonna work in the library there actually you might like to see their library <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="531" who="S0326">is it good is it?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0327"><vocal desc="gasp"/> it is breathtaking it is and there's a wonderful librarian I mean a real scholar that I'm working with he's found all these marvellous books and prints and works and I actually held with my own hands the very last Turner etching that he did it was fabulous erm I mean if you wanted tomorrow morning to meet we could arrange a time</u>
<u n="533" who="S0326">yeah maybe I'll come I'd like to see er the library</u>
<u n="534" who="S0327">and I can then take you in it opens at ten we could meet at half past ten or something <pause dur="short"/> want to do that?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0326">yes yeah I'll just check what I I'm doing tomorrow morning and tomorrow <unclear/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0327" trans="overlap">alright I mean if you could only come later I mean I'll probably be there I if I go half past ten I'll be finished by twelve er you know then I could erm er even go round with you if I could bear to see the Kiefer again</u>
<u n="537" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="538" who="S0327">er there is also except you can't see them together there is a wonderful <vocal desc="cough"/> exhibition in the <anon type="place"/> gallery of <trunc>m</trunc> er Moroni who's a sort of er slightly forgotten erm sixteenth century artist mostly portraits but psychologically so <trunc>in</trunc>incisive and amazing erm so both those I mean the best thing would be for me to <trunc>f</trunc>find a way of introducing you to there's this bloke called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who arranges these things and then he can get you in any time erm otherwise officially friends are <trunc>s</trunc>are supposed to get in for nothing only on a Friday at nine o'clock</u>
<u n="539" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="540" who="S0327">but you know I can always do it if I can get hold of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> alright let me know about tomorrow morning er</u>
<u n="541" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I will</u>
<u n="542" who="S0327">and I think what we could do is you come up to the library with me then you could go go across and see the the show <vocal desc="cough"/> erm cos you know it's er they do have the most the most wonderful collection <unclear>think it would be an opportunity</unclear></u>
<u n="543" who="S0326">do they have nice sort of work tables at</u>
<u n="544" who="S0327">the <trunc>w</trunc> yes I mean I'm sorry I I don't use it more <pause dur="short"/> there's a whole bunch of three or four of these artists who that came up in the seventies really <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> but as you see it's got all that Wagnerian stuff you know the and they're very physical there's a lot a lot of matter on them</u>
<u n="545" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="546" who="S0327">did you manage all your? would you like some more?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0326"><unclear>no</unclear></u>
<u n="548" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0326">there was a lot <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="550" who="S0327">you haven't done badly <unclear/> maybe I'll have to eat these myself later mm</u>
<u n="551" who="S0326">do you know when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is back from <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0327">yeah I believe Saturday just <unclear>when I was</unclear> talking yesterday she seems in quite good spirits which is nice well it'll be nice to see everybody together</u>
<u n="553" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="554" who="S0327">erm <pause dur="short"/> I mean I'm doing ham again and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and your mum would I expect you one of you to bring a pudding and your apparently your mum said oh well I've got some of last year's Christmas pudding left</u>
<u n="555" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="556" who="S0327">said that sounds like something <unclear/> would say if you want to describe a person</u>
<u n="557" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="558" who="S0327">that he er he looks rather like last year's Christmas pudding</u>
<u n="559" who="S0326">maybe <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will make a cake</u>
<u n="560" who="S0327">oh</u>
<u n="561" who="S0326">have you seen erm pictures of her cakes?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0327">no</u>
<u n="563" who="S0326">should probably show you them they look quite spectacular <pause dur="short"/> erm let me just find it <pause dur="long"/> just click on this it's easier to see</u>
<u n="564" who="S0327"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is she Italian?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0326">no it's her business name <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0327">it's her business name bake a cake design I see that's very grand oh how wonderful hang on hang on <pause dur="short"/> hang on cake pear parsnip ginger and roast chestnut I want some</u>
<u n="567" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you should come to the bakery one day maybe</u>
<u n="568" who="S0327">yeah oh blimey <pause dur="long"/> oh look at that one</u>
<u n="569" who="S0326"><unclear/> that's a wreath <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0327">that's a wreath?</u>
<u n="571" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="573" who="S0326">this one's cool <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="574" who="S0327">er what's in it? <pause dur="short"/> that doesn't say looks like a yeah oh that's great is that edible?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0326">yeah it's all edible</u>
<u n="576" who="S0327">gold leaf? edible golf leaf?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0326">er something edible gold <unclear>something</unclear> she does a lot of she's very interested in er <trunc>s</trunc> erm in gardening and flowers and edible flowers on her cakes</u>
<u n="578" who="S0327">did she go to school to learn this?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0326">no she's erm dunno how she learnt it actually <vocal desc="laugh"/> she never went to patisserie school or</u>
<u n="580" who="S0327">that's a wreath as well <pause dur="short"/> beetroot parsnip and carrot cake spelt and <trunc>c</trunc> that sounds really amazing <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh look at the tarts <pause dur="short"/> so it's just a it's just a patisserie? just a cake shop?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0326">erm yeah er they</u>
<u n="582" who="S0327">doesn't they don't have anything else?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0326">they don't have bread</u>
<u n="584" who="S0327">they don't have bread</u>
<u n="585" who="S0326">they have coffee it's only open on Sundays and</u>
<u n="586" who="S0327">oh it's only open one day a week?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0326">and on in December it's open on Wednesday's</u>
<u n="588" who="S0327">right so she spends all week making them?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0326">well she doesn't really she has a lot of people who work for her now</u>
<u n="590" who="S0327">does she?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0326">that she's trained erm so she kind of just does things like she does a lot of sort of jobs for <trunc>comp</trunc> like for like fashion companies</u>
<u n="592" who="S0327" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="593" who="S0326">and stuff and like gets them cake for their parties she does a lot of time like going to meetings to discuss what to do</u>
<u n="594" who="S0327">yes</u>
<u n="595" who="S0326">and then the other people do the the cooking the baking</u>
<u n="596" who="S0327">that's absolutely brilliant</u>
<u n="597" who="S0326">and she writes erm cookbooks</u>
<u n="598" who="S0327">does she? well er you have hit lucky be careful you don't get fat</u>
<u n="599" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I haven't really I don't eat much of them because I don't like cake that much</u>
<u n="600" who="S0327">oh don't you? oh <pause dur="short"/> I see</u>
<u n="601" who="S0326">she makes nice er sausage rolls that I eat <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="602" who="S0327">okay <pause dur="short"/> now er come and see if you can give me a hand in er with the computer <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="603" who="S0326">sure</u>
<u n="604" who="S0327">if you wouldn't mind it's just one of those little things <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has actually more or less showed me how to do this but I'm not there's certain things I can't do let me quickly show you the the exhibition that I'm <pause dur="short"/> this is the idea of the exhibition erm it's going to be called Measure for Measure <pause dur="short"/> the nice thing about that title is nobody can criticise it</u>
<u n="605" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0327">so this er none of this is to scale erm but it's just an approximation of in fact I have that's what I have to do to rescale things so we've got</u>
<u n="607" who="S0326">and you'll be able to round up originals?</u>
<u n="608" who="S0327">well at at first I thought because there's a new erm exhibition erm head of exhibitions called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have you heard of him?</u>
<u n="609" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="610" who="S0327">he's a very clever sharp probably not very profound journalist art journalist and erm I wanted to show I wanted to get something really really great like Piero's Flagellation do you know Piero's Flagellation?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="612" who="S0327">which is arguably I mean all of these things are <trunc>argu</trunc>arguably the greatest painting in the world I think I've got a picture here which is in Urbino I mean it's a small it's on panel and I said I said well that's what I'd really like and he said oh we'll be able to get that and he said if we don't we can go up the road to the <anon type="place"/> gallery to get the baptism or er Piero's Baptism or something and I just thought oh absolutely wonderous this <unclear/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="614" who="S0327">well of course it's all crap you can't you know</u>
<u n="615" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="616" who="S0327">er and nor should you those those really great works shouldn't travel so what we've agreed is that I will stick to the to drawing so that nearly all these are in this country <vocal desc="cough"/> erm that which is such a wonderful erm image is at the Louvre and I don't know it's <unclear/> look isn't that wonderful?</u>
<u n="617" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="618" who="S0327">it's just such a great drawing you know so I'm drawing attention to the geometry that that's the basis or erm triangle and the stretched outness of the body and so on erm that's <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so here we've got the classics <unclear/> Turner <unclear>Raphael</unclear> again I don't know if I'll get those two Piero might not get those but I would like to get them and of course the thing is it's it's not like me getting them having an institution like that behind you</u>
<u n="619" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="620" who="S0327">of course is you know that's a whole different thing</u>
<u n="621" who="S0326">and when and it would be the sort of inauguration of this new space?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0327">I it probably won't be the inauguration I mean it it is very very far ahead erm but it really has to be er they they can't go out to borrow the stuff until there's a good picture of what the exhibition's going to be about erm so so this is this is how it's looking at the moment so what I want to do I haven't been able to er <trunc>s</trunc> I can't remember now I want to get this up and I think I couldn't change the titles let's have a look <pause dur="short"/> some <unclear/> illustrator <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="623" who="S0326"><unclear>those are</unclear> very secure <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="624" who="S0327">well I'll tell you something <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I had er all this stuff up here and all my passwords somebody said you can't do that you know anybody can come in and get them so I I put them all in the computer or something and then I lost them</u>
<u n="625" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="626" who="S0327">so I thought you know it's <trunc>g</trunc> if somebody comes and steals this it the whole thing will be such a disaster erm I just have to make sure nobody does if I can er wait a minute no I want two page two <pause dur="short"/> well that's in preview so I want to put it into illustrator <pause dur="long"/> got all the instructions here <pause dur="long"/> mm oh okay now if I want to move this I click on it and I can move it</u>
<u n="627" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="628" who="S0327">if I want to click on that and move it I can't why not?</u>
<u n="629" who="S0326">erm you see I don't use this program but I can probably figure it out</u>
<u n="630" who="S0327">I'm sure you can</u>
<u n="631" who="S0326">how do you make the box?</u>
<u n="632" who="S0327">ah you just click and drag it across</u>
<u n="633" who="S0326">er so these are the instructions?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0327">yes look I've dragged it across oh wait a minute I've got to click on that okay and then it should</u>
<u n="635" who="S0326"><unclear/></u>
<u n="636" who="S0327">it should move well it is moving there so maybe</u>
<u n="637" who="S0326">but not up and down</u>
<u n="638" who="S0327">but not like that and I've not grasped layers oh it's gone back to <trunc>t</trunc> oh no wait a minute</u>
<u n="639" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="640" who="S0327">it's gotta be on T for type</u>
<u n="641" who="S0326">erm why? you <trunc>w</trunc>what do you wanna do? what exactly er you <trunc>wa</trunc> do you wanna do to that text?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0327">I would like to put it on that level there</u>
<u n="643" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="644" who="S0327">I'd like to be able to move it where I want</u>
<u n="645" who="S0326">then you just have to make sure you're on that to move it</u>
<u n="646" who="S0327">I just have to make sure I'm on that</u>
<u n="647" who="S0326">and if you wanna change the text</u>
<u n="648" who="S0327" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="649" who="S0326">then you'll be able you</u>
<u n="650" who="S0327">then I just well you er that's solved it and I want to make this smaller and how do I keep it in proportion?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0326">erm you should have gone from the corner</u>
<u n="652" who="S0327">ah</u>
<u n="653" who="S0326">so if you do apple Z maybe it'll undo that</u>
<u n="654" who="S0327">yeah probably wasn't right to begin with go from the corner that's right <pause dur="short"/> no it didn't do it it didn't</u>
<u n="655" who="S0326" trans="overlap">oh no it didn't erm you could</u>
<u n="656" who="S0327" trans="overlap">no I think what I have to do is there</u>
<u n="657" who="S0326">yeah you can do it up there too</u>
<u n="658" who="S0327">do I click it like that? so it's fixed?</u>
<u n="659" who="S0326">yeah it's fixed</u>
<u n="660" who="S0327">like that? so then maybe</u>
<u n="661" who="S0326">no then you do it from here you click er new <unclear>menus</unclear></u>
<u n="662" who="S0327">oh do I?</u>
<u n="663" who="S0326">I think so</u>
<u n="664" who="S0327">ah okay so</u>
<u n="665" who="S0326">as long as they're fixed they should stay erm</u>
<u n="666" who="S0327">yes okay so</u>
<u n="667" who="S0326">they should move together <pause dur="short"/> yeah see they're they're moving together</u>
<u n="668" who="S0327">they're moving together okay it's a pity the original is not right but okay that's very that's helpful let me just see if I can er then I can get I think I've got it</u>
<u n="669" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0327">I think I've got it now this one let me just er I'm not sure what that is then click on that and then I put T for type and then and do a question mark okay I've got that now if I want erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> the two pages is asking too much for me I think if I want two pages together erm</u>
<u n="671" who="S0326">sitting them side by side?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0327">yes <unclear/> have that</u>
<u n="673" who="S0326">you <trunc>dr</trunc></u>
<u n="674" who="S0327">it's gonna come up in preview so I've gotta do it in illustrator as well haven't I?</u>
<u n="675" who="S0326">yeah if you drag it into <trunc>illustra</trunc></u>
<u n="676" who="S0327">you drag it into illustrator <pause dur="long"/> I have learnt a bit but I cannot hold it in my head</u>
<u n="677" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="678" who="S0327">I cannot it's terrible <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="long"/> okay so I can get this er now what? did get serious with me cos I</u>
<u n="679" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="680" who="S0327">keep clicking what have I done here?</u>
<u n="681" who="S0326">I dunno erm</u>
<u n="682" who="S0327"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="683" who="S0326">I dunno what this this erm black screen is</u>
<u n="684" who="S0327">it's suddenly saved unsave so <unclear>must</unclear> put that again into illustrator <pause dur="long"/> okay</u>
<u n="685" who="S0326">so this is part of your proposal?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0327">yes er er I want to get this er so now I want to make sure I want to move this to the <trunc>l</trunc> the whole thing now</u>
<u n="687" who="S0326">you er need to hold it at the top on that grey bar</u>
<u n="688" who="S0327">okay <unclear/></u>
<u n="689" who="S0326">maybe you <trunc>un</trunc> <unclear/> I don't understand this <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="690" who="S0327">oh god <unclear/> just put it</u>
<u n="691" who="S0326"><unclear>maybe</unclear> click here double click <unclear>no</unclear></u>
<u n="692" who="S0327">well what? er it honestly <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it drives me barmy oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="693" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="694" who="S0327">erm so I'm but if I want to move the whole thing</u>
<u n="695" who="S0326">the whole thing</u>
<u n="696" who="S0327">apple <unclear>all</unclear> why isn't it?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0326">where do you wanna move it to?</u>
<u n="698" who="S0327">to the left here so <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="699" who="S0326">oh that's not to do with that that's just to do it like this erm although your computer's quite slow it's stuck on that erm if you just</u>
<u n="700" who="S0327">okay well I don't want to <trunc>p</trunc> fiddle with it if it's if there's er any problem it's just so that I can then see the two side by <trunc>se</trunc> side if you see what I mean?</u>
<u n="701" who="S0326">yeah that's what I'm doing but I dunno why it er keeps doing this black thing</u>
<u n="702" who="S0327">no nor do I <pause dur="short"/> oh I hate computers</u>
<u n="703" who="S0326">these are in the way but if you <trunc>ho</trunc> see those two arrows?</u>
<u n="704" who="S0327" trans="overlap">there there are two of them look there's there it is underneath</u>
<u n="705" who="S0326">er</u>
<u n="706" who="S0327">well let's get rid of that that okay we've got that goes there and then that goes there so I I want to sort of match them up in terms of size yes I can do that so if I want to change <vocal desc="cough"/> <unclear/> I want to change <pause dur="short"/> ah that's not coming up now now why can't I change that?</u>
<u n="707" who="S0326">erm mm what? click on it where do you wanna you wanna move it?</u>
<u n="708" who="S0327">yes can't</u>
<u n="709" who="S0326">it must be in er the</u>
<u n="710" who="S0327">I think I'd better leave that one then I daren't</u>
<u n="711" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="712" who="S0327">I daren't it's er you know save changes don't save I'll just er work on this <unclear/></u>
<u n="713" who="S0326">yeah I think that one might be the file is is not in edit mode</u>
<u n="714" who="S0327" trans="overlap"><trunc>d</trunc> is not not <trunc>ed</trunc> but it says editable PDF I'll I'll I'll sort that at some point I have noticed every time somebody else does something of course then something goes wrong and then erm so I'll leave that at the moment</u>
<u n="715" who="S0326">okay</u>
<u n="716" who="S0327">alright <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thank you very much erm let's have a look at the diary now for these various things erm <pause dur="short"/> so tomorrow we meet or we don't meet er so tomorrow is out and then Friday Saturday morning is there a chance of you coming Sunday?</u>
<u n="717" who="S0326">I <unclear>can</unclear> do Sunday</u>
<u n="718" who="S0327">okay it doesn't have to be too terribly early I mean say ten o'clock?</u>
<u n="719" who="S0326">yeah ten o'clock</u>
<u n="720" who="S0327">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that'll be really wonderful I <trunc>th</trunc> you see what I want is for the remember those big boards?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0327">I might be able to do two at a time but there are three that I want to do so maybe I might <trunc>als</trunc>also ask you to come maybe on the Tuesday as well</u>
<u n="723" who="S0326">yeah I can do the Tuesday I can't do the Monday</u>
<u n="724" who="S0327">okay <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> let's say ten o'clock okay that's absolutely great for those two days</u>
<u n="725" who="S0326" trans="overlap">so er Sunday Sunday and Tuesday</u>
<u n="726" who="S0327">Sunday <pause dur="short"/> that's absolutely brilliant and I mean there's only that amount of work if you fancy doing some other work I can probably find something I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> left his erm if you feel like doing some physical work there's er the cleaning the terrace at the back if you fancy doing that?</u>
<u n="727" who="S0326">yeah I don't mind those</u>
<u n="728" who="S0327">alright be good for you to do some physical work what do you do physical?</u>
<u n="729" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm</u>
<u n="730" who="S0327">any sport?</u>
<u n="731" who="S0326">no I walk around do a lot of walking</u>
<u n="732" who="S0327">cycling?</u>
<u n="733" who="S0326">no it's more effort to <trunc>s</trunc> walk than cycle</u>
<u n="734" who="S0327">well walking's very good but I feel that you should <unclear>somehow</unclear></u>
<u n="735" who="S0326">dancing</u>
<u n="736" who="S0327"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah well that's that's that's</u>
<u n="737" who="S0326" trans="overlap">nightclubbing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="738" who="S0327">that's that's that's moving around isn't it <pause dur="short"/> okay that's absolutely great <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thank you</u>
<u n="739" who="S0326">right I'm just gonna put those in the <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="740" who="S0327">oh well what now what do you think about tomorrow then? will you kindly remember I'm er getting very absent minded</u>
<u n="741" who="S0326">yeah no I will just you er do you have a mobile phone?</u>
<u n="742" who="S0327">I've got your</u>
<u n="743" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I'll I'll send you an email erm</u>
<u n="744" who="S0327">yes but don't er don't ever <trunc>t</trunc> I never use my mobile</u>
<u n="745" who="S0326">yeah okay I</u>
<u n="746" who="S0327">it would have to go here but I mean I've I've said tenish so ideally would be to meet there around ten and then I go we go upstairs or say or</u>
<u n="747" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="748" who="S0327">ten fifteen in the entrance I'll put query</u>
<u n="749" who="S0326">cos I have a feeling there might be something tomorrow but I can't remember</u>
<u n="750" who="S0327">okay well just let me know one way or the other</u>
<u n="751" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="752" who="S0327">erm if you can or you can't and if you can't well then we're coming up to erm I don't how <trunc>l</trunc>how long they otherwise you could think of a Friday and then I can let them know you're coming</u>
<u n="753" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="754" who="S0327">good alright</u>
<u n="755" who="S0326">alright</u>
<u n="756" who="S0327">that's absolutely great do you want a bag for your book?</u>
<u n="757" who="S0326">erm I've got a bag actually</u>
<u n="758" who="S0327">you've got a bag?</u>
<u n="759" who="S0326"><unclear>okay</unclear> thanks very much for lunch</u>
<u n="760" who="S0327">it was a pleasure <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>well</unclear> it's not a problem <unclear/> now I just have to <trunc>f</trunc> drop out of the front if I drop to the right I've got the the Co-op</u>
<u n="761" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="762" who="S0327">if I drop to the left I've got my health centre</u>
<u n="763" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="764" who="S0327">it's so convenient okay well I'll er</u>
<u n="765" who="S0326"><unclear/> need to put this in here</u>
<u n="766" who="S0327">see you on the twenty-first when's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> coming?</u>
<u n="767" who="S0326">I'm not sure when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s back</u>
<u n="768" who="S0327">be nice to see him and catch up</u>
<u n="769" who="S0326">but everyone'll be here for Christmas <unclear/></u>
<u n="770" who="S0327" trans="overlap">I think everybody'll be here on the twenty-first</u>
<u n="771" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="772" who="S0327">and you're going to <anon type="place"/> on Christmas Day?</u>
<u n="773" who="S0326">yeah to <anon type="place"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
