<text id="SECS">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:32:46</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-06</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0439 S0444</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Kitchen - home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Halloween party, relationships, work, future, holiday, new job, friends, interview, the past</topics>
		<activity>Catch-up with friend from Oxford before holiday</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, announcing, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0439">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern - Non-accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0444">
				<exactage>25</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace></birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Oxford, UK</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 10 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Pearson marketing executive</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0439">erm who won sexiest <trunc>pri</trunc>? ah oh it was hilarious actually erm it was a guy called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0439">and he dressed as erm Miss Piggy</u>
<u n="5" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0439">and he is er six foot seven <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0444">awesome</u>
<u n="8" who="S0439">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah he had a wig and the fake boobs</u>
<u n="9" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0439">and the <trunc>dre</trunc> he was really he was really good actually he <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="11" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got voted second</u>
<u n="13" who="S0444">and what did he <unclear>go as</unclear>?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0439">oh it was horrible it was creepy he went as a cow</u>
<u n="15" who="S0444">is that because his girl well his <unclear>ex</unclear> nominated him?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0439">yeah cos we were <unclear/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0439">he was kind of like weirdly avoiding me all night erm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> didn't wanna</u>
<u n="20" who="S0439" trans="overlap">obviously</u>
<u n="21" who="S0444">make <unclear>him</unclear> feel a bit on edge</u>
<u n="22" who="S0439">erm I dunno well <unclear>I just think he was avoiding me</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> he invited you to her thing</u>
<u n="24" who="S0439">well no he didn't invite me</u>
<u n="25" who="S0444">oh she did</u>
<u n="26" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I was about to buy yeah she invited me</u>
<u n="27" who="S0444">well obviously then she can't reject you just because <unclear/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah but erm then we were sitting outside and I was like oh like like in the during the week he was messaging me like all the way up until the party and I was just like well you can't really be <unclear>voted in</unclear> can you? cos you're sleeping your your girlfriend is the one whose party it is and he was like yeah true blah blah blah and then on the night he got she was like now <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's also nominated for sexiest man and I was like <vocal desc="laugh"/> he's not gonna win that <vocal desc="laugh"/> he didn't win that but we were sitting outside and he's like ah didn't you win? I was like no like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was gonna vote in me and he was like yeah good point <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> but yeah and then like the like I I didn't really talk to him that much actually and then me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> left</u>
<u n="29" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0439">and literally the moment I left <pause dur="short"/> he turned round he messaged <unclear/> on Whatsapp and was like oh why are you leaving? you're leaving really quickly like why didn't you say goodbye to me? and I was like why would I say goodbye to you? you were clearly ignoring me</u>
<u n="31" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0439">all</u>
<u n="33" who="S0444" trans="overlap">all night</u>
<u n="34" who="S0439">evening like <pause dur="short"/> and he's just like oh but you looked really hot I like spent the whole evening looking at you like I really want to do inappropriate things to you I was like what? like you know that's creepy you absolute creep</u>
<u n="35" who="S0444">that is a bit creepy</u>
<u n="36" who="S0439">I was like I've proved my point I was hotter than the girl you're sleeping with high five me I had a better looking man on my arm high five me and boom you broke up <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>high five you for laughing</unclear></u>
<u n="38" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I know I was like I feel mean</u>
<u n="40" who="S0444">I bet at that point I was like I've I've I've lost I've lost the point of why you were saying lol</u>
<u n="41" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/> the whole thing</u>
<u n="42" who="S0444" trans="overlap">also there is a place near here on the map called <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0439">oh is there? I bet er I wonder if that's full of</u>
<u n="44" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> called <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0439">I wonder if that's full of lolz</u>
<u n="46" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0439">but how are you? how is life with you?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0444">yeah it's alright it's just been really like overwhelming and non stop at the moment</u>
<u n="49" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0444">so they've changed my job so I'm looking after</u>
<u n="51" who="S0439" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="52" who="S0444">history and geography now</u>
<u n="53" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0444">but that's because they want my strategic brain on things</u>
<u n="55" who="S0439">you do have a good strategic brain</u>
<u n="56" who="S0444" trans="overlap">to say that that's kind of what they'll use to get me promoted next year</u>
<u n="57" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0444">cos obviously I had to tell them about the interview because there was a travel ban</u>
<u n="59" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="60" who="S0444">and me having to say I need to be in <anon type="place"/> for a <trunc>me</trunc>meeting they were like why can you not do it over Hangout on the phone? and being really like wow</u>
<u n="61" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh so you cos obviously for any other job you would've had to pay yourself but <pause dur="short"/> so how come you were allowed to get them to pay for this one?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0444">because I was down in <anon type="place"/> for training two days later</u>
<u n="63" who="S0439">ah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0444">so I stayed and to be honest I was doing work</u>
<u n="65" who="S0439"><unclear/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0444">for meetings like</u>
<u n="67" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0444">and in the end it turns out that you know regardless of whether I get the job or not I'm still working in geography I'm working on the <unclear/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0444">I'll work with whoever gets the job so actually all the stuff that I've done is research</u>
<u n="71" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0444">so and then I did say to them I you know do you want me to take the time off? I think I need to take half a day a day or whatever I don't mind</u>
<u n="73" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah they shouldn't though should they?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0444">but they didn't say anything about it but like they were <unclear/> it was like it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos it's all on</u>
<u n="75" who="S0439">oh yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0444">so it was the person who's kind of not my manager but the manager above that</u>
<u n="77" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0444"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm which which is alright but <pause dur="short"/> but she was only she's only in an interim role cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is now going secondary</u>
<u n="79" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0444">it's all going down</u>
<u n="81" who="S0439">all going down <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0444">erm it's all going down but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I told her straight <unclear>up</unclear> when she got the job I just you know even she's not even in post yet and I I was just chatting to her and then she was saying that she wants to shake things up <unclear>in</unclear> product management I was like well that's quite interesting cos the product management jobs they've been talking about are quite marketingy strategy so <unclear/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0444">cos that's what they told me but it's like seeing er it's it's seeing the strategy and the campaign through</u>
<u n="85" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0444">and it's not the <trunc>typ</trunc> it's not the typical <unclear/> development job</u>
<u n="87" who="S0439">ah okay</u>
<u n="88" who="S0444">so it's kind of like well that <unclear>could feed</unclear> a bit more strongly to my strengths doesn't it?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0439">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> that experience so far and I have got a service manager which is <unclear/> what <unclear/> they kind of you know they gave that as it gave the CV a bit of a boost saying look I have done something with management <unclear/> before</u>
<u n="91" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah course yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0444">so yeah but I talked to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and and said you know she's quite interesting and then she was like yeah you're good at marketing but you'd be great at product</u>
<u n="93" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0444">I remember thinking that when you you know when you <unclear/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I think loads of people have said that about you <unclear>apparently that you'd be really good</unclear></u>
<u n="96" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah quite a lot well everybody like obviously I wasn't shouting it from the rooftops</u>
<u n="97" who="S0439">no but</u>
<u n="98" who="S0444">but it was the kind of thing like everybody</u>
<u n="99" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear>it's also</unclear> <unclear/> wanted to do wasn't it?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0444">yeah but everybody's been positive</u>
<u n="101" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0444">about it and got <unclear>crushed</unclear> basically by <unclear/> team</u>
<u n="103" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/> didn't you?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0444">yeah but my science <trunc>tea</trunc> the science team that I used to work with the product managers were like you and one of the girls who's already a product manager you are my tips for being future stars and we don't say that lightly</u>
<u n="105" who="S0439">ah that's good</u>
<u n="106" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and and she was the one pushing me to be like she was basically like <unclear/> like have you applied? have you applied? have you applied?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0444">so originally the jobs were only BTEC roles so I was a bit <unclear><trunc>edg</trunc></unclear> I was I didn't really want to apply for them</u>
<u n="109" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0444">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0439"><unclear>oh yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="112" who="S0444">he was the one hiring for them so I got in touch with him to say that this is the <unclear/> I think this one needs subject expertise and he was like yeah usually I go for someone who's been in colleges or whatever and I was like <unclear>yeah well</unclear></u>
<u n="113" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0444">he was like but you know I'm a great admirer of the work that you do <unclear>and like</unclear> some of those skills might make you successful in product management let's get some time to talk about it so I'm meeting with him</u>
<u n="115" who="S0439">oh that's cool</u>
<u n="116" who="S0444">erm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0439">cos that's all you can do is just make connections and meet these people isn't it?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0444">yeah exactly cos he already knows me from working on the science <unclear/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0444">but do you know what? actually I'm more than a marketer like</u>
<u n="121" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0444">it's the stuff that I've <unclear>built up</unclear> before so like it's the editorial stuff it's the you know this is what the grad training programme <unclear/> for like</u>
<u n="123" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear>I was I was</unclear> literally that was on the tip of my tongue I was gonna say that's what we were designed for</u>
<u n="124" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0439">we were designed to be into like develop our skillset and make er have a really broad skillset</u>
<u n="126" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> but if you look at how many people from the training programme have gone into product management</u>
<u n="127" who="S0439">yeah agreed</u>
<u n="128" who="S0444">there you go so you know the interview was a rough one</u>
<u n="129" who="S0439">was it? what did you have to do?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> it was an hour and a half</u>
<u n="131" who="S0439">er</u>
<u n="132" who="S0444">I had to do I had to write a paper <unclear/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0439" trans="overlap">do you want a drink by the way?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0444">what have you got?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0439">erm I've got some cans in the back I've got like Coke but I think it's a bit flat I've got tea coffee</u>
<u n="136" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I can deal with flat Coke flat Coke <unclear/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0439" trans="overlap">flat Coke?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0444">yeah erm I had to do a proposal</u>
<u n="139" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0444">one how I would support customers effectively throughout the lifecycle of the qualifications</u>
<u n="141" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0444">it was it was GCSE and A level geography <pause dur="short"/> and then the next bit was how they're grown er the market share</u>
<u n="143" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="144" who="S0444">so it's stuff that I kind of knew</u>
<u n="145" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0444">so I came out with <vocal desc="laugh"/> quite a detailed report but like the like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who the one that pushed me into product management jobs from the science team</u>
<u n="147" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0444">she checked it twice until it was you know she thought yep it's pretty good now</u>
<u n="149" who="S0439">yep</u>
<u n="150" who="S0444">which is a compliment from her so</u>
<u n="151" who="S0439">yeah and it's always good I think when you're applying for a job within a company people always try and help you</u>
<u n="152" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="153" who="S0439">and they're really <trunc>suppor</trunc> I think a lot of them are quite supportive of it</u>
<u n="154" who="S0444">like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sat sat down with me <unclear/> cos basically I had</u>
<u n="155" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0444">I'd gone out at the weekend</u>
<u n="157" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0444">with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and his friends</u>
<u n="159" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0444">we'd got absolutely plastered cos it was a bottomless brunch</u>
<u n="161" who="S0439">oh no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0444">ended up falling over really badly</u>
<u n="163" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh shit</u>
<u n="164" who="S0444">getting concussion</u>
<u n="165" who="S0439">shit oh my god</u>
<u n="166" who="S0444">and like we didn't know this at the time</u>
<u n="167" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0444">cos everybody just thought I was drunk and I was like no no this is more than just</u>
<u n="169" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0444">you know a prosecco or whatever that I might have to go to my uncle and auntie's they thought I'd completely lost it</u>
<u n="171" who="S0439">oh no</u>
<u n="172" who="S0444">cos they they just thought I was drunk <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0444">erm and er ever since that I had a massive headache</u>
<u n="175" who="S0439">shit</u>
<u n="176" who="S0444">and I couldn't see properly</u>
<u n="177" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0444">like I was seeing things a bit I thought oh you know the next day it's like ah I'm probably just hungover but okay</u>
<u n="179" who="S0439">mm yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was really good at looking after me he was like we can get you know you can</u>
<u n="181" who="S0439">go to the hospital</u>
<u n="182" who="S0444">we can go to hospital if you want and I was like oh no it should be fine cos you know I'm a bit of a drama queen when it comes to overanalysing things so it might just <unclear/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear>we all a bit drama queen every now and again</unclear></u>
<u n="184" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's just a headache you know it's just a hangover</u>
<u n="185" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0444">because you know everybody says they get worse as you get older kind of thing</u>
<u n="187" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0444">erm you know so I'm just like maybe that's what it is</u>
<u n="189" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0444">and erm but it kept getting worse and worse and paracetamol wasn't taking it away at all</u>
<u n="191" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0444">and I'd been taking it for a couple of <unclear>days</unclear> I went to the <anon type="place"/> at what point should I stop taking the paracetamol? who do I go to? there's no walk in centre</u>
<u n="193" who="S0439">really? not in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0444">in <anon type="place"/> mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0439">that's shit</u>
<u n="196" who="S0444" trans="overlap">or in <anon type="place"/> the only things that they've got are minor injury units which can't deal with head injuries or anything like that</u>
<u n="197" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0444">so I went to the <anon type="place"/> what do I do? cos obviously I'm not gonna turn up to A and E because I'm not it's not like blood's spurting out of my ear or anything</u>
<u n="199" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0444">erm but it was like I kept seeing like <trunc>wa</trunc> you know when you've got like an ocular migraine</u>
<u n="201" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah you can yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0444" trans="overlap">like wavy lines and dots and stuff but it was like everything's kind of fuzzy and my eye movements just felt a lot slower</u>
<u n="203" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="204" who="S0444">so it was just a bit like I'm not entirely comfortable with this</u>
<u n="205" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and even when you like you were like that even moving your eyes hurt yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it hurt like honestly like I got it to like here and it would just hurt</u>
<u n="207" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0444">cos then what I'd done is I'd hit my neck</u>
<u n="209" who="S0439"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0444">and then I'd they said that even though it was like a small bruise they could tell from where it was on my neck that I'd fallen really badly</u>
<u n="211" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0444">erm which I had done I'd fallen down like steps I'd fallen to the side of</u>
<u n="213" who="S0439"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0444">it was just gross</u>
<u n="215" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="216" who="S0444">erm luckily <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0439">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0444">it <trunc>wa</trunc> cos I've had concussion before but that was when I was a lot younger I kind of blacked out I didn't black out but I swear I must've blacked out at some point <unclear/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah but lots of rugby players get concussion from like playing</u>
<u n="220" who="S0444" trans="overlap">like <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0439">but they carry on and <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0444" trans="overlap">exactly and I think that's what that's kind of what it was but none of us could remember if I'd hit my head or not erm <pause dur="short"/> but obviously I did</u>
<u n="223" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0444">or at least part of my face or something so by the time that it got they said right if paracetamol and ibuprofen together don't work go to the doctor so I did and they're like yeah it's concussion you know it's it's you know it's still early days but if it's still there like</u>
<u n="225" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0444">you know I just I just kept getting the <unclear/> and obviously staring at the screen's not gonna help either</u>
<u n="227" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no not at all</u>
<u n="228" who="S0444">but until that point nobody knew that it was concussion or anything so I'd just been completely dazed for like half the time</u>
<u n="229" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0444"><unclear/> people just <unclear>thought I was completely out of it</unclear> I was like I'm really sorry I can't actually form words but the problem is that</u>
<u n="231" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0444">a lot of the things that concussion related are also chronic fatigue syndrome related</u>
<u n="233" who="S0439">oh okay</u>
<u n="234" who="S0444">like the sensitivity to lights the not being able to form words and I was like but this is different</u>
<u n="235" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0444">but I can't like tell erm so when it got round to applying for the <unclear/> jobs</u>
<u n="237" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0444">I was like</u>
<u n="239" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you weren't really with it yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0444">I'm concussed I can't erm so I didn't end up applying for them anyway</u>
<u n="241" who="S0439">that's a shame</u>
<u n="242" who="S0444">but they ended up being stopped anyway cos of the recruitment freeze so</u>
<u n="243" who="S0439" trans="overlap">ah there's still there's still a recruitment freeze? <unclear/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0444">no they just started it again</u>
<u n="245" who="S0439">ah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0444">erm</u>
<u n="247" who="S0439">oh sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0444">no that's fine erm <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was really nice she was like if the job reopens then we'll definitely have a chat but let's have a chat anyway like <unclear/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah what? like?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0444">erm so then this</u>
<u n="251" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear>all you'd want is</unclear> more advice and help isn't it?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah and then this job came up in geography which is maternity cover</u>
<u n="253" who="S0439">I'll leave that the chicken in for a little bit longer</u>
<u n="254" who="S0444">yeah and they'd basically reopened the job cos I don't think they got enough candidates or they didn't like the look of the candidates that they had</u>
<u n="255" who="S0439">oh that's cool</u>
<u n="256" who="S0444">so I talked to the highway manager who is kind of I've got my product manager and then I've got her manager</u>
<u n="257" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0444">so they obviously see the work that I've done and things like that and they they know who I am they've worked with me</u>
<u n="259" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0444">I've talked to them quite often we've been to like negotiations and stuff like that together so it's like oh okay so I kind of talked to her to say you know basically is this a bit of a joke me applying?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0444">and she went <unclear>no you</unclear></u>
<u n="263" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you don't wanna apply for a job if you're if you genuinely think you can't get it</u>
<u n="264" who="S0444">yeah exactly erm so you know she was like they're <pause dur="short"/> you should go for it like I don't see any reason why you wouldn't get an interview</u>
<u n="265" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="266" who="S0444">this was on the Friday the deadline for the job was on the Monday so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was <unclear/> I was like what do I do? like you know cos I'd already looked through the job spec</u>
<u n="267" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0444">like going through I was like I actually think you know I can</u>
<u n="269" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0444"><unclear/> <unclear>for</unclear> this</u>
<u n="271" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0444">erm <pause dur="short"/> so yeah so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> bless him looked through my cover letter and CV and then <pause dur="short"/> I was kind of just putting thoughts down erm together but then I was on holiday with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> cos we were taking a long weekend so</u>
<u n="273" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0444">it was like oh god erm so then by the time that I got it in it was like midnight on Monday obviously</u>
<u n="275" who="S0439">obvs</u>
<u n="276" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well you know at least at least you made the deadline</u>
<u n="278" who="S0444">yeah but the only thing is was that <unclear/> wanted to keep reverting back to my graduate trainee CV</u>
<u n="279" who="S0439" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0444">I was like that's not</u>
<u n="281" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I hate it when that happens</u>
<u n="282" who="S0444" trans="overlap">that's like that is not helpful</u>
<u n="283" who="S0439">yeah I hate it when that happens</u>
<u n="284" who="S0444" trans="overlap">erm and er but basically I got a call to interview within less than twenty-four hours</u>
<u n="285" who="S0439">that's that's sexy</u>
<u n="286" who="S0444"><unclear>well</unclear> <unclear/> looking out for it probably</u>
<u n="287" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0444">so</u>
<u n="289" who="S0439">looking out for your</u>
<u n="290" who="S0444">erm <pause dur="short"/> so yeah but it was alright but I think I just got a bit I kind of researched too much that er my brain was just full it was just like a verbal dump</u>
<u n="291" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0444">of my brain</u>
<u n="293" who="S0439"><unclear/> everything you know</u>
<u n="294" who="S0444">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> bearing in mind that erm I can't remember even if I told you this bearing in mind that you know that one of their questions I did turn round and answer when they said why do you think you're the right person for this job? the last question in the interview I waffled on for a bit and then basically said because there's no one quite like me</u>
<u n="295" who="S0439">ah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0439">no that's good though</u>
<u n="298" who="S0444" trans="overlap">they laughed but it's true nobody else is gonna have editorial marketing and service management experience unless they're me</u>
<u n="299" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I mean that's true I think you should like I don't think there's anything wrong with saying that I think you should be like yeah boom I'm awesome I have all these skills</u>
<u n="300" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0439">hire me</u>
<u n="302" who="S0444">so we'll just see what they say like to be honest the people were so <trunc>lovel</trunc> like obviously I work with one of the people <trunc>s</trunc> day to day <pause dur="short"/> she'll give me feedback the other person I'd never met before</u>
<u n="303" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0444">but she was lovely I was like jeez is she really liking my interview or is she just that enthusiastic and everybody went yeah she's just that enthusiastic</u>
<u n="305" who="S0439" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0444">I was like that's good but it's <unclear/> that she wasn't like scowling at me cos that <unclear/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I know that puts you off when you're in an interview with someone who's a bit like comes across as like grumpy isn't it? cos you can never read them</u>
<u n="308" who="S0444">mm mm so mm <pause dur="short"/> we'll see but that was pretty much that it was like I haven't done any research I hadn't done anything that's why I hadn't even thought of <unclear/> or even looking at stuff</u>
<u n="309" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="310" who="S0444">before that was <unclear/> cos I was like I can only deal with one thing at a time</u>
<u n="311" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh no <unclear>hon don't worry</unclear></u>
<u n="312" who="S0444">in order to survive</u>
<u n="313" who="S0439">a job is far more important than a <trunc>hol</trunc> like all we're gonna do</u>
<u n="314" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0439">is literally turn up at Gatwick and see what happens</u>
<u n="316" who="S0444">oh yeah but it was just that kind of thing where I was like if this were normal I'd've been a bit more organised and actually figured out how to get to Gatwick</u>
<u n="317" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="318" who="S0444">or how it was gonna work or you know stuff like that I was just a bit like it's not that I'm not looking forward to the holiday</u>
<u n="319" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0444">I've just got a lot to get through first which I'm sure you did too</u>
<u n="321" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="322" who="S0444">erm so yeah I was just a bit like oh say <unclear/> oh <unclear/> for good <unclear/> are so good</u>
<u n="323" who="S0439">well you sound very manic</u>
<u n="324" who="S0444">well yeah but <pause dur="long"/> I survived and you know this holiday will be fun it will be mental space and it will be fun</u>
<u n="325" who="S0439">it'll just be <unclear/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0444" trans="overlap">there's no pressure it's</u>
<u n="327" who="S0439" trans="overlap">there's no pressure to do anything we can just wander round eat if we get cold we can go <pause dur="short"/> you know to the cinema or we can go up to the hotel and chill we can go for <trunc>dr</trunc> like but there's no pressure because er</u>
<u n="328" who="S0444" trans="overlap">we're in a business suite by the way</u>
<u n="329" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0444">when I was looking at it <unclear>and thinking I was like</unclear> oh hello</u>
<u n="331" who="S0439">I know</u>
<u n="332" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and because also like it's unlike it's not like Berlin where there's so much history and stuff to see like</u>
<u n="334" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="335" who="S0439">with this we don't have to rush around</u>
<u n="336" who="S0444">it kind of looks like the same stuff they keep saying</u>
<u n="337" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0444">er one screen shot <unclear/> my phone earlier which is why my battery's dead erm <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> so yeah but I'll look through this stuff but basically palaces castles</u>
<u n="339" who="S0439" trans="overlap">palaces castles and some statues</u>
<u n="340" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> statues cafés done</u>
<u n="341" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0444">oh and some nice parks and the river <anon type="place"/> there you go <pause dur="short"/> I also love the fact that we're going to <anon type="place"/> first</u>
<u n="343" who="S0439">I know</u>
<u n="344" who="S0444">kind of just making my life I'm just like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I'm kind of excited about <anon type="place"/> as well</u>
<u n="346" who="S0444">like <pause dur="short"/> so we're going to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> via <anon type="place"/> without a guidebook</u>
<u n="347" who="S0439">yep <pause dur="short"/> but with a <trunc>p</trunc> with a private transport from the airport to the hotel</u>
<u n="348" who="S0444">but when I put in that reservation number it only showed me the pick up time for the way back</u>
<u n="349" who="S0439">well <unclear/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> the way there but we'll <unclear>find out</unclear></u>
<u n="351" who="S0439">I'll check my email it should be we should have one there</u>
<u n="352" who="S0444">we do I checked the email cos I was gonna this was after I rung you and I <trunc>r</trunc>rang you rang god</u>
<u n="353" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="354" who="S0444">just after I rang you and erm I was kind of just checking it's the kind of seat where okay we've only <trunc>g</trunc> we it's only hand luggage</u>
<u n="355" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0444">it's only one piece of hand luggage it was just really basic stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="357" who="S0439">oh that's okay</u>
<u n="358" who="S0444">and I checked the reservation number it was like it was only showing the way back but in the email it does say we're gonna pick you up from this</u>
<u n="359" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0444">when you go to <anon type="place"/> you need to go to this bit and this kind of thing <unclear/> well obviously we're gonna have one <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0439">we'll be fine we're big and ugly enough to look after ourselves</u>
<u n="362" who="S0444">beautiful enough</u>
<u n="363" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I know <unclear/> people just said to me like why why are you going to <anon type="place"/>? I'm like dunno</u>
<u n="364" who="S0444">it's the kind of thing we do <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was it was cheap never been there before why not? and they were like oh okay</u>
<u n="366" who="S0444">apparently it's the cheapest stag do destination</u>
<u n="367" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I did <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> that's what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to me like are you are you going on a stag do? I'm like no why?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="369" who="S0439"><unclear/> well that's where stags go I'm like well we're not going on a stag</u>
<u n="370" who="S0444" trans="overlap">apparently that's where Eurotrip was filmed as well I'm like oh great</u>
<u n="371" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well we're cool enough well hey we're <pause dur="short"/> we're going okay</u>
<u n="372" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0444">and it's got all the communist era stuff that we kind of like as well</u>
<u n="375" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we're we're on it</u>
<u n="376" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="377" who="S0439">and even if it's a bit rubbish <unclear/></u>
<u n="378" who="S0444">it will not be rubbish</u>
<u n="379" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah even if</u>
<u n="380" who="S0444">it won't be rubbish <unclear/></u>
<u n="381" who="S0439">yeah even if it is a bit like people <trunc>wait</trunc> place you wouldn't go for like a whole week we're only going for three days and I would love to see it you know I have <unclear>no problems going anywhere</unclear></u>
<u n="382" who="S0444" trans="overlap">hey it's the only capital that borders three countries</u>
<u n="383" who="S0439">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0444">and we get a <anon type="place"/> road trip</u>
<u n="385" who="S0439">I know tell me about it</u>
<u n="386" who="S0444">and it's but this time we can go oh you wouldn't get this on EasyJet</u>
<u n="387" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0444">oh my gosh we're flying British Airways we're gonna get a drink</u>
<u n="389" who="S0439">we're not flying British Airways are we? are we?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0444">oh I thought we were</u>
<u n="391" who="S0439">oh love it no no we're flying EasyJet both ways</u>
<u n="392" who="S0444">oh bollocks</u>
<u n="393" who="S0439">you wouldn't get this on Ryanair</u>
<u n="394" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you definitely wouldn't get that on British Airways</u>
<u n="395" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="396" who="S0439">no we're flying with EasyJet both ways I've got boarding passes printed them today</u>
<u n="397" who="S0444">mm <pause dur="short"/> maybe it's maybe I'm just going bonkers <unclear/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="399" who="S0444">I just wanted my vodka and Coke at ten in the morning <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0439">with Naples we're flying <unclear/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0444">there was one of them that <trunc>w</trunc> am I going bonkers?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0439">I dunno I do love though that erm people are like oh yeah we're going to <anon type="place"/> and then <unclear/> <unclear>all three of us</unclear> are going to Bratislava and I'm like what? I'm like for ninety-nine pounds</u>
<u n="403" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0439">all inclusive pretty much and they're like what? <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like yep <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="405" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="406" who="S0439"><unclear>and I feel like</unclear> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0444">but how do you afford it on your salary?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0444">and I'm like not being funny but I have a brilliant friend who finds <vocal desc="laugh"/> really cheap deals <pause dur="short"/> like it's not just that they're cheap they're actually like quite high quality as well</u>
<u n="410" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0444">and like</u>
<u n="412" who="S0439">like <pause dur="short"/> like yeah business class suite you know like private transport fuck it love it</u>
<u n="413" who="S0444">why not?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="415" who="S0444">erm <pause dur="short"/> they do have a classical music festival going on</u>
<u n="416" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="417" who="S0444">but I couldn't actually <unclear/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> we might stumble across it</u>
<u n="419" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="420" who="S0439">yeah no Secret Escapes is genuinely like one of my favourite favourite sites now</u>
<u n="421" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> but everybody looked really dubious when I said yeah so we're flying to <anon type="place"/> then we're getting like an airport transfer and they were like right and I was like yeah but it's through a reputable site</u>
<u n="422" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0439">that's the thing though it is like I trust Secret Escapes</u>
<u n="424" who="S0444">yeah especially like with Berlin like</u>
<u n="425" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="426" who="S0444">the first time we did it we <unclear>were just</unclear> a bit like what? what?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0439">it works so well <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0444">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying to me that when he looked on the on the British Airways website</u>
<u n="429" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="430" who="S0444">and they were kind of advertising cheap Christmas market type deals he said they did have one but the cheapest one was Prague for about a hundred and thirty and I was like yeah we were oh a hundred and seventy I was like yeah but we went to Berlin for a hundred and thirty</u>
<u n="431" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0444">obviously like I was like yeah yeah well</u>
<u n="433" who="S0439">we went to <anon type="place"/> you know home of German markets</u>
<u n="434" who="S0444">hello but erm</u>
<u n="435" who="S0439">I do love a good Christmas market are you going anywhere before Christmas apart from with me?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0444">we were thinking of going to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="438" who="S0444">but the problem is is that I'm not sure about <pause dur="short"/> time <unclear>or</unclear> money</u>
<u n="439" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> to find a place</u>
<u n="441" who="S0439">oh yeah of course like deposits I hate deposits</u>
<u n="442" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and then I'm just a bit I'm just a bit worried <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously we've got <anon type="place"/> then we've got two weeks in the middle</u>
<u n="443" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="444" who="S0444">then it's <anon type="place"/> and then it's kind of <pause dur="short"/> that</u>
<u n="445" who="S0439" trans="overlap">Christmas</u>
<u n="446" who="S0444">and it's just that kind of thing I can't be saying to work that I'm knackered and exhausted</u>
<u n="447" who="S0439" trans="overlap">if you keep going away</u>
<u n="448" who="S0444">if it's <anon type="place"/> one week <anon type="place"/> the next</u>
<u n="449" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0444"><anon type="place"/> the one after that and then <anon type="place"/> and I was just like I need them then I've gotta be careful cos I have pushed it so hard for the past two weeks</u>
<u n="451" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="452" who="S0444">that I've just gotta be like do you know what?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0439">time for a little chill</u>
<u n="454" who="S0444">done now</u>
<u n="455" who="S0439">and <unclear/> it's not like <pause dur="short"/> you know when January rolls around again it's not like you can't go somewhere else</u>
<u n="456" who="S0444">exactly so <pause dur="short"/> because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wanted to go to <anon type="place"/> and I was like</u>
<u n="457" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0444">that's great but I just can't like</u>
<u n="459" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="460" who="S0444">I physically was just like I just physically cannot</u>
<u n="461" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0444">do another like holiday because you know not one like <anon type="place"/> where you wanna go round and you wanna <unclear/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <anon type="place"/> was I would like if I was in <anon type="place"/> I'd spend I'd want to see everything</u>
<u n="464" who="S0444">mm so yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm but erm <pause dur="long"/> potentially might go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0439">oh for Christmas?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0444">if that <pause dur="short"/> if the flights are kind of looking possible but I</u>
<u n="467" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="468" who="S0444">I dunno to be honest I'm hope I need to know where I'm living what I'm doing <unclear/></u>
<u n="469" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="470" who="S0444">or where I'm gonna be by that point so yeah so basically I kind of said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos I had to tell them about this interview <pause dur="short"/> erm she was like oh well you should've told us first I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> there was actually no time to tell you</u>
<u n="471" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0444">cos there was no turnaround basically erm because I was on holiday on the day that I'd applied for the job and I wasn't gonna</u>
<u n="473" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="474" who="S0444">I wasn't gonna say it <unclear/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="476" who="S0444">and erm</u>
<u n="477" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/> they don't actually have the right to know though</u>
<u n="478" who="S0444">they don't</u>
<u n="479" who="S0439">you don't have to tell them</u>
<u n="480" who="S0444">no erm like if it went to second interview I'd tell them</u>
<u n="481" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="482" who="S0444">but and she was like er and she was like well you know why are you? you know and I was like well it's always in our <unclear/> it it was originally the way that I wanted to go was into commissioning</u>
<u n="483" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="484" who="S0444">and publishing but then I enjoyed marketing so much</u>
<u n="485" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0444">I went into that and I'm now at the crossroads where I either really dedicate <unclear>myself</unclear> to marketing and take the CIM diploma and what have you or I start exploring product management and see whether that's</u>
<u n="487" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and give it a go</u>
<u n="488" who="S0444"><unclear/> the way to go <pause dur="short"/> and when I explained that I was at a crossroads they seemed she seemed a bit better about it cos she was like oh yeah well I'm at a crossroads too I can really <trunc>empathi</trunc>empathise with that and then it's like mm but you've gotta do what's best for you and I was like well to be honest there aren't any opportunities for progression in marketing</u>
<u n="489" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="490" who="S0444">the opportunities they did have for people like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have been cut because of the recruitment freeze so</u>
<u n="491" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="492" who="S0444">and she was like yeah yeah but I don't want you to think that there aren't opportunities <unclear/> there aren't and she was like that's what we wanted to talk to you about we wanted to talk to you about <unclear>geography and whether you can</unclear></u>
<u n="493" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0444">take it on and it was like yeah okay but now it's like double the work <unclear/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="496" who="S0444">erm and erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah and then it was like well you know all this kind of stuff and it was just like you've gotta</u>
<u n="497" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you can say what I want to hear but</u>
<u n="498" who="S0444" trans="overlap">you've gotta do what's best for you and er and that's what that's what's gonna help you with your promotion next year and I was like yeah well we'll see but</u>
<u n="499" who="S0439">empty promises isn't it?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0444">mm but <pause dur="short"/> because there are so many people taking maternity leave in product management coming up there are gonna be more roles <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="501" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> is anybody else leaving?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0444">not at the moment</u>
<u n="503" who="S0439">that's good</u>
<u n="504" who="S0444"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has got a new job in international</u>
<u n="505" who="S0439">ah cool</u>
<u n="506" who="S0444">cos he wasn't liking them on the train</u>
<u n="507" who="S0439">mm <pause dur="long"/> so what's he doing in international now?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0444">he's not started yet but he's just gonna be a a product management associate and in the traditional sense of the word</u>
<u n="509" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's good</u>
<u n="510" who="S0444"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does say hi</u>
<u n="511" who="S0439">cool</u>
<u n="512" who="S0444">and erm she was like tell <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hi I was like I will do she is even more bonkers than usual and has now joined the university dancesport team don't ask three nights a week of er</u>
<u n="513" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="514" who="S0444">of training <pause dur="short"/> not even going there</u>
<u n="515" who="S0439">wow</u>
<u n="516" who="S0444">erm but yeah hopefully that might force her to leave work at a reasonable hour</u>
<u n="517" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="518" who="S0444">rather than doing two hours of overtime every day</u>
<u n="519" who="S0439">why was she doing that?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0444">just so much to do</u>
<u n="521" who="S0439">god</u>
<u n="522" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I love my job</u>
<u n="524" who="S0444">how about you? so your new job</u>
<u n="525" who="S0439">my new job er</u>
<u n="526" who="S0444" trans="overlap">when does that happen? it hasn't started</u>
<u n="527" who="S0439">start on the sixteenth</u>
<u n="528" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0439">yeah starts on the sixteenth of November it's all happened so quickly we've had a massive</u>
<u n="530" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="531" who="S0439"><trunc>s</trunc> restructure</u>
<u n="532" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="533" who="S0439">erm <pause dur="short"/> and it's literally been a three week turnaround like they announced the restructure we restructured</u>
<u n="534" who="S0444">that's really good</u>
<u n="535" who="S0439">I know really quick really good only for UK and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="537" who="S0439">which is international</u>
<u n="538" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="539" who="S0439">erm <pause dur="short"/> and basically what they're doing is they're just merging the teams</u>
<u n="540" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="541" who="S0439">which is fine but then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who is head of global</u>
<u n="542" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="543" who="S0439">he needed a project coordinator to work with him</u>
<u n="544" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="545" who="S0439">erm and so basically I kid you not two weeks ago we had a meeting and we were like all the credit coordinators will will er carry on as usual but they're <trunc>basi</trunc>basically what happens at the moment is we have IEB which is the <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/></u>
<u n="546" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="547" who="S0439">and then we have the UK schools team</u>
<u n="548" who="S0444">mm mm</u>
<u n="549" who="S0439">they both kind of work independently of each other despite that we're all under the family of education</u>
<u n="550" who="S0444">mm mm</u>
<u n="551" who="S0439">erm they have their own editors project coordinators whatever you wanna call them and then we do our job we don't do any hands on editing but we organise the development editor the copy editor <anon type="place"/> er <anon type="place"/> which is like an <anon type="place"/> reviews</u>
<u n="552" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="553" who="S0439">we organise all of that we do some hands on content when it comes to the review side but we don't have to do any physical like lots of hands on content and stuff</u>
<u n="554" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0439">all fun now they're merging them they've created two departments they've created the project coordinator department and then the content department so the content department are basically gonna be the original UK team but they <pause dur="short"/> the UK structure was they were a lot more invested in the content so</u>
<u n="556" who="S0444">right</u>
<u n="557" who="S0439">so now what they're gonna do is they're gonna have a project coordinator work with a content specialist</u>
<u n="558" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="559" who="S0439">and the DE</u>
<u n="560" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="561" who="S0439">because we don't really have time to check proofs as much as we should and so they're gonna do more things like that but and they were all there was all spaces for us there were no redundancies made it was really good</u>
<u n="562" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="563" who="S0439">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who is he's really high up in the company he he's completely head of global which works with</u>
<u n="564" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="565" who="S0439">Australia South Africa India and he basically works together on e-distribution and content to make it global</u>
<u n="566" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> your training got you</u>
<u n="567" who="S0439">erm so what I he and he needed a project coordinator and he basically they what they said is one of us is gonna have to go and work for him anyway so this is the job who wants to apply for it? and they opened it up and everybody else was really scared to do it</u>
<u n="568" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="569" who="S0439">they were just like well we don't know what it is cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't really even know what it is at the moment cos his whole team is he kind of works separate</u>
<u n="570" who="S0444" trans="overlap">changing yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0439">but there's other <trunc>str</trunc> like streams of it</u>
<u n="572" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="573" who="S0439">erm and like no one really knows what they're gonna do and he's just like I want you to be really heavily involved in the content at the moment because we're still redoing this restructure I'm not entirely sure what your job's gonna be and everybody was kind of a bit put off by it they were a bit scared and that and he was like well we want you to do project management we want you to work with the programme manager we want you to like maybe go to South Africa we want you to work with e-distribution we want you to <trunc>sch</trunc></u>
<u n="574" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and <unclear/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="576" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0439">and like they we want you to do scheduling and I was just like it just seemed like it aligned to what I was</u>
<u n="578" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0439">good at originally like cos I had my project management qualification and everything</u>
<u n="580" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="581" who="S0439">and after the meeting everyone's like oh I don't know if I should apply and then within five minutes I'd applied</u>
<u n="582" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0439">and he saw my CV and apparently he was really excited by it he was like and I had a meeting with him he's like why why do you do what you do? I was like what do you mean? he's like well your skillset is so much more advanced than what you're doing so why are you why are you a project coordinator? I was like well because the job I kind of applied for wasn't the job I thought I was gonna be doing</u>
<u n="584" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="585" who="S0439">and he was like so you fell into by accident? I was like yes</u>
<u n="586" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yep</u>
<u n="587" who="S0439">he was like <pause dur="short"/> standard</u>
<u n="588" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="589" who="S0439">and so pretty much no one else actually applied for it because they actually realised that I was gonna get it anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0444" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="591" who="S0439">erm like all the managers wanted me to do it all of the like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> my like my <trunc>m</trunc> current manager <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0439">she wanted me she was like I'd put you forward for it anyway like everybody wanted me to do it and so literally last week he was like yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got the role so I'm gonna be now working in e-distribution and global work streams</u>
<u n="594" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="595" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="596" who="S0444">sounds very grand</u>
<u n="597" who="S0439">it's quite exciting</u>
<u n="598" who="S0444">mm <pause dur="short"/> well it's good it's a new challenge it's something new</u>
<u n="599" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna be really different because it's working with things like product families on like <pause dur="short"/> like publishing systems and stuff like that it's a lot more invested in where the products go after creation</u>
<u n="600" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="601" who="S0439">which is something I've never done before I've just created the products I've never actually looked at where they go afterwards and how what I do as a project coordinator impacts upon what happens after <pause dur="short"/> cos having things like erm even really simple things like saying in the blurb of a book oh there's a CD ROM well when it's digital there isn't a CD ROM and yet you actually have customers ringing in being like where's my CD?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0444">mm mm</u>
<u n="603" who="S0439">and it's just like what the fuck?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh it's so true</unclear></u>
<u n="605" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="606" who="S0444">erm</u>
<u n="607" who="S0439">so I officially start on the sixteenth but I've kind of been working with him</u>
<u n="608" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="609" who="S0439">this last week <pause dur="short"/> and the girl who's who's originally was working for him is a complete idiot oh my god she's really weird</u>
<u n="610" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="611" who="S0439">like her last day was today but she was somebody who like talked non stop I had about five maybe not even five conversations with her I know her entire life</u>
<u n="612" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0439">she's been engaged three times she is pregnant with her boyfriend she's four months pregnant with her boyfriend's baby they've been dating for five months</u>
<u n="614" who="S0444">oh</u>
<u n="615" who="S0439">they spend every single weekend together</u>
<u n="616" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh god</u>
<u n="617" who="S0439">and four nights or and two nights during the week</u>
<u n="618" who="S0444">oh jeez</u>
<u n="619" who="S0439">they're inseparable but she's not a <trunc>commi</trunc> she's a complete commitment phobe</u>
<u n="620" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="621" who="S0439">I was like yes okay</u>
<u n="622" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and they're having a kid?</u>
<u n="623" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="624" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="625" who="S0439">and been engaged three times</u>
<u n="626" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="627" who="S0439">erm <pause dur="short"/> I kid you not she talks incessantly</u>
<u n="628" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="629" who="S0439">just yabber yabber yabby and <trunc>sh</trunc> her boyfriend apparently works for the <anon type="place"/> and it's all high security and she has to be vetted and she can't talk about her job his job and yet she can pretty much spent the entire lunchtime talking about oh he's in the <anon type="place"/> and he's a chemist but I can't tell you what he does but he's a chemist and he's in the erm it's like fuck off like</u>
<u n="630" who="S0444">so what's she doing? going to a new job? or just <unclear>not</unclear>?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0439">she can't she can't go to a new job pregnant can she? they won't give her <trunc>t</trunc> maternity leave <unclear>so she</unclear></u>
<u n="632" who="S0444" trans="overlap">that's what I mean</u>
<u n="633" who="S0439">so she's moving to <anon type="place"/> to be with him cos they don't live together</u>
<u n="634" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="635" who="S0439">he lives in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="636" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0439">erm she's moving to <anon type="place"/> <trunc>t</trunc>tomorrow erm</u>
<u n="638" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0439">and she said er and she said yeah well we looked at the finances and it seemed like it would be it would be I'd get just as much money without work as I would would working I was like that doesn't make any sense you've got you've they've bought a house they've now got a mortgage <pause dur="short"/> a baby a mortgage and a relationship after five months</u>
<u n="640" who="S0444">wow</u>
<u n="641" who="S0439">and I was like how does that work? how can you quit a job and go and buy a house?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="643" who="S0439">I was so confused I was just like you know when you're just listening to someone and you're like I don't understand</u>
<u n="644" who="S0444" trans="overlap">how? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="645" who="S0439">like you don't even make logical sense</u>
<u n="646" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="647" who="S0439">but she's officially gone she left today</u>
<u n="648" who="S0444" trans="overlap">let's hope it works out for them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="649" who="S0439">mm <pause dur="short"/> her last day was today it was so funny <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like can you get her a card and some flowers? cos I <trunc>w</trunc> like I was like yeah that's fine erm <pause dur="short"/> and he came over he was like I was like who do you want me to sign the card? he's like I don't know I don't <trunc>kn</trunc> I was like cos I don't know who knows her he's like I don't know who knows her</u>
<u n="650" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="651" who="S0439">because she sits on her own she's really like and no one really she doesn't work with anybody cos</u>
<u n="652" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="653" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's literally just <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and her like there's no other team</u>
<u n="654" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="655" who="S0439">and he was like well we could just make up some <trunc>na</trunc> I was like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we can't make up names to put in her card like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="656" who="S0444"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="657" who="S0439">we can't just randomly sign the card ten times so I had to go round my team and ask them to sign it they're like who's this for? I'm like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do I know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? no <pause dur="short"/> who is she? she's that person over there I've never even seen her before</u>
<u n="658" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="659" who="S0439">just sign the fucking card look there's a space er fill it</u>
<u n="660" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="661" who="S0444">oh <unclear>that's</unclear></u>
<u n="662" who="S0439">but it was good cos the day I got in I got in at half seven</u>
<u n="663" who="S0444">oh god</u>
<u n="664" who="S0439">I know</u>
<u n="665" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I wasn't even in I was <trunc>st</trunc> oh I felt no I was I was actually genuinely feeling I've been feeling grim most mornings but <pause dur="short"/> I was like you can get up because you need to wash your <trunc>hai</trunc> obviously did not wash my hair erm <unclear>I thought you</unclear> get up so you can wash your hair and like you know you can get to <anon type="place"/> fine and you're not gonna look like a tramp I look like a tramp <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="666" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you don't look like a tramp</u>
<u n="667" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and then I saw on Twitter it was like the John Lewis advert comes out at eight o'clock and I was like well I think I'm gonna stay in bed till eight</u>
<u n="668" who="S0439">and people have been talking about that all day I haven't seen it though</u>
<u n="669" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> advert <pause dur="short"/> it's not as good as Monty the penguin for obvious reasons</u>
<u n="670" who="S0439" trans="overlap">Monty the penguin oh was amazing</u>
<u n="671" who="S0444">still quite sweet I spent the first bit being like I don't get it</u>
<u n="672" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="673" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="674" who="S0439">I think you're always like that with the John Lewis advert though</u>
<u n="675" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="676" who="S0439">like that advert with the little boy</u>
<u n="677" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="678" who="S0439">and the <unclear>and actually</unclear> Monty the penguin you didn't know he wasn't really a penguin until the <unclear/> the end</u>
<u n="679" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> I'm just gonna <trunc>l</trunc> relive that moment mentally in my head</u>
<u n="680" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="681" who="S0439" trans="overlap">when he gets a girlfriend</u>
<u n="682" who="S0444">oh my god</u>
<u n="683" who="S0439">but</u>
<u n="684" who="S0444">I was like well you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> took me to John Lewis to see Monty the <trunc>pen</trunc> like Monty's garden <unclear/></u>
<u n="685" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah I remember you saying</u>
<u n="686" who="S0444">last last year I was like I don't really wanna do anything moon related</u>
<u n="687" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="688" who="S0444"><unclear>to be honest not really</unclear></u>
<u n="689" who="S0439">I haven't seen it I'm sure I'll get round to it at some point</u>
<u n="690" who="S0444">mm <pause dur="short"/> what do you think of er Hello?</u>
<u n="691" who="S0439">I like it</u>
<u n="692" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I saw quite a funny little it was a really short video <pause dur="short"/> mm usually I don't like this kind of thing but</u>
<u n="693" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="694" who="S0444">it was <vocal desc="laugh"/> a dad started to play Hello on his phone and his little toddler she goes <shift new="singing"/> hello <shift new="normal"/> and he goes hi</u>
<u n="695" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="696" who="S0444">and I was like oh my gosh that'd be so cool if you actually did <unclear>it to</unclear> Adele that was like <shift new="singing"/> hello it's me <shift new="normal"/> yes? I've been wondering yes?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> after all these years</u>
<u n="698" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="699" who="S0439">you're ringing me? after all these years</u>
<u n="700" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="701" who="S0439">I saw you yesterday</u>
<u n="702" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="703" who="S0444">exactly you're getting my humour now</u>
<u n="704" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="705" who="S0444">oh</u>
<u n="706" who="S0439">but apparently there's <trunc>loa</trunc> I've seen the parody of that on erm Facebook where a girl text her ex boyfriend being like hello erm what is it? I can't even you know when you sing a song and you know the words and then you try and say it?</u>
<u n="707" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="708" who="S0439">hello is it me you're</u>
<u n="709" who="S0444">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's me I've been wondering after all these years</u>
<u n="710" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0444">if you'd like to meet</u>
<u n="712" who="S0439">like to meet he's like I every time I come and see you I ask you to go out for a drink and you always tell me to fuck off and <unclear>they're</unclear> like I've called you a thousand times no you haven't</u>
<u n="713" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="714" who="S0444">there's a there's a picture that's like <vocal desc="laugh"/> missed calls Adele one thousand</u>
<u n="715" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="716" who="S0439">I quite like it as a song</u>
<u n="717" who="S0444">I do</u>
<u n="718" who="S0439">I think it's nice <pause dur="short"/> I'm not entirely sure who she's singing about but cos she can't be still singing about her ex boyfriend he must be fucked off after a while</u>
<u n="719" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <trunc>sh</trunc>she could be <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="720" who="S0439">he must be like seriously <unclear/> like</u>
<u n="721" who="S0444" trans="overlap">after <trunc>t</trunc> after twenty-one he's like</u>
<u n="722" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="723" who="S0444">fuck's sake she's still talking about this four years later</u>
<u n="724" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah seriously love you know like we're er we're over <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="725" who="S0444">cos I was thinking like if I was to see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> now all I'd really say is you know hope things are going well for you</u>
<u n="726" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="727" who="S0444">you know cool you know do you know what I mean? whereas</u>
<u n="728" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="729" who="S0444">for other people it's different</u>
<u n="730" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="731" who="S0444">isn't it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="732" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear>shut up</unclear></u>
<u n="733" who="S0444">isn't it? mm mm</u>
<u n="734" who="S0439">I don't I don't wanna be with him though</u>
<u n="735" who="S0444">no</u>
<u n="736" who="S0439">I don't <unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="737" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> but is it a bit?</u>
<u n="738" who="S0439">it's fine perfectly fine</u>
<u n="739" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's okay?</u>
<u n="740" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="741" who="S0444">so there wasn't any kind of questioning of that?</u>
<u n="742" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no no not at all <pause dur="short"/> no I told him I told him I didn't want to</u>
<u n="743" who="S0444" trans="overlap">both very clear?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0439">I was like firstly I don't think you should like you've just come out of a relationship</u>
<u n="745" who="S0444">mm oh how's that been going by the way?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and ah not very well I don't think I think she's got some issues well I would have some issues <unclear/></u>
<u n="747" who="S0444" trans="overlap">well I would have some issues if I'd moved half way across the world and then he dumped me</u>
<u n="748" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah she's not a happy bunny but she doesn't like I don't think she knows that he's seeing me but erm</u>
<u n="749" who="S0444">well that's definitely not gonna go down well</u>
<u n="750" who="S0439">yeah I know like he's like I'm really sorry but do you mind if you don't put anything on my Facebook wall? I was like yeah that's fine <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> we just came down and we spent the day and we chilled and it was fine</u>
<u n="751" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="752" who="S0439">and then we went to the party and like nothing happened</u>
<u n="753" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="754" who="S0439">he just met everybody and it was really it was really fun it was nice everybody like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> loved him</u>
<u n="755" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="756" who="S0439">and he has been really making it like he's been trying</u>
<u n="757" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="758" who="S0439">like he's seeing a counsellor</u>
<u n="759" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="760" who="S0439">erm and cos he had depression he <trunc>ha</trunc> and he's seeing a counsellor and he's like I was so critical of you and I'm so sorry</u>
<u n="761" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="762" who="S0439">like he's really admitting all his faults and stuff and I was like</u>
<u n="763" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="764" who="S0439">that's fine that's great you know I don't hold it against you I've got no problems with you like there's no <trunc>resen</trunc>resentment there</u>
<u n="765" who="S0444">mm mm</u>
<u n="766" who="S0439">I just don't feel that way about him anymore</u>
<u n="767" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="768" who="S0439">I don't look I just don't <trunc>tru</trunc> I wouldn't trust him as far as I could throw him <pause dur="short"/> cos he's saying all the right things now but no</u>
<u n="769" who="S0444">not right now</u>
<u n="770" who="S0439">no and I <trunc>d</trunc> I don't want it like</u>
<u n="771" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="772" who="S0439">last night I went to the fireworks with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I was so happy</u>
<u n="773" who="S0444" trans="overlap">having fun</u>
<u n="774" who="S0439">yeah I like having someone there having like a boyfriend there would've ruined that moment</u>
<u n="775" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="776" who="S0439">because we were all there together and we were all single and we were just happy and chilling and having fun having a laugh</u>
<u n="777" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="778" who="S0439">but the moment you bring a boyfriend or a girlfriend into that situation the dynamic changes</u>
<u n="779" who="S0444">mm <pause dur="short"/> how were the fireworks?</u>
<u n="780" who="S0439">oh my god they were amazing <unclear>they were</unclear></u>
<u n="781" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I saw I saw a really big fireworks display in <anon type="place"/> which was probably the most interesting thing in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="782" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="783" who="S0444">erm and that ah at least <unclear>I got to</unclear> see some fireworks</u>
<u n="784" who="S0439">I love fireworks so much but it <trunc>w</trunc> it was like a good solid fifteen minutes of fireworks it was really good</u>
<u n="785" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="786" who="S0439">really really good actually <pause dur="short"/> normally like council ones are a bit shitty</u>
<u n="787" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="788" who="S0439">but no it was a nice evening</u>
<u n="789" who="S0444">cos I was sad I didn't get to see any fireworks</u>
<u n="790" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="791" who="S0444">mm <pause dur="short"/> I liked bonfire night</u>
<u n="792" who="S0439">yeah I think bonfire night's one probably one of my favourite nights of the year <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but no and then we went into town to try and find a like an open Costa or Starbucks and we couldn't</u>
<u n="793" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="794" who="S0439">and then went home and had hot chocolate and then I came back here</u>
<u n="795" who="S0444">right nice</u>
<u n="796" who="S0439">but oh my god oh</u>
<u n="797" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh what's going on with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and what's his face?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh nothing</u>
<u n="799" who="S0444">erm</u>
<u n="800" who="S0439">nothing's going on there but erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s brother moved here</u>
<u n="801" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="802" who="S0439">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s super nice I really like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's really chilled he's really good</u>
<u n="803" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="804" who="S0439">erm and we all get on really well as a four so like <anon type="place"/> will be fine</u>
<u n="805" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="806" who="S0439">erm <pause dur="short"/> but last week <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> my French friend found out</u>
<u n="807" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yep yep</u>
<u n="808" who="S0439">that her ex boyfriend is having a baby and getting married</u>
<u n="809" who="S0444"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh</u>
<u n="810" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and they broke up a year ago so it's like a year later</u>
<u n="811" who="S0444" trans="overlap">okay yeah yeah</u>
<u n="812" who="S0439">he's having a baby and getting married erm and so last week she was on like a bit of a train wreck like I'm so alone</u>
<u n="813" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="814" who="S0439">my life is over</u>
<u n="815" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yep</u>
<u n="816" who="S0439">I'm gonna die with like cats erm <pause dur="short"/> so she was like this weekend last weekend we're I'm gonna go out and get absolutely smashed and get with somebody I was like yeah you do that you know go out get drunk</u>
<u n="817" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><trunc>h</trunc>have fun</u>
<u n="818" who="S0439"><unclear/> we'll dance we'll have fun we'll have a girly time get with someone who did she get with?</u>
<u n="819" who="S0444">oh god <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="820" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but I kid you not it was like it wasn't even cool like she followed him round the entire night</u>
<u n="821" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh <unclear/> <unclear>yikes</unclear></u>
<u n="822" who="S0439">like everywhere he went she followed him</u>
<u n="823" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh god <unclear/></u>
<u n="824" who="S0439">she <unclear>you know</unclear> she was like trying to grind on him and like grabbing his hand and putting his hand on her waist</u>
<u n="825" who="S0444"><unclear>oh my god</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="826" who="S0439">and <pause dur="short"/> oh and then like</u>
<u n="827" who="S0444">not cool <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="828" who="S0439">and then she was like kiss me he's like no no I don't think I should he she was like please kiss me he was like</u>
<u n="829" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh gosh</u>
<u n="830" who="S0439">yeah exactly and then she was like oh no you can come home with me come home with me</u>
<u n="831" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh fuck man</u>
<u n="832" who="S0439">and he was like hell no <unclear>be that guy</unclear> no he did kiss her but he's like I'm not coming home with you</u>
<u n="833" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> well fair play to him like</u>
<u n="834" who="S0439">yeah exactly that's what we said I was like I was like I love you he's like really? I was like yes because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does like commitment really badly like the moment she kisses a guy she thinks they're gonna get married</u>
<u n="835" who="S0444" trans="overlap">that's it yeah yeah</u>
<u n="836" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="837" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="838" who="S0439">erm <pause dur="short"/> and so she kissed him and she was kind of one of those people that when she like kisses someone or something she kind of gets like really proud of it she's like oh I got with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> blah blah blah I was like I've been telling you all night to stay away because I knew I could see what was happening I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> stop it you're just following him like a puppy she's like no I'm not I'm like yes yes you really are and she was like no I'm not I'm like I can see what's happening <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and you're gonna try something on with him and it's just gonna go very badly wrong cos we see these people every week you know</u>
<u n="839" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah so it's not like you know</u>
<u n="840" who="S0439">mm and she's like but you got with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I was like before I knew <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like it's different</u>
<u n="841" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="842" who="S0439">erm and me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are fine so</u>
<u n="843" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah and it's just like oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> do you remember that time that <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="844" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm yeah exactly erm so <pause dur="short"/> so on Sunday I saw her and apparently after that she got with another guy I was like okay that's <unclear>you know</unclear></u>
<u n="845" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="846" who="S0439">erm and she was really like embarrassed about it</u>
<u n="847" who="S0444">oh</u>
<u n="848" who="S0439">and I was like well no offence it's your own fault</u>
<u n="849" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="850" who="S0439">like I told you not to do this</u>
<u n="851" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="852" who="S0439">and you basically just turned round and told me to piss off and I'm like and then she was like yeah but I think I really like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm like no you don't like you've known him for like</u>
<u n="853" who="S0444" trans="overlap">no let's not do <trunc>g</trunc> that <unclear>don't</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="854" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you've known him for like a week you've had like five <trunc>conversa</trunc> not even five conversations with him</u>
<u n="855" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="856" who="S0439">you got drunk at a party he was the new guy on the scene so you went after him like <unclear/></u>
<u n="857" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> textbook yeah</u>
<u n="858" who="S0439">yeah I was like you don't like him? she goes yes I do <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I don't understand why you don't <trunc>understa</trunc> you don't believe me I'm like</u>
<u n="859" who="S0444" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="860" who="S0439">because you kissed him once when you were drunk and no offence but you asked him to go home with you and he said no and she was like oh yeah <trunc>cra</trunc> like and she was like doesn't he find me attractive? I was like oh my god</u>
<u n="861" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh here we go spiral</u>
<u n="862" who="S0439">I was like it's not that he doesn't find you attractive he just doesn't want that like he got he's erm he's being he's going through through a divorce he's thirty-one years old like he's going through a divorce he doesn't want your he doesn't want to be in a relationship with anybody let alone you</u>
<u n="863" who="S0444" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="864" who="S0439">I was like it's not cos he doesn't think you're pretty he doesn't think you're not because he doesn't think you're cool <pause dur="short"/> he just doesn't want that</u>
<u n="865" who="S0444" trans="overlap">just <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="866" who="S0439">just so don't go there and she was like oh <unclear/> I'm gonna be alone for the rest of my life no one loves me what's wrong with me? and I was like you know when your sympathy for someone just completely cuts off</u>
<u n="867" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="868" who="S0439">I was like I am tired of listening to you whine <pause dur="short"/> and then cos I went round to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s on Monday and we were talking about it</u>
<u n="869" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="870" who="S0439">and like I told them that she got with somebody else just because it just came up and <unclear>like</unclear> I didn't know that she I thought everybody knew cos she'd got with <trunc>g</trunc> with this guy in public apparently in front of everybody at the party and she then she got angry at me <unclear>cos she said</unclear> I can't believe you told them that I got with someone else because I really like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and now <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> think gonna think I'm a slut I'm like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was happy to know that you got with somebody else like</u>
<u n="871" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it wasn't just him</u>
<u n="872" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="873" who="S0439">no and she was like</u>
<u n="874" who="S0444">ah</u>
<u n="875" who="S0439">and it just went from bad to worse and then she like sent <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> texts and was being like you know next time like I tell you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> stuff can you not talk to the boys about it? and it was just ah</u>
<u n="876" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="877" who="S0439">so much drama I was like I don't need this</u>
<u n="878" who="S0444">ah</u>
<u n="879" who="S0439">like</u>
<u n="880" who="S0444">yeah just yeah not</u>
<u n="881" who="S0439">so much drama from one party <pause dur="short"/> one person</u>
<u n="882" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="883" who="S0439">like</u>
<u n="884" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="885" who="S0439"><unclear>that's why I just I wouldn't</unclear></u>
<u n="886" who="S0444" trans="overlap">is she feeling a bit better now?</u>
<u n="887" who="S0439">she no not really she's gone back to <anon type="place"/> for the weekend like she was gonna go back to <anon type="place"/> for the weekend anyway</u>
<u n="888" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="889" who="S0439">but she gets really bad FOMO you know like fear of missing out</u>
<u n="890" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah yeah FOMO yeah</u>
<u n="891" who="S0439">and she gets it really badly so I was round <pause dur="short"/> so I went round <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s on Monday</u>
<u n="892" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="893" who="S0439">I didn't see her Tuesday I didn't see her Wednesday but I was <unclear>with</unclear> <unclear/> last night for the fireworks</u>
<u n="894" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="895" who="S0439">and she was like oh where are you? I was like at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s she goes oh what are you talking about? like</u>
<u n="896" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="897" who="S0439">the fireworks and she was like oh <pause dur="short"/> I wish I was there it's just like</u>
<u n="898" who="S0444">mm yeah</u>
<u n="899" who="S0439">it's kind of like once when we were in <anon type="place"/> she got really paranoid at the three of us you know like that me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were like got on better than us and like</u>
<u n="900" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="901" who="S0439">we kind of got over that and she we'd just got to a point where all three of us were like fine again and she was comfortable with us</u>
<u n="902" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="903" who="S0439">like there was a time when I wouldn't even tell her I was with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because she'd get annoyed</u>
<u n="904" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="905" who="S0439">erm and now I think she's gone straight back to it like at the moment it's like I'm with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="906" who="S0444">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="907" who="S0439">it's like she's like oh you're not with me like oh</u>
<u n="908" who="S0444">oh yeah and it's just like <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I dunno it's I mean I <trunc>c</trunc> I <trunc>c</trunc> I can see why she's feeling <unclear>maybe</unclear> insecure anyway but</u>
<u n="909" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she is I think she is a really insecure person well she is yeah</u>
<u n="910" who="S0444">she is but like <unclear>I dunno</unclear> I dunno the best the best way to try and get over the <unclear>hurt</unclear> is to do something for yourself and</u>
<u n="911" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="912" who="S0444">you know build a life for yourself you were happy you came to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="913" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="914" who="S0444">you built a life for yourself it's it's what you do I'm not <unclear/></u>
<u n="915" who="S0439"><unclear/></u>
<u n="916" who="S0444">you know I'm better than I was in terms of happiness</u>
<u n="917" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="918" who="S0444">you know in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="919" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="920" who="S0444">much better than you know that <anon type="place"/> time when I was</u>
<u n="921" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="922" who="S0444">on the edge erm</u>
<u n="923" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="924" who="S0444">but you know there are options I don't know which options are gonna stay open</u>
<u n="925" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="926" who="S0444">I don't know which options are gonna stay closed but you know it's like <unclear/> you do something for yourself <unclear>and it's</unclear></u>
<u n="927" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah if you're not happy you've just gotta change something</u>
<u n="928" who="S0444" trans="overlap">you've just gotta do something for yourself <unclear>and if you</unclear></u>
<u n="929" who="S0439">even if it's one thing you've just gotta change it</u>
<u n="930" who="S0444" trans="overlap">exactly <unclear>whereas mine</unclear> just seems to be every bloody thing going</u>
<u n="931" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah at the same time</u>
<u n="932" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="933" who="S0439">job house</u>
<u n="934" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s moving <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s moving in with the bro</u>
<u n="935" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="936" who="S0444">that's gonna change things completely it's a different <unclear/></u>
<u n="937" who="S0439" trans="overlap">do you think?</u>
<u n="938" who="S0444">yeah cos er he's not with his parents anymore</u>
<u n="939" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="940" who="S0444">so that's gonna change the dynamic</u>
<u n="941" who="S0439">do you think they'll go out and be more like laddy and stuff?</u>
<u n="942" who="S0444">I reckon so but that will be a good thing</u>
<u n="943" who="S0439" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="944" who="S0444">in the way that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actually has a life because</u>
<u n="945" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="946" who="S0444">with a three hour round commute</u>
<u n="947" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="948" who="S0444">he's got no time for a life at the moment Monday to Friday</u>
<u n="949" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="950" who="S0444">so it's like what have you been up to? well yeah work and</u>
<u n="951" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="952" who="S0444">just the gym and then just chilling and it's like <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="953" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="954" who="S0444">do you know what I mean? whereas and he's got a new job he's got a permanent job now</u>
<u n="955" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="956" who="S0444">with <anon type="place"/> that's not hanging over him anymore</u>
<u n="957" who="S0439">that's good</u>
<u n="958" who="S0444">so it's like all like it's kind of like it's not changing for me</u>
<u n="959" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="960" who="S0444">but it'll change how we are cos it's the kind of thing where it's like it's a house it's not</u>
<u n="961" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="962" who="S0444">you know it's not like you know his parents' <unclear>where</unclear> you know</u>
<u n="963" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="964" who="S0444">things have to be quiet or you <trunc>ha</trunc> you know it's the kind of thing where you're on your best behaviour we can just sit and lounge on the couch if we want to</u>
<u n="965" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="966" who="S0444">like you know that kind of <unclear/> so that'll be different <pause dur="short"/> that'll be different for him but then it's kind of like well you know what? like it was getting to the point where when <vocal desc="laugh"/> when he got this job he was like and I kind of brought up the question I was like so how much is it you'll be earning? and it was ten grand more than me and I was like I don't have a problem with him earning</u>
<u n="967" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="968" who="S0444">more than me cos he's in a different industry and that's just the way that it goes but I was like I seriously need to get a job <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's actually</u>
<u n="969" who="S0439" trans="overlap">what are you on at the moment? twenty?</u>
<u n="970" who="S0444" trans="overlap">like twenty-four</u>
<u n="971" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="972" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I'm not even that but</u>
<u n="973" who="S0439">that's so bad isn't it?</u>
<u n="974" who="S0444">so</u>
<u n="975" who="S0439" trans="overlap">especially in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="976" who="S0444">well that's what I mean cos I was like I'm not being funny but if I'm having to pay six hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="977" who="S0439">that's half a salary isn't it?</u>
<u n="978" who="S0444" trans="overlap">a month that's pretty much yeah</u>
<u n="979" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="980" who="S0444">when you when you take out like</u>
<u n="981" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that's poor</u>
<u n="982" who="S0444">other <unclear>things</unclear> I'm just like I don't even wanna be here <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="983" who="S0439">cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got a nice <unclear>better</unclear> better pay rise didn't she?</u>
<u n="984" who="S0444">she got about thirty and a half</u>
<u n="985" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="986" who="S0444">when she went into product management so when they asked me about salary I said something in the region of that</u>
<u n="987" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="988" who="S0444">with scope to review it <pause dur="short"/> bearing in mind the role that I would be doing so</u>
<u n="989" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="990" who="S0444">it's kind of like</u>
<u n="991" who="S0439">and I don't know if they'd give you that cos you're an internal and I don't think they'd bump up your salary <unclear/></u>
<u n="992" who="S0444" trans="overlap">well they <trunc>g</trunc> they gave <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that one</u>
<u n="993" who="S0439">oh really?</u>
<u n="994" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="995" who="S0439">was she on twenty-three?</u>
<u n="996" who="S0444">no she was on a little bit more but not masses more</u>
<u n="997" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm oh okay that's pretty good then</u>
<u n="998" who="S0444">but I but I basically <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos the science team <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos I can't say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear>without you like who</unclear>?</u>
<u n="999" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0444">what? are you talking about yourself?</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1002" who="S0444">I was like why did you sell yourself short? like you I was like I don't know what wage to go for</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0444">I can't say thirty-five cos that's er twelve grand</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0439">yeah <unclear/> though</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yes the job might you know do that but they kind of like I was kind of <unclear>look</unclear> you know <pause dur="short"/> as I haven't been in product management before I think a product management associate salary</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0439">mm thirty grand's good</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0444">of around that</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I'd be happy with thirty grand</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0444" trans="overlap">is you know where it should start <unclear>with</unclear></u>
<u n="1011" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0444">with scope to review it bearing in mind the tasks</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0444">that I will be executing you know</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0444">so you know I think I think that was fine but it was I'm really glad that I got you know I know that you definitely have been saying you know change come on now change</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0444">and then <unclear/> it's like prod prod</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah but you like you can you</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0444" trans="overlap">but it was a good thing but it was more the kind of thing where</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you had to kind of wait it out a little bit cos obviously you er you couldn't just change job after being ill</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0444"><vocal desc="cough"/> no it's more like <unclear>a thing</unclear> of it's I knew that I needed to do it but the opportunity or the <trunc>t</trunc> it just didn't</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0444">feel like there were ways to do that whereas</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0444">actually it all ended up happening at once something may come of it something may not but</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah you never know it's worth trying</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0444">er something is well I think the <trunc>thi</trunc> the thing er the thing is now that I know that at least something is changing</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0444">so my role is changing</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0444">that's you know that's already that's already done</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0439">yep new house</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0444" trans="overlap">my house is definitely gonna change</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0439">and I think the privacy might <trunc>d</trunc> if you say <unclear/> you did go to the annex or something like you did decide to pay a bit more</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the privacy <unclear>would be</unclear> so much better</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0439" trans="overlap">the privacy'd be nice especially like if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came to stay and stuff like</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0439">just that privacy</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0444">just having <trunc>s</trunc> like I know it sounds ridiculous but having a sofa or like</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0444">something</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0439">but also <unclear/> like there's not the constant not fear that someone will walk in but you <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="1044" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's not like</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0439" trans="overlap">cos there's someone always there just like wandering around outside and you're just like oh</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0444">exactly so</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0444">you know <pause dur="short"/> I am not I am a people person</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0444">so it'll be quite interesting to see but it's not like I can't invite people round and be like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1051" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm no</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0444">everybody round like you know</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0444">or if you came to stay it'd be like dude right flat sorted done</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0444">I mean they've kind of said the kitchen facilities aren't brilliant enough for you to make full meals so you can use the kitchen but</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0444">I was kind of like</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1060" who="S0444">I was kind of like do you know what? <pause dur="short"/> like I didn't say anything I didn't do any emails or anything I was just like do you know what? I'm just gonna wait until I come back from <anon type="place"/> then I'll</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0439" trans="overlap">decide yeah</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0444">decide cos it was just I'm I'm not kidding my brain was about to explode</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0444">I've been kind of not arguing with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but we've kind of just been I think because I've been so stressed and <unclear/> like that it was just like the <trunc>la</trunc> the lack of communication or how things have been like were communicated <unclear>I was a bit</unclear> like oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="1065" who="S0439">did you have an argument or?</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0444">yeah but it was a kind of not one that we'd had before but because you know things have been getting better in terms of communication cos he's not brilliant</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0439" trans="overlap">men aren't</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0444">at saying stuff <unclear/></u>
<u n="1069" who="S0439" trans="overlap">just they aren't</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0444">so you know he's getting better but he's like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's actually through the things that I do that I show you that I care like</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no but the thing is men don't like it's not enough it's not enough</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> no and that's what I was saying to him and he took it as a criticism and I was like well no it's not a criticism of you because it's you as a person</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's it's just men in general</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0444">it's just everyone in general and</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0444">I'm just saying that especially at moments when I'm tired and stressed</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0444">and I just need that a bit more cos it's like I'm like if you say I look nice or you know</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0444">it <trunc>w</trunc> it was the kind of thing where on the Wednesday we went out to celebrate his job</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0444">erm and that had meant that you know by coming to his I was doing the double the commute in the morning and things like that</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0444">and er he he appreciated it but it was another thing I was like you know when I cook for you like you know when you're tired or you're preparing for your interview</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0444">you know that's that's I'm more of an actions person and I was like that's great but I need some <unclear>of the</unclear> words too</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0444">but but it was kind of like</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/> like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying to me like this week he's been like flirting and stuff</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1091" who="S0439">and I was just like well no offence but you're you're <trunc>l</trunc>literally should stop communicating like the reason like we didn't go anywhere was because</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0444">you didn't communicate</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you didn't communicate with me like if you'd told</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0439">like the reason I pulled back and I never really let him in was</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and then you got <trunc>s</trunc> I thought you were gonna he was communicating too much <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1097" who="S0439">yeah but the reason like I kind of pulled back and never really liked him was because I didn't know that he liked me</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0439">like he never he was like yeah but I did like you like I bought you some lip gloss I was like what the fuck?</u>
<u n="1100" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1101" who="S0439">like <unclear>you know I mean</unclear> girls er girls need to be told</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0444" trans="overlap">a verbal affirmation it's</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0439">because like and I think er what's confusing for girls is that for most girls the act of sex itself</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0439">is a representation of love</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0439">but nowadays it's not</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0444">exactly</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0439">so if you need that verbal affirmation</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1111" who="S0439">you can't just have an action</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah it's really weird cos it was like yeah well as friends we weren't ever <pause dur="short"/> not insecure but you you never wondered about how you were</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0439">mm yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0444" trans="overlap">as friends whereas when you're in a relationship it's like oh well how are we doing? because you know everybody's automatic assumption about the job has been ah but you'll move in with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm like hell no</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0444">no no no no no no no like cos I'm like you know what?</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no offence that didn't pop into my head at all <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1118" who="S0444">no not yours but I mean like other people who don't know me</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0444">as well and have just said oh yeah I'm with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and er you know</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0444"><unclear/> best friends and now we're we're go out and they don't know much more than that</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0444">erm and they're like oh yeah great you don't have to be long distance anymore and it's like <pause dur="short"/> yeah no erm I'd still be living separately establishing my own life</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0444">obviously I get to see him more and blah blah blah but no no</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0444">not right now</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0444">I I'd rather get myself sorted</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0444">and</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and just not obviously not that you're in a bad place at all but if <unclear>you're</unclear> like at the moment you've been quite stressed and tired and stuff moving in with each other at this moment would not it'd just be a recipe for disaster and you'd just end up snapping and then you'd yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1134" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sigh"/> like er exactly and we both know that <pause dur="short"/> we both know that and <unclear>it was it was like it was like</unclear> <unclear/> I'm not being funny but <pause dur="short"/> if things go well we've got time to do that</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0444">and if they don't then it's a good thing you know we caught it when we did</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0444">but you know it's the kind of thing where</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0444">we are ridiculously slow you know that as much as anybody else</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well yeah</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0444">but it's not</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0439" trans="overlap">eight months did it take you to have sex?</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0444" trans="overlap">nine</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0439">nine months? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1146" who="S0444">no not to have sex to er actually have from from him <unclear/> him thinking I like you</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/> a while to have sex though <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1148" who="S0444">from him being like I like you to kind of actually being like you know I want to go out with you that that was a good nine months so that gives you a pretty good indication and</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh yeah I was with you for the whole thing</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0444" trans="overlap">you were there you were there</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0439">that was a rollercoaster <unclear>of a ride</unclear> that one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1152" who="S0444" trans="overlap">hell yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> so you know and <unclear/> <unclear>it's that kind of thing</unclear></u>
<u n="1153" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0444">where do you know what? with him having a new house a new job you know actually having more of a life</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0444">not because he didn't want one but because you weren't able to then that's gonna change the dynamic</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0439">yeah of course it will</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0444">and you know I'd rather get used to that dynamic changing than get used to my own dynamic changing</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0444">and er you know see how <unclear>things work out</unclear> cos it could be that <pause dur="short"/> you know he moves in starts becoming a lad and becomes a completely different person don't think that would happen</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1162" who="S0444">but do you know what I mean? <unclear>or</unclear></u>
<u n="1163" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0444">I become a product manager and that's it it's work work work</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I rule the world yeah</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0444">and it's work work work</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0444">you know you just don't you just don't know what's gonna happen but</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah you just don't know what'll happen but I think that's really you've got a logical way of thinking about it like I'm glad that you don't just dive in and be like</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1171" who="S0439">we're gonna live together we're gonna be together forever and like that and just no</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear>and no</unclear> I mean you know we we know that I think that's also because he's very logical like he's even more logical than me and I'm not that logical</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0444">but someone has to be <pause dur="short"/> erm but it's more like <unclear>I think it's like</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> no it's like there are a lot of people at work like my entire department pretty much all the girls moved in with their boyfriends after four months</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0439">really?</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0444">yeah all because of different circumstances</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0439">that makes me wanna cry yeah</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0444">like you know but I was and they're like oh so so when are you gonna move in? I'm like well that's another like year and a half two years at least like</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh yeah I don't I <unclear/> rush it</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I'm just like I don't wanna rush into it like</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0439">well it's like I like my space my space is nice</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0444" trans="overlap">he <pause dur="short"/> yeah I like my space he adores his space sort of thing</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0444">he's an introvert I'm an extrovert we're opposites like</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0439">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I'm an extrovert but I love my space</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0444">that's true that is true <pause dur="short"/> introvert extrovert</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just no <unclear/></u>
<u n="1188" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I've definitely become a little bit more introverted</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0439">that's good</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0444">because I've had to be</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0444">I have to go home and rest <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1193" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0444">and <unclear/></u>
<u n="1195" who="S0439">but also I think if you're going out with somebody who's an introvert you can't completely bombard them all the time</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0439">because they'll just become even more introverted</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0444">yeah I know but</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0439" trans="overlap">the more you try and push them the more they'll just retreat <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> exactly but you know we'll just see but I think the good thing at the moment is that I feel there are possibilities</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0439">good</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0444">and that the world isn't closed off to me and to be honest the fact that everybody's been like you're great at what you do and</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0444"><vocal desc="nonsense"/> and they're like yeah but people think really highly of you and it's not gonna notice where people like</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0444">the people higher up in the <unclear/> <unclear>I'm like well</unclear> that's great erm and that's all happened while I've been ill and</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0444">like it was like on Wednesday I met up with some of the another person in the science team who'd also kind of given me a few quick pointers</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0444">erm cos they'd had a <trunc>m</trunc> product management interview recently</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0444">and she was like yeah but we want you back like</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0444">we want you back and <pause dur="short"/> we we we wanted you with us when you were ill and we didn't care that you were ill</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0439" trans="overlap">we still want you yeah</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0444">we <trunc>j</trunc> we just <unclear/></u>
<u n="1217" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/> risk is if you accept this job and it's not in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1218" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0439">it's not <unclear/> stuck in Oxford</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0444">it's not in Oxford it's London</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0439">oh that's good</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0444">definitely London</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0439">cos I think I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="1224" who="S0444" trans="overlap">cos it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="1225" who="S0439">I think</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0444" trans="overlap">no I couldn't do another job if it's in <anon type="place"/> that was</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> stuck in Oxford you'd be stuck in Oxford for another like a few <trunc>year</trunc> like two years</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0444" trans="overlap">like I said like I've pretty much said to myself obviously it depends what jobs come up</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0444">but if there if there is a flurry of jobs that happens and they're in London I'm like <unclear>got that</unclear></u>
<u n="1231" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0444">but everybody was like oh would but would you move to <anon type="place"/> with your current job? I'm like no not a chance</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0444">it doesn't</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0439">no commuting it doesn't work</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0444">er not</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0439">you don't wanna spend two or three hours of your day living on a train</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0444">but also <pause dur="short"/> if I was in the Londonoffice but my my entire department's in <anon type="place"/> I've been doing the work in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1239" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0444">this week and it's just not</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0444">effective because you haven't got loads of conversations with people</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0444">there's nobody in there in</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0444">you know in <anon type="place"/> who does marketing apart from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but he works on a different thing so yeah it's kind of like I dunno</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0444">I I'm not gonna move to <anon type="place"/> there isn't if it was the kind of thing that I was like I dunno married with kids</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0444">and a lot lot older</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0444">then yeah maybe I'd stick in London because I have to and</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0444">you know I'd just deal with the gripes you know but I don't have to</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0444">so</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0439">there's no point doing something like that if you yeah if it's not necessary</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1259" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear>it's a waste of time</unclear></u>
<u n="1260" who="S0444">not necessary like <pause dur="short"/> there'd have to be a lot there there'd have to be a lot of reasons for me to move to London</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0444">and feel secure</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0444">outside of work <pause dur="short"/> to make it <unclear>work there</unclear></u>
<u n="1265" who="S0439" trans="overlap">cos the thing with working in London is that you have to make friends and it's a very big place</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's a hard place to make friends</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that's the thing like it's so big and everyone's like oh you'll meet loads of people but because it's so big I actually think a lot of people get lonely because they don't know how to make friends</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's so and that's one of the things I just <unclear>like</unclear> the main thing with people in London <unclear>is like the</unclear> loneliness</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0444">but erm yeah but we shall see</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0439">yeah you'll be fine</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0444">everything is changing for everyone</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0444"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got a new job</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0444">you've got a new job</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0439">where's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> gone?</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0444">she's still in the army</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0444">but she's not gonna be a musician anymore she's gonna work in the recruiting side of things</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0439">ah</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0444">which she's quite glad about cos she needed a change</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1284" who="S0444">well she's been passed over for promotion a lot of times and</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah I remember</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0444">it's gotten to the point well she's been she's going to be passed over again</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0439">shit</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0444">so it means that people who started three years after her</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0439" trans="overlap">are above her</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0444">are above her</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0439">it's a joke isn't it?</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and it's it it's an absolute joke because it's just a personal vendetta that the people in authority have got against her</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0444">not that she did anything wrong with them</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0444">I don't know but you know and it was just that kind of thing <unclear/></u>
<u n="1297" who="S0439" trans="overlap">political isn't it?</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0444">do you know what? you know and she's going to a normal Monday to Friday nine to five which'll be really different</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear>that'll be</unclear> good mm</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0444">erm so <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah no more kind of three o'clock starts at the <anon type="place"/> which is what it's like at the moment</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0439">er</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0444">well they have to they have to do it <unclear>when everyone's</unclear> quiet but</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0444">er yeah it's pretty <unclear/> she's like oh yeah I <unclear>played for</unclear> prince Andrew today <unclear/></u>
<u n="1305" who="S0439">nice I'm sure he loved it</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0444">he did</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0439">oh did he? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1308" who="S0444">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was like oh yeah I met I met Sarah and Eugenie and Beatrice I was like oh very good</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0439">nice</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0444">had a right chat with them very good <pause dur="short"/> I'm just like yeah</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0439">if I was a royalist I'd care</u>
<u n="1312" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1313" who="S0439">no I know what you mean</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0444">no but er</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear>it is</unclear> pretty cool though if I met Philip I'd be I'd be absolutely I'd be so happy</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0444" trans="overlap">if he said something to you you'd be even happier</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0439">I would cry I'd be <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="1318" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/> something offensive <unclear>you'd be like I love</unclear> you</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0439" trans="overlap">even if yeah even <trunc>i</trunc> even if <unclear/> something offensive to me I'd be like oh my god you're the best person ever</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0444"><unclear>I know</unclear></u>
<u n="1321" who="S0439">it's so good cos at the moment my team is now pretty much only me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and then my old manager called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who is above <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1322" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0439">so he's like the head of the department</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0439">but he's like the dad of the like the</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0439">grandad of the department</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0439">like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> controls it really but he's just the one who signs all like the</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh is he? yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0439">she'll be like I wanna do this and he'll be like oh okay but he's the most politically incorrect person I know</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1333" who="S0439">and he just he knows that I love that sense of humour so he'll come over to me and tell me something completely inappropriate and then the woman <trunc>s</trunc> who sits next to me is called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she's lovely but she does not have that sense of humour</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1335" who="S0439">and her face just drops every time</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0444">ah</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0439">it'll be something really offensive and then she'll just be like mm it's like</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1339" who="S0439">oh christ's sake <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just laugh it's funny</u>
<u n="1340" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1341" who="S0439">like today he <trunc>w</trunc> it completely came out of my mouth and it was really bad he was like we were talking about tornados and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> turned round and said yeah but tornados for some reason seem to always like go through the trailer parks and just destroy them I was like maybe there's a reason why</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1343" who="S0439">and then I was like oh my god I actually said that out loud</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1345" who="S0439">oh god oh no</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1347" who="S0439">and he burst out laughing and <unclear>this other woman</unclear> was like why? because you think the trailer <trunc>tra</trunc> like trailer trash should be like blown away? I was like well yes that was that was the joke</u>
<u n="1348" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1349" who="S0439">she was like oh</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0444">tumbleweed</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1352" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1353" who="S0439">I was like erm some people got it <vocal desc="laugh"/> some people find it funny</u>
<u n="1354" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1355" who="S0439"><unclear/> sense of humour but yeah</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1357" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1358" who="S0439">sense of humour where the lower class citizens should be swept</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0444" trans="overlap">corporate risks</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1361" who="S0444">inappropriate sense of humour</u>
<u n="1362" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1363" who="S0444">also</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that's me</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0444">what's with the I want to do inappropriate things to you? hello there are much better ways of saying that kind of thing but</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I know I know I know I was just like</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0444" trans="overlap">ah sorry</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0439">it was just like well maybe no offence but if you'd actually spoken to me you would've got the chance I was like <pause dur="short"/> maybe was the key word in that sentence but yeah</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0444" trans="overlap">so will there be a round two and three of the after party?</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0439">what? <unclear/> mm</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0444">mm I'm trying not to be like you're just like oh</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0439">she's upstairs she won't know she doesn't hear <pause dur="short"/> erm he wants to us to meet up again and it doesn't bother me like it's kind of just like best friends who have sex</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0444">oh oh oh oh oh</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no that's not a grey area</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1376" who="S0439">you were in a grey area cos you liked him</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0444">yeah true</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0439">I'm not in that grey area</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0444">but is he in that grey area? <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing in</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I don't know I don't think so</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0444">er</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0439">I've told him I don't want anything <unclear/></u>
<u n="1383" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah but that doesn't mean anything</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0439">but there's no pressure and I don't think</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0439">that's what we both like there's no pressure</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0444">yeah and that's what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I were kind of saying as well</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I think there was so much pressure on your on you two to be together</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0444">er it's it's the kind of thing where both of us turned round today <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos er <trunc>obviousl</trunc> it it wasn't the kind of thing where we were arguing but it's just that kind of things are settling</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0444">and I was just like oh okay but I was having a terrible time like basically being shouted at</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0439">by him?</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0444">by no no no</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0444">not by him by work people</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh my god</unclear></u>
<u n="1397" who="S0444">in the middle of training like over email and all this kind of</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0439" trans="overlap">shit</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0444">like being like it's the marketing execs fault and this was being sent to like the biggest people in the business</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and they're blaming you?</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0444">yeah and it's not my fault</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0439"><vocal desc="gasp"/> shit</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0444">and it's nothing to do with me well it is something to do with me but it's not my fault</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0439">that's appalling</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0444">so basically luckily my manager stepped in</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah so your line manager I was thinking that in my head literally that moment</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> stepped in and was like</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0439">fuck off <unclear/></u>
<u n="1409" who="S0444" trans="overlap">to be fair it's took everybody by surprise and there are reasons for this this this this this</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0444">and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came up to me today and was like just to give you the context of that and I was like that's fair enough but after everything that was going on I was like I really do not appreciate that</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and also via email is just so unfair</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0444">well I was at a training course but it was just that kind of oh god it was that kind of thing where like <pause dur="short"/> yeah I don't know but anyway so I was just having a really really <unclear/></u>
<u n="1414" who="S0439" trans="overlap">bad day</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0444">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> then erm but it was the kind of thing where <trunc>m</trunc> like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I were <unclear>basically</unclear> saying today to each other kind of you know I want us but without <pause dur="short"/> that you know I want it to be like it was when we were friends in the way that there wasn't any pressure or measuring of the relationship obviously there's gonna be that</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0444">from time to time but there's just been a lot of kind of <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>figuring out</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1418" who="S0439" trans="overlap">but do you wanna know what the massive difference is?</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0444">what?</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0439">you've got something to lose</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0444">that's the thing</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that's the pressure like at the moment</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0444" trans="overlap">that's the thing and the pressure comes from that and that's the reason for the verbal affirmation because otherwise I'm like</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0444">are we at risk of losing things?</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0444">and I think that <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that's the big thing for me like that's the thing that</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and that's exactly what it is and I was just like</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and er the moment you put a label on it</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0444"><unclear/> <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1432" who="S0439">it's <unclear/> you've got something to lose like at the moment it's fine <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0439">I know that I'm fine without <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it doesn't bother me at all you know like I know that without him I can function perfectly fine</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0439">erm <pause dur="short"/> and it there's no pressure on it and we're happy and it's comfortable and we can do that and carry on as friends and there's no there's nothing confusing in it</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0439">the moment you say well actually I wanna be with you again let's be together</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0439">is the moment the pressure happens because there's that pressure to keep it going</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0439">and it <trunc>bec</trunc> and it's that's that's where I think my downfall is <pause dur="short"/> it's just you've got something to lose</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0439">and therefore there's the risk</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0444">mm <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> yeah we're screwed aren't we?</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0444">okay <pause dur="short"/> we're just gonna end up living together aren't we? when we're old</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0439">yep</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0444">cool <pause dur="short"/> as long as you've got</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0439" trans="overlap">woo</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0444">fill me with carbs and I take you on nice places on holiday and research some of it <unclear>be</unclear> fine</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0439">and have a kitten</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0444">I'm not having a fucking kitten</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0444">I'm having a puppy</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0439">you have a puppy I'll have a kitten</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0444">we're gonna have to teach them to get on though</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0439">yep</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0444">that's okay then</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll be alright</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0444">yeah it's just it's just one of those things where I</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah you will have an argument every now and again</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0444">it takes work it takes time but in the end if all goes well then <pause dur="short"/> mm that'll be what it will be and it's the kind of thing where it's like look <pause dur="short"/> you know we we did the brave you know we did the brave thing eventually</u>
<u n="1464" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1465" who="S0444">but you know cos I was like well why did we do the <unclear>grey</unclear> thing? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1466" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0444"><unclear/> now er cos I asked him while we were on the coach cos before <unclear>all that started and</unclear> I was like I don't know why I just didn't ask you out</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0444">what would you have done if I'd've asked you out? he went <vocal desc="laugh"/> well I wouldn't've laughed at you like you did at me and I was like oh yeah but I was overwhelmed and feeling quite like</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0439"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1471" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0439">not to sound horrible but I think he would've said no</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0439">and er I don't think you would be where you are now</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0444">exactly I think his answer would've been I don't know at which point I would've been like I'm rejected I'm horrible I'm spiralling</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0444">so</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0439">and like</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0444">I don't know it happened the way it happened you can't change it and I</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0444">I <unclear>wouldn't be cos I</unclear> think both of us were like I don't think we want that we don't just wanna jump straight into that because we have too much to lose in terms of a friendship</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0444">like but like</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0439">I fully admit that I'm one of these girls that I do not boys don't instantly look at me and <trunc>f</trunc> like fancy me no no no you know what I mean? like you have those girls</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that's like oh yeah</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear>you're like</unclear> oh my gosh she's amazing and stunning but once they get to know me they really like me</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0439">and I think</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0444">you take a while to grow on people <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm telling you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1490" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I do I do take a while but once I've grown I'm stuck there like mould</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1492" who="S0439">but erm</u>
<u n="1493" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1494" who="S0444">you just likened yourself to mould <unclear/></u>
<u n="1495" who="S0439">yep</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0444">okay</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0439">I did</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0444">I'm just gonna just gonna go with that one</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0439">yep</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0439"><unclear/> the other day I was talking to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I was like she has she went to a wedding when she was in Oz and she had some photos like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1502" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm how was it?</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0439">oh really good she really <trunc>enjo</trunc> she er she <trunc>w</trunc> didn't wanna be there she like wanted to come home back here but the wedding was really good and it was really pretty and the weather was beautiful I was like oh but I was like oh you look so amazing if I was a guy I'd be all over you like herpes</u>
<u n="1504" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1505" who="S0439">and she was like you're the sexiest and the grimmest person I know I'm like</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1507" who="S0439">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1508" who="S0444">and that's why you love me</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1511" who="S0439">but er no she really enjoyed it but it wasn't the same she didn't wanna be there</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0444">okay</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0439">she doesn't like Australia she just wanted to come back here and like her</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0439">sister in law is <unclear>just</unclear> going through a really hard time she's just had another baby her husband is not putting in any effort he doesn't wanna be a dad really</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0439">even though it's the second child he's still just like I don't really want children they tie you down</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1519" who="S0439">so <unclear/></u>
<u n="1520" who="S0444" trans="overlap">well well a bit late now</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm and basically <trunc>sh</trunc>she's been like the sister in law's been the whole time making <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> feel guilty for not being there</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0444">it's not her fault</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0439">yeah and being like oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> well you're getting to thirty and like you really should be having children but no offence I don't actually think you'd be a very good mum anyway and like</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0444">fuck off</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0439">yeah and she said and like you really should come home you know you've only got a few months left in England I don't understand why you don't bother coming home now like why are you gonna wait until June? why prolong it? just come back now and she's like woah and she's like and also when you go and come back like don't move to <anon type="place"/> I know you want to move to <anon type="place"/> but you only wanna move to <anon type="place"/> cos like your friend lives there and you know you can't live your life through your friends but you know family's so much more important like we're important to you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like you've got to prove that we're important and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like wow this is my birthday and you're just telling me that I'm gonna be a shit mum I'm nearly thirty and that my life is crap like wow and she just spent pretty much her whole birthday crying</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0439">but no I was like what a bitch</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0444">total projection</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0439">mm yeah that's what I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I was like you're she's so unhappy with what she <trunc>i</trunc> what she what she's got but she's projecting it onto you</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0444">mm so when are you going?</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0439">when are we going? <pause dur="short"/> if</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0444" trans="overlap">June</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0439">all goes well June <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got to be out of the country on June the nineteenth</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0444">so what are you thinking? are you thinking you're gonna see how this job goes?</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0444">and maybe do it for three months? or?</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah exactly I'm gonna see how this job goes and if I enjoy it and stuff like er my plan is still I'd like to go I don't really think I don't see why the job would stop me <unclear>unless it</unclear></u>
<u n="1538" who="S0444" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0439">unless it goes really well erm but also this might be the opportunity that I can move to Australia branch so it's like you know if I make connections there is that</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0439">erm <pause dur="short"/> even if it's just for like kind of like <trunc>temp</trunc>temporary contract</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0439">erm <pause dur="short"/> but I still I think I'd still like to go like I think if I don't I'd regret it and I just keep going round and round <unclear/></u>
<u n="1544" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear>otherwise</unclear> you'd rather do that other course</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0439">I still would like to do psychology it's just so confusing there's just so much I wanna do and not enough money to do it <unclear>with</unclear></u>
<u n="1546" who="S0444">well why don't you give yourself the time until it comes to crunch point where you have to make a decision?</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well that's what I was thinking</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0444">when when is the crunch point? in terms of when are you in your head thinking?</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0444">I need to book tickets by this point or is that <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I don't really have one</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0444">that's not really a factor</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0439">just I can just book them whenever erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got to be out the country by June like er June the nineteenth cos she I think she wants to go travelling around Europe first</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0444">oh okay</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0439">cos she's got to basically she's got to be out of England but she doesn't have to be out of Europe like she can go anywhere essentially</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0444">oh how long is that for?</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0439" trans="overlap">but she's got ninety days</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0444">ninety? okay</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0439">ninety days per country but she obviously she's not gonna spend ninety days per country</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1561" who="S0439">that's how many <trunc>t</trunc> that's how you've got to be out of the country by by the end of that that point maybe</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1563" who="S0439">so I think she's gonna try and make the most of that and go to just like round Europe I've already done quite a lot of Europe</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0444">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0439">so I don't really need to so I will see yeah when she is ready to go back to Oz</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0444">cos it's not it's not like you have to follow her straightaway</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no no that's no</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0444">you <unclear/> got you you can see how it goes like</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0439">exactly and <unclear/></u>
<u n="1570" who="S0444" trans="overlap">even if it's like July or</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0439">yeah like that doesn't bother me</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1573" who="S0439">I'd still like to go I think</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0439">erm I think it would I've been really wanting to do something like that for ages and it just seems like a good time and I think this job'd be good in terms of opening up</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0444">closed doors</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0439">closed doors and meeting loads of people and</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0444">impressing them</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0439">exactly so</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0444">you could always say I'm going to Australia for two weeks do you want me to add on a week in Australia to work?</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0444">cos if they like you enough they'll probably say yes</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0439">exactly if I make an impression then boom <pause dur="short"/> but cos this like erm this job the thing with my other job is that you couldn't go anywhere this job can actually go somewhere technically if I wanted to the only person above me is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1584" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1585" who="S0439">and he's the director of global like I'm not I'm not saying</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0439">I'd replace him but</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0444">no</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0439">the amount of people I can meet and</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0444" trans="overlap">but you'd have to yeah and it's the kind of thing where they could create a role for you that expands on what you do or <unclear/> direction yeah</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I could if I wanted to go higher up if I wanted to go higher up in terms of the board and stuff it's a good place to meet people and to do things and to get exposure so <pause dur="short"/> that's yeah that's something I didn't consider</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0444">oh I know somebody who's left <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1593" who="S0439">you're kidding? where did she go?</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0444">she is doing her foundation degree in animal management</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0439">ah bless her that's good for her <pause dur="short"/> er where is she? in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0444">somewhere kind of <anon type="place"/>y countrysidey</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0444">kind of <pause dur="short"/> specialist college kind of thing</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0439">oh when did she leave?</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0444">end of October so she's only just left</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0444">she left last Friday</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0439">was people <trunc>shock</trunc> were people shocked by it?</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0444">erm well she'd been doing her kind of studies already</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0444">and then I think she <trunc>s</trunc> took she started the foundation degree and I don't know whether it was before or during that she'd just started</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0444">and she was just like this is just too much</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0439">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0444">erm for her to do that and get the experience</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0444">and you know and erm so she decided to</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0439">quit</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0444">quit and I think it was a shock to her <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1615" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0444">and to everyone else but everybody was kind of like well it's still the right thing to do</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0439" trans="overlap">the right thing to do</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0444">and she was like oh no oh no <unclear/> I was like it'll be the right thing like</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you'll be fine</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0444"><unclear>no</unclear> so <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1621" who="S0439">ah</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0444">good</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0439">good for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1624" who="S0444"><unclear/> there are no more former trainees left <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1625" who="S0439">true only you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> left aren't you?</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0444">yep <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got made a <unclear>editory</unclear> person product editor</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0439">yeah I remember that though</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> in history</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s doing alright?</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0444">she is I think she hasn't been well but I haven't really seen her much recently</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0439" trans="overlap">has she not?</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0444">but I think she's in her own groove and</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0444">things are going good</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that's good</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0444">so yeah but the house where she's in they're trying to sell it</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0444">while they're still tenants they're <trunc>sti</trunc> their contract still stands</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0444">so it lasts erm them until like August but they're trying to sell the house during that so they've got people coming round</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0444"><unclear>there's that which is</unclear> a bit <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I think that's</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0444">that's causing a bit of stress but yeah and I think no I think she's good she's good</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0439" trans="overlap">she's good</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0444">erm <unclear/> I just haven't even been with it</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0444">either in work or out of the office I'm just like</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0444">no clue</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1652" who="S0444">don't know anything anymore</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0439">manic</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0444">so er yeah right shall we clear this up and then we can get to <unclear/> what time <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it is late it's half twenty to eleven</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> oh</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0439"><unclear>sorry</unclear></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
