<text id="SECU">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:43:04</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-03-22</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0326 S0329</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>fried chicken, a break in Mersea Island, Essex, sea food, fishing, family, gyms exercise, washing </topics>
		<activity>Mother and son talking over dinner at home</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, announcing, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0326">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>12</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0329">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>English</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>50</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Literary Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2>French</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0326">what did you what did you so when you went out with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0329">walked I mean it's difficult cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is a vegetarian</u>
<u n="3" who="S0326">did you have any oysters?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0329">I did <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0326">where's the other <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0329">what?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0326">where's the other <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0329">he's out with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been in in erm <unclear>Israel</unclear> and he's just come back <pause dur="short"/> have some erm bread or something if you want? <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm hungry I've been in the gym <pause dur="short"/> don't mind if I <unclear/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0326">got any chilli I can put on it? what?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0329">I don't know you know what's in this house</u>
<u n="11" who="S0326">not really?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0329">why not? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0326">what are we going to do about the fish? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0329">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0326">what?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0329"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will get it <pause dur="short"/> in that goes</u>
<u n="17" who="S0326">I like chilli</u>
<u n="18" who="S0329">mayonnaise might go</u>
<u n="19" who="S0326">I like spicy though you know? when you get it at PFC it's always spicy</u>
<u n="20" who="S0329">what?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0326">when you have it at PFC or Dixie <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0329">you don't eat that</u>
<u n="23" who="S0326">yeah I do</u>
<u n="24" who="S0329">please tell me you don't eat that</u>
<u n="25" who="S0326">I have eaten it</u>
<u n="26" who="S0329">well they coat it in something don't they? I just put these in the oven</u>
<u n="27" who="S0326">yeah they got breadcrumbs</u>
<u n="28" who="S0329">yeah the colonel's eleven mix of eleven the the secret recipe of his eleven herbs and spices <pause dur="long"/> erm okay so you went for a walk and then you said fuck this we're going to go back and have a drink and play pool so you hung around you played pool?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0326">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we were quite tired cos me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> stayed up all of Saturday</u>
<u n="30" who="S0329">what did you do when you stayed up?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0326">partied it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s birthday innit?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0329">oh <pause dur="short"/> how did you party?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0326">just went around the place you know? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0329">good wings man <pause dur="long"/> want another two?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0326">mm just one for now thank you</u>
<u n="36" who="S0329">erm <pause dur="short"/> so you were tired and you hadn't so you went to bed early?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0326">not that early</u>
<u n="38" who="S0329">what did you eat? did you eat in the pub?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0326">we went to this other pub to have a bit of food</u>
<u n="40" who="S0329">what did you what did you have?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0326">mussels</u>
<u n="42" who="S0329">what were they like?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0326">nice</u>
<u n="44" who="S0329">how did you know about it?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0326">the other pub?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0329">mm</u>
<u n="47" who="S0326">internet</u>
<u n="48" who="S0329">and what were your what how were they cooked?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0326">in some like white sauce and I think garlic I don't know like not actual white sauce coloured white sauce normal</u>
<u n="50" who="S0329">moules marinière?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0326">probably yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0329">wine and garlic and parsley and cream?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0326">yeah that kind of thing <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0329">okay and then you got up and cooked you breakfast?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0329">were there any other couples there?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0326">I don't think anybody else was staying there there was another couple like one other person there for breakfast</u>
<u n="58" who="S0329">in the pub?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0329">and what was breakfast?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0326">erm it was good actually they had smoked salmon and scrambled eggs and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got kippers she didn't know what they were so I told her to get kippers she wasn't really hungry</u>
<u n="62" who="S0329">she never had a kipper?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0326">I don't think so <pause dur="long"/> no it was just so it was just kippers it was good</u>
<u n="64" who="S0329">and then and then went off to the seaside?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0326">we went for another long walk up to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0329">mm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0326">and then back to the pub for a minute to get our stuff get <trunc>whe</trunc> our waterproofs go on the boat</u>
<u n="68" who="S0329">where did you get on the boat from?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0326">the dock the end of the pier</u>
<u n="70" who="S0329">and was it like a tourist boat?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0326">what's a tourist boat?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0329">well I mean you pay you don't mind I'll hang up my bra</u>
<u n="73" who="S0326">I like hired that boat out didn't I?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0329">you hired a whole boat?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0326">well I just saw it on the internet I said I was emailing her it's not it's not people <unclear/>her she's happy to take people out she uses that boat for fishing in the winter and in the summer she just does tours round the island of like twelve people <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0329">so you emailed her and you said</u>
<u n="77" who="S0326">I want to come fishing on Tuesday with one other person are you available?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0329">how much did that cost?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0326">thirty quid an hour</u>
<u n="80" who="S0329">fucking expensive present <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0326">it's all that recordings innit? <pause dur="long"/> the forecast was for rain but it didn't rain it got sunny</u>
<u n="82" who="S0329">what kind of boat was it?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0326">just like a little boat you know?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0329">was she a nice lady?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0326">she was really nice</u>
<u n="86" who="S0329">how old is she?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0326">young like young and pretty just like she comes from all her family is fisher fishermen and women her husband does the the sort of big deep sea fishing on a bigger boat</u>
<u n="88" who="S0329">and she said I know where to go and catch a fish</u>
<u n="89" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0329">it's funny cos she knows basically all their she <trunc>kno</trunc> she knows all of them that go that go out fishing now and they're sort of just blokes she's actually the only girl doing it and they just use the radio to sort of tell each other jokes and chit-chat and you know they <trunc>shou</trunc> they shouldn't really be doing that and like complaining about stuff they saw in the paper and asking what they were having for tea there's about like seven of them sort of dotted around the island fishing <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0329">that's so funny <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0326">when you were there were you there long enough to see the tide all the way out and all the way in?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0329">erm <pause dur="long"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then you went down to the company shed</u>
<u n="94" who="S0326">yeah actually first we went back to the pub to have another drink</u>
<u n="95" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm can you get me a bottle of my Vichy water please no out not a cold one <pause dur="long"/> darling will you open it for me? not <unclear/></u>
<u n="96" who="S0326"><unclear/><pause dur="long"/> got a lighter in Colchester Colchester's well funny Essex is funny man I <trunc>ca</trunc></u>
<u n="97" who="S0329">yeah Essex is funny</u>
<u n="98" who="S0326">everyone's everyone's friendly</u>
<u n="99" who="S0329">everyone's a criminal there we are</u>
<u n="100" who="S0326">oh cheap one anyway</u>
<u n="101" who="S0329">mm why don't you just go and get the ordinary bottle opener? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0326"><vocal desc="cough"/> <pause dur="long"/> yeah then we went to the company shed</u>
<u n="103" who="S0329">mm it's quite a big black shed is it a black little shed?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0326">it's not black</u>
<u n="105" who="S0329">but it's quite big?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0329">I remember it being black but</u>
<u n="108" who="S0326">I mean it's not that big</u>
<u n="109" who="S0329">no but I mean it's like</u>
<u n="110" who="S0326">bigger than this room</u>
<u n="111" who="S0329">yeah it's a proper kind of</u>
<u n="112" who="S0326">like the size of the cafe</u>
<u n="113" who="S0329">but there's another one which is no bigger than this kitchen wasn't that one?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="115" who="S0329">and what oysters did you have?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0326">erm I can't remember their names I only had one type though</u>
<u n="117" who="S0329">did they call were they called <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="119" who="S0329">Colchester's?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="121" who="S0329">were they big and fat?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0329">were they local?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0326">I presume so yeah <pause dur="long"/> and probably they're the nicest oysters I ever had though I think</u>
<u n="125" who="S0329">they are nicest oysters</u>
<u n="126" who="S0326">I can't really remember what the other oyster I've had tasted like</u>
<u n="127" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> were these all just briny and delicious?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0329">did you have anything else?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0326">I had some tiger prawns</u>
<u n="131" who="S0329">presumably they're not local</u>
<u n="132" who="S0326">no <vocal desc="cough"/> and some crab I had a whole crab actually <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0329">did they prepare it or did they give you a hammer and tongs? did you get anything out of it?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0326">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> knew what she was doing <pause dur="long"/> then we went back to the pub went back to the station</u>
<u n="135" who="S0329">and did you find out how old she is? <pause dur="long"/> I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> quite likes his new bedroom I however find his bedroom so much noisier than my bedroom it's like a sound tunnel</u>
<u n="136" who="S0326">well where does the noise come from?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0329">well it's aeroplanes and things like that and <trunc>re</trunc> traffic you can hear much more traffic from my room and well you don't hear people</u>
<u n="138" who="S0326">you can hear aeroplanes in my room quite loud</u>
<u n="139" who="S0329">really really loud yeah you don't hear them in the front</u>
<u n="140" who="S0326">are you switching back you run out of things to do?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0329">what?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0326">are you just going to switch them back you've run out of things to do?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0329">sip some back?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0326">switch them</u>
<u n="145" who="S0329">mm erm <pause dur="long"/> well <pause dur="short"/> I also find it quite airless and uncomfortable I'm not yeah I might have to switch them back</u>
<u n="146" who="S0326">I thought you was well into it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="sound of bell"/>
<u n="147" who="S0329"><unclear/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0326">is there anymore chicken?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0329">one little wing you can have it</u>
<u n="150" who="S0326">what it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0329">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0326">what's he saying?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0329">ah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0326">go on get your reading glasses on</u>
<u n="155" who="S0329">got the worst room in our house next year cos we took names out of a hat and I was last <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0326">he's on a bad run isn't he? <pause dur="long"/> will he live with the same people next year? <pause dur="short"/> shall I keep on talking to myself?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0329">hang on <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0326">why do you always write such long text messages? <pause dur="long"/> cos you do it with one finger <pause dur="long"/> done now?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0329">you are so cheeky</u>
<u n="160" who="S0326">I can't remember I can't remember the last time that I talked to you without you doing that for half the time</u>
<u n="161" who="S0329">now you know what it feels like</u>
<u n="162" who="S0326">I never do it when I'm talking to someone I'll wait till I'm  finished to do text messages</u>
<u n="163" who="S0329">cos that's how important you are it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> though</u>
<u n="164" who="S0326">yeah he can wait twenty minutes</u>
<u n="165" who="S0329">he's all sad</u>
<u n="166" who="S0326">is he going to live with the same people next year?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0329">he moves into a new house in June and it's from June till June</u>
<u n="168" who="S0326">is he going to live with the same people in his third year?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0329">in his third year he's going abroad for a year</u>
<u n="170" who="S0326">cos <unclear/>you just reverse it so there won't be a next time</u>
<u n="171" who="S0329">yeah but</u>
<u n="172" who="S0326">so you <unclear/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0329">I'm not sure that these people are on his course so</u>
<u n="174" who="S0326">how bad is it?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0329">I'm going to ask</u>
<u n="176" who="S0326">what did you say to him?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0329">he said we took names out of a hat and I was last and I said well if you took names out of a hat it doesn't make any difference whether you're first or last erm and he showed me pictures of all the people in his house and it's strictly body beautiful they're amazingly good looking I said it just means <unclear/>or the most beautiful person <unclear/>as compensation there's ten of them</u>
<u n="178" who="S0326">how do you get any work done if there's ten people in the house? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0329">nice salad isn't it? <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0326">what's wrong with the room then?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0329">don't know shall I ask him? don't you want me to text?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0326">I don't mind but don't write him an essay just say what's wrong with it maybe try using more than one finger <pause dur="long"/> does it have like a lounge a big sitting room? I don't know anything about</u>
<u n="183" who="S0329">all I know is that he was moving in June and we're paying rent all through summer</u>
<u n="184" who="S0326">Airbnb <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0329">so</u>
<u n="186" who="S0326">I bet he can sublet it</u>
<u n="187" who="S0329">I think a lot of them will stay they'll take a month out but <pause dur="long"/> it'll still be nice in summer you know you go to you're near <unclear/> it's down to the sea he's really near to Devon</u>
<u n="188" who="S0326">does his friends have cars? probably right?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0329">hope not did you hear about this plane crash?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0326">what plane crash?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0329">on a passenger plane crashed over the Alps killing all on board and a few British people</u>
<u n="192" who="S0326">what's this book?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0329">hands off I haven't read it yet</u>
<u n="194" who="S0326">surprising <pause dur="long"/> I didn't realise the snails that you could eat were just normal garden snails</u>
<u n="195" who="S0329">someone's pulling your leg</u>
<u n="196" who="S0326">no I was looking at a book that cook book the St John's cookbook there were all these dishes of er snails in them and it's like go and pick them yourself out the garden</u>
<u n="197" who="S0329">no</u>
<u n="198" who="S0326">I've never I've never been more sort of I can't I thought it was a joke when I was reading that whole book I read it from start to cover almost</u>
<u n="199" who="S0329">from start to cover?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0326">the back cover mainly</u>
<u n="201" who="S0329">from cover to cover do you notice something different about me tonight?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="203" who="S0329">I'm not drinking wine <pause dur="short"/> I went to the gym on the way home</u>
<u n="204" who="S0326">how was that?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0329">it was good erm I went yesterday as well basically go about three times a week now I'm going to start increasing my programme there <pause dur="short"/> I don't do very much I just do half an hour on the cross trainer</u>
<u n="206" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0329">do you think it's not enough?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0326">well you'd get more exercise walking home probably</u>
<u n="209" who="S0329">I'm sweating you think that's not enough exercise?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0326">I don't know I mean I've never been on a cross trainer</u>
<u n="211" who="S0329">it's supposed to be the best exercise</u>
<u n="212" who="S0326">I've only ever seen sort of people in film do it when they and it's always sort of elderly</u>
<u n="213" who="S0329">oh let's find out <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0326">how come I'm still hungry?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0329">what shall I ask? how good exercise is the cross trainer?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0326">you're not even doing text now are you?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0329">well <trunc>re</trunc> you said it's no good and you've only seen in on films</u>
<u n="218" who="S0326">that's what I didn't say it was no good</u>
<u n="219" who="S0329">is cross <pause dur="short"/> trainer <pause dur="long"/> scorch fact with a full body cross trainer workout there is no no there are few better all-round exercise to be <unclear/><pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0326">that's good innit?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0329">ten mistakes you're making on the cross trainer well if you're proud of yourself for making it to the gym <pause dur="long"/> make sure that you're using enough resistance you shouldn't feel like you have even five minutes left in you when you step off she says you're a <trunc>sl</trunc> stand up straight that's interesting <pause dur="short"/> don't enter your information most machines are calibrated for a hundred <unclear/> person aim to burn around a hundred calories in ten minutes you don't change directions going backwards doesn't just stop you from <unclear/> it also changes <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0326">what is this kind of food?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0329">coriander seeds <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0326">what else can you do at the gym? weights</u>
<u n="225" who="S0329">I can't do anything cos of my arm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0326">rowing <pause dur="short"/> do you have an instructor?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0329">no</u>
<u n="228" who="S0326">stairmaster?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0329">okay that's interesting <pause dur="long"/> that's interesting as far as I'm concerned benefits of a cross trainer</u>
<u n="230" who="S0326"><vocal desc="cough"/> hello</u>
<u n="231" who="S0329">yes hello sorry sorry I've got a life</u>
<u n="232" who="S0326">what you've got a life reading about cross trainers on your Iphone while you're trying to have dinner with your son?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0329">what is it about my children they're so demanding</u>
<u n="234" who="S0326">not demanding but you know like I'm not like sort of like this on my phone</u>
<u n="235" who="S0329">I'll talk to you</u>
<u n="236" who="S0326">alright then</u>
<u n="237" who="S0329">yes I agree you're right <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0326">but also if I'm sitting there I'm just bored you know?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0329">oh I'm frightfully sorry that you're bored and now it's time to do the tidying up with your mummy</u>
<u n="240" who="S0326" trans="overlap">but I yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0329">I'm going to light the fire and I'm going to read how do you feel about that?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0326">I don't mind we were just meant to be having dinner innit?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0329">oh my days oh my days <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="long"/> we could have tea and chocolate</u>
<u n="244" who="S0326">what?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0329">we could have tea and chocolate if you weren't so grumpy</u>
<u n="246" who="S0326">I can't have that anyway</u>
<u n="247" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's just a threat well first of all you've got to light the fire you've gotta tidy up and light the fire if you tidy up with me you'll learn some lessons about how to actually tidy up</u>
<u n="248" who="S0326">I know how to tidy up</u>
<u n="249" who="S0329">I don't think so <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/>is serious block of chocolate junkie and once a bar is open every time I open the fridge there's just a little bit more gone no darling</u>
<u n="250" who="S0326">why not?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0329">because it's there's not enough to justify it</u>
<u n="252" who="S0326">there is enough to justify it</u>
<u n="253" who="S0329">wash it up</u>
<u n="254" who="S0326">no you wash it up</u>
<u n="255" who="S0329">no you wash it up</u>
<u n="256" who="S0326">you wash it up I'll put it in the dish washer</u>
<u n="257" who="S0329">you wash it up we can have orange and chocolate after that and tea</u>
<u n="258" who="S0326">I'll do the rest you wash it up</u>
<u n="259" who="S0329">no darling you don't know how to wash it up wash it up</u>
<u n="260" who="S0326">why can't I put it in the dishwasher?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0329">wash it up when I got a dishwasher <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to me you know that is the end of family life and she was right</u>
<u n="262" who="S0326">what do you mean that's the end of family life?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0329">well she was really shocked she said it's really important that your children learn how to do the washing</u>
<u n="264" who="S0326">yeah I learned that's how I mean I'm good at washing up and I do it all the time cos I'm a <unclear/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0329">you have become a lot better at it I do think so</u>
<u n="266" who="S0326">I'm better than you at it</u>
<u n="267" who="S0329">no I'm good at washing up you're better than <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he is a very superficial washer upper he has to be fed <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0326">where did you go with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to the restaurant?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0329">oh I don't know where they've gone</u>
<u n="270" who="S0326">it's</u>
<u n="271" who="S0329">they will have gone probably tomorrow or somewhere he gets he goes out classy places <unclear/> he's taken me out anywhere erm can that be true? I might challenge him on it</u>
<u n="272" who="S0326">did he sell paintings?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0329">no</u>
<u n="274" who="S0326"><unclear/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0329">he inherited it no I mean he made it out of property and I don't know put the things in there he has earnt money in his time but not really from painting <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0326">money <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> has he shown his paintings?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0329">well he hasn't got a gallery erm he has shown them and I think that as he moves into this next phase of his life it's perfectly possible that he might he might properly you know he's not an artist like they have the an artist's career in the way that erm granny and grandad have had but that's only one way to have an art artist's career erm he's not he's basically not doing the he needs success he just does it because he's compelled he only went to art school he went to art school in Edinburgh which was very you know <unclear/>and serious course <pause dur="long"/> and he paints most days and he's got a studio so you know it's all a serious operation <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0326">again</u>
<u n="279" who="S0329">I'm so sorry I just had to er I'll get that <unclear/> cup of tea</u>
<u n="280" who="S0326">what kind of chocolate you have?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0329">oh it's orange Green and Black's dark <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0326">we need to get a better sort of drying system <unclear/> washing up</u>
<u n="283" who="S0329">well you know what I'm what I'm going to try and get?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0326" trans="overlap">cos you can start drying now</u>
<u n="285" who="S0329"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to do erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <unclear/> when he comes back I want</u>
<u n="286" who="S0326">I thought you weren't going to use him anymore?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0329">why did you think that?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0326">I don't know I thought you said that</u>
<u n="289" who="S0329">I don't know erm I'd like to move the kitchen sink to move this whole unit up so that we can put the drying rack on the wall so we have more space the other side of the sink the same you ask the question and I have an answer</u>
<u n="290" who="S0326">am I meant to get this picture?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0329">it's at the hotel you need to look there's more there get rid of it</u>
<u n="292" who="S0326">these things these things don't need to be cleaned man these ones</u>
<u n="293" who="S0329">I don't know where you came up with that idea <pause dur="short"/> one of my big secrets of how to where to put things is they make some kind of Russian art <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0326">can you pass me my drink please? I'll fill it up <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0329">oh listen one of my glasses yet another one smashed in here</u>
<u n="296" who="S0326">in where?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0329">in the dryer and that will be because you did something like this okay? this is a glass</u>
<u n="298" who="S0326">I didn't smash it though</u>
<u n="299" who="S0329">no but I but I watched you just push that bottle rationale use the common sense darling</u>
<u n="300" who="S0326">why don't you dry up?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0329">why don't you learn a bit of <unclear/> about my glasses <unclear/>? I think you should say sorry mum I will do better</u>
<u n="302" who="S0326">well there's still not enough room for it where am I going to put that?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0329">well the thing is if you if you didn't pull <unclear/>my darling</u>
<u n="304" who="S0326">even if so where will I put that one?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0329">well there's plenty of space there's the whole there's that whole area if you employ a <unclear/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0326">I'm trying to wash up I'm not trying to do a puzzle</u>
<u n="307" who="S0329">okay</u>
<u n="308" who="S0326">have you been to that restaurant in <anon type="place"/> called <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0329">called what?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0326"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0329">no never heard of it</u>
<u n="312" who="S0326">or <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0329">no I don't know that darling why?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0326">I dunno I just wondered</u>
<u n="315" who="S0329">what what it is what kind of?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0326">well it's next to the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0329">oh yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0326">you know that new sort of smart looking thing next to the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0329">yes I have seen it yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0326">why don't we use your rational skills to for somewhere to put this?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0329">why don't you just fill it up with water and chuck it all over the floor <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> is there enough water in that kettle?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0326">I don't know I'm using it to soak that thing</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
