<text id="SEDD">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:12:56</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0324 S0325</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANONs house</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>School</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about school </activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, announcing, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T04</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0324">
				<exactage>14</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>14</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0325">
				<exactage>13</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>9</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Japanese -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0325">basically I was in French by myself because we were really early from assembly and I was sat there</u>
<u n="2" who="S0324">in the mobile?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0325">yeah and there was two classrooms</u>
<u n="4" who="S0324" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="5" who="S0325">and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came in there and she was like like that and I was like hi</u>
<u n="6" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0325">cos I don't like waving to people</u>
<u n="8" who="S0324">what was she in the class opposite?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0325">I think so but she was standing in like the little lobby bit with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0324" trans="overlap">what were you just sitting down on your own? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0325">well no because like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were sat over there and there was like me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on this table</u>
<u n="12" who="S0324" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="13" who="S0325">and then I was just looking at the door and she was there and I was like she was like <vocal desc="misc"/> and I was like and I was just calm <unclear/> wave at me like one time I was walking to school and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> waved at me and I didn't wave back</u>
<u n="14" who="S0324"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0325" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0324">oh</u>
<u n="17" who="S0325">she waved at me and I was just like mm and she sort of smiled and but we were on the other side of the street so it's really awkward it wasn't really like waving distance cos you know when you're really close to someone</u>
<u n="18" who="S0324" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0325">and you wave?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0324">and when it's really far away you can't tell if they're waving at you</u>
<u n="21" who="S0325">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0324">or someone else in your direction</u>
<u n="23" who="S0325">and that's really depressing when they're waving at someone behind you and you're like</u>
<u n="24" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0324">you turn around mm <pause dur="short"/> mm when we talk in maths and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> always thinks that you're talking to him</u>
<u n="26" who="S0325">yeah he's like what? and I'm like not talking to you</u>
<u n="27" who="S0324">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0325">yeah but I don't understand because I'm not actually looking at him like he's there and I'm looking past him like he can't he see that cos if I was talking to you and I just kind of started yeah so how how do you <vocal desc="laugh"/> like isn't that just weird?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0324" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0325">I don't understand</u>
<u n="31" who="S0324">cos you're not even looking at him</u>
<u n="32" who="S0325">and I'm not having a conversation that I would be I'm like yeah hi and he's like I didn't say anything and I'm like yes cos cos I'm not talking to you I'm talking past you and then everyone on that table is like what?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0324">I really didn't get that thing in maths when she was saying that the exact dancer thing she's so annoying</u>
<u n="34" who="S0325">I know and then she was like I really don't understand why I bother teaching half the people in here and I was like ha ha</u>
<u n="35" who="S0324" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="36" who="S0325">she always says this to me cos I'm just sitting there</u>
<u n="37" who="S0324" trans="overlap">then don't be a teacher</u>
<u n="38" who="S0325">and I'm just like ha ha ha ha</u>
<u n="39" who="S0324">she's so annoying</u>
<u n="40" who="S0325">and then I'm like and then she's like about to tell everyone off and I'm like Miss can I just can I just go to the toilet now?</u>
<u n="41" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0325">cos she was like I was like can I go to the toilet? and she was like no I was like why? and she was like well you've just had the whole of lunch and I was like yeah but I didn't need to go at lunch and she was like what so you've just had the sudden urge to go when you were walking up here? and I was like yeah and then she was like oh as I was sitting there doing that sheet I was like I really need a wee</u>
<u n="43" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0325">and then I finished and I was like Miss I'm finished can I go? and then you didn't even notice me leave</u>
<u n="45" who="S0324">yeah sorry</u>
<u n="46" who="S0325">I walked right past you I looked at you and you were just like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> oh my god you're sitting in front of me</u>
<u n="47" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0325">and I was just like oh alright then</u>
<u n="49" who="S0324">yeah probably cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is so funny</u>
<u n="50" who="S0325">oh my gosh and then today in English she goes I can't read like well yeah you're the one that said that you read like half a page in nine seconds so like that would never happen and she literally went</u>
<u n="51" who="S0324">yeah and then how it goes seven eight nine ten eleven</u>
<u n="52" who="S0325" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0324">seconds</u>
<u n="54" who="S0325">and then like ten nine eight seven and I'm like what?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0324">how can you read that fast? you can't read that fast</u>
<u n="56" who="S0325">exactly</u>
<u n="57" who="S0324">that's stupid</u>
<u n="58" who="S0325">and she goes oh yeah well basically if I get my phone taken off me I'm gonna just give them the old phone cos she didn't even</u>
<u n="59" who="S0324">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0325">like she didn't even <unclear/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0324" trans="overlap">like she chickened out just shove it in my pocket</u>
<u n="62" who="S0325" trans="overlap">because what I would have done is put it in my pocket and she'd be like no give it</u>
<u n="63" who="S0324">and be like give me a go</u>
<u n="64" who="S0325">and be like fine then and give her the old one like what's the point of just being like cos if she's like give it to me then she could just be like like that and then she'd be like give it to me and then you'd be like</u>
<u n="65" who="S0324">yeah and then give the old phone that that's really a good idea</u>
<u n="66" who="S0325">that is a good idea</u>
<u n="67" who="S0324">if you actually do it yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0325">but then what if they see like you that you've got an Iphone six and you hand over an Iphone four?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0324">mm don't wanna <unclear/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0325">that's not</u>
<u n="71" who="S0324"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0325">and then but my Iphone four is dead maybe I should just bring my Iphone four to school? yeah but I completely forgot we weren't allowed to use it like in between lessons</u>
<u n="73" who="S0324">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0325">and so she was like <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> you put your phone away and she completely seen me but she didn't know my name so I was just like alright then</u>
<u n="75" who="S0324" trans="overlap">well why does yeah why does she always know my name why does she always call me <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0325">yeah it's cos you're like the famous <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> the maths girl</u>
<u n="77" who="S0324">yeah she doesn't know</u>
<u n="78" who="S0325">no I'm sure she does cos I'm sure all the teachers were in a room and they were like hurray for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> distinction</u>
<u n="79" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0324" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0325" trans="overlap">and I'm sure it was cos I'm sure they were all like <event desc="sound of clap"/> clapping it was like well we were all cheering for you and I'm like what in the staffroom?</u>
<u n="82" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0324">so embarrassing</u>
<u n="84" who="S0325">and like every teacher came up to you and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> was like here's your class paper</u>
<u n="85" who="S0324" trans="overlap">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> all she had said like how was I supposed to know that I did well on that?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0325" trans="overlap">yeah they were like well done in the maths and you were like</u>
<u n="87" who="S0324" trans="overlap">because I was like because it was like twenty out of fifty and it was like how is that good?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0325">yeah cos she just goes your results well done</u>
<u n="89" who="S0324">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0325">and then I was like congratulations and you were like er what? and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> was like</u>
<u n="91" who="S0324" trans="overlap">I was like I got twenty</u>
<u n="92" who="S0325" trans="overlap">so you know you got a distinction? and you were like actually no and every time <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> comes up to you I'm next to you standing there really awkwardly like I actually am in top set maths</u>
<u n="93" who="S0324">I need to get <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> email do you know what it is?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0325">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0324">what?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0325"><anon type="email"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0324">oh okay cos my dad needs to email him <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0325">well I think it's <anon type="email"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0324" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0325">his name is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0324">I think so but I don't know</u>
<u n="102" who="S0325" trans="overlap">and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0324">how do you spell <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> though?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0325"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0324">mm maybe</u>
<u n="106" who="S0325"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0324">it's quite a hard one for spelling</u>
<u n="108" who="S0325">today in French <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> was trying to make us all cos basically because we've got speaking controlled</u>
<u n="109" who="S0324" trans="overlap">do you want some more water?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0325">erm yes please cos we've got speaking controlled assessment in like a month she was like so guys we need to</u>
<u n="111" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0325">we need to practise <pause dur="short"/> you need to practise your pronunciation and she was like right okay everyone after me and she said the sentence and</u>
<u n="113" who="S0324" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0325">nobody said anything and we were all just like</u>
<u n="115" who="S0324">mm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0325">and she was like the silence is deafening</u>
<u n="117" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0325">and we were like and she was like come on guys you're not gonna get better unless you open your mouths and we were all like</u>
<u n="119" who="S0324"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0325">and she was like</u>
<u n="121" who="S0324">like <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0325">yeah and she goes</u>
<u n="123" who="S0324">open your mouth</u>
<u n="124" who="S0325">right okay come on <foreign lang="fre">je me</foreign> and we were all like je mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and she's like <foreign lang="fre">dispu depuis</foreign> or whatever it is <unclear/> and we're like dispu and she's like and then she comes up to me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos I was standing next to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like writing this thing and she goes</u>
<u n="125" who="S0324" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0325">this one's a bit tricky this word right okay ready repeat after me and she made us just us two like repeat this word and she was like <foreign lang="fre">corvee en Normand</foreign> or whatever it was and we were just like corvee <unclear/> and she was like perfect like thanks</u>
<u n="127" who="S0324">I'm so glad we don't have to do that in Spanish I literally have no idea how to pronounce anything in Spanish</u>
<u n="128" who="S0325">neither do I in French it's really hard she's like hah like the lady outside was like erm <foreign lang="fre">peron</foreign> and I was like parent and she was like <foreign lang="fre">peron</foreign> and I was like parent and she was like no parent and I was like hah on</u>
<u n="129" who="S0324" trans="overlap">is that the lady with the short hair?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0325">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0324">she's really annoying</u>
<u n="132" who="S0325">and then she goes to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she goes very good <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> very good cos it was really awkward cos we had to go out in pairs and me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were there and she and she was like very good <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0324" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> good as in <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0325"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> yeah and and then she was just like to me she was like</u>
<u n="135" who="S0324" trans="overlap">actually there's no other <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> any more is there?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0325">no she was goes to me she asked me she goes what do your parents do? and I go oh yeah my mum works in a library my dad is a teacher</u>
<u n="137" who="S0324" trans="overlap">is this in French or English?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0325" trans="overlap">yeah and she goes what school does he teach in? in French</u>
<u n="139" who="S0324">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0325">and I go oh he doesn't teach in a school like in English and she goes well just make it up and I was like oh okay and then afterwards she goes you need to be able to understand the question I was like I did understand the question I said he doesn't teach in a school and she was like yeah but you don't understand the question and I was like no no I did understand the question and she was like you need to be able to understand the question but I I understood the question</u>
<u n="141" who="S0324">what so you said he was a teacher and she?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0325">she goes what school? and I go he doesn't teach at any schools and she goes well just understand the question answer the question and I'm like what? but she but she's kinda hard to understand cos her English isn't that great and she's just like I'm</u>
<u n="143" who="S0324" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0325">I'm confusing for you now and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like what?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0324">what?</u>
<u n="146" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0324">we need to go in five minutes yay lucky you actually</u>
<u n="148" who="S0325" trans="overlap">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s not even coming though</u>
<u n="149" who="S0324">seven minutes</u>
<u n="150" who="S0325">I'm just gonna have an hour lesson by myself actually that was probably</u>
<u n="151" who="S0324">did you manage to find <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0325">well you did tell me to tell her</u>
<u n="153" who="S0324" trans="overlap">were you supposed to?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0325">oh right <unclear/> and she's not gonna be checking her emails nobody checks their emails like he emails <unclear/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0324" trans="overlap">but I can remember that one time when I checked my emails and there was that my old buddy in year seven? she was like oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do you remember me? and then I replied and then she replied back</u>
<u n="156" who="S0325">and then did you reply back after that?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0324">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0325">and then did she reply after that?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0324">I don't know I haven't check my emails</u>
<u n="160" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0325">well the one time he emailed you was like well cos I turned up for my lesson and he wasn't there and then like</u>
<u n="162" who="S0324" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0325">three months later in business I checked my emails and it was like dear parents to my email address dear parents I'm very sorry to say that I've broken my leg so there'll be no lessons this week</u>
<u n="164" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0324">has he got hold of your parents' email?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0325">yeah he has my parents' email like</u>
<u n="167" who="S0324">tell him to tell him today that you never check your emails and then <unclear/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0325" trans="overlap">but he just but he never sends emails he never sends us emails it was lucky I had my clarinet and he's like sorry I can't do tomorrow</u>
<u n="169" who="S0324">why did you bring your clarinet?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0325">I just left it yesterday cos I had to use it today</u>
<u n="171" who="S0324" trans="overlap">did you not need to practise?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0325">I did think about that when I got home cos I was gonna get my old clarinet out and then I was like no I can't be bothered</u>
<u n="173" who="S0324">have you even actually practised this week?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0325">I practised on Sunday</u>
<u n="175" who="S0324">and was that it?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0325">well yeah because I couldn't practise Monday morning took it to jazz band</u>
<u n="177" who="S0324">yeah but what about Thursday Friday Saturday Sunday?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0325">what of last week?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0324">yeah well like between last Wednesday and today?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0325">I have practised but not my scales cos scales are boring</u>
<u n="181" who="S0324" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0325">and I don't practise them I just wing it like he goes right okay so you really the scales need to be your the main focus of your practise this week and I go okay and then just play loads of pieces that he doesn't even want me to play like this one piece I could never play and we gave up on it cos he was like no you can't play this in your grade you're not good enough and I still play it I keep playing it and I'm just like yeah you know</u>
<u n="183" who="S0324" trans="overlap">but not your piece that you're supposed to play on your own?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0325">no I mean I've played all of that and but then he goes one like literally I played my the really long piece probably the worst I've ever played it like I used to be able to play it really well last week</u>
<u n="185" who="S0324" trans="overlap">oh that's the same with mine my like the more you practise</u>
<u n="186" who="S0325" trans="overlap">as I practise I get worse yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0324">the worse you get and it just sounds really sloppy and like</u>
<u n="188" who="S0325" trans="overlap">yeah and cos I had a tough reed on I had to take a breath like every bar and probably the worst I've ever played it in my life and then he goes yeah that was really good and I was like</u>
<u n="189" who="S0324">really?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0325">really? so I'd rather he'd be more honest with me and be like look yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0324" trans="overlap">it probably was really good</u>
<u n="192" who="S0325">no but it wasn't like I literally had to take a breath every bar and I had to restart it like three times</u>
<u n="193" who="S0324" trans="overlap">well it's a good job you don't have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who always shouts at you when you take a breath or when you don't take a breath like last lesson she I didn't take a breath</u>
<u n="194" who="S0325" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0324">and then she shouted at me for not taking breaths and then I took a breath and she was like you have to stop taking breaths there</u>
<u n="196" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0324">you've just told me I had to <unclear/></u>
<u n="198" who="S0325">what's the time?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0324">I don't know erm fifty-one</u>
<u n="200" who="S0325" trans="overlap">I should probably go</u>
<u n="201" who="S0324">minutes past fifty oh right yeah do you want to go?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0325">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0324">bye</u>
<u n="204" who="S0325">bye</u>
<u n="205" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
