<text id="SEFQ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:28:25</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-10-29</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0511 S0513</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Dining room at home, Bury St Edmunds, Suffolk</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Cooking, baked Alaska, grating cheese, Halloween party, recruiting, memories, discrimination, age of consent.</topics>
		<activity>Supper with the boys</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, Explaining, Inquiring, Anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0511">
				<exactage>43</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Bury St Edmunds</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>11 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Programme Director</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- limited; Spanish -- limited; Swahili -- limited</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0513">
				<exactage>14</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>R.P.</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Bury St Edmunds</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>11 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>German -- conversational</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0511">no not now we're not gonna rush <trunc>g</trunc> watch a film now we're having supper there is that recording? yeah</u>
<u n="2" who="S0513">yeah <unclear>probably</unclear></u>
<u n="3" who="S0511">erm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0513" trans="overlap">it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0511">so guess what I just discovered? well I I've <trunc>remem</trunc> I discovered last time I was away I've just rediscovered it erm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0513" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="7" who="S0511" trans="overlap">erm <foreign lang="fre">omelette en surprise</foreign></u>
<u n="8" who="S0513">omelette surprise what's that? omelette with omelettes on top?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0511">no that's like a proper French term for <pause dur="short"/> it's quite clever <pause dur="short"/> <foreign lang="fre">omelette en surprise</foreign> <pause dur="short"/> are you going to guess?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0513">it means omelette on surprise</u>
<u n="11" who="S0511">yes it's baked Alaska</u>
<u n="12" who="S0513">er and you plan to attempt to bake baked Alaska?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0511">no I don't plan to try and make it no</u>
<u n="14" who="S0513" trans="overlap">oh good that's good</u>
<u n="15" who="S0511">no I'm just</u>
<u n="16" who="S0513"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0511">telling you what it was called</u>
<u n="18" who="S0513">gonna try <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0511">there was <trunc>w</trunc> I just thought there was one in the Co-op in the freezer section one day in the summer and then it wasn't there the next day so I'm er I dunno how though it would work I just don't understand how it could be in the freezer really but anyway cos it has to be hot on the outside</u>
<u n="20" who="S0513">well maybe you warm it up</u>
<u n="21" who="S0511">yeah but <trunc>y</trunc> well yeah but how do you do that without the ice cream melting? well I suppose that is the whole the whole issue with <foreign lang="fre">omelette en surprise</foreign> like I might actually try and cook it soon so that I have the opportunity to say <foreign lang="fre">omelette en surprise</foreign> anyway</u>
<u n="22" who="S0513">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0511">granny used to make it when we were children it was uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s favourite you know birthdays and stuff not just</u>
<u n="24" who="S0513" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0511">anyhow it was like do you want <unclear>pie</unclear> with that?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0513">yes please can I <unclear/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0511" trans="overlap">do you wanna get it out of the fridge then?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0513">yeah okay yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0511">okay the er <pause dur="long"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0513">mm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0511">mm <pause dur="short"/> so what else have you been up to this last couple of days while you've been away?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0513">homework</u>
<u n="33" who="S0511">I can't believe you've really been doing that much homework</u>
<u n="34" who="S0513">yeah I've been doing quite a lot and erm I didn't really wake up <pause dur="short"/> yesterday</u>
<u n="35" who="S0511">what all day?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0513">pretty much and then <pause dur="short"/> erm I was at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="37" who="S0511">working</u>
<u n="38" who="S0513">er erm but</u>
<u n="39" who="S0511">was what time did you start when you went to work?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0513">half ten</u>
<u n="41" who="S0511">okay so it wasn't like a nine o'clock start <vocal desc="laugh"/> or anything? okay</u>
<u n="42" who="S0513">and then erm I was <unclear/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0511">mm oh oops <pause dur="short"/> did they need <unclear>Allen keys</unclear>? <event desc="sound of grating"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0511">that's probably enough</u>
<u n="45" who="S0513"><unclear>I don't know</unclear></u>
<u n="46" who="S0511">you need to get you push it harder <event desc="sound of grating"/> no you're pushing it harder but in the wrong direction you're pushing it harder when it's going that way <event desc="sound of grating"/> when I was at my clinic thing</u>
<u n="47" who="S0513">uhu</u>
<u n="48" who="S0511">there was this cookie demonstration erm in this special room and</u>
<u n="49" who="S0513" trans="overlap"><unclear/> there's like bars on the windows <unclear>so we couldn't get in</unclear></u>
<u n="50" who="S0511">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> no no we were in <vocal desc="laugh"/> thank you erm and there was erm so she was there and she had all this like posh kit and then there were <trunc>s</trunc> cameras like above her so you could actually see what she was doing and then a screen showing what she was doing and things</u>
<u n="51" who="S0513">yeah we have that in art</u>
<u n="52" who="S0511">sorry?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0513">we have that in art</u>
<u n="54" who="S0511">have that in art?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0513">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0511">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0513">mm we have that in art</u>
<u n="58" who="S0511">what a screen so you can see what the teacher's doing?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0513">well they've got a camera above the work</u>
<u n="60" who="S0511" trans="overlap">really? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0513">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0511">I find that quite surprising don't look at me like I'm from Mars <vocal desc="laugh"/> what</u>
<u n="63" who="S0513" trans="overlap">like was at <anon type="place"/> in our <unclear>like er</unclear> so</u>
<u n="64" who="S0511">across but er if I <trunc>w</trunc> so you can see what the <trunc>a</trunc> teacher's doing but surely the teacher I dunno when I was at school they used to do it vertically on the wall</u>
<u n="65" who="S0513">mm it's quite hard <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0511">well I dunno artists in films are always doing things on the easel kind of vertically</u>
<u n="67" who="S0513">they're not vertical</u>
<u n="68" who="S0511">well no but uprightish well I dunno schools these days <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="long"/> erm have you seen <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at all?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0513">erm no no I have actually yeah I did</u>
<u n="70" who="S0511">is doing anything over half-term is she away or anything?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0513">mm she's having a Halloween party but we're at going in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s aren't we?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0511">no</u>
<u n="73" who="S0513">aren't we?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0511">well we were never due to be at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s actually</u>
<u n="75" who="S0513">well who said we were going for dinner then?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0511">no we were due to have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> here</u>
<u n="77" who="S0513">oh right</u>
<u n="78" who="S0511">did you want to go to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s then?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0513">yeah it would be nice but you can't really pick me up there so</u>
<u n="80" who="S0511">why not?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0513">cos you'll be asleep</u>
<u n="82" who="S0511">I think I can stay up as late as your party needs to go on for</u>
<u n="83" who="S0513">mm wanna pick me up at midnight?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0511">yeah if you want</u>
<u n="85" who="S0513">mm okay</u>
<u n="86" who="S0511">but that will mean I'm left here with you know hordes of marauding trick-or-treaters</u>
<u n="87" who="S0513">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0511"><vocal desc="laugh"/> thanks for that knocking at the door</u>
<u n="89" who="S0513"><unclear/> but I mean</u>
<u n="90" who="S0511">yes yeah well you'll <trunc>w</trunc> get the yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0513">to</u>
<u n="92" who="S0511">yeah cos I thought Halloween was Friday but actually it's Saturday <pause dur="long"/> is her is it her mum and dad having a party or is just her so to speak?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0513">erm her I think</u>
<u n="94" who="S0511">well you could definitely go to it</u>
<u n="95" who="S0513">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0511">is it fancy dress? <pause dur="short"/> gotta say yes say yes say yes</u>
<u n="97" who="S0513">no even if it was I wouldn't be wearing a pumpkin</u>
<u n="98" who="S0511">can I get all the Halloween stuff out of the loft?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0513">mm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0511">like festoon you in it</u>
<u n="101" who="S0513">if you feel the need</u>
<u n="102" who="S0511"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no mm now that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and mm isn't coming I'm not I don't feel very Halloweeny now all of a sudden I don't know if I can really be bothered for and particularly if you're going to be out we might turn like the lights off and ignore the doorbell</u>
<u n="103" who="S0513"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="104" who="S0511">or is that just really crap? like it's I mean <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> but anyway luvvy even if we had been planning to go to <unclear>granny</unclear> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s thing you can always say that you want to do something different and we can say yes or no</u>
<u n="105" who="S0513">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0511">obviously but that was why <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was only bringing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s going to a party and and apparently it was this really important party and if she missed this party then you know the world would just about end or whatever <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> I mean clearly if there are other people also going in <anon type="place"/> it would make sense for some lift sharing to happen</u>
<u n="107" who="S0513">I don't know any all <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friends</u>
<u n="108" who="S0511">oh cos you don't know her friends right?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0513">well I do but well</u>
<u n="110" who="S0511">yeah but not yeah not not <trunc>y</trunc> it's not like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and whatnot <pause dur="short"/> fine fine <pause dur="short"/> you get the details and we'll do it</u>
<u n="111" who="S0513">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0511">hell worst case scenario I can always just give you the money for a taxi you know?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0513">that will cost you like a lot</u>
<u n="114" who="S0511">taxis in <anon type="place"/> don't cost a lot</u>
<u n="115" who="S0513">I could walk from and get the bus</u>
<u n="116" who="S0511">sorry?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0513">and the bus probably doesn't run at night</u>
<u n="118" who="S0511">mm <pause dur="short"/> you can't walk home from <anon type="place"/> at midnight <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0513">it's <anon type="place"/> it's not <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0511">yeah but that's like eight miles away or something <vocal desc="laugh"/> no don't be ridiculous I'll <trunc>c</trunc> I'll pick you up this is my job <pause dur="long"/> but you must find out the score on with what you're supposed to take et cetera</u>
<u n="121" who="S0513">what would I be supposed to take?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0511">when I go to parties which obviously are a regular occurrence I take a bottle of wine</u>
<u n="123" who="S0513">er mm I doubt that would go down very well with her parents</u>
<u n="124" who="S0511">yeah so you might take I dunno I've got a few pumpkins</u>
<u n="125" who="S0513"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0511">well I dunno crisps you well you could take like you know a Coke or whatever</u>
<u n="127" who="S0513">I suppose</u>
<u n="128" who="S0511">anyway you speak to her about it <pause dur="short"/> well I tell you what actually if you're gonna be out on Saturday and I'm here then maybe erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I will go to erm the James Bond film</u>
<u n="129" who="S0513">it's not very good</u>
<u n="130" who="S0511">I know you said it wasn't very good and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was just saying it wasn't very good I think that you must have adopted your it's not very good from him or vice versa the reviews</u>
<u n="131" who="S0513" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="132" who="S0511">are saying it's the best one in years</u>
<u n="133" who="S0513">I didn't really understand what was going on</u>
<u n="134" who="S0511">mm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0513" trans="overlap">well you have to have you have to watched the last three like recently to understand <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0511">what the storyline isn't self-contained?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0513">no which I thought was a bit shitty but you know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0511">oh that's surprising yeah well I never understand what's going on though so it would you know make no difference to me at all</u>
<u n="139" who="S0513">you don't even understand what's going on in James Bond? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0511">no they're just jumping from roof to roof and there's a baddy normally</u>
<u n="141" who="S0513"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said the stunts weren't very impressive which I thought</u>
<u n="142" who="S0511" trans="overlap">I mean</u>
<u n="143" who="S0513" trans="overlap">was odd <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0511">when I saw <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the other <trunc>d</trunc> that's er he said that it was just a bit subdued</u>
<u n="145" who="S0513"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0511">a bit trying to be sophisticated not not over-the-top enough</u>
<u n="147" who="S0513">yeah it was <trunc>m</trunc> exactly Roger Moore an aeroplane flew through a building but then it it didn't like keep on flying and I thought that was shite <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0511">but it flew through the building what and then what?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0513" trans="overlap">and and then it crashed <vocal desc="laugh"/> rather than continuing flying which is</u>
<u n="150" who="S0511" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I read erm something in the paper about erm there's a scene where they're going up the river in London in the night</u>
<u n="151" who="S0513">uhu</u>
<u n="152" who="S0511">yeah and <trunc>h</trunc> just how <unclear/> to film that scene is quite difficult cos they really it's not all CGI'd or whatever they actually filmed that scene</u>
<u n="153" who="S0513">what?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0511">at night</u>
<u n="155" who="S0513" trans="overlap">going up a river</u>
<u n="156" who="S0511" trans="overlap">in London</u>
<u n="157" who="S0513" trans="overlap">in a boat?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0511">in the dark and there was helicopters over it or something</u>
<u n="159" who="S0513">no I don't think a helicopter over London isn't that difficult</u>
<u n="160" who="S0511">well how do you know? because you can't you're not allowed to fly things over London you have to get like special dispensation obviously</u>
<u n="161" who="S0513">they had to close a bridge and then</u>
<u n="162" who="S0511" trans="overlap">yeah and you have to get all the residents to agree well I don't suppose you have to get them all to agree</u>
<u n="163" who="S0513">yeah I doubt they</u>
<u n="164" who="S0511" trans="overlap">but there are the some of the er</u>
<u n="165" who="S0513" trans="overlap">they were just driving a boat</u>
<u n="166" who="S0511">well well it was in the paper</u>
<u n="167" who="S0513" trans="overlap">er</u>
<u n="168" who="S0511">all about it <pause dur="short"/> and I read a thing the other day about</u>
<u n="169" who="S0513" trans="overlap">what did they actually crash a helicopter into London Bridge? I doubt it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0511">that seems unlikely <pause dur="short"/> erm I read the other day about one of these posh squares in London that's often used for erm like period dramas and stuff</u>
<u n="171" who="S0513">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0511">and how er</u>
<u n="173" who="S0513" trans="overlap"><unclear>yeah do you wanna get</unclear></u>
<u n="174" who="S0511" trans="overlap">how they're like the the residents there are just completely fed up with it and the erm cos the council charge the film companies or whatever so they're happy for it to happen again and again and again but the people who live there are obviously getting irritated</u>
<u n="175" who="S0513">I'm not sure why you'd be that irritated it's not like there are many like explosions or pyrotechnics with period dramas</u>
<u n="176" who="S0511">no but those squares they're such a the <trunc>gr</trunc> the parky bit in middle in those posh ones are sort of private so you couldn't go there because there was well the they the one they objected to was like a fashion show part of London Fashion Week there's gonna be a big tent in their garden</u>
<u n="177" who="S0513">oh no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0511">for two weeks well if somebody said I'm putting that up in my garden for two weeks I'd be pissed off</u>
<u n="179" who="S0513">yeah but you wouldn't like stop them they're just posh <unclear/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0511">yeah I'm I'm I'm not defending rich people darling don't get the wrong end of the stick <pause dur="short"/> right so this week er since I last saw you er my administrator who I've only had for three months and who's become ill and she was going she's gone in for an operation to the hospital she's quite badly ill actually <pause dur="short"/> er then announced on the day her last day before going in for the hospital that she was resigning <pause dur="short"/> and not coming back</u>
<u n="181" who="S0513">yeah so</u>
<u n="182" who="S0511" trans="overlap">so well that's quite inconvenient <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0513">if she's an administrator you should do it yourself <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0511">well I haven't got the time but <trunc>ye</trunc> you've got to find erm it's a question of how quick you can get somebody in because er people in other jobs have got to give four weeks' notice and you have to advertise and then interview them so that takes two weeks and then they've got to give their notice or whatever whatever whatever</u>
<u n="185" who="S0513">there are quite a lot of unemployed people in Britain</u>
<u n="186" who="S0511">there are quite a lot of unemployed people in Britain you're right and they have just been doing some advertising for some receptionist at my in the building I work in so I looked at these CVs cos it's just an administrative post like you say and luckily I didn't lead to look at most of the CVs cos in the covering email I could tell that they were illiterate and like the the my administrator sends you know emails to like proper people the she needs to use a capital I when she says I you know</u>
<u n="187" who="S0513"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0511">er mm <pause dur="short"/> but so what happened was about I've been quite patient with this administrator and it's not her fault she got ill but I have gone out of my way to be supportive and I did struggle when she cos she could have told me she was going to leave like two weeks ago to actually not tell me till the last day is just unprofessional</u>
<u n="189" who="S0513">oh oh no</u>
<u n="190" who="S0511"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well it won't help when she wants a reference er cos I'll try to be nice but it's it really is pretty unprofessional I mean there's no need for it cos she could have just been honest with me anyway so then I was standing in the kitchen about twenty minutes later and I saw one of the guys who works for one of our managers and I said oh hi how are you doing? and she said oh fine I've got to start thinking about job hunting and I said oh cos hers she's on a temporary contract with these people and I quite like this woman and I <trunc>wou</trunc> do you wanna come and work for me?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0513">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0511">and she said yeah sure so that was that sorted</u>
<u n="193" who="S0513" trans="overlap">so that was lucky</u>
<u n="194" who="S0511"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm it was very lucky mm mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0513" trans="overlap">is she literate?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0511">yeah yeah yeah she's er like she's a grown-up erm like a proper grown-up professional with degrees and stuff and the reason that she's happy to be my administrator is</u>
<u n="197" who="S0513"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="198" who="S0511">yeah exactly so she has erm her she's got her degrees are in marketing and journalism and that sort of thing and she's been a journalist in Australia she's an Australian and then she's been working in a laboratory in Africa for a year to do something or other and then she's come to England erm and so she doesn't have a particular kind of career path and she's been working with these erm one of my genetics ones on a marketing thing which was always going to be time limited and she was due to finish at Christmas but she's working full-time but she <trunc>c</trunc> moved to working for them part time now and then work for me part-time and then the two'll go along side by side <pause dur="short"/> and then in that time she can also think about getting herself a proper proper job <pause dur="long"/> she's got a radio station actually in Australia</u>
<u n="199" who="S0513">run one?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0511">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0513">mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0511">twenty-four twenty-four hours a day so yeah <trunc>r</trunc> and it was like staffed by young people and it was like a community thing I think she's also</u>
<u n="203" who="S0513" trans="overlap">maybe like Radio <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0511">yeah it's er well it's er mm Radio <anon type="place"/> is reasonably professional cos that's that's BBC Radio <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> the erm crazy local ones are like the called or <anon type="place"/> Radio</u>
<u n="205" who="S0513">called what Radio?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0511"><anon type="place"/> and it's like kind of <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> and there's hospital radio in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0513">is there?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0511">mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0513">a hospital has a radio frequency?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0511">uhu hospitals always have had radio frequencies</u>
<u n="211" who="S0513">what so you can</u>
<u n="212" who="S0511">play</u>
<u n="213" who="S0513" trans="overlap">see who's</u>
<u n="214" who="S0511">stuff on the</u>
<u n="215" who="S0513" trans="overlap">dying?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0511"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no it's so that people who are hospital can listen to the radio</u>
<u n="217" who="S0513">oh right yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0511">and like every song is dedicated to somebody in the hospital <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's quite a big you know it's kind of a significant thing hospital radio it's just a thing that's always been</u>
<u n="219" who="S0513">mm bit like tapping into their walkie-talkie radios cos to see if the relative was in a crash</u>
<u n="220" who="S0511">no it's not for checking out who's who's in A and E this week <pause dur="short"/> you would have have you heard in the news that a boy was killed at a school in <anon type="place"/> yesterday?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0513">mm I think I saw it headlined somewhere</u>
<u n="222" who="S0511">does that make you erm sort of scared?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0513">I don't know what were the details?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0511">well apparently it's a very good school highly regarded <vocal desc="misc"/> so like a school like yours not some kind of inner city dangerous place that you'd think that it's</u>
<u n="225" who="S0513" trans="overlap">yeah but what happened?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0511">I dunno some other kid stabbed him</u>
<u n="227" who="S0513"><unclear/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0511">well this sounds like the kind of school where no one has knives</u>
<u n="229" who="S0513">actually <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> probably has a knife</u>
<u n="230" who="S0511"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0513">erm <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> something like that</u>
<u n="232" who="S0511">is he the one in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s year?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0513">no</u>
<u n="234" who="S0511">no is he</u>
<u n="235" who="S0513" trans="overlap">he's in mine he's alright he's bright but he just doesn't make very good decisions</u>
<u n="236" who="S0511">yeah mm <trunc>y</trunc>yeah that's a really sensible way of looking at it and <trunc>c</trunc>carrying a knife is a really bad decision <pause dur="long"/> well <pause dur="short"/> yeah so I don't know the ins and outs but I heard a thing on the radio when I was <unclear>running</unclear> this morning and they were talking about I think at that point they were saying they were going to close the school for a week for everyone to I dunno whatever and this psychologist was saying that's probably a bad idea it's much important that the young people there can be together <pause dur="short"/> rather than at home potentially alone cos of course mums and dads are at work <pause dur="long"/> terrible yeah I mean not er obviously it's terrible when it happens in inner city schools as well it's crazy cos in American schools they have metal detectors don't they as you go in</u>
<u n="237" who="S0513">yeah well they do now</u>
<u n="238" who="S0511">well it doesn't stop anything does it? <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0513">I doubt that there is exactly like eagle eye watching them with the metal detectors <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0511">they're not like what?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0513">they don't eagle eye always alert with the metal detectors at schools and</u>
<u n="242" who="S0511">well I imagine they're like those ones at the airport though they can't be cos then</u>
<u n="243" who="S0513" trans="overlap">yeah er</u>
<u n="244" who="S0511" trans="overlap">then they are set <unclear/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0513">I mean the staff would not give a shit <vocal desc="laugh"/> who's gonna man metal detectors?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0511">well there must be one</u>
<u n="247" who="S0513" trans="overlap"><unclear>the chances are</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0511">well there erm in American schools they have police officers onsite as well mm</u>
<u n="249" who="S0513">there is in London sometimes I think</u>
<u n="250" who="S0511">oh there was a I saw on the news yesterday a police officer who just assaulted a student was sacked</u>
<u n="251" who="S0513">why?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0511">well cos he assaulted the student</u>
<u n="253" who="S0513">yeah but why did he assault the student?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0511">I don't know I think she was being misbehaving in the classroom so he was called in whereupon he just assaulted her <vocal desc="laugh"/> so that's how it ended so of course being this having <trunc>s</trunc> these days someone there was er someone videoed it</u>
<u n="255" who="S0513">I think some schools in London have policemen</u>
<u n="256" who="S0511">do you?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0513">some schools in London</u>
<u n="258" who="S0511">you think have police officers?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0513">yeah I'm pretty sure someone in camp said that so mm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0511">sorry?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0513">pretty sure someone on camp said their school have one</u>
<u n="262" who="S0511">well they I was thinking they might have one allocated like erm <pause dur="short"/> like when you were at primary school there was a like your your kind of priest bloke who wasn't</u>
<u n="263" who="S0513"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0511">you know he so he's kind of comes in regularly but he's not you know doesn't live there or whatever <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0513">of course he doesn't live there <vocal desc="laugh"/> but er</u>
<u n="266" who="S0511" trans="overlap">you say that when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was at nursery in London he thought that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> his key worker er lived at the nursery</u>
<u n="267" who="S0513" trans="overlap">yeah thought</u>
<u n="268" who="S0511"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he thought some of the erm some of the other kids flew in from Africa every day <pause dur="short"/> it's funny isn't it? when <trunc>y</trunc> funny what little kids think <pause dur="short"/> even though we'd always tried to be really multicultural and all the rest of it er</u>
<u n="269" who="S0513"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s just a complete twat <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0511"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is not a complete twat <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is an extraordinarily individual</u>
<u n="271" who="S0513">erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> whatever you say <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0511">yes he is <pause dur="short"/> so are you going to come with me to pick them tomorrow?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0513">I don't see any reason at all to <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0511">did you go with daddy to drop them?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0513">no <pause dur="short"/> I was out with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0511">mm you seem to have spent a lot of the time on your own then this last few days have you no I suppose you were in the shop and then you were with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and you've done some homework <pause dur="short"/> I was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the other morning</u>
<u n="277" who="S0513" trans="overlap">just <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0511"><unclear/> slept a lot I was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the other day how <pause dur="short"/> well I don't is it not very long ago that you started sleeping late in the mornings so it's like within the last few months</u>
<u n="279" who="S0513">yeah I'm a lot tireder</u>
<u n="280" who="S0511">yeah but it seems to be like sometimes you still get up at seven and other times you don't get up till eleven it's not like you started getting up at eight and then nine and then ten</u>
<u n="281" who="S0513" trans="overlap">yeah sometimes sometimes my alarm wakes me and sometimes I sleep through</u>
<u n="282" who="S0511">oh I see</u>
<u n="283" who="S0513">I think it depends cos I put it here it depends if I stick it on my bedside table or <pause dur="short"/> by the charger</u>
<u n="284" who="S0511">your phone?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0513">yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0511">yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0513">but you know I'm it's often at dad's it depends if <pause dur="short"/> it lands with the speaker down or not</u>
<u n="288" who="S0511">you must have got a <trunc>h</trunc> so you've just to set the the volume to like just the right volume that it's</u>
<u n="289" who="S0513" trans="overlap">I've set it to full <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0511">oh okay and</u>
<u n="291" who="S0513"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0511"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> do you have a you do you turn the alarm off at the weekends or non-school days?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0513">er not usually well er Saturday I've got tennis and</u>
<u n="294" who="S0511">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0513" trans="overlap">I I think it is off for some</u>
<u n="296" who="S0511" trans="overlap">yeah I did think of emailing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> your tennis coach to recommend that he changed the lessons round</u>
<u n="297" who="S0513"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0511">to the other order you know you you know you laugh but probably no one's ever suggested it to him <pause dur="short"/> it makes much more sense to have young kids earlier <pause dur="short"/> cos they're all up at the crack of dawn</u>
<u n="299" who="S0513">yeah was I up at half five like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when I was twelve</u>
<u n="300" who="S0511">he doesn't get up at half five <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0513">I mean he gets up at like half past six</u>
<u n="302" who="S0511">and seven yeah and he always has done he's never got up at five or half five it's always been six that he wakes <pause dur="short"/> but he doesn't come out of the room until seven</u>
<u n="303" who="S0513" trans="overlap">but I remember one time when I was about that age right just like until about nine</u>
<u n="304" who="S0511">well I don't know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been consistently getting up at the same time <pause dur="short"/> you I think you were probably a bit more kind of irregular really whereas he's really quite consistently yeah you were all or you've never been quite as early as him</u>
<u n="305" who="S0513">mm</u>
<u n="306" who="S0511">I don't think <pause dur="short"/> god I hope there are did <trunc>y</trunc> where where were you yesterday morning when it was really heavy rain?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0513">asleep <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0511">right no you missed that did you?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0513"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0511">it was really heavy rain</u>
<u n="311" who="S0513" trans="overlap">I woke up at erm like well I woke up at seven to turn my alarm off then I went back to sleep and then I woke up a bit later when dad when to <anon type="place"/> and then I woke up at twelve when he got back from <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0511">right <vocal desc="laugh"/> so you've been doing a bit of resting then</u>
<u n="313" who="S0513"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0511">erm it was <trunc>h</trunc> really heavy rain when I was driving to work at like eight</u>
<u n="315" who="S0513" trans="overlap">yeah yeah he said it was horrible</u>
<u n="316" who="S0511">really</u>
<u n="317" who="S0513" trans="overlap">driving to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0511">yeah and I was trying to <trunc>dr</trunc> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was driving down from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> she'd been in <anon type="place"/> and she said she was thinking when she was driving along about our boys being away camping er and what did she say? let me see er</u>
<u n="319" who="S0513">they've gotten off lightly haven't they?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0511">sorry?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0513">they've gotten off lightly haven't they?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0511">well I don't know we'll have to wait and so anyway she says sure your boys will be fine and happy but driving home in extremely heavy rain yesterday morning I did wonder how it could possibly be fun</u>
<u n="323" who="S0513"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="324" who="S0511"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and I said yeah I really wondered that yesterday morning too <vocal desc="laugh"/> but anyway we will find out tomorrow when we get them</u>
<u n="325" who="S0513">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="326" who="S0511">so erm I was gonna light the fire and sit in front of it and read a book</u>
<u n="327" who="S0513">yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0511">what are you going to do?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0513">er I might read a bit I'll probably do some history research</u>
<u n="330" who="S0511">do some for a history project you're doing what is it?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0513">erm it's ten percent on Monday</u>
<u n="332" who="S0511">it's ten percent on Monday? what does that mean?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0513">ten percent of my GCSE <pause dur="short"/> on Monday <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="334" who="S0511">is er is that why it has to be handed in on Monday?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0513" trans="overlap">yeah yeah it's the exam on Monday it's like an hour of writing I think a twenty mark question</u>
<u n="336" who="S0511">what you have exams <pause dur="short"/> I thought coursework happened during the year not exams</u>
<u n="337" who="S0513">well it's a controlled assessment</u>
<u n="338" who="S0511">oh I've heard of those</u>
<u n="339" who="S0513">er five percent a few months like a month ago</u>
<u n="340" who="S0511">okay what's it about?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0513">erm the impact of liberalisation on society from nineteen fifty-nine to seventy-nine</u>
<u n="342" who="S0511">uhu what's the key issues?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0513">abortion</u>
<u n="344" who="S0511">wrong</u>
<u n="345" who="S0513">what?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0511">wrong</u>
<u n="347" who="S0513">legalisation</u>
<u n="348" who="S0511" trans="overlap">that's not the first one</u>
<u n="349" who="S0513" trans="overlap">of abortion</u>
<u n="350" who="S0511" trans="overlap">sorry?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0513">legalisation of abortion what are you saying <trunc>abor</trunc>abortion's wrong?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0511">no I'm not saying abortion's wrong <vocal desc="laugh"/> saying like the first thing you should say where like where <trunc>i</trunc>is not abortion</u>
<u n="353" who="S0513">well</u>
<u n="354" who="S0511">well so what are the other things you're going to list?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0513">erm the four things that I know you're gonna say it should be women's rights but the four things we've been given</u>
<u n="356" who="S0511">yes</u>
<u n="357" who="S0513">are law changes</u>
<u n="358" who="S0511">yes</u>
<u n="359" who="S0513">which is the legalisation of abortion er the erm divorce reform act the legalisation of homosexuality and erm the abolition of the death penalty</u>
<u n="360" who="S0511">oh so so you're only doing stuff to do with the law are you?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0513">yeah we're only doing actual changes</u>
<u n="362" who="S0511">changes in the law? <vocal desc="laugh"/> there are other actual changes such as the availability of contraception</u>
<u n="363" who="S0513">yeah that's under</u>
<u n="364" who="S0511">under</u>
<u n="365" who="S0513" trans="overlap">divorce and abortion and stuff</u>
<u n="366" who="S0511"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's not really anything to do with divorce er well I suppose it's something to do with abortion</u>
<u n="367" who="S0513" trans="overlap">yeah it's something to do with abortion</u>
<u n="368" who="S0511">yeah but there was no I <trunc>d</trunc> I guess there wasn't a law needed they just invented contraception</u>
<u n="369" who="S0513">mm</u>
<u n="370" who="S0511">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay and unfortunately the legalisation of homosexuality at that time</u>
<u n="371" who="S0513">yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0511" trans="overlap">no well I suppose that was step forward</u>
<u n="373" who="S0513" trans="overlap">you had to be you had to be twenty-one</u>
<u n="374" who="S0511">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0513" trans="overlap">and in private</u>
<u n="376" who="S0511">yeah and yeah I mean there was still a lot of erm <pause dur="short"/> even when I was young there was still lots and lots of dreadful discrimination against gay people so whereas kind of women by <trunc>th</trunc> kind of the the differences that abortion and divorce and contraception brought on kind of had a er I guess it feels to me like a really quick impact whereas yeah homosexual rights seemed to take a lot of seemed to have taken</u>
<u n="377" who="S0513" trans="overlap">and the</u>
<u n="378" who="S0511" trans="overlap">a lot longer to come in</u>
<u n="379" who="S0513" trans="overlap">age of consent was only equalled in like two thousand and one</u>
<u n="380" who="S0511">it is is that actually properly equal now?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0513">I think so yeah but only</u>
<u n="382" who="S0511">ah but</u>
<u n="383" who="S0513" trans="overlap">yeah two thousand and one</u>
<u n="384" who="S0511">yeah they <trunc>di</trunc></u>
<u n="385" who="S0513" trans="overlap">and er you weren't allowed to be gay in the army <pause dur="short"/> until two thousand and two</u>
<u n="386" who="S0511">and yes</u>
<u n="387" who="S0513" trans="overlap">America was two thousand and eleven</u>
<u n="388" who="S0511">I thought you still weren't allowed to be gay in the army</u>
<u n="389" who="S0513">mm no <unclear/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0511" trans="overlap">oh no you're allowed to be gay but you're not allowed to tell anyone it's like don't say don't ask they have this thing <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="391" who="S0513">oh</u>
<u n="392" who="S0511">so <trunc>basi</trunc> it's still discriminatory and I think the way they got round legalising erm for the age of consent cos I think is the age of consent now eighteen?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0513">no it's sixteen it was eighteen in like the nineties and it's sixteen now</u>
<u n="394" who="S0511">no no it was sixteen when I was growing up but at one point for homosexuals it was eighteen but there are issues</u>
<u n="395" who="S0513" trans="overlap">oh yeah right do you mean the age of consent for heterosexual people?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0511">yes</u>
<u n="397" who="S0513">oh right yeah that's like always been sixteen</u>
<u n="398" who="S0511">yeah oh right so the so for gay people it went down to eighteen and then to</u>
<u n="399" who="S0513" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0511" trans="overlap">sixteen?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0513">yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0511">okay alright great right I mean how ridiculous that you like change the law just like still make it unequal</u>
<u n="403" who="S0513">yeah well the same thing happened for <unclear/> I suppose mm</u>
<u n="404" who="S0511">the same thing happened for what?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0513">er for something else that the same thing happened they changed it but didn't do anything cos it was can't remember er but yeah it was abortion and it was still like really hard to get an abortion</u>
<u n="406" who="S0511">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0513" trans="overlap">two doctors had to agree that there was a significant health risk to the mother or the child</u>
<u n="408" who="S0511">yes there was something about abortion the other day <pause dur="short"/> oh the er erm I was reading an interview with erm <vocal desc="misc"/> one of the <trunc>fam</trunc> one of the famous feminists from the sixties and the seventies I can't remember which one it was and the interviewer asked her if she was surprised to see er abortion rights being clawed back so you know how the States <unclear>play it</unclear> where there has been the right to abortion but those rights are kind of being lost?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0513">yeah well the Catholic church is always pissing about <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0511">well and she said interestingly that she never expected us to keep all those rights first time round cos like ultimately all of this equality stuff is about ownership and ownership ultimately comes down to fertility and so like when the shit really hits the fan and stuff really starts to bite then people start to try to control fertility and that was her view <pause dur="short"/> mm so you've got an exam what that's like an hour long?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0513">yeah twenty marks</u>
<u n="412" who="S0511">okay and they're gonna ask what three three essay questions or something like that?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0513">no just the one twenty mark question</u>
<u n="414" who="S0511">one twenty mark question?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0513">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0511">where you're gonna have to write about</u>
<u n="417" who="S0513" trans="overlap">what what</u>
<u n="418" who="S0511" trans="overlap">all these five things?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0513" trans="overlap">what was the impact of liberalisation <unclear>and this kind of thing</unclear></u>
<u n="420" who="S0511">what er this liberalisation then it's maybe that means</u>
<u n="421" who="S0513" trans="overlap">it's people having more freedom to do as they they want</u>
<u n="422" who="S0511">er and and you're interpreting that as as meaning through the through the law?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0513">but but but that's how</u>
<u n="424" who="S0511" trans="overlap">having more freedom through the law?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0513">Mrs <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> interprets it anyway</u>
<u n="426" who="S0511">well I'm sure she's right <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's just I don't think of it as like that myself <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0513">mm</u>
<u n="428" who="S0511">okay right so are you gonna do some more revision then?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0513">er maybe</u>
<u n="430" who="S0511">okay I'll light the fire <pause dur="short"/> let me stop this thing <pause dur="short"/> blimey we've been here half an hour <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> can you put that in the dishwasher luvvy?</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
