<text id="SEGJ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:30:00</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-02-24</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0632 S0635</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Living Room in a shared House in Finchley London; speakers’ home.</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Honeymoon, USA, Iceland, Boston, Portland Maine, Family, California road trip, San Francisco, LA, camping, hotels, motels, National Parks, desert, Outsider Art, food.</topics>
		<activity>Newly married couple reminiscing over what happened on their honeymoon about 6 moths ago. </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0632">
				<exactage>26</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kings Lynn, Norfolk, UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>England</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Neutral</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Carer/ Freelance Illustrator and writer</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0635">
				<exactage>26</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Perth</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Scotland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Non- regional - slight influence of American mother, lived in Cambridgeshire most of my life</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Illustrator and careworker</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0632">so <pause dur="short"/> what was the first thing we did on our honeymoon? <trunc>wh</trunc>when do you count our honeymoon starting? would you say it started when we arrived on the East Coast of America or did it start when we arrived in San Francisco?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0635">I would start with the East Coast cos there were lots of good things that happened</u>
<u n="3" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0635">there erm so we</u>
<u n="5" who="S0632" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="6" who="S0635">got in quite late at night did we?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0632">I think it was quite late at night by the time we got to Portland cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> took us to that pizza place that sold pizza by the slice and was really really good</u>
<u n="8" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0632">that she doesn't go to but she knows is really good</u>
<u n="10" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0632">I mean I assume she didn't go there</u>
<u n="12" who="S0635">no I don't think so not with her diet</u>
<u n="13" who="S0632">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0635">yeah yeah oh yeah so we were with lots of people on the plane weren't we? so we had the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> were</u>
<u n="15" who="S0632">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0635" trans="overlap">we met up with them in Iceland and erm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0632"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and</u>
<u n="18" who="S0635"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0635">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then we all got to Boston and we dashed on a bus up to Portland</u>
<u n="21" who="S0632">we did</u>
<u n="22" who="S0635">erm</u>
<u n="23" who="S0632" trans="overlap">did we say <trunc>good</trunc> did we say goodbye to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at Boston or did they get on the bus to Portland too?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0635">they got on the bus to Portland too they must have done yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0632">yeah feel like they get off somewhere else to us or something or just I guess it was just when we were getting taxis at the at the other end</u>
<u n="26" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0632">we got a taxi with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and they or got in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s car even or did we get a taxi? I can't remember</u>
<u n="28" who="S0635" trans="overlap">we did get a taxi yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0632">and the</u>
<u n="30" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I remember to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house</u>
<u n="31" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0635">and then we checked in at that hotel</u>
<u n="33" who="S0632">that B and B</u>
<u n="34" who="S0635">which was cute yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0632">really sweet big old house</u>
<u n="36" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="37" who="S0632">in Portland and yeah we were starving so she took us to that pizza place and we ate pizza in our really quite big chintzy room <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0635">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was a really good pizza what was the flavour? can't remember now? it was</u>
<u n="39" who="S0632">yeah I feel like</u>
<u n="40" who="S0635" trans="overlap">really unusual</u>
<u n="41" who="S0632" trans="overlap">like yours was like Canadian bacon and something <vocal desc="laugh"/> I didn't know</u>
<u n="42" who="S0635">oh I wish I could remember now cos I I think it was weird there was something strange on it</u>
<u n="43" who="S0632">yeah I feel like they were slightly adventurous flavours I don't think I wrote that down I don't think I was recording what flavour pizza we had the night we landed we were just really tired and</u>
<u n="44" who="S0635" trans="overlap">oh that's gonna annoy me now</u>
<u n="45" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's a crucial detail that you need to remember</u>
<u n="46" who="S0635">it is the food was good yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0632">I don't think we even took pictures of it or anything we were just knackered so</u>
<u n="48" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I I feel like I did I think I sent my band a lot of pictures of the strange food I was eating</u>
<u n="49" who="S0632">oh that's gonna be</u>
<u n="50" who="S0635">but</u>
<u n="51" who="S0632">quite hard to find isn't it? right back in the depths of your phone</u>
<u n="52" who="S0635">I'll just look up the pizza places in Portland <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0632">pizza places in Portland and what their er menu is</u>
<u n="54" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0632">cos it was really good and then the next day we spent the day just enjoying Portland</u>
<u n="56" who="S0635">yeah we <trunc>wa</trunc>walked up and down really <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I guess had work</u>
<u n="57" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0635" trans="overlap">we'd meet her at the farmers' market</u>
<u n="59" who="S0632">we met her at the farmers' market</u>
<u n="60" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0632">and I got a a weird smoothie as well like Redbush tea smoothie or something and it was really nice talked to a bunch of people as we walked around</u>
<u n="62" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0632">is that the day we went to erm hot supper as well? cos that was really good like it was all about food</u>
<u n="64" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="65" who="S0632" trans="overlap">in Portland cos like the the B and B was insanely good with erm the breakfast was just like a tray of desserts and some fresh fruit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0632">but like all baked that morning at god knows what time</u>
<u n="68" who="S0635">oh yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0632">like cinnamon rolls and things just fresh out of the oven</u>
<u n="70" who="S0635">yeah yeah it was great</u>
<u n="71" who="S0632">cantaloupe melon every day</u>
<u n="72" who="S0635">mm yeah I think we had a good wander round we did Hot Suppa at some point we did The Great Lost Bear</u>
<u n="73" who="S0632">I think we did them on different days didn't we?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah we did</u>
<u n="75" who="S0632">cos that would have been a <trunc>m</trunc> bit much but</u>
<u n="76" who="S0635">I think we did The Great Lost Bear on our last day</u>
<u n="77" who="S0632">and you had the almighty cheeses sandwich</u>
<u n="78" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="79" who="S0632">which is</u>
<u n="80" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0632">two two toasted cheese sandwiches <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0632">forming a sandwich I didn't enjoy The Great Lost Bear as much as Hot Suppa</u>
<u n="84" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0632">like that was cuter and the food was just like it was it was really filling and nice and</u>
<u n="86" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0632">indulgent but it just wasn't as greasy and also</u>
<u n="88" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0632">I liked the fact they had natural light The Great Lost Bear was very I guess that's you know part of its charm like it's like</u>
<u n="90" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0632">very dark even though you're there in the middle of the day it feels like you're there in the middle of the night</u>
<u n="92" who="S0635">yeah yeah it's a mashed potato bacon and scallion pizza</u>
<u n="93" who="S0632">oh that's what you had</u>
<u n="94" who="S0635"><trunc>ye</trunc></u>
<u n="95" who="S0632">the mashed potato thing</u>
<u n="96" who="S0635" trans="overlap">it had mashed potato on it yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0632">that's why it was weird mm yeah that sounds true</u>
<u n="98" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0632">then we went up to see <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a few times and had a few nice meals with them</u>
<u n="100" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0632"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> kept making scallops and things like that that I was like yes</u>
<u n="102" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0632">I love scallops</u>
<u n="104" who="S0635">yeah oh that's right yeah we did we had a really good</u>
<u n="105" who="S0632">few a few dinners</u>
<u n="106" who="S0635" trans="overlap">a couple of evenings with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0632">talking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about seeing bears cos we were excited</u>
<u n="108" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="109" who="S0632">about maybe seeing a bear in</u>
<u n="110" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0632">California</u>
<u n="112" who="S0635">and we looked through a lot of his old photographs which were beautiful</u>
<u n="113" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0635">like when of er was it <trunc>d</trunc>Death Valley?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0632">yeah yeah it weren't they like road tripping in some old car</u>
<u n="116" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0632" trans="overlap">through Death Valley? it's like bit scary <vocal desc="laugh"/> probably didn't have air conditioning</u>
<u n="118" who="S0635">no maybe yeah I mean it looked</u>
<u n="119" who="S0632">no</u>
<u n="120" who="S0635">looked rough I think he was notorious for dragging them through places</u>
<u n="121" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's why your</u>
<u n="122" who="S0635">that they were</u>
<u n="123" who="S0632" trans="overlap">family motto was can we eat it in the ambulance?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0635">yeah mm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0632">ah and that was lovely and then but we didn't see the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>s on that leg of the journey did we? We just went straight to the airport</u>
<u n="128" who="S0635">yes that's how I yeah I think we agreed to see them on the way back didn't we?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0632">did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> drop us at the airport or did we did we get a bus to the airport?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0635">I'm pretty sure we got the bus again and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> dropped us off at the bus station yeah I remember <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and caught our flight to San Francisco</u>
<u n="132" who="S0635">San Francisco yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah and there was lightning on the flight on the</u>
<u n="133" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0635">and we could see lightning at the window</u>
<u n="135" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and we were like above lightning clouds and they were all</u>
<u n="136" who="S0635" trans="overlap">which is pretty amazing</u>
<u n="137" who="S0632" trans="overlap">lighting up</u>
<u n="138" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0632">yeah I saw some great things from that plane cos on the way over to America</u>
<u n="140" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0632">via Iceland we saw like Greenland from above</u>
<u n="142" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0632">and it was amazing</u>
<u n="144" who="S0635">it was a pretty exciting plane trip</u>
<u n="145" who="S0632">yeah and then erm yeah all the stormy weather although these were our least eventful flights cos the flights back</u>
<u n="146" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0632">were the ones that kept getting delayed and cancelled and decompressing so</u>
<u n="148" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0632" trans="overlap">we had to land</u>
<u n="150" who="S0635">yeah the storms were scary but they were pretty far away it was just like little</u>
<u n="151" who="S0632">it was like</u>
<u n="152" who="S0635" trans="overlap">flashes <trunc>f</trunc>far away</u>
<u n="153" who="S0632" trans="overlap">hey look at it wasn't even mentioned like by the captain or anything</u>
<u n="154" who="S0635">no</u>
<u n="155" who="S0632">it was just like just</u>
<u n="156" who="S0635" trans="overlap">it was kind of er overnight flight wasn't it?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0632">it was</u>
<u n="158" who="S0635" trans="overlap">so <trunc>as</trunc>asleep and I'd wake up and look out the window and it would be like <vocal desc="misc"/> yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and it was really strange so yeah did we land in San Francisco in like the wee hours of the morning? or</u>
<u n="160" who="S0635">no</u>
<u n="161" who="S0632" trans="overlap">was like two AM or something?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0635" trans="overlap">it was late at night yeah it was like at night in San Francisco</u>
<u n="163" who="S0632">I guess cos the time difference</u>
<u n="164" who="S0635">yeah and you picked up our rental car and then I didn't realise it had a handbrake</u>
<u n="165" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0635">and yet it still drives perfectly fine with it on and makes a strange smell <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0632">and we fell out because <vocal desc="laugh"/> because I was really annoying that that happened</u>
<u n="168" who="S0635">oh I was really annoyed that it was happened <vocal desc="laugh"/> that it was happened yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0632">that it was happened</u>
<u n="170" who="S0635">it was so annoying</u>
<u n="171" who="S0632">and then</u>
<u n="172" who="S0635" trans="overlap">in fact yeah we got to that sort of strange Motor Inn on Lombard street</u>
<u n="173" who="S0632">oh yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0635">and instead of just trying to sleep</u>
<u n="175" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="176" who="S0635">I called the rental company and told them what I'd done</u>
<u n="177" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> to confess</u>
<u n="178" who="S0635">yeah and we thought we might swap the car but I sort of figured I'd try it first</u>
<u n="179" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and they and I also called a load of places to see if they would <vocal desc="laugh"/> the car's here to see if they would swap it and no one seemed to be that interested</u>
<u n="181" who="S0632">no they didn't seem that bothered did they? they were like</u>
<u n="182" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh you did that that's okay</u>
<u n="184" who="S0635">but it was kind of a bummer to be like oh one of our cars all bust <vocal desc="laugh"/> just like on the first day</u>
<u n="185" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I was like well we're gonna go like driving in the mountains I kind of want the handbrake to work <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0635">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0632">but it was fine the whole trip and I did end up forgetting that we ever did that</u>
<u n="188" who="S0635">yeah yeah it wasn't that big a deal</u>
<u n="189" who="S0632">no it wasn't</u>
<u n="190" who="S0635" trans="overlap">but it was really annoying and the yeah it's cos I'd been driving <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s car and it like was a similar setup like didn't have a handbrake you know just sort of neglected to you know it just I just er I pulled away and it went</u>
<u n="191" who="S0632">and it went <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0635"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0632">oh dear</u>
<u n="194" who="S0635">yeah but the <pause dur="short"/> yeah but then we went to we sort of just walked out found a good place for breakfast didn't we?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0632">yeah I think we'd looked up where the good place for breakfast was nearby and</u>
<u n="196" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0632">it was good it was a good dining time things and</u>
<u n="198" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0632">and it was like only like two doors down from the bike rental wasn't it?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0635">it was close there yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0632" trans="overlap">but we did that the next day</u>
<u n="202" who="S0635">that was the next day that's it we sort of we walked didn't we pretty much all of it for</u>
<u n="203" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0635">the first part walked up Lombard street to the windy street and then</u>
<u n="205" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0635">got our first view from the top of the hill of Alcatraz and</u>
<u n="207" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0635" trans="overlap">walked down to the kind of pier</u>
<u n="209" who="S0632">Pier thirty-nine is it?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0635">yeah something like that</u>
<u n="211" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0635">which is the</u>
<u n="213" who="S0632" trans="overlap">see all the seals</u>
<u n="214" who="S0635">very touristy area but it was kind of</u>
<u n="215" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0635">good to see</u>
<u n="217" who="S0632">yeah we just kind of</u>
<u n="218" who="S0635">and we had a Hard Rock cocktail</u>
<u n="219" who="S0632">we did <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0635">and yeah we saw the seals erm</u>
<u n="223" who="S0632">oh we wanted to walk inwards towards the park and everything didn't we? then we walked via the the Chinese district</u>
<u n="224" who="S0635">yes</u>
<u n="225" who="S0632">and we caught <unclear>braid</unclear> of some sort</u>
<u n="226" who="S0635" trans="overlap">oh yeah that was amazing</u>
<u n="227" who="S0632">but we didn't know what it was for <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0635">yeah that was really good and yeah then we got to sort of the more the like central square which didn't really have a whole load going in it was er</u>
<u n="229" who="S0632" trans="overlap">no it was it was nice it was</u>
<u n="230" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0632">like a nice looking place psst <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> no</u>
<u n="232" who="S0635">Chinatown had a lot more going for it</u>
<u n="233" who="S0632">yeah it was great window shopping in Chinatown</u>
<u n="234" who="S0635">yeah it was great</u>
<u n="235" who="S0632" trans="overlap">all the all the fish and stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="237" who="S0632">but like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just looked at me when I said fish</u>
<u n="238" who="S0635"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah she probably did</u>
<u n="239" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm fish</u>
<u n="240" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0632">but yeah that was that was a bit exhausting we eventually got the bus didn't we cos we've finished up in the park as the sun was going down</u>
<u n="242" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0632">and we I think we did our first Whole Foods</u>
<u n="244" who="S0635">yeah well we walked up to <trunc>gr</trunc> yeah we walked up to Grace Cathedral park first</u>
<u n="245" who="S0632">uhu</u>
<u n="246" who="S0635">and then we met that strange helping lady</u>
<u n="247" who="S0632">she's a helper</u>
<u n="248" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0635">you know to help us with the</u>
<u n="251" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I'm helpful I'm a helper yeah that was it wasn't it?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and like</u>
<u n="253" who="S0632">all the people in San Francisco were like on some sort of <vocal desc="laugh"/> you said they were all on some twelve-step programme cos they were all about making a big deal about how they were helping you</u>
<u n="254" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0632">which is really nice to be helped but they'd like just make sure you realised they were being really helpful</u>
<u n="256" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0632">it's like hey I don't mind I'm a I'm a helpful person that's what I do I might as well have a big H on my forehead</u>
<u n="258" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0632" trans="overlap">the helper</u>
<u n="260" who="S0635"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0632">yeah that's what that woman said wasn't it?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0635">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="263" who="S0632">and it was like thanks all she did was tell us that the erm that the er what what are they called?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0635">that the trams are</u>
<u n="265" who="S0632">the trams</u>
<u n="266" who="S0635" trans="overlap">that they weren't running that day</u>
<u n="267" who="S0632" trans="overlap">are they trams? cable cars</u>
<u n="268" who="S0635">cable cars yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0632">I guess it's the same thing really</u>
<u n="270" who="S0635">uhu and <trunc>the</trunc> or trolley buses or whatever they are</u>
<u n="271" who="S0632">yeah she's like they're not running today</u>
<u n="272" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="273" who="S0632">like oh</u>
<u n="274" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0632">so we oh yeah and then we got a bus to</u>
<u n="276" who="S0635">Haight-Ashbury</u>
<u n="277" who="S0632">Haight-Ashbury</u>
<u n="278" who="S0635">yeah which is quite a distance</u>
<u n="279" who="S0632">yeah it was alright</u>
<u n="280" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I mean it was a bit of a Camden wasn't it?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0635">basically yeah but druggy</u>
<u n="283" who="S0632" trans="overlap">is what</u>
<u n="284" who="S0635">but</u>
<u n="285" who="S0632">it reminded me of</u>
<u n="286" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="287" who="S0632">and then we went to the big botanic gardens that were closed</u>
<u n="288" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0632">with the big giant greenhouse</u>
<u n="290" who="S0635">yeah we had a drink a cocktail I think</u>
<u n="291" who="S0632">oh yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0635" trans="overlap">at Haight-Ashbury and we</u>
<u n="293" who="S0632">I had a blood orange Paloma</u>
<u n="294" who="S0635">and we ran into the servers in Whole Foods later</u>
<u n="295" who="S0632">we did <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0635">but we also that was our first Amoeba Records was in Haight-Ashbury</u>
<u n="297" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="298" who="S0635">and we popped in a guitar shop</u>
<u n="299" who="S0632">that's right we did loads that day actually</u>
<u n="300" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0632" trans="overlap">cos we walked almost all of it</u>
<u n="302" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="303" who="S0632">apart from a couple of bus rides</u>
<u n="304" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0632">cos things were really far away</u>
<u n="306" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0632">and erm and yeah we did our first Amoeba Records</u>
<u n="308" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0632" trans="overlap">we had the Paloma in that really cute little bar and then we sat</u>
<u n="310" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0632">outside and then we wanted just to get a salad and eat it in the park didn't we?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0635" trans="overlap">so we did yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0632">so we did</u>
<u n="314" who="S0635">and we ran into our servers from the cocktail bar in whole food</u>
<u n="315" who="S0632">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0635">and then the other guy in Whole Foods was helpful as well cos he told us not to buy forks cos he had free ones</u>
<u n="317" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0635">he was like I'm a helper I like to do helpful things</u>
<u n="319" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0635"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0632">you also work here and it's your job to help us</u>
<u n="322" who="S0635">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0632">but thank you anyway</u>
<u n="324" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0635">so he yeah so we yeah and then we went and ate our salad in Golden Gate park and walked up to the greenhouse which was closed</u>
<u n="327" who="S0632">but pretty</u>
<u n="328" who="S0635">pretty</u>
<u n="329" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and there were all the giant succulents</u>
<u n="330" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="331" who="S0632">everywhere</u>
<u n="332" who="S0635">oh yeah and the cactuses</u>
<u n="333" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I mean not everywhere but especially there they were like huge</u>
<u n="334" who="S0635">uhu and I think we were pretty worn out by that point</u>
<u n="335" who="S0632">we were we just got the the bus home but the bus home route was really pretty</u>
<u n="336" who="S0635">yeah it was awesome cos the sun was sort of setting and</u>
<u n="337" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0635">they're quite unusual the buses they're</u>
<u n="339" who="S0632">did we just go to like a corner shop and get some beers to drink in our room?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0635">I think we did yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0635">like yeah I think that's right</u>
<u n="343" who="S0632">something like Sierra Nevada or something</u>
<u n="344" who="S0635">yeah yeah yeah that's right and then we probably just watched crappy TV</u>
<u n="345" who="S0632">yeah we we would have watched Frasier or something wouldn't we?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0635">uhu yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0632">just gone to sleep</u>
<u n="348" who="S0635">adverts for erm Farmers Only dot com</u>
<u n="349" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Farmers Only dot com yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="351" who="S0632">you don't have to be lonely with Farmers Only dot com <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="354" who="S0635">yeah that was quite good so yeah that was definitely day one</u>
<u n="355" who="S0632" trans="overlap">so that was like yeah day one on the West Coast</u>
<u n="356" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="357" who="S0632">but we we knew we wanted to go to bed early really didn't we because</u>
<u n="358" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="359" who="S0632">we were gonna go cycling the next day</u>
<u n="360" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0632">and we went just round the corner and rented those bikes</u>
<u n="362" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="363" who="S0632">erm</u>
<u n="364" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0632">and yeah and then we cycled to and most of the way across the Golden Gate bridge</u>
<u n="366" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0632">and we were cycling down by the beach you could see all the people working out</u>
<u n="368" who="S0635">uhu yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="370" who="S0635">lots of people jogging</u>
<u n="371" who="S0632">we went really early actually and I'm glad that we did cos</u>
<u n="372" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="373" who="S0632">one that by the time we were cycling home there were just hordes of people cycling</u>
<u n="374" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0632">of Golden Gate bridge like it less crazy when we went and there was no fog</u>
<u n="376" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="377" who="S0632">cos I know it was notorious for fog but it was a really clear bright sunny day</u>
<u n="378" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0632">as far as I can remember and then we we cycled to that weird park with all the like fake ancient Greek architecture we like had a little sit down there do you remember?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I do it was in it's in the room</u>
<u n="381" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="382" who="S0635">and it's called something park I can't remember</u>
<u n="383" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="384" who="S0635">mm yeah oh was it Palace of the Fine Arts for something wasn't it?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh yes that's it yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and it's like really sort of faux Roman</u>
<u n="387" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0635">wasn't it?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0632">it's faux classical</u>
<u n="390" who="S0635" trans="overlap">with er with historical building for an area with no real history like</u>
<u n="391" who="S0632">well yeah not that history anyway</u>
<u n="392" who="S0635">no</u>
<u n="393" who="S0632">but yeah not that ancient classical European history <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0635">no yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0632">but it was it was really nice and I can't even remember what we did that evening did we we really wanted to go to a tiki bar</u>
<u n="396" who="S0635" trans="overlap">that was the same day we left I think we did that the morning before we drove off down <unclear/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and then we drove oh</u>
<u n="398" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0632">we never did get to that tiki bar</u>
<u n="400" who="S0635">no they were like fully booked</u>
<u n="401" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0632">oh and then we drove down to the big oh my god we really packed it in</u>
<u n="404" who="S0635">yeah we did</u>
<u n="405" who="S0632">and so that that meant that our dinner that night was in that kind of roadside place that I had my first fish <unclear>tacos</unclear> and they were really good</u>
<u n="406" who="S0635">yeah I had a burger I think it was really nice and they sold sort of plaid shirts in their gift shop and I had a bagel and a coffee</u>
<u n="407" who="S0632" trans="overlap">uhu and it was quite a wholesome like roadsidey place</u>
<u n="408" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah it was just called the Roadhouse I think it was great</u>
<u n="409" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it was really nice it was a good first experience down</u>
<u n="412" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="413" who="S0632">Highway one</u>
<u n="414" who="S0635">yeah I mean we drove past like really cool beaches and stuff that we didn't really stop for and there were some weird roadworks so it was kind of slow moving but it didn't</u>
<u n="415" who="S0632">it was quite slow moving and I felt like</u>
<u n="416" who="S0635" trans="overlap">it honestly didn't matter</u>
<u n="417" who="S0632">there was quite a lot of sprawl</u>
<u n="418" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0632">to begin with before we got out onto like the what you</u>
<u n="420" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="421" who="S0632">what you hear about Highway one with all the amazing views and the</u>
<u n="422" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0632">cliffs and the crazy crazy twisty roads that go really close to the sea</u>
<u n="424" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah it's great I mean it was only just really the start of it but that was definitely when I I mean it was relaxing to know that the car was kind of fine</u>
<u n="425" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0635">but then it was just great to be on the road as well</u>
<u n="427" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0635">like it just it was really fun</u>
<u n="429" who="S0632">ah and so that was the night that we got to er</u>
<u n="430" who="S0635">er Ventana?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0632">oh Ventana</u>
<u n="432" who="S0635" trans="overlap">in Big Sur?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0635">must have been yeah which was great that was a really nice campground</u>
<u n="435" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="436" who="S0635">and we got there sort of just it was getting darker and it was <trunc>re</trunc> just really beautiful in that area</u>
<u n="437" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah the sun was setting but everything was easy to find</u>
<u n="438" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="439" who="S0632">spelt really good we pitched</u>
<u n="440" who="S0635">little redwood trees</u>
<u n="441" who="S0632">redwood trees <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="442" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0632">and yeah comfortable comfortable night</u>
<u n="444" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="445" who="S0632">think I was a bit sad the next morning cos I got the text from</u>
<u n="446" who="S0635">oh yeah</u>
<u n="447" who="S0632">mum that <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> had had to be put down</u>
<u n="448" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0632">so in all those pictures from the next day I'm looking like a bit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0632">a bit sad in the eyes</u>
<u n="452" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0632">but erm but it was a really good day still cos we went to Pfeiffer State</u>
<u n="454" who="S0635" trans="overlap">Pfeiffer State beach</u>
<u n="455" who="S0632">and I <trunc>thi</trunc> and</u>
<u n="456" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I've seen a lot of photos that other people have taken of that recently it's a really like popular gem that people are saying</u>
<u n="457" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="458" who="S0635">like oh you should see Pfeiffer State beach</u>
<u n="459" who="S0632">it's a nice beach</u>
<u n="460" who="S0635">yeah cos that big sort of rock with a hole in it that the</u>
<u n="461" who="S0632">that the waves crash though</u>
<u n="462" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0632">yeah that was cool</u>
<u n="464" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="465" who="S0632">and then</u>
<u n="466" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and those giant kelp</u>
<u n="467" who="S0632">yeah there's</u>
<u n="468" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0632">lots of kelp and there was those stone towers those cairns</u>
<u n="470" who="S0635">yeah yeah it was a really nice beach really nice beach and then we stopped on my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s recommendation at</u>
<u n="471" who="S0632">at Poet's house</u>
<u n="472" who="S0635">yeah the Henry Miller was the museum is that right?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0632">maybe</u>
<u n="474" who="S0635">something like that</u>
<u n="475" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0635">yeah gotta remember this too</u>
<u n="477" who="S0632">yeah it's important information isn't it?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="479" who="S0632">that was a really cool spot though honesty system coffee on the porch and it was basically just a book shop in what used to be his house wasn't it?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0635">erm I think so yeah Henry Miller Memorial library</u>
<u n="481" who="S0632">psst <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> Henry Miller Memorial library yeah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0632">slash bookshop and there was that big</u>
<u n="484" who="S0635">there was a</u>
<u n="485" who="S0632" trans="overlap">fluffy cat</u>
<u n="486" who="S0635">big raggedy old cat there and free coffee that you could help yourself to</u>
<u n="487" who="S0632">it was quite dreamy laid back</u>
<u n="488" who="S0635">yeah I didn't actually wanna buy anything but they had</u>
<u n="489" who="S0632">no</u>
<u n="490" who="S0635" trans="overlap">books and records and stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0632">yeah well it was a cool little spot to stop at and there was obviously some sort of open air theatre that they</u>
<u n="492" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="493" who="S0632">weren't using at the time</u>
<u n="494" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah it was kind of the first taste of some of the stuff I really liked about California which was the sort of people sort of just doing what they want in a very beautiful</u>
<u n="495" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0635">place like <unclear>setting up</unclear> <unclear/> things and art and not really very profit driven and stuff but I guess it's a bit hippy</u>
<u n="497" who="S0632">yeah I <trunc>thi</trunc></u>
<u n="498" who="S0635" trans="overlap">but like</u>
<u n="499" who="S0632">I think it is a bit hippy yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0635" trans="overlap">that was the most inspiring</u>
<u n="501" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it was really nice</u>
<u n="502" who="S0635">thing about it yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="505" who="S0632">I enjoyed that</u>
<u n="506" who="S0635">erm and yeah and the like cute little gas stations like tiny little gas pumps next to camp shops and stuff that we stopped in</u>
<u n="507" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="508" who="S0635">to kind of get a few supplies and</u>
<u n="509" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="510" who="S0635">things like that and I'm pretty sure we had to stop in a Walmart or something to get additional camping supplies</u>
<u n="511" who="S0632">yeah I think we wanted a few more bits and bobs like another ground mat and stuff didn't we?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had loaded us up with her really quite vintage camping stuff which was dented and burned and</u>
<u n="513" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>ye</trunc></u>
<u n="514" who="S0635">kind of strange in all in Ziploc bags and yeah we got a roll mat didn't we and maybe some other stuff?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0632">yeah I can't remember what we felt like we were</u>
<u n="516" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="517" who="S0632">conspicuously missing</u>
<u n="518" who="S0635">but felt like we had a pretty good setup really</u>
<u n="519" who="S0632">we were pretty well setup</u>
<u n="520" who="S0635">better than some people I would have thought but yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0632">was the next night</u>
<u n="522" who="S0635" trans="overlap">so so</u>
<u n="523" who="S0632" trans="overlap">Montaña de Oro?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0635">after Pfeiffer State beach yeah it must have been</u>
<u n="525" who="S0632">wow I can't believe</u>
<u n="526" who="S0635" trans="overlap">where were</u>
<u n="527" who="S0632" trans="overlap">they were that close together</u>
<u n="528" who="S0635">where did we have dinner after that? was that maybe where we stopped for that not that appealing fish place where it was like a beautiful</u>
<u n="529" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0635" trans="overlap">location but like</u>
<u n="531" who="S0632">really good location but the food wasn't very good</u>
<u n="532" who="S0635">yeah and it was quite expensive</u>
<u n="533" who="S0632">but we picked up like some slim Jims and spinach tortillas and a bag of grated cheese so we could make dinner at our campsite</u>
<u n="534" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="535" who="S0632">I <unclear/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I think I think we stopped on Monterey</u>
<u n="537" who="S0632">did we stop in Monterey?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0635">for I think either a Walmart or a Whole Foods yeah but I didn't really get much of a sense of the place <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was</u>
<u n="539" who="S0632" trans="overlap">remember driving through Carmel at some point</u>
<u n="540" who="S0635">oh yeah</u>
<u n="541" who="S0632">it smelt amazing</u>
<u n="542" who="S0635">and it was all sort of misty yeah it was amazing</u>
<u n="543" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and it smelt really strongly of pine and the sea</u>
<u n="544" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="545" who="S0632">it was just amazing but yeah that was gorgeous and we stopped at some non-chain supermarket that was quite expensive and we were worried that there was water coming out of the bottom of our car <vocal desc="laugh"/> do you remember that?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0635">oh yeah yeah that was much later it think</u>
<u n="547" who="S0632">no that wasn't much later</u>
<u n="548" who="S0635">no maybe a couple of days later</u>
<u n="549" who="S0632">it was either that day or the day after I think</u>
<u n="550" who="S0635">yeah I do remember yeah we sort of came up it was <pause dur="short"/> cos there's another highway more in slightly more inland from Route one</u>
<u n="551" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="552" who="S0635">I think and we'd somehow got onto that for a while and that was like a small town there which was quite cool</u>
<u n="553" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="554" who="S0635">yeah I remember that</u>
<u n="555" who="S0632">yeah and where was where was the place that we went to the antiques place? like that was on the road from somewhere to somewhere</u>
<u n="556" who="S0635" trans="overlap">oh that might have been that day</u>
<u n="557" who="S0632">so yeah cos there were all these different campsites there was</u>
<u n="558" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="559" who="S0632">Ventana which was easy</u>
<u n="560" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="561" who="S0632">erm the private and then we went to Montaña de Oro which was a state park which was a state park which was</u>
<u n="562" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0632">it was like the hardest ever <pause dur="short"/> what's the word? I can't think cos I'm full of <unclear>coal</unclear></u>
<u n="564" who="S0635">er</u>
<u n="565" who="S0632"><trunc>p</trunc> not puzzle I guess puzzle will do</u>
<u n="566" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="567" who="S0632">to work out</u>
<u n="568" who="S0635">yeah cos we got</u>
<u n="569" who="S0632" trans="overlap">what where the hell our pitch was cos</u>
<u n="570" who="S0635" trans="overlap">we</u>
<u n="571" who="S0632">no one was on duty</u>
<u n="572" who="S0635" trans="overlap">for one reason or <trunc>ano</trunc> I think it was hard to find in the first place er and then like we maybe drove around the whole kind of area like the state park and we found the main campsite but not no we didn't even find the main campsite did we? like it was all really hard to find</u>
<u n="573" who="S0632">we did eventually find a campsite but we were like</u>
<u n="574" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0632">like well we're not pitched here cos we're pitched in the like I can't remember what they called them but like solo</u>
<u n="576" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0632">campsites where you're the only person for a mile</u>
<u n="578" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="579" who="S0632" trans="overlap">but it was like well ours is called ST seven or something</u>
<u n="580" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="581" who="S0632">but and we were looking at the map and there was nothing on there called ST seven but there was deer and badger and rattlesnake and and eventually we somehow worked out that like badger must be ST one and you <trunc>kn</trunc> like there was a code and there was a name and they weren't often put in the same place</u>
<u n="582" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="583" who="S0632">and I think and some place somehow we found both the names together so we could work out that our booking was actually</u>
<u n="584" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="585" who="S0632" trans="overlap">called badger</u>
<u n="586" who="S0635">it was a tiny</u>
<u n="587" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and then looked for badger</u>
<u n="588" who="S0635">it was a tiny photocopied hand-drawn handwritten map on a pin board in the in the park and that without that like we'd have just never found it</u>
<u n="589" who="S0632">and that was like miles away from</u>
<u n="590" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="591" who="S0632">the main campsite as well wasn't it?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="593" who="S0632">it was just like by the side of the road</u>
<u n="594" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="595" who="S0632">and you could see it highlighted</u>
<u n="596" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="597" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and it said <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="598" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0632">and then it said ST one badger</u>
<u n="600" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0632">and it was like oh so ST one is badger and badger is up there but not before we'd already pitched in the wrong place and had people come and tell us we couldn't pitch there cos it was their pitch</u>
<u n="602" who="S0635">yeah it was like looking for a Post-it note in a national park literally</u>
<u n="603" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and</u>
<u n="604" who="S0635" trans="overlap">but we did actually get there after expending too much energy but we did yeah and we got up</u>
<u n="605" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="606" who="S0635">got up the hill and</u>
<u n="607" who="S0632">it was it was a knackering cos it's a <trunc>hi</trunc> it was a hike to camp the campground wasn't it? so you couldn't drive there</u>
<u n="608" who="S0635">it was</u>
<u n="609" who="S0632">you had to drive as close as you could park your car and then hike well we'd already done that once in the wrong place</u>
<u n="610" who="S0635">yeah so then we had to go back up unpack go back down again <pause dur="short"/> and load up the car go to the next one and then go back up and <trunc>c</trunc> and <trunc>p</trunc> I mean we ended up doing the hike maybe like <vocal desc="laugh"/> seven or eight times I think in one yeah</u>
<u n="611" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I was so tired I was so tired</u>
<u n="612" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="613" who="S0632">and that really galling thing was it was stunningly beautiful</u>
<u n="614" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="615" who="S0632">and the sun was going down as we were like</u>
<u n="616" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="617" who="S0632">finally pitching in the right place and I was like</u>
<u n="618" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="619" who="S0632">if this is the wrong place I'm not moving again</u>
<u n="620" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0632">but I was getting really upset cos we'd bought that nice like local wine and I wanted to sit up there and drink it as the sun went down</u>
<u n="622" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0632">but instead we were like racing the sunset and I was so tired</u>
<u n="624" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0632">that was just that was like that was probably the lowest point</u>
<u n="626" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0632">of the trip because on the whole it was a brilliant trip and even that</u>
<u n="628" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="629" who="S0632">was great but it was just</u>
<u n="630" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="631" who="S0632">there were that one evening I was just really pissed off because <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="632" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0632">I couldn't believe how hard it was to find out pitch we'd left plenty of time to pitch before sunset</u>
<u n="634" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="635" who="S0632">but we spent like over an hour looking for our pitch and then probably another two hours pitching and re-pitching in the right place</u>
<u n="636" who="S0635">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0632" trans="overlap">but anyway I was quite happy because we did actually make it the thing is I wish we were staying for more than one night cos we stayed for one night and we woke up in the morning after all the <vocal desc="misc"/> and barking noises all night</u>
<u n="638" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm yeah it was <unclear>cool</unclear></u>
<u n="639" who="S0632">and then it was like we were on a cliff in the clouds we were up on a cliff overlooking the sea <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos</u>
<u n="640" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah it looked totally different</u>
<u n="641" who="S0632" trans="overlap">like fog was so thick</u>
<u n="642" who="S0635">mm and we saw like a little jogger run round like a little ghost somewhere on the distant cliff</u>
<u n="643" who="S0632" trans="overlap">all in white</u>
<u n="644" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="645" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah and we did do one of the little walks</u>
<u n="646" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="647" who="S0632">cos it said there was rattlesnakes that we had to be careful where we stepped</u>
<u n="648" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="649" who="S0632">that was quite exciting</u>
<u n="650" who="S0635">famous for like California quails I think and rattlesnakes</u>
<u n="651" who="S0632" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="652" who="S0635">and</u>
<u n="653" who="S0632">cos I think I saw we saw the quails</u>
<u n="654" who="S0635">we did yeah</u>
<u n="655" who="S0632">yeah but we didn't see any rattlesnakes</u>
<u n="656" who="S0635">no</u>
<u n="657" who="S0632">and yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="659" who="S0632">and that was all good and then we felt filthy and we wanted to go to the Madonna Inn that really er kitsch place</u>
<u n="660" who="S0632">uhu</u>
<u n="661" who="S0635">for lunch but we were filthy and the facilities there weren't good enough for us to get clean in</u>
<u n="662" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="663" who="S0632">so</u>
<u n="664" who="S0635">and there weren't any <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="665" who="S0632">well there weren't any I think</u>
<u n="666" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="667" who="S0632">there were some communal showers</u>
<u n="668" who="S0635">I don't think there were <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="669" who="S0632" trans="overlap">somewhere or well there were at least communal toilets that were just the worst</u>
<u n="670" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0632" trans="overlap">like they smelt so bad they were so filthy that</u>
<u n="672" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="673" who="S0632">you couldn't even like have a hand basin wash of any sort so</u>
<u n="674" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah yeah so we went to a Whole Foods and then I and freshened up in their bathrooms</u>
<u n="675" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I I got my wedding gel nails taken off</u>
<u n="676" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yes you want to the nail place</u>
<u n="677" who="S0632">at the mall</u>
<u n="678" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and I went somewhere I think I went to like TK Maxx to not buy any clothes while you were doing that</u>
<u n="679" who="S0632" trans="overlap">while I did that</u>
<u n="680" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="681" who="S0632" trans="overlap">didn't take long it only cost me five dollars and they took them all off cos they started falling off with all the camping and it just looked stupid erm yeah so we freshened up and no one would know would have known that we hadn't had a proper shower <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="682" who="S0635">yeah yeah no we did good yeah</u>
<u n="683" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and we were we went to the Madonna Inn and we had our strange lunch amongst all the insane decor</u>
<u n="684" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="685" who="S0632">this Barbie doll meets German beer house</u>
<u n="686" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="687" who="S0632">and yeah ate heartily I think the antiques place must have been on that day as well</u>
<u n="688" who="S0635">I think it was too</u>
<u n="689" who="S0632">but wasn't there something palace that people like really suggested and we drove up to but didn't go on?</u>
<u n="690" who="S0635" trans="overlap">oh was that that day? I think it must have been</u>
<u n="691" who="S0632">yeah it was in that area</u>
<u n="692" who="S0635">yeah erm Hearst castle</u>
<u n="693" who="S0632">Hearst castle</u>
<u n="694" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="695" who="S0632">cos that's really like chintzy and tacky too but it was it was quite expensive and you had to go like on their tour</u>
<u n="696" who="S0635" trans="overlap">it was really expensive you you had to yeah like</u>
<u n="697" who="S0632" trans="overlap">er and you couldn't like get up to it on your own you had to wait for a bus to come and take you to the actual place and</u>
<u n="698" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="699" who="S0632">it's like quite a big time commitment</u>
<u n="700" who="S0635">it would have taken the whole day yeah</u>
<u n="701" who="S0632">and we didn't have the whole day we we needed to</u>
<u n="702" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="703" who="S0632">get to our next campsite</u>
<u n="704" who="S0635" trans="overlap">but we did kind of see it up on the hill and we</u>
<u n="705" who="S0632">we saw it up on the hill yeah</u>
<u n="706" who="S0635" trans="overlap">stopped in the kind of there was the centre here</u>
<u n="707" who="S0632">looked through the books</u>
<u n="708" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="709" who="S0632">at the pictures of <vocal desc="laugh"/> what it looks like</u>
<u n="710" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0632">okay yeah okay</u>
<u n="712" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I think as European it's kind of like it would have been interesting from like a cultural perspective but like not</u>
<u n="713" who="S0632">I wasn't desperate to see it for its opulence</u>
<u n="714" who="S0635" trans="overlap">like yeah we've seen a lot of really opulent old buildings don't have to see a fake one</u>
<u n="715" who="S0632" trans="overlap">that are that are real yeah</u>
<u n="716" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="717" who="S0632">but erm we needed to get to our next campsite anyway and</u>
<u n="718" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="719" who="S0632">that was a really nice one too</u>
<u n="720" who="S0635">mm yes that one like like it was such a relief even though it wasn't like really fancy</u>
<u n="721" who="S0632">it wasn't really</u>
<u n="722" who="S0635">to have someone just be like oh yeah here's your spot we have wi-fi like there's</u>
<u n="723" who="S0632">you name's literally on it</u>
<u n="724" who="S0635">yeah like there's showers and a pool and it's like yeah</u>
<u n="725" who="S0632" trans="overlap">there was a good shower block and there was a nice pool and we were really close to the even though it wasn't as</u>
<u n="726" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="727" who="S0632">scenic as the other one it was actually easier to get to the beach</u>
<u n="728" who="S0635">yes yeah</u>
<u n="729" who="S0632">cos although we weren't on the cliff overlooking it</u>
<u n="730" who="S0635">that's true yeah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0632">we just walked under an underpass <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="732" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="733" who="S0632">and we were at the beach and that's when</u>
<u n="734" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="735" who="S0632">we invented wave crouching</u>
<u n="736" who="S0635">yeah and we got weird black stuff stuck to our feet</u>
<u n="737" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="738" who="S0635">and er I think we saw those giant like <pause dur="short"/> weird bug things or something</u>
<u n="739" who="S0632">the like beach erm wood</u>
<u n="740" who="S0635">woodlice</u>
<u n="741" who="S0632">woodlice</u>
<u n="742" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="743" who="S0632">yeah the I think</u>
<u n="744" who="S0635" trans="overlap">they were kind of horrible</u>
<u n="745" who="S0632">we saw those in Pfeiffer State beach</u>
<u n="746" who="S0635">oh okay oh yeah we did cos we when we were picking up rocks</u>
<u n="747" who="S0632">all the rocks</u>
<u n="748" who="S0635" trans="overlap">from the cairns yeah</u>
<u n="749" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="750" who="S0635">they were under there</u>
<u n="751" who="S0632">we saw pelicans I think at the</u>
<u n="752" who="S0635">oh yeah</u>
<u n="753" who="S0632">at the other beach and we saw avocado trees we'd got</u>
<u n="754" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="755" who="S0632">south enough they were huge</u>
<u n="756" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="757" who="S0632">avocado trees</u>
<u n="758" who="S0635">yeah it was nice there it was like kind of a family campground thing</u>
<u n="759" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it was quite family friendly and</u>
<u n="760" who="S0635" trans="overlap">but it was cute it was like a proper American experience</u>
<u n="761" who="S0632">we had a a second erm</u>
<u n="762" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="763" who="S0632">in a night in a row having erm the er slim jim burrito for dinner with a Whole Food salad and</u>
<u n="764" who="S0635">and a Sierra Nevada</u>
<u n="765" who="S0632">and a Sierra Nevada</u>
<u n="766" who="S0635">beer yeah</u>
<u n="767" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I think we had <unclear/> too cos they had the nice <trunc>firepl</trunc> cos we weren't allowed to light a fire</u>
<u n="768" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="769" who="S0632">in the last place</u>
<u n="770" who="S0635">yeah they had like <unclear/> which we did</u>
<u n="771" who="S0632">we did</u>
<u n="772" who="S0635">it was quite it was a good night actually</u>
<u n="773" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it was</u>
<u n="774" who="S0635">I felt pretty good there</u>
<u n="775" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="776" who="S0635">yeah and I think we'd been to that antique shop that day and I think the next day we did some laundry finally and I remember</u>
<u n="777" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="778" who="S0635">you started to write down notes from the honeymoon maybe the last time that you <trunc>d</trunc> or first or last but you you kind of started</u>
<u n="779" who="S0632">I think I I did start writing notes while we were doing the laundry I sat by the pool and wrote up what we'd done so far</u>
<u n="780" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="781" who="S0632">erm</u>
<u n="782" who="S0635">yeah there was nice warm pool there</u>
<u n="783" who="S0632">it was really brief but I just was like ah so much is happening every day it's gonna be</u>
<u n="784" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="785" who="S0632">too easy to forget</u>
<u n="786" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="787" who="S0632">what we've done every day</u>
<u n="788" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="789" who="S0632">but that was only yeah three days down the coast and</u>
<u n="790" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="791" who="S0632">the next day we drove to LA</u>
<u n="792" who="S0635">yeah yeah after that we drove to LA</u>
<u n="793" who="S0632">and we stopped to see those elephant seals <pause dur="short"/> I feel like that was the day we saw the elephant seals</u>
<u n="794" who="S0635">yes it was on yeah between California and</u>
<u n="795" who="S0632">well it's all California</u>
<u n="796" who="S0635" trans="overlap">between yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="797" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="798" who="S0635">Los Angeles and that area yeah er well I guess it was Santa Barbara wasn't it?</u>
<u n="799" who="S0632">it could be Santa Barbara</u>
<u n="800" who="S0635">which is erm which was right near where we were staying and we stopped at quite a good breakfast place didn't look fancy but the food was good</u>
<u n="801" who="S0632">oh yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0635" trans="overlap">it was like a diner yeah</u>
<u n="803" who="S0632">yeah we had a good</u>
<u n="804" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="805" who="S0632">hearty breakfast there</u>
<u n="806" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="807" who="S0632">and then we were just driving to LA and there was</u>
<u n="808" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="809" who="S0632">a sign that said elephant seal beach or elephant seal</u>
<u n="810" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="811" who="S0632">viewing point and we're like stop there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="812" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="813" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and they were hilarious</u>
<u n="814" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="815" who="S0632">and numerous</u>
<u n="816" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="817" who="S0632">and</u>
<u n="818" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="819" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="820" who="S0635">I remember the landscape being quite sort of flatter outside LA</u>
<u n="821" who="S0632">yeah it it sudden flattened off quite a lot</u>
<u n="822" who="S0635">and</u>
<u n="823" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="824" who="S0635">everything was very dry</u>
<u n="825" who="S0632">it was so dry</u>
<u n="826" who="S0635">I mean it looks like I guess you've seen it from lots of films and stuff and it just looks like sort of I've seen it in lots of films that kind of I guess <trunc>coun</trunc> like California countryside</u>
<u n="827" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="828" who="S0635">like where it's not state parky it's just sort of flat and</u>
<u n="829" who="S0632">farmy? or</u>
<u n="830" who="S0635">farmy</u>
<u n="831" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="832" who="S0635">yeah dry but mm</u>
<u n="833" who="S0632">yeah so we <pause dur="short"/> we got into LA that night and we booked into our Hollywood hotel</u>
<u n="834" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="835" who="S0632">and that</u>
<u n="836" who="S0635">oh we drove through Malibu</u>
<u n="837" who="S0632">we drove through Malibu we did</u>
<u n="838" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah which was fun like an erm episode of MTV Cribs</u>
<u n="839" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="840" who="S0635">yeah just</u>
<u n="841" who="S0632">where you don't get to look inside any of the houses <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="842" who="S0635">no</u>
<u n="843" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="844" who="S0635">no but they all looked amazing</u>
<u n="845" who="S0632">they were just insane</u>
<u n="846" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="847" who="S0632" trans="overlap">all piled on top of each other down down the coast</u>
<u n="848" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="849" who="S0632">and</u>
<u n="850" who="S0635">mega fancy</u>
<u n="851" who="S0632">so fancy was that and that was that first night the night we went to the Mexican place like almost next to our hotel?</u>
<u n="852" who="S0635">yes which we were like the only people in it and we had horchatas with a cactus in apparently</u>
<u n="853" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="854" who="S0635">and but it was good</u>
<u n="855" who="S0632">it was good</u>
<u n="856" who="S0635" trans="overlap">good food</u>
<u n="857" who="S0632">yes</u>
<u n="858" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="859" who="S0632">I think we had a really low key night that night</u>
<u n="860" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="861" who="S0632">cos we were just knackered and we were like hotel and had showers and just</u>
<u n="862" who="S0635">yeah did we do anything other than the Mexican? I feel like we must have done but maybe we didn't</u>
<u n="863" who="S0632">maybe we did but <trunc>wha</trunc> I feel like we had <trunc>li</trunc> dinner quite early cos we were the only people in there</u>
<u n="864" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="865" who="S0632">and then maybe we went back and like relaxed a bit before going out again</u>
<u n="866" who="S0635">yeah what did we do? I'm pretty sure we went and had a look in a we sort of walked up to the Hollywood Forever cemetery</u>
<u n="867" who="S0632">we did</u>
<u n="868" who="S0635">but it was closed</u>
<u n="869" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="870" who="S0635">erm but we got a nice sense of like the kind of houses and stuff and</u>
<u n="871" who="S0632">yeah we definitely did</u>
<u n="872" who="S0635">people and the and sort of all the</u>
<u n="873" who="S0632" trans="overlap">did we go next door to the</u>
<u n="874" who="S0635" trans="overlap">the palms in the sunset</u>
<u n="875" who="S0632">did we just go next door to the bar?</u>
<u n="876" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="877" who="S0632">into the punk hairdresser's bar?</u>
<u n="878" who="S0635">I think we did yeah I dunno if that was when we saw the dog</u>
<u n="879" who="S0632">no I think we saw the dog the next day or</u>
<u n="880" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="881" who="S0632">did we not?</u>
<u n="882" who="S0635">I think no I think that was that day</u>
<u n="883" who="S0632">oh we did see the dog that day?</u>
<u n="884" who="S0635">yeah a really nice small puppy</u>
<u n="885" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah you're right we did and that</u>
<u n="886" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and we followed it in and it peed everywhere</u>
<u n="887" who="S0632">and it peed everywhere but</u>
<u n="888" who="S0635" trans="overlap">but no one cared</u>
<u n="889" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it was adorable and we had a couple of beers local beers</u>
<u n="890" who="S0635">uhu canned</u>
<u n="891" who="S0632">canned</u>
<u n="892" who="S0635">and we spoke to the nice lady there I think and said we have one day in LA tomorrow like what would you do?</u>
<u n="893" who="S0632">if you had one day in LA</u>
<u n="894" who="S0635">and she was like oh I'd just go to the beach <pause dur="short"/> so we did</u>
<u n="895" who="S0632">well she said that <trunc>ac</trunc> she'd go to erm Venice Beach and she'd see a gig and we did look up what gigs were on</u>
<u n="896" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="897" who="S0632">but there weren't any</u>
<u n="898" who="S0635">no</u>
<u n="899" who="S0632">good ones that we could go to that last minute</u>
<u n="900" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="901" who="S0632">erm but yeah so we we came there the next day for breakfast as well</u>
<u n="902" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="903" who="S0632">cos we liked it</u>
<u n="904" who="S0635">which was good</u>
<u n="905" who="S0632">I had to had some sort of matcha green smoothie and</u>
<u n="906" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="907" who="S0632">pancakes or something <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="908" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="909" who="S0632">and then we we did do Venice Beach and it was really fun all the people watching it's so huge</u>
<u n="910" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="911" who="S0632">and all the skaters and the bodybuilders and the people on the <unclear>boardwalk</unclear></u>
<u n="912" who="S0635">yeah er yeah I just drove us there we parked in front of the house with a huge cactus which was amazing</u>
<u n="913" who="S0632">huge</u>
<u n="914" who="S0635" trans="overlap">on kind of a <unclear/></u>
<u n="915" who="S0632">we were kind of a slightly more like not suburban but I guess maybe a bit suburban like people</u>
<u n="916" who="S0635">yeah it was gorgeous</u>
<u n="917" who="S0632">a</u>
<u n="918" who="S0635">but yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0632">residential area</u>
<u n="920" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="921" who="S0632">and and we walked up</u>
<u n="922" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="923" who="S0632">Abbot Kinney</u>
<u n="924" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="925" who="S0632">that really cool street full of antiques and</u>
<u n="926" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="927" who="S0632">boutiques and <unclear/></u>
<u n="928" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="929" who="S0632">which was nice didn't buy anything too expensive</u>
<u n="930" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="931" who="S0632">but nice to browse and</u>
<u n="932" who="S0635">yeah it was cool to kind of see and it was sort of like boutique fashion and stuff like a sort of a fancy LA</u>
<u n="933" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="934" who="S0635">things</u>
<u n="935" who="S0632">I it was a bit of a cocktail day as well because like</u>
<u n="936" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="937" who="S0632">we stopped in that nice place for lunch</u>
<u n="938" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="939" who="S0632">at Venice Beach and I had and like er like a <unclear/> or something that it was</u>
<u n="940" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="941" who="S0632">called and it was really hot and spicy</u>
<u n="942" who="S0635">and I had an asparagus and bacon pizza</u>
<u n="943" who="S0632">you always remember your pizza toppings <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="944" who="S0635">yeah it was unusual</u>
<u n="945" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it's important to you</u>
<u n="946" who="S0635">and it was really good</u>
<u n="947" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="948" who="S0635">it yeah</u>
<u n="949" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I had another <unclear>fish taco</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="950" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="951" who="S0632">er and we went up to the the top of that building for another cocktail cos it said it had a good view</u>
<u n="952" who="S0635">yes</u>
<u n="953" who="S0632">of the whole beach</u>
<u n="954" who="S0635">we did yeah</u>
<u n="955" who="S0632">and the sun was setting</u>
<u n="956" who="S0635" trans="overlap">it as good and we did go and sort of squat in the water</u>
<u n="957" who="S0632">yeah we did</u>
<u n="958" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and swim a bit and then our pants got wet so we had to sit and let them dry</u>
<u n="959" who="S0632">yeah I went commando</u>
<u n="960" who="S0635" trans="overlap">it was erm yeah</u>
<u n="961" who="S0632">I had to do it really subtly but</u>
<u n="962" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="963" who="S0632">cos we were I just wanted to paddle and then a big wave <trunc>ca</trunc> I kind of wished that I had brought my swimming costume so we could have swum</u>
<u n="964" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah it was an amazing beach</u>
<u n="965" who="S0632">it was a</u>
<u n="966" who="S0635" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="967" who="S0632">lovely lovely beach but erm I <trunc>di</trunc></u>
<u n="968" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="969" who="S0632">I wasn't expecting to swim so I just wanted to paddle er</u>
<u n="970" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="971" who="S0632">and my pants got wet</u>
<u n="972" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="973" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="974" who="S0635">yeah I remember that</u>
<u n="975" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="976" who="S0635">and then yeah big big murals we kind of wandered around having had a good meal</u>
<u n="977" who="S0632">then we just and then I think we went to we we got back in the car and we drove to the erm er Amoeba Records in LA</u>
<u n="978" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="979" who="S0632">which is super massive</u>
<u n="980" who="S0635">yeah it was dark by then and that was kind on was that on Sunset Boulevard?</u>
<u n="981" who="S0632">yeah I think so at least very close to it</u>
<u n="982" who="S0635" trans="overlap">one of the big <pause dur="short"/> er yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>whi</trunc> it's where all the star <trunc>wa</trunc>walks are</u>
<u n="983" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="984" who="S0635">and stuff which we didn't really pay any attention to</u>
<u n="985" who="S0632" trans="overlap">we weren't really I wasn't paying attention to that at all cos</u>
<u n="986" who="S0635">no</u>
<u n="987" who="S0632">it's just pavements with names in</u>
<u n="988" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="989" who="S0632">erm</u>
<u n="990" who="S0635" trans="overlap">but Amoeba was great</u>
<u n="991" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="992" who="S0635">and they were playing Whammy over the</u>
<u n="993" who="S0632">they were they were playing</u>
<u n="994" who="S0635" trans="overlap">the B fifty-twos</u>
<u n="995" who="S0632">Whammy</u>
<u n="996" who="S0635">and we bought like another armload of records</u>
<u n="997" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="998" who="S0635">Apples in Stereo</u>
<u n="999" who="S0632" trans="overlap">for the car</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0635">and Guided by Voices mostly</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0635">yeah it was very good</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0632">and we must have just gone to bed</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0635">yeah I think we did</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0632">I don't think we had incredibly late nights I think cos we did get out early and get</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0632">get a lot in in the day we were just ready to go to sleep</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0632">and when we were in hotels we were like we're in a hotel we've gotta make the most of</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0632">having a bed and a shower and</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0632">curtains</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0635">when did we go to the Watts Towers? did we</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0632" trans="overlap">that was the next day that was</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I feel like it was the same day cos the next day we went straight to Salvation <trunc>Mou</trunc> and we didn't do them both on the same day</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0635">so I think we must have done the Watts Towers in the morning before we went to the beach</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0632">right</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0635">I think we did</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0632">yeah we did you're right</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0632">you're right we did</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0635" trans="overlap">cos I but I didn't feel like quite enough of one day</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0632">jeez though I mean</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0632">that not enough for one day like</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0635" trans="overlap">no well I just knowing that we crammed so much in</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0632">I really felt like we went on a</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0632">different day but yeah I guess we did the Watts Towers first</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah I was thinking that too</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0632">so I was so glad we went cos</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0632">you just have to ignore all that like hysteria about it being a bad neighbourhood and stuff cos</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah all the Tripadvisor things</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0632">it's like really? and I felt bad for feeling worried about going cos we were it there were just like children playing outside <vocal desc="laugh"/> and</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah it was a really nice little art community</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0632" trans="overlap">with a really nice community centre</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0632">and they had that that exhibition on Thirty Years and I Still Can't Breathe and it made me wanna cry</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I hadn't like expected that I'd expected to go and see this piece of outsider art that I'd read about a hundred times and I loved</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0632">but erm we were waiting in the community centre for the <trunc>t</trunc> for our tour to start which</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0632">just turned out to be me you and the tour guide who was amazing</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0632">er so it was like a <trunc>per</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> almost like a personal tour but</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah it was great he was really sweet</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0632" trans="overlap">while we were waiting and I was</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0632">yeah while we were waiting and I erm and I was looking at all the artwork it it really hit me really hard</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0632">like I couldn't I don't know I just felt</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0635" trans="overlap">well the area was part of that famous face riots wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0635">I guess thirty years ago in the eighties or</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0632">it's <unclear/> historically</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0635">yeah and just sort of saying how it still hasn't changed and</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0632"><trunc>ye</trunc> <vocal desc="sigh"/> but <trunc>anyw</trunc></u>
<u n="1062" who="S0635" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0632">yeah anyway that was an unexpected blow and like they kind of brought in the the <trunc>hi</trunc>history of the slave trade and er seeing like little Union Jacks on the ships and things in the artwork</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0632">and you're like oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1066" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0632">so yeah that was like an unexpected little little punch there I was really glad that we went for lots of reasons</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0632">and the Watts Towers were just as amazing as I had expected them to be</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0632">erm</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah better to be honest</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0632">well our tour guide was a really</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0632">cool guy who really knew a lot of little details about it that you don't necessarily</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0632">get from the big books that just talk about it as an overall thing</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0632">you need more about like the layout of it and</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0632">like where the all the different bottles were from like what kind of bottle this was and</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah and like his wife's high-heeled shoes or something</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0632">and her boots</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0635">boots stuck in the wall</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0632" trans="overlap">that he'd like set in the wall yeah</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0635">yeah yeah I think there's something about being inside like <trunc>s</trunc> them you know like a that's what how they were meant to be seen not like photos in a book or something</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0632">yeah like big cos they</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0632">that's the whole point of those</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0632">those large <trunc>enviro</trunc> like environments that you actually</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0632">go inside and move around inside cos that's the way they're meant to be experienced</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it's it's a 3D immersive experience</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0632">so it was so good to be able to go</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0632">it would have been great if I could have gone before writing my dissertation but</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0635" trans="overlap">oh I know</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0632">but it was it was really good to go having</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0632">like read so much about them to actually go</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0632">and be in them cos all of the theory that I'd written about was like you need to go and be in them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1106" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I was like I haven't been in these and I really want to</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0632">and you know that's part of their subversive power taking over space and all that learning about his reasons for sticking it where he did cos the the cable cars used to go by but they don't any more</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0632">so it was all really interesting</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and now it's like the only reason that like white tourists would go to Watts probably</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0632" trans="overlap">would go there is to see</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0632">that yeah</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0632">although some people had never heard of it they just seemed like they'd stumbled across it like those people who took our photograph for us</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0635">yeah I'm sure</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0632">cos that</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0635" trans="overlap">there's a lot of people in LA who like have never been there or heard it</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0632">I thought that was really cool</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0632">I loved that</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0635">yeah that was great that really like made me happy seeing <pause dur="short"/> real outsider art mm</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0632">and those two days in a row wasn't it</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0635">yeah so I guess</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0632" trans="overlap">just mm</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0635">the next day we just like we were just so pleased to see outsider art that we should just do that <vocal desc="laugh"/> again <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1131" who="S0632">well we were</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0635" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1133" who="S0632">always gonna</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0632">go and see <trunc>p</trunc> er</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0632">er Salvation mountain because</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0632">big big <unclear>bucketless</unclear> tick there</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0632">and it was so funny having come from like Ventana campground which was all lush and green and foresty and then just like less than a week later we were driving through the desert</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0632">to to Niland</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0635">Niland yeah</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0632" trans="overlap">almost almost in Mexico</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0635" trans="overlap">we stopped at the Elliott Smith mural in Echo park before</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0632">ah</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0635">that which was cool for me to see</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah that was cool took your picture</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0635">yeah I don't think there was anything else</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0632">no</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0635">other than that except that yeah the landscape just completely changed it's like to I mean to</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0632"><vocal desc="sneeze"/></u>
<u n="1154" who="S0635">dry dry dry and dry I mean it wasn't really a very pleasurable drive for the first hour or two maybe? like it was like the sort of area outside of California</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0632" trans="overlap">just sprawl</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0635">like big it just seems like big towns kind of <pause dur="short"/> endless it seemed like a kind of rough places I dunno they just seemed like harsh places to live like very hot dry</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0635">boxy buildings</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0632">yeah cos there were little towns even</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0632">quite far out in the desert and it just didn't seem like a fun place to live</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0632">quite rough looking and freight trains just hurdling through</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0632"><trunc>everyth</trunc> I was just so hot</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0635">yeah we even ran into like Mexican border patrol didn't we?</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0632" trans="overlap">we did</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0635">even though we didn't cross the border</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0632" trans="overlap">we didn't cross the border we were close enough but there was like some sort of checkpoint</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0632">and they</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I think cos of all the trains</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0632">they checked our passports</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0632">and they must get so many people come down there to see Salvation mountain though</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0635">yeah I think people either come for because they live there or to see Salvation mountain or because they've hitched a ride from Mexico on a freight train <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1177" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0635">I don't know</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0632" trans="overlap">we came to see Salvation mountain</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0635">yeah we were one of those <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1181" who="S0632">I was so excited</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0632">oh but oh my god it was hot</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0632">I think the moment I stepped out of the car you could feel the heat coming from above and below like all the sand was like reflecting the heat back up</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0632">I've never been so hot in my life</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0635">I'm not sure I have either yeah</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0632">it was just ridiculous but I was absolutely adamant to get out of the car and explore I think we spent a good half an hour out in the</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0632" trans="overlap">sun er I think it was unfortunate the way it <unclear>timed</unclear> out cos it was pretty much midday <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1192" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0632">and we knew we knew we needed to get there we like</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0635">and it was July</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and and get back again so we needed</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0632">basically we couldn't avoid it being around midday</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0635">no</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0632">it could be slightly earlier or slightly later but</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and there was there's nowhere to stay near there</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0632">no and you I don't wanna be stuck out there</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0635">no</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0632">so but it was totally worth it was just</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0632">everything and more that I</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0632">expected it to be</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0632">and there weren't too many people there</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0635">no</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0632"><trunc>sor</trunc> and it was free</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0635">no and after and we heard the er caretaker yelling at his wife which I</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0632" trans="overlap">he did</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0635" trans="overlap">thought thought was a strange juxtaposition to the message of peace and love</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0632">yeah and Slab city nearby but it's like you know what? if had to live in this heat I'd probably be just about ready to kill anyone</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0635" trans="overlap">well I think Slab city clears out in the summer cos it is just too hot to be there and I</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it's too hot</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and I think the caretaker kind of has to be there but</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0632">and go mad</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0635">yeah it's pretty rough</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0632">yeah it's too no you can't live in a caravan in the desert</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu yeah</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0632" trans="overlap">in midsummer and</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0635">we got out and took some photos of Niland as well just cos it was so</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0632">it was so</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0635">run down like</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0632">so empty and run down</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0632">oh yeah and then was that the night we drove to Palm Springs?</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0635">yeah cos that was where we stayed yeah so</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0635">after that we yeah</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0632">that was a bit of a relief</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0635">so we went back to Palm Springs still really hot but</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0635">we had a pool</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0632">well they had mechanisms for coping with it like every every</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0632">business had an awning that jetted out</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0632">cold mists of watery air</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0632">like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1244" who="S0635">yeah and</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0632">and</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0635">it was like er we did the mystery hotel thing so it was like</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0632">we didn't know where we were gonna stay</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0635" trans="overlap">it cos almost nothing to stay there and it was really good <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it was like a motel but like a really nice motel</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0632">and our room was literally by the pool</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0632">just walked out of our door and into the pool and talked to the other tourists</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0632">sit sit out there and cool down</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0632">we were right next to the kind of mountain that backs it as well</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0632">I felt like that's part of the reason it was a bit cooler like especially our hotel cos it was in like</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0632">the shade of the mountain half the day</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and there were hummingbirds flying around and</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0632">there were</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0635">big cactuses out the front and they had a sort of gothic font that said royal inn or whatever it as</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0632">Royal Sun inn</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0635">Royal Sun inn yeah</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0635">and I think we after having a quick break we went out and had tiki bar and a kind of snacky dinner</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0632">we did we we went for their like sharers' platter and</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0632">a couple of cocktails at the tiki Bar</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0632">which was really fun cos we didn't get to</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0632">go in San Francisco so</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0635">no</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0632">but there were lots of like tiki type places</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0632">in Palm Springs it was</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0632" trans="overlap">such a party town my impression of it was definitely like party town for the retired <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1282" who="S0635">I'd love to go back it was <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1283" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1284" who="S0635">like it was so good so good</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0632">oh it was mental and so yeah I would like freshen up go out have tiki drinks come home again and then the next day <vocal desc="gasp"/> it was so hot but needed to go and get breakfast and as per usual and as per our generation we had to google where the best place for breakfast was</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so we went to</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0635">Pinocchio's</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0632">Pinocchio's which was so camp and they had bottomless champagne for breakfast for three dollars ninety was it?</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0635">something <trunc>r</trunc> like that yeah</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0632" trans="overlap">something obscene bottomless champagne for less than four dollars and I knew that we were going into the desert that day so I shouldn't really drink but I also was like I'm on honeymoon and there's bottomless champagne <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1292" who="S0635">and <trunc>everyo</trunc> I mean it was completely packed out</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0632" trans="overlap">everyone</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0635">everyone</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0635" trans="overlap">in there was doing it</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0632">that's why</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0635">you know</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0632">I asked the waitress about it cos I was we were waiting for our seat and every single person was drinking champagne or some sort of champagne with like</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0632">erm oh I can't remember what you call them now but when you just put like a</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0635" trans="overlap">it's like a mimosa</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0632">a mimosa</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0635" trans="overlap">or orange juice yeah</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah you put some like fruit puree or juice in there and so I I had mine as a mimosa as well</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0632">so it was a bit more breakfasty</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0632">but erm yeah and I did not finish my bottle of champagne but if I had they would have replaced it</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0632">but that's why I asked the waitress I was like is it some sort of party of celebration today cos I'm noticing</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0632">everyone's got champagne and it's like eight o'clock <vocal desc="laugh"/> in the morning</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0635">yeah and there were the two Mexican busboys who seemed kind of harassed cos it was just overrun</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0635">with kind of drunk people <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1317" who="S0632" trans="overlap">they were really really</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0635" trans="overlap">er in the morning but yeah</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0632" trans="overlap">really good like erm service though</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah yeah it was great</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0632" trans="overlap">erm yeah she was just like oh that's our bottomless champagne</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0632">and I'm like I have to have that I don't even remember what I ate but I remember the champagne</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I didn't get to have any cos I was driving</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0632">I know I wish we could have taken like the remainder of the bottle with us or something just to make sure that you had some wine and stuff in Napa that was why we wanted to buy a bottle and</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0632" trans="overlap">take it back to our</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0635">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0632" trans="overlap">hotel room</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0635" trans="overlap">they usually have beers in the evening</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0635" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1333" who="S0632">I know it's not fair you have to be the designated driver</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm yeah er so what <trunc>di</trunc> else did we do that day? was that Joshua Tree?</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0632">that was Joshua Tree</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0632">so it was really insane for me to drink like half a bottle of champagne</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0632" trans="overlap">that morning but did take a huge</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0632">bottle of water with us</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0632">and it was a few hour drive to Joshua Tree and I've had a big breakfast so by the time we got there I'd probably sobered up and</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> rehydrated and that was a really gorgeous place we went to the was it the Hidden Valley? the secret valley? that they they <unclear/> it out and now it's all I mean it's all reclaimed by the native species and stuff but</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0635">the secret valley?</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0632">yeah the place that we walked</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0635">oh that was called oh the</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0635">yeah I think that's probably right yeah</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0635">yeah that was kind of a naturey walk yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's cool</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0632">yeah so we saw that big kind of iguana thing</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0635">yeah we saw an iguana yeah I mean it wasn't a long well it was like a mile around or something</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah it was just like a mile round but we took it easy cos we didn't wanna get too hot</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah and we saw people climbing the big Burrito rock or whatever</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah people free crimeing free crimeing?</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0635"><vocal desc="laugh"/> free climbing</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0632" trans="overlap">free climbing the Burrito rock</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0635">yeah we saw and iguana and we sort of drank a lot and sprang between rocks drank a little water</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0632">yeah enjoyed the landscape and</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0632">the <unclear>pinion</unclear> trees</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0635" trans="overlap">kind of reminded</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1366" who="S0635">cos we were not long <trunc>wha</trunc> Buffy and it reminded me the</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh yeah the the like erm</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0635" trans="overlap">the first Slayer scenes</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0632" trans="overlap">primals Slayer <trunc>sl</trunc></u>
<u n="1370" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0632" trans="overlap">scenes and things yeah cos that's definitely where they filmed it</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0632">and we <trunc>w</trunc> we saw Skull Rock and you got in the eye socket</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0635">yeah yes</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0632">just</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and and before that we went to the antique place somewhere</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0632">did we go to the antique place before?</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0635">Joshua Tree yeah</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0632">oh</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0635">and you bought your red jacket</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0632">yeah I did</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0635">and we spoke to the lady there and she told us to go to Pappy and Harriet's later</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0632">she yeah had recommendations</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0635" trans="overlap">so we did mm</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0632">she was like go to Pappy and Harriet's for dinner</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0635">and before</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0632" trans="overlap">the frontiers town</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0635">and before we went into the park we went to the croquet <trunc>mu</trunc> croquet? crochet museum as well</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0632">did</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0635" trans="overlap">which was great</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0632">we did that before?</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0635">we must have done yeah</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0632">wow yeah the</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0632">the World Famous Crochet museum <vocal desc="laugh"/> that</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0632">really is as small as it looks</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0635">in</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0632">in the pictures</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0635">and Shari Elf's studio and then there was the sort of art gallery outside with all all</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0632">all the</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0635" trans="overlap">all the flowers made out of clear dildos and guy came</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and solar panels</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0635">yeah and the</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1406" who="S0635">guide came out with like a box of art stuff and was like oh you should come back at night and they're all lit up <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1407" who="S0632">it looks amazing</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0635">yeah it was pretty cool</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it was so funny yeah</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0632">Shari Elf's studio was great the way</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0632">that was like more of that honesty system just it's here for whoever stumbles across it kind of</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0632">like cos the the World Famous Crochet museum I have seen on the internet and it is just that green box full of crochet <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1416" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0632">it was like I think it does just have like a donations box and just</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0632">let yourself in look at the crochet leave leave a dollar</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0632">if you like</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0632">don't steal anything unless you're a dick</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0635">I thought her studio was really special as well</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0632">it was</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0632">it was such an unusual thing to me to be able just to wander into someone else's studio and</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0632">look at everything</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0635">yeah it was great that was very cool</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and she had stuff for sale as well and you bought the T-shirt</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I bought a T-shirt</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0632" trans="overlap">you're wearing</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0635">I'm wearing it now black hole in space</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0635">yeah yeah very inspiring I liked Joshua Tree in general as a place</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0632">was it frontiers town or pioneers town?</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0635">mm I think</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I feel it</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0635">Pioneertown I wanna say oh</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0632">maybe it's frontiers town</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0632">but cos that was just a set wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0635">yeah yeah it's er it was I guess was used in old</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0632">westerns?</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0635">old western films yeah and now it's kind got a barn where they sell books and do concerts and have a really nice diner</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0635">yeah it is Pioneertown</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0632">Pioneertown and we saw Emi Sunshine's sound check <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1450" who="S0635">yeah she's so cool</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0632">and I had some sort of burrito bowl it was really nice</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0635">yeah I remember the coffee being good as well just had a great vibe</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0632">yeah really nice it was so like western like</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0632">I've never been anywhere like that before but it was really friendly and you know with like swinging stable doors and everything's wood and</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah and there was that guy in the bathroom and he was like he was started humming Amazing Grace or something and his friend was like why are you singing man? and he was like I sing when I'm scared <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1457" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1458" who="S0635">cos he was scared of Emi Sunshine</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1460" who="S0635">it was good but yeah <trunc>li</trunc> and they had like posters on the walls for all the bands that had played there like Vampire Weekend and Future Islands and</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0632" trans="overlap">such a cool spot yeah</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0635">loads of people yeah</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0635">yep and then after</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0632" trans="overlap"><unclear>where to</unclear></u>
<u n="1466" who="S0635">I guess we were back to Palm Springs</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0632">for another night and I think we spent that more at the hotel talking to that Dutch boy</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0635">oh yeah do you remember where we ate? like oh well I guess we ate at Pappy and Harriet's yeah</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0632" trans="overlap">we <trunc>y</trunc>yeah we had our main meal there</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0635">uhu <pause dur="short"/> I think we'd we'd often just get brunch or have a snacky one</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0635">and then</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0632">the next morning we had a an aborted breakfast attempt cos the place were were gonna go to first was like it's gonna be like an hour wait</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0635">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0632" trans="overlap">to be seated so we went to the next best place</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0635">which still had a long wait yeah</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0632" trans="overlap">so like we went and just and it wasn't as long as they said it was gonna be</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0635" trans="overlap">no no it turned out to be alright yeah yeah it was kind of a weird little place <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1479" who="S0632">yeah it was alright</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0632">but we were like we don't really have time to</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0635">mess around</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0632">cos we were well well we we'd booked something by then I think we had booked Kernville by then</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0635">yeah I guess that was next wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0632">yeah and that again the landscape changed completely</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0632">driving from Palm Springs up to Kernville</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0632">still really droughty</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0632">but you could tell that it wasn't meant to be as dry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1492" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0632">and it definitely wasn't deserty</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0632">but it took a long time that was a long drive I think that day</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0632">that you had to do <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1498" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0632">but it was a really nice place</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah it was it was a very long drive oh it was gorgeous that was our first kind of California mountains</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0632">yeah well we started</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0632">to cos we were inland by then so</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0632">but that was a really cute that was like a motel that was just really cute with the er the barbeque we could use outside our front door and then the whole walkway down to the river</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0632">and we were drinking our beers out of the jam jar cups</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0632">that were there and we went to the local store which was like such a local store and it sold guns as well as</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0635" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0632">local produce and sausages that we put on the barbeque</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0635" trans="overlap">that was great</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0632">and yeah it was like proper proper rural</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0635">yeah the</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and like I actually saw a man in dirty <trunc>li</trunc> erm denim dungarees with a trucker cap on and no shirt</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0635">yeah with a shopping basket</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0632">with a shopping basket</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah it was great</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and that and I was like wow he's like a stock character and he's real</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1522" who="S0635">I remember being a bit freaked out by the drive up there cos we went through California City which just had</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0632">oh it was bleak</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0635">it was really grim and it looked like the town from Napoleon Dynamite or something and it</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0632">it was it <trunc>wa</trunc> there was nothing</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0632">much but it's why it was such a long drive</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0632">cos there was nothing much between</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0635" trans="overlap">there was some guy sort of walking in the like in the middle of nowhere</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0635"><trunc>t</trunc> home from work or something I mean just really dry and we went through Red Rock national park</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0632">yeah yeah and we saw as sign that said seventy-two miles to the next Mcdonald's</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1536" who="S0635">they always to have and even in Kernville like the like you could see they <trunc>w</trunc> you just wondered where people shopped and got their stuff like it was so everything was so far away</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0632">it was quite a cute little town it had a</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0632" trans="overlap">little centre didn't it with a couple of clothes stores and a</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0632">and a coffee shop that was also a a pharmacy that was quite confused when you wanted a coffee <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1542" who="S0635">yeah like Kernville actually had stuff sorted out but I think it was like the <unclear>old the</unclear> place though <unclear/></u>
<u n="1543" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it was when you're starting to get like</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0632" trans="overlap">civilised a bit again and</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0632">it was really pretty up there</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0632">and you could tell that they were suffering a bit with the drought because they were still fairly low</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0632">like the higher up places were doing better but they were quite low down</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0635" trans="overlap">there was a big lake up there which as dry dry dry wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah exactly lake Isabella</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0632">was meant to be like</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0632">more than twice as full</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0635">mm but</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0635">that was one of the nicest hotels I think wasn't it? that was really nice</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0632">it was really clean and quaint</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0632">and it had good facilities</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0632">it was nice</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0635">yeah and it was really nice cooking food on their own barbeque and then walking down to the river and the dog that came to say hi</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0632">mm lots of newts and things down under the rocks</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0632">fish in the river it was really nice</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah it was</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0632">and like I guess we got there and just chilled out and had a barbeque on our own and</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0632">and the next day we went to the ghost town? maybe?</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0635">yeah we did yeah ghost town</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0632">and we bought the Mamas and the Papas cos we had to buy something from a shop so that we could go into the ghost town</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1578" who="S0635">and again we were the only people there</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0632">we were the only people</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah so we</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0632" trans="overlap">so he gave us a personal tour <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1582" who="S0635">yeah we bought like a Mamas and Papas record which was so great and like a few old photographs</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0635" trans="overlap">some postcards I think and a tour of the ghost town which wasn't strictly a ghost town cos none of all the houses had been kind of pulled from other</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0635">like</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0632">it was like a <trunc>reconstru</trunc> like</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0635" trans="overlap">places <trunc>y</trunc>yeah</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0632">oh this is the oldest building here it was built in like eighteen fifty but it it used to be over there</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0632">and and all these buildings are from another town like thirty miles away and it was like and he was going on about like the jail being haunted and stuff</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0635">yeah I enjoyed it</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0632">it was fun</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I thought it was silly</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0632">it was silly</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0632">but it was all I was definitely enjoying it with my tongue firmly in my cheek</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0635" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0632">it was like it's not a ghost town it's <trunc>pr</trunc> it's about as it's only a little bit more authentic that Pioneertown cos it's like</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0632">it's not even on the ground where it originally stood and it's all been rebuilt and</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0632" trans="overlap">who's to say?</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and it's full of dummies and</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it's full of yeah</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0635" trans="overlap">like</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0632" trans="overlap">like plastic dummies</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0635" trans="overlap">props and stuff</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0632" trans="overlap">like playing parts</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> with each other</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> but I kind of I kind of enjoyed the spirit of it that it was like this guy ran it and he also ran his antiques store and</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0632">I don't think there there wasn't like much of a budget behind it or a big team it was just like we're open</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> there's a thing here</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0635">yeah we had a good</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0632" trans="overlap">we'd appreciate a contribution</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0635">we did spend quite a long time there actually <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1621" who="S0632">we did</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0635">it was good</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0632" trans="overlap">spent ages there</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0635">yeah and what else did we do that day?</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0632">we went to <trunc>w</trunc> the the local restaurant for dinner</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0635">that was great</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0632" trans="overlap">that had the view over the valley with the river down the bottom</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0632">and I had some blackened fish</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0635">yeah the supermarket was one of the best things about that place</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0632">the I <trunc>thi</trunc></u>
<u n="1632" who="S0635" trans="overlap">like it was a proper like local farmers</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I think we started to throttle back a bit when we got to Kernville cos we'd</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0635">we did</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0632" trans="overlap">had so many intense days</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0632">that we were just like you know what let's not try and do too much we've got a nice place to chill out by the river we can just sit back</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0632">and catch our breath a bit</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0632">but we did do something every day</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0635">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0632">I think that day we had a lie in and then we just went to the ghost town and then we came back</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0635">I think that's right</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0632">had some dinner and sat outside with some beers again</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0632">and I started to write again but I didn't I didn't that was the last time I wrote and I just stopped</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0635" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0632">writing after that</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0635">uhu yeah that was good and then and then we went and I guess we had to leave time each day cos at this point we weren't really planned like we hadn't booked anything so we had to kind of plan our next</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0632">yeah we'd have to</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0635" trans="overlap">route every day</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0632">use the time in the day to find out</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0632">where we were going to stay next</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0635">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0632" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0635">so then from there we went up through the Trail of a Hundred Giants didn't we that's er</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0632" trans="overlap">we did yeah</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0635">which was great</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I really liked that</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0632">and</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0632">we were right back into the forest and the mountains again and it</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0632">got cooler and greener and lusher</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0635">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was really good <pause dur="short"/> yeah you just sort of parked up and then we walked around and the hundreds giants you'd get inside the giant trees</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0635">walk on them climb on them go through them and they had tunnels cut out of them</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0632">yeah it was so cool</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0635">yeah and there was like nice squirrels and stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1673" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1674" who="S0635">I think we saw quite a big one</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0632">yeah cos they've got unusual types there haven't they?</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0632">but yeah cos they've got unusual types there</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0632">but yeah that that was the next few days driving up through erm Kings Canyon and Sequoia wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0635">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0632">but where did we stay?</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0635">so we went pretty much out of the whole area to that night we stayed in not Fresno that was the other one but it was somewhere else <trunc>Vil</trunc> it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="1683" who="S0632">yeah I feel like it was a V place but</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0635" trans="overlap">let let me look on the map</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0632">we didn't really get up to much that was just a place to put our heads down wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0635">I think that's right</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0632">yeah so we had a couple of days</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0632">kind of looping in and out of the national park</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0632">so it was like we stayed in a silly motel ate some pizza and then drove back into the national park up up a bit more and then</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0632">back out to Fresno</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0635">Visalia</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0632">Visalia</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0632">yeah they were those two nights were like probably like the crummiest weren't they?</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0632">cos we just <trunc>w</trunc> booked lucky dip erm motels and we weren't as lucky as we were in Palm Springs</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I think especially the one in Fresno was</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0632">particularly a dive</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0635">yeah I can't remember much about Visalia to be honest</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0632">no there wasn't much to remember</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0635">until <unclear>er</unclear></u>
<u n="1707" who="S0632">one of them was Fresno the one that we went to the erm er the steakhouse that was posh accidentally?</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0635">yes we had the very expensive</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0632">cos that probably the worst place we stayed in</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0632">but the poshest place we ate in <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1712" who="S0635">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0632">but we like very quickly walked into like quite a posh little redeveloped part of town</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0635">yeah it was a steak place that was supposed to be really nice and but we had sort of our hiking shoes still on and I</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0632">I think that was the day we we'd swum in the swimming hole</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0632">as well so I wasn't clean from a shower I'd just been wet from <trunc>swimmi</trunc></u>
<u n="1718" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0632" trans="overlap">some wild swimming</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0635">that was the day after so I think we did General Sherman that day</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0632">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and then like just lots of driving up through the mountains and</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0632">lots of really scenic driving and then</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0632">when we saw all those cars pulled</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0632">over and people looking down the hill we had to know what they were looking at</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0632">and it was a swimming hole and we</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0635" trans="overlap">that was very cool</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0632" trans="overlap">had the spontaneous swim and</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0635">yeah and</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it was so lovely</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0635">people blasting music out of portable speakers and stuff</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1736" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0632">yeah it felt quite teenage</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0635">yeah it was really good though</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0632">but it was really fun just to do that and then</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0632">er we were starving when we got to Fresno and I wanted to</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0632">eat somewhere nice and and I was like oh it's very posh but we told them we were on our honeymoon</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0632">and they gave us a free box of chocolates and it was quite nice to be treated nicely I just wish I'd known it was going to be that posh then I would have</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0632">freshened up before we left our hotel room but yeah that was the worst hotel room and the</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0632">nicest restaurant</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0635">I think</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0632" trans="overlap">all in the same stay</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0635">it was <unclear>Tulare</unclear> <trunc>wa</trunc> or Visalia I can't remember that we stayed in but I think we had I think we went to that place that was kind of like a Subway pizza?</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0632">yeah I remember that</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0635">yeah I'd sort of forgot about it and we yeah we must have just watched stupid TV</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0635">they had a pool but I don't know if we used it or not</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0632">no I no we didn't I don't</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0635" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0632">I don't think we really paid much attention cos</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0635">no</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it wasn't very interesting</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0635">yeah we got got in and got out</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0632">it was just somewhere to sleep and</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0632" trans="overlap">we ate and we slept and then we got back</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0632">into the national park because there weren't many places to stay</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0632">on the way up because I think</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0632">camping in a national park is</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0632">pretty exclusive and we were lucky</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0632">to get that place in Yosemite that we did get</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0632">otherwise we'd have had to drove back out of Yosemite and gone some little town on the outskirts</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0632" trans="overlap">of the park</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0635">yeah there were some cool looking camping spots but they just book up so fast</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0632" trans="overlap">they just yeah we just couldn't get them</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0635" trans="overlap">which would have been cool but and I managed to smash my phone jumping <trunc>o</trunc>on a rock</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0632">oh yeah that was really annoying</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I smashed the <unclear>the</unclear> screen it was but then <trunc>i</trunc></u>
<u n="1787" who="S0632">you got</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0635" trans="overlap">luckily I managed to fix it like the morning after in the mall</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0632">yeah I suppose at least that was one of the upsides to going out of a national park was that you could get that sort of thing sorted at the mall</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0635">yeah and they did fix it reasonably fast and we erm <pause dur="short"/> we did we did a bit of shopping for our families didn't we? we got it out of the way</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0632">I guess so</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0635">I think I remember you getting your mum some stuff</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0632">oh yeah I think I did yeah</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and my brother er but then we got the hell out of there and drove right through Yosemite</u>
<u n="1795" who="S0632">yeah which was amazing</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1797" who="S0632">but it gave me nightmares <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1798" who="S0635">yeah it was pretty <unclear>rock and</unclear> but was that and we saw that photographer photographing a deer right up close and</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0632">yeah from like a yard away</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0635">you saw that rare kind of mountain goat ram thing</u>
<u n="1801" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh yeah I did see that really weird sheep thing</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0635" trans="overlap">which I didn't see mm</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0632">with big spiral horns</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0632">and yeah I saw loads as yeah as soon as we got into Yosemite it was like a Disney movie and all the animals came out <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1806" who="S0635">and we saw the bear</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0632">and we saw the bear</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0635">yeah we saw lots of people pulled up by the road and</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0632">again we had to go what are they looking at?</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0632">the we're gonna look at it too</u>
<u n="1812" who="S0635">pulled up next to the</u>
<u n="1813" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1814" who="S0635">yeah sort of asked what people are looking at and yeah that's a bear so we</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0632">it went that way</u>
<u n="1816" who="S0635">ran round and saw him slinking off into the woods</u>
<u n="1817" who="S0632">it was awesome</u>
<u n="1818" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1819" who="S0632">and that was still relatively low down compared to how high up we got</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0632">because that was why it was giving me nightmares was because when we finally found again it was another hard one to find cos it was a national park</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0632">but when we eventually found our kind of camp it was like a little <trunc>te</trunc> it was like a little tent cabin wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0635">oh it was</u>
<u n="1825" who="S0632" trans="overlap">we didn't need to pitch our own</u>
<u n="1826" who="S0635">yeah interesting</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it was really cool and we had to put our stuff in the bear box and</u>
<u n="1828" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1829" who="S0632">but it was so high up and all the roads leading up there they didn't really have safety barriers</u>
<u n="1830" who="S0635">no no</u>
<u n="1831" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and I didn't realise how much it affected me until that night and I don't know if it was cos we were sleeping at such a high altitude</u>
<u n="1832" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1833" who="S0632">but my all my dreams that night were about driving off a cliff <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1834" who="S0635">and some guy sort of was knocking on someone's door being like</u>
<u n="1835" who="S0632">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1836" who="S0635">have you seen like someone or other and the guy was like no and it was really odd like was er</u>
<u n="1837" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah it was quite eerie</u>
<u n="1838" who="S0635">either he was confused or maybe the altitude was getting to lots of people</u>
<u n="1839" who="S0632">maybe</u>
<u n="1840" who="S0635" trans="overlap">it was kind of strange up there</u>
<u n="1841" who="S0632">it was</u>
<u n="1842" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1843" who="S0632" trans="overlap">well we were sleeping at like eight thousand feet</u>
<u n="1844" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1845" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and then we went up another couple of thousand to walk around or something</u>
<u n="1846" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah we had breakfast with like a nice family of cool</u>
<u n="1847" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh yeah we had to</u>
<u n="1848" who="S0635" trans="overlap">media people I'm not really sure who they were but they were</u>
<u n="1849" who="S0632" trans="overlap">cos yeah we had to get seated with you it was the system wasn't it? you got</u>
<u n="1850" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1851" who="S0632" trans="overlap">seated with whoever you were seated with but we made conversation with them and</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0635">yeah it was a good breakfast</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0632">it was a nice breakfast very nice and basic</u>
<u n="1854" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1855" who="S0632">you got what you got there wasn't a frilly menu</u>
<u n="1856" who="S0635">no</u>
<u n="1857" who="S0632">it was like do you want porridge or do you want bacon and eggs?</u>
<u n="1858" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1859" who="S0632">and erm yeah so we talked to them for a bit and</u>
<u n="1860" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1861" who="S0632">we</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0635">and then we had headed up er</u>
<u n="1863" who="S0632">we we</u>
<u n="1864" who="S0635" trans="overlap">we did like a short one didn't we? it was something er I guess Tuolumne Tuolumne meadows wasn't it was where we were staying?</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1866" who="S0635">erm <pause dur="short"/> and then the <pause dur="short"/> er yeah Tuolumne meadows and there was like a sort of spring wasn't there? <pause dur="short"/> like a natural spring water thing</u>
<u n="1867" who="S0632">yeah well we did</u>
<u n="1868" who="S0635" trans="overlap">but it was kind of gross</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0632">we did that we did that walk around the side of that lake first didn't we?</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0635">oh yeah that was that was nice</u>
<u n="1871" who="S0632">that was really nice</u>
<u n="1872" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1873" who="S0632">and then we drove to the the place with the natural carbon spring</u>
<u n="1874" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0632">erm and yeah it was just really scenic and then we walked down by the river and sat down for a bit</u>
<u n="1876" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1877" who="S0632">but I always describe it as it was a really there was really short easy walks and I thought we took them slow I knew we'd taken them slow but while by the time we got back in the car it was like three or four hours had passed or something and I was like what? like we just kind of wandered around a bit and then sat down for a bit and walked back to the car and I think it must have been all to do with the altitude</u>
<u n="1878" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1879" who="S0632">it's like we were in slow motion or something like we're just like walk for a few minutes sit down walk for a few more minutes sit down like we really took it easy we</u>
<u n="1880" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1881" who="S0632">didn't go very far</u>
<u n="1882" who="S0635">no</u>
<u n="1883" who="S0632">and it took us most of the day <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1884" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1885" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1886" who="S0635">I felt really heavy like I was I dunno yeah</u>
<u n="1887" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1888" who="S0635">under water or something</u>
<u n="1889" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah it was really strange</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0635" trans="overlap">like yeah really felt just heavy like oh and it yeah we did like basically the child walk <vocal desc="laugh"/> or whatever</u>
<u n="1891" who="S0632" trans="overlap">we did yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1892" who="S0635">and it was like phew</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0632">there were like middle aged men powering off in front of us with sticks and stuff but</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0632">I'm glad we took it easy we know</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1897" who="S0632">you know I didn't wanna test my limits too much up on a foreign</u>
<u n="1898" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0632">mountain</u>
<u n="1900" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1901" who="S0632">but erm yeah it was really beautiful up there</u>
<u n="1902" who="S0635">yeah it was still very cool</u>
<u n="1903" who="S0632">trying to enjoy the peace</u>
<u n="1904" who="S0635">and we saw the little like <trunc>g</trunc> are they pocket gophers or were they</u>
<u n="1905" who="S0632">pocket gophers yeah we saw pocket gophers</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0635" trans="overlap">going up and down yeah it was cool yeah</u>
<u n="1907" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0635">very nice and then like er yeah we drove down a really scary windy road coming up</u>
<u n="1909" who="S0632" trans="overlap">terrifying yeah</u>
<u n="1910" who="S0635">oh the the Tioga pass I guess</u>
<u n="1911" who="S0632" trans="overlap">that was after my erm nightmares as well</u>
<u n="1912" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1913" who="S0632">and I was worried that my nightmares were a premonition</u>
<u n="1914" who="S0635">oh it was really scary</u>
<u n="1915" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1916" who="S0635">that mm none of the drives had bothered me until that one and I was like woah</u>
<u n="1917" who="S0632">it's can't wait to get off this</u>
<u n="1918" who="S0635">yeah it's freaky</u>
<u n="1919" who="S0632" trans="overlap">part of the road</u>
<u n="1920" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1921" who="S0632">it's like I'm sure you could really enjoy this view if you weren't really terrified <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1922" who="S0635">yeah I was erm I was aware that it was amazing but I was also like</u>
<u n="1923" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1924" who="S0635">yeah it was really scary and then we got down to that er gas station restaurant it was like a</u>
<u n="1925" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1926" who="S0635" trans="overlap">gas station that does really good food right by lake Mono?</u>
<u n="1927" who="S0632">yeah like Mono lake</u>
<u n="1928" who="S0635" trans="overlap">which was a pretty lake yeah mm which has kind of big funny rocks in it and I think we saw it from the air</u>
<u n="1929" who="S0632">coming down the mountain</u>
<u n="1930" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1931" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1932" who="S0635">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1933" who="S0632" trans="overlap">but yeah</u>
<u n="1934" who="S0635">it was great</u>
<u n="1935" who="S0632">it was yeah that was a cool little stop and I had some sort of mango margarita <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1936" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1937" who="S0632">and some a bite to eat and then I guess we drove to Tahoe</u>
<u n="1938" who="S0635" trans="overlap">Tahoe <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah we must have got to Tahoe</u>
<u n="1939" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh my <trunc>g</trunc></u>
<u n="1940" who="S0635">from there yeah</u>
<u n="1941" who="S0632" trans="overlap">so we went from Yosemite to Tahoe</u>
<u n="1942" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1943" who="S0632">in one day</u>
<u n="1944" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1945" who="S0632">having already done some walks and things and</u>
<u n="1946" who="S0635">yeah yeah and we'd accidentally booked a casino which cost twice as much as we thought it did</u>
<u n="1947" who="S0632">yeah I think the</u>
<u n="1948" who="S0635">the</u>
<u n="1949" who="S0632">the Expedia website had gone wrong and it was cos we wanted it for two nights didn't we?</u>
<u n="1950" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1951" who="S0632">and I think it was giving us the rate for one</u>
<u n="1952" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1953" who="S0632">we booked it and it was double</u>
<u n="1954" who="S0635">it was still pretty cool though</u>
<u n="1955" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it it was a nice</u>
<u n="1956" who="S0635">and it wasn't that bad</u>
<u n="1957" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it was a nice room</u>
<u n="1958" who="S0635">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1959" who="S0632">and it wasn't that bad</u>
<u n="1960" who="S0635">it was kind of a funny thing to do</u>
<u n="1961" who="S0632">it was a funny thing to do</u>
<u n="1962" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1963" who="S0632">cos we were like oh fine it cos we were on the Nevada side then weren't we?</u>
<u n="1964" who="S0635">uhu yeah</u>
<u n="1965" who="S0632">for briefly we were on the Nevada side and we we tried to gamble but we're rubbish at it</u>
<u n="1966" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1967" who="S0632">so we didn't really you drew all those tattoos on me</u>
<u n="1968" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1969" who="S0632" trans="overlap">that must have been the second night though</u>
<u n="1970" who="S0635">yeah it was</u>
<u n="1971" who="S0632" trans="overlap">the first night we went down to the erm that beachfront café</u>
<u n="1972" who="S0635">yeah cos it was still light when we got there</u>
<u n="1973" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and I had a pineapple cider and it was amazing</u>
<u n="1974" who="S0635" trans="overlap">oh yeah that was good we need to find that yeah</u>
<u n="1975" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah I'd have that again that was just the most delicious I had two because they were</u>
<u n="1976" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="1977" who="S0632" trans="overlap">so good</u>
<u n="1978" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah and I had a pretty good beer whatever it was</u>
<u n="1979" who="S0632">and yeah some just some nice burgers and there was all string lights and</u>
<u n="1980" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1981" who="S0632">it was basically outdoors</u>
<u n="1982" who="S0635">and there was that really stoned guy trying to <unclear/> table</u>
<u n="1983" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh my god he was really struggling</u>
<u n="1984" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and he wrote like the letter S like he's like that's not an S that's a five and he like did it over and over and then he'd do a backwards S and he was just like</u>
<u n="1985" who="S0632" trans="overlap">he was like that's not an S it's a five it's like it's good enough I mean it's it's essentially the same shape</u>
<u n="1986" who="S0635" trans="overlap">he just gave up he was completely gone</u>
<u n="1987" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I know well it wasn't your name at all at the end he I think he wrote <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> with a Z</u>
<u n="1988" who="S0635">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1989" who="S0632">or like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and in the end the best he could do was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1990" who="S0635"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1991" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and I was like fine that's us</u>
<u n="1992" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="1993" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1994" who="S0635">I think they gave us some sort of <unclear>blinky</unclear> thing and we just went for a walk round the beach but</u>
<u n="1995" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="1996" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="1997" who="S0632">yeah we just <trunc>ca</trunc> back and and the next day we went back to the beach</u>
<u n="1998" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="1999" who="S0632">on and we got a canoe to canoe on the lake</u>
<u n="2000" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah and we saw someone setting up a wedding and</u>
<u n="2001" who="S0632">which was nice cos we'd just got married</u>
<u n="2002" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I just like canoeing yeah</u>
<u n="2003" who="S0632">yeah we just canoed about the place cos I like canoeing</u>
<u n="2004" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2005" who="S0632">and that was very nice and chilled out actually</u>
<u n="2006" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2007" who="S0632" trans="overlap">so we spent the morning canoeing then we noodled around town a bit but there wasn't really much to see</u>
<u n="2008" who="S0635">no</u>
<u n="2009" who="S0632">and</u>
<u n="2010" who="S0635">I remember us going in some sort of cowboy shop type thing</u>
<u n="2011" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah we saw some</u>
<u n="2012" who="S0635" trans="overlap">like looking at boots and stuff</u>
<u n="2013" who="S0632" trans="overlap">some that was probably the best place we found well</u>
<u n="2014" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2015" who="S0632">I wouldn't wanna buy anything cos they were like ridiculously expensive but like</u>
<u n="2016" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2017" who="S0632">properly like gem-laden boots with like</u>
<u n="2018" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2019" who="S0632">different coloured leather on and like everything was so <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="2020" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="2021" who="S0632">so that was quite cool but yeah</u>
<u n="2022" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and then we had another expensive steak dinner after yeah</u>
<u n="2023" who="S0632" trans="overlap">but we expected it this time</u>
<u n="2024" who="S0635">yeah on the top</u>
<u n="2025" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and we dressed up</u>
<u n="2026" who="S0635" trans="overlap">floor of the</u>
<u n="2027" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2028" who="S0635">hotel and they had a nice old man with moustache server he was cool</u>
<u n="2029" who="S0632">he was cool he was really nice and</u>
<u n="2030" who="S0635">and the food was nice</u>
<u n="2031" who="S0632">the food was nice and then we had a few drinks then we went back to our hotel room and you drew tattoos on me er like anti-gambling tattoos</u>
<u n="2032" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2033" who="S0632">like a a paradise the <vocal desc="laugh"/> no er like three cards which were like twenty-seven and the words</u>
<u n="2034" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2035" who="S0632">hit me</u>
<u n="2036" who="S0635"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2037" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2038" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2039" who="S0632">and erm and the dice with the I don't know how to stop</u>
<u n="2040" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2041" who="S0632">but also the John Muir tattoos as as inspired by</u>
<u n="2042" who="S0635" trans="overlap">we did all sorts of stuff</u>
<u n="2043" who="S0632" trans="overlap">by our recent Yosemite visit</u>
<u n="2044" who="S0635">yeah and a UFO and</u>
<u n="2045" who="S0632">I believe</u>
<u n="2046" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2047" who="S0632">yeah but and I and I made a point of going downstairs to the casino with my tattoos out but no one commented on it</u>
<u n="2048" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2049" who="S0632">you know what? in a lot of places in America people are really friendly and chatty but I'll tell you what a casino is not one of them</u>
<u n="2050" who="S0635">no no people have got their game on</u>
<u n="2051" who="S0632" trans="overlap">they they're <trunc>to</trunc> everyone was like in a bad mood almost it was like</u>
<u n="2052" who="S0635">one guy talked to me in the</u>
<u n="2053" who="S0632">oh yeah he</u>
<u n="2054" who="S0635" trans="overlap">elevator it was like three grand up or something but it was early in the evening so</u>
<u n="2055" who="S0632" trans="overlap">he he was like are you guys are you guys playing? how how how much money are you up? are you up or down I think he said are you</u>
<u n="2056" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2057" who="S0632">up or down? and we're like oh we haven't gambled yet</u>
<u n="2058" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2059" who="S0632">erm cos we don't really gamble</u>
<u n="2060" who="S0635">no we spent</u>
<u n="2061" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and he was like oh you've gotta get on it man I'm three grand up and he was like I'm pumped</u>
<u n="2062" who="S0635"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2063" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay and <trunc>m</trunc> you and I erm spent six dollars on the <trunc>g</trunc></u>
<u n="2064" who="S0635" trans="overlap"><trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="2065" who="S0632">fruit machines and were like that's enough I've lost six dollars I don't need to lose any more</u>
<u n="2066" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2067" who="S0632">and I was too shy to go on like the black <trunc>d</trunc> jack I feel like I suffer under peer pressure and I'd be like pressured to stay and pressured to to gamble more than I wanted to</u>
<u n="2068" who="S0635">that's you kind of have to know what you're doing to not get <unclear>scuppered</unclear></u>
<u n="2069" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah I don't want to gamble</u>
<u n="2070" who="S0635"><vocal desc="cough"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2071" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I I'd just feel like I should cos I'm here</u>
<u n="2072" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="2073" who="S0632">and we did a little bit and it was fun and</u>
<u n="2074" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2075" who="S0632">that guy didn't accept our driving licences as ID</u>
<u n="2076" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2077" who="S0632">and that was really annoying cos everyone else did so we had to go and get our passports and then we were</u>
<u n="2078" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2079" who="S0632">served by someone else anyway who didn't even ID us</u>
<u n="2080" who="S0635">yeah yeah it was all very silly it was a bit stupid</u>
<u n="2081" who="S0632">it was a big stupid</u>
<u n="2082" who="S0635">but the room was nice and comfy</u>
<u n="2083" who="S0632">yeah it was really a huge room</u>
<u n="2084" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="2085" who="S0632">really comfy room and we had two bathrooms didn't we?</u>
<u n="2086" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2087" who="S0632" trans="overlap">so we could shower at the same time</u>
<u n="2088" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2089" who="S0632">but not together <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2090" who="S0635">that was fun</u>
<u n="2091" who="S0632">un-honeymoony thing to do but</u>
<u n="2092" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="2093" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like I'm I'm gonna have a separate bathroom to you</u>
<u n="2094" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2095" who="S0632">but yeah it was quite</u>
<u n="2096" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2097" who="S0632">luxurious after the camping that was like</u>
<u n="2098" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2099" who="S0632" trans="overlap">properly clean and</u>
<u n="2100" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="2101" who="S0632">lovely</u>
<u n="2102" who="S0635">and then the next day we did where did we go to after Tahoe? was that Auburn?</u>
<u n="2103" who="S0632">yeah we went to Auburn</u>
<u n="2104" who="S0635">yeah which was we just kind of picked it cos it was between Napa</u>
<u n="2105" who="S0632"><trunc>ye</trunc> between Tahoe and Napa</u>
<u n="2106" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and Napa yeah</u>
<u n="2107" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2108" who="S0635">and it wasn't like a big place like Sacramento or</u>
<u n="2109" who="S0632">yeah we didn't wanna stay in a big place but it turned out to be a lovely little town</u>
<u n="2110" who="S0635">uhu yeah</u>
<u n="2111" who="S0632">really friendly people a couple of erm of nice restaurants and</u>
<u n="2112" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2113" who="S0632">that really friendly woman who was who was planting flowers outside her gallery who told us</u>
<u n="2114" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah we just</u>
<u n="2115" who="S0632" trans="overlap">like the history of the town and her family</u>
<u n="2116" who="S0635" trans="overlap">we just walked in the art gallery and the show was all people who'd be students at the art college and mostly <trunc>un</trunc>under one particular tutor it was all sort of a tribute to I think who'd just retired</u>
<u n="2117" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2118" who="S0635">and it seemed like it had a lovely like community vibe and people loved the school there and like they came back every year for the reunion and it was a big deal and</u>
<u n="2119" who="S0632">yeah it did seem to have a lovely community vibe</u>
<u n="2120" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm and there was that dentist who makes giant sculptures outside his dentist practice</u>
<u n="2121" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2122" who="S0635">of women like</u>
<u n="2123" who="S0632" trans="overlap">giant warrior women</u>
<u n="2124" who="S0635" trans="overlap">muscly women</u>
<u n="2125" who="S0632">who are naked yeah</u>
<u n="2126" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="2127" who="S0632">so that was like a little</u>
<u n="2128" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2129" who="S0632">extra bonus piece of outsider art</u>
<u n="2130" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah and we ate at that nice fish restaurant I think or something opposite the art gallery</u>
<u n="2131" who="S0632">yeah I don't was it a fish restaurant?</u>
<u n="2132" who="S0635">I don't know but it</u>
<u n="2133" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2134" who="S0635">it was good</u>
<u n="2135" who="S0632">it was nice anyway but yeah we we only kind of flew through there and</u>
<u n="2136" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2137" who="S0632">people</u>
<u n="2138" who="S0635">but</u>
<u n="2139" who="S0632">were really friendly there</u>
<u n="2140" who="S0635">but the next day we went to the old part of town thinking we'd seen like what the old part of town was</u>
<u n="2141" who="S0632">oh yeah</u>
<u n="2142" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and it was like really like historic looking sort of goldminey town</u>
<u n="2143" who="S0632">it was it was really gorgeous</u>
<u n="2144" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2145" who="S0632">yeah you're right cos we went for breakfast</u>
<u n="2146" who="S0635">yeah it was awesome</u>
<u n="2147" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and that was a really nice place for breakfast too</u>
<u n="2148" who="S0635" trans="overlap">it was like Awful Annie's something like</u>
<u n="2149" who="S0632">Awful Annie's yeah</u>
<u n="2150" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2151" who="S0632">in the old part of town and we ate out on the kind of balcony porch thing</u>
<u n="2152" who="S0635">yeah it was really good</u>
<u n="2153" who="S0632">and it was really good yeah</u>
<u n="2154" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and that was just a cool spot I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="2155" who="S0632">and there were some nice like old-fashioned signs hanging up I think</u>
<u n="2156" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2157" who="S0632">so we wandered around that area before</u>
<u n="2158" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2159" who="S0632">before getting back in the car</u>
<u n="2160" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2161" who="S0632">to drive to Napa</u>
<u n="2162" who="S0635">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah we drove to Napa we got into Napa</u>
<u n="2163" who="S0632">cos we'd booked our motel which was a decent motel</u>
<u n="2164" who="S0635" trans="overlap">did we go straight for our mud bath? I feel like we might have done</u>
<u n="2165" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I think we did I think we were deciding what to do on each day cos we didn't have much time left</u>
<u n="2166" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="2167" who="S0632">and</u>
<u n="2168" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2169" who="S0632">and er the things to do there were wine wine and more wine but</u>
<u n="2170" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2171" who="S0632">it was also like there are these natural springs and mud baths in Calistoga</u>
<u n="2172" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2173" who="S0632">and erm we went to like a proper old school mud bath place where they just put you in a tank of mud and</u>
<u n="2174" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2175" who="S0632">leave you to it</u>
<u n="2176" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2177" who="S0632">and that was that was pretty cool but yeah I think we went straight there checked in</u>
<u n="2178" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="2179" who="S0632">at our motel</u>
<u n="2180" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2181" who="S0632">and then went or did we even check in at our motel or did we go straight to Calistoga?</u>
<u n="2182" who="S0635" trans="overlap">maybe yeah</u>
<u n="2183" who="S0632">cos I'd booked it on the phone from the restaurant that morning</u>
<u n="2184" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2185" who="S0632">and we arrived we had our appointment</u>
<u n="2186" who="S0635">uhu sat in some mud</u>
<u n="2187" who="S0632">sat in some mud</u>
<u n="2188" who="S0635" trans="overlap">showered each other off with a hose</u>
<u n="2189" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah we did</u>
<u n="2190" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah had a swim after that as well in a nice hot pool</u>
<u n="2191" who="S0632">yes we did</u>
<u n="2192" who="S0635">and the water was all like from the natural hot spring so it had a kind of</u>
<u n="2193" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2194" who="S0635">weird</u>
<u n="2195" who="S0632">that's right</u>
<u n="2196" who="S0635" trans="overlap">feel and taste and smell</u>
<u n="2197" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it did but</u>
<u n="2198" who="S0635">which was nice</u>
<u n="2199" who="S0632" trans="overlap">there was like</u>
<u n="2200" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2201" who="S0632">there was like a mineral build up everywhere wasn't there?</u>
<u n="2202" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2203" who="S0632">and there was lots of signs</u>
<u n="2204" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2205" who="S0632">about how it's not dirt it's just a natural side effect of the spring water</u>
<u n="2206" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2207" who="S0632">yeah I swam so much</u>
<u n="2208" who="S0635">yeah and I think we got kind of a good sense of the layout of Napa</u>
<u n="2209" who="S0632">I think cos we drove through a lot of the</u>
<u n="2210" who="S0635" trans="overlap">at the mm</u>
<u n="2211" who="S0632">again different landscape or the vineyards</u>
<u n="2212" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="2213" who="S0632">and the</u>
<u n="2214" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2215" who="S0632" trans="overlap">kind of more rolling green hills even in the drought it was more green</u>
<u n="2216" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2217" who="S0632">but yeah it was pretty</u>
<u n="2218" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2219" who="S0632">and the next day the last was it no was it the last full day on our honeymoon or the penultimate?</u>
<u n="2220" who="S0635" trans="overlap">the I think it was yeah I think it was the last er day</u>
<u n="2221" who="S0632">cos that's that was the wine tasting day</u>
<u n="2222" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2223" who="S0632">and we weren't sure where we wanted to go cos there were so many that we ended up going to the most young</u>
<u n="2224" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2225" who="S0632">hip places <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2226" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2227" who="S0632">but erm I don't regret it cos I didn't really necessarily need a tour of a vineyard</u>
<u n="2228" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2229" who="S0632">erm but it was really nice to sit in that like quite cool bar midtown and</u>
<u n="2230" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2231" who="S0632">try all the different wines with and look through their book of</u>
<u n="2232" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2233" who="S0632">toilet poetry</u>
<u n="2234" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2235" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and</u>
<u n="2236" who="S0635">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2237" who="S0632">and we bought one from that place didn't we?</u>
<u n="2238" who="S0635">we did yeah</u>
<u n="2239" who="S0632">was that the Catacomb</u>
<u n="2240" who="S0635">it was yeah</u>
<u n="2241" who="S0632" trans="overlap">one? the red wine from there</u>
<u n="2242" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2243" who="S0632">and then we went up to that</u>
<u n="2244" who="S0635" trans="overlap">then it was back to Calistoga I think</u>
<u n="2245" who="S0632">was it back up to Calistoga?</u>
<u n="2246" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2247" who="S0632">where we had lunch?</u>
<u n="2248" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2249" who="S0632">at the kind of ribs place?</u>
<u n="2250" who="S0635">yeah I think</u>
<u n="2251" who="S0632" trans="overlap">that</u>
<u n="2252" who="S0635" trans="overlap">it was</u>
<u n="2253" who="S0632">quite divey but good it was back up that area I'm not sure</u>
<u n="2254" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2255" who="S0632" trans="overlap">if it was quite that far but it was back up that way</u>
<u n="2256" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2257" who="S0632">more south</u>
<u n="2258" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="2259" who="S0632">and then we were just passing that place that was a</u>
<u n="2260" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="2261" who="S0632">really cool vintage erm petrol station but it was actually a wine tasting bar</u>
<u n="2262" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah that was cool</u>
<u n="2263" who="S0632" trans="overlap">so well obviously we have to go in there</u>
<u n="2264" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2265" who="S0632">bought our second bottle of wine and that was a cool place cos they had like a secret room that they took us in</u>
<u n="2266" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2267" who="S0632">just cos they were quiet and they were like this and they were like look at our cool little room for functions and things</u>
<u n="2268" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2269" who="S0632">erm</u>
<u n="2270" who="S0635">yeah it was good</u>
<u n="2271" who="S0632">and again I got to taste all the wine cos you were driving</u>
<u n="2272" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2273" who="S0632">but then we bought two bottles and</u>
<u n="2274" who="S0635">mm and we went to some really good sort of barbeque place then</u>
<u n="2275" who="S0632">yeah we did that</u>
<u n="2276" who="S0635" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="2277" who="S0632">in between the two</u>
<u n="2278" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2279" who="S0632">the the ribs place</u>
<u n="2280" who="S0635">that was great</u>
<u n="2281" who="S0632">the pulled pork and ribs I can't remember what it was called</u>
<u n="2282" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm no</u>
<u n="2283" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it was named after someone</u>
<u n="2284" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2285" who="S0632">like Bobby's or something</u>
<u n="2286" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2287" who="S0632">but erm we bought the wine with the coolest bottles <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2288" who="S0635">yes</u>
<u n="2289" who="S0632">but it was really tasty and then we took it back to our motel room so you could actually drink some <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2290" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2291" who="S0632">well not our motel room cos they had a weird kind of island in the middle didn't they which was like erm</u>
<u n="2292" who="S0635">like the car park</u>
<u n="2293" who="S0632" trans="overlap">grass</u>
<u n="2294" who="S0635">and the</u>
<u n="2295" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2296" who="S0635">swimming pool yeah</u>
<u n="2297" who="S0632">yeah so it was like car park all around the edge</u>
<u n="2298" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2299" who="S0632" trans="overlap">but in the middle it was like a green with a</u>
<u n="2300" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2301" who="S0632">with a couple of tables for parasols in the swimming pool <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2302" who="S0635">yeah so we drank all the wines</u>
<u n="2303" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2304" who="S0635">that we tried and we <pause dur="short"/> yeah had a swim I think didn't we? and just</u>
<u n="2305" who="S0632">I think we had actually managed to get some Whole Foods to like bits to eat with the wine kind of thing</u>
<u n="2306" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2307" who="S0632">cos the night before we tried to do that and we were running up to the Whole Foods</u>
<u n="2308" who="S0635" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="2309" who="S0632">and someone from the dark shouted Whole Foods is closed <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2310" who="S0635"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2311" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like</u>
<u n="2312" who="S0635">it was like who said that?</u>
<u n="2313" who="S0632">and it was like eight o'clock</u>
<u n="2314" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="2315" who="S0632">but I was like I guess we're</u>
<u n="2316" who="S0635" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="2317" who="S0632">not in a big city any more</u>
<u n="2318" who="S0635" trans="overlap">we found that place that was like almost a <trunc>b</trunc> like a fast food place that served wine</u>
<u n="2319" who="S0632">yeah you're right</u>
<u n="2320" who="S0635" trans="overlap">they were like a Mcdonald's with a wine cellar</u>
<u n="2321" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it was it was</u>
<u n="2322" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2323" who="S0632">again it was like another local chain or something wasn't it?</u>
<u n="2324" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2325" who="S0632">and it was like we went there and we ordered a burger and it was like</u>
<u n="2326" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="2327" who="S0632">would you like some wine with that? and I says well I guess we've just arrived in Napa</u>
<u n="2328" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2329" who="S0632">we've had our mud bath</u>
<u n="2330" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2331" who="S0632">let's have some wine our burger</u>
<u n="2332" who="S0635" trans="overlap">that's right yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2333" who="S0632">and we could take the rest of the bottle home couldn't we?</u>
<u n="2334" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2335" who="S0632">cos it was like you can open the bottle and drink it here but we'll also let you take it home which was</u>
<u n="2336" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2337" who="S0632">again good for you cos you were driving</u>
<u n="2338" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="2339" who="S0632">so you you could only have a sip with your meal</u>
<u n="2340" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2341" who="S0632">and yeah god yeah Napa's just all about wine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2342" who="S0635">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2343" who="S0632">and then I guess after that we drove back to San Francisco did we we just drive straight to the airport or did we stay another night somewhere?</u>
<u n="2344" who="S0635">erm no I'm pretty sure Napa was our last night</u>
<u n="2345" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2346" who="S0635" trans="overlap">cos I remember yeah I remember sort of us when we were having the two bottles of wine we've bought <pause dur="short"/> by the pool and just feeling really nostalgic like thinking back</u>
<u n="2347" who="S0632" trans="overlap">reminiscing</u>
<u n="2348" who="S0635">over everything we'd seen</u>
<u n="2349" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2350" who="S0635">and how much we loved it there and yeah just looking at the palm trees and things and just how different everything</u>
<u n="2351" who="S0632" trans="overlap">soaking in the</u>
<u n="2352" who="S0635" trans="overlap">the heat and the shape of the doors</u>
<u n="2353" who="S0632" trans="overlap">sunset</u>
<u n="2354" who="S0635">and how</u>
<u n="2355" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2356" who="S0635">yeah how you don't really see it anywhere else it was just great</u>
<u n="2357" who="S0632">yeah you're right</u>
<u n="2358" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I loved it</u>
<u n="2359" who="S0632">and we had a huge clear-out in fact we left quite a lot of rubbish in the room so we left a tip</u>
<u n="2360" who="S0635">oh yeah</u>
<u n="2361" who="S0632" trans="overlap">cos we wanted to get rid of a lot of stuff so we filled the bin up as much as possible and plus a few things next to it</u>
<u n="2362" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah we had to get back down to two suitcases or whatever yeah</u>
<u n="2363" who="S0632" trans="overlap">so we had to eject a lot of things and</u>
<u n="2364" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2365" who="S0632">cos we did couldn't fit everything in the bin sensibly we left at tip didn't we</u>
<u n="2366" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2367" who="S0632" trans="overlap">on the bed like as a sorry there's loads of trash in here <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2368" who="S0635">yeah and I think I tried to clean up the car a little bit as well cos it</u>
<u n="2369" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2370" who="S0635" trans="overlap">had really been through the wars being a little white car</u>
<u n="2371" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2372" who="S0635">been through like four or five national parks <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2373" who="S0632" trans="overlap">well we did nearly like three thousand miles or something ridiculous</u>
<u n="2374" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah we did yeah</u>
<u n="2375" who="S0632" trans="overlap">didn't we? so I guess we just drove straight to the airport checked in the car and</u>
<u n="2376" who="S0635">yeah I really needed to pee and had to pee at the bottle</u>
<u n="2377" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh my god yeah</u>
<u n="2378" who="S0635" trans="overlap"><trunc>ye</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2379" who="S0632" trans="overlap">you peed in that bottle</u>
<u n="2380" who="S0635">cos we were at the</u>
<u n="2381" who="S0632">oh</u>
<u n="2382" who="S0635" trans="overlap">cos there's that the like the world's longest bridge or whatever</u>
<u n="2383" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2384" who="S0635">and it was ridiculous and there's like nowhere to stop and there's tolls and like long queues</u>
<u n="2385" who="S0632" trans="overlap">the tolls are really confusing cos we thought we had an EZpass from the</u>
<u n="2386" who="S0635">which we must have done</u>
<u n="2387" who="S0632" trans="overlap">from the car rental</u>
<u n="2388" who="S0635" trans="overlap">cos I still haven't received anything from them</u>
<u n="2389" who="S0632" trans="overlap">cos there was there was nothing about it and we're like we're we thought we had an EZpass and he was like do you have your card or something or like</u>
<u n="2390" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2391" who="S0632" trans="overlap">you know cos it's a rental car</u>
<u n="2392" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2393" who="S0632">and he was like oh well it'll if you don't have the money on you which we didn't</u>
<u n="2394" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2395" who="S0632">it'll be a thirty dollar fine or something</u>
<u n="2396" who="S0635">no it'll be more than that but we've never been billed for it so</u>
<u n="2397" who="S0632" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="2398" who="S0635">so I think</u>
<u n="2399" who="S0632" trans="overlap">not by not by them or by the car rental people</u>
<u n="2400" who="S0635">no</u>
<u n="2401" who="S0632">they did have an EZpass <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2402" who="S0635">yeah it was <unclear>awesome</unclear> yeah I dunno</u>
<u n="2403" who="S0632">it was <unclear>awesome</unclear></u>
<u n="2404" who="S0635">but yeah we got through the tolls and then yeah finally made it to the airport it was a bit of a</u>
<u n="2405" who="S0632"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="2406" who="S0635">stress that drive but it was alright</u>
<u n="2407" who="S0632">ah</u>
<u n="2408" who="S0635">and then yeah we were scot-free and but then that was the one where our flight decompressed</u>
<u n="2409" who="S0632">and we had to stop in Newark</u>
<u n="2410" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2411" who="S0632">yeah oh my god yeah er cos I had a horrible feeling on that flight I felt really nervous for some reason</u>
<u n="2412" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu uhu</u>
<u n="2413" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I don't know if it was just the lead-up having a bit of a hectic day</u>
<u n="2414" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2415" who="S0632">with not much fun in it</u>
<u n="2416" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2417" who="S0632">just kind of getting to the airport getting on the plane</u>
<u n="2418" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="2419" who="S0632">and just feeling really horrible about being I think it was cos I was worried about stuff in my suitcase I was</u>
<u n="2420" who="S0635" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="2421" who="S0632">worried about</u>
<u n="2422" who="S0635">oh yeah</u>
<u n="2423" who="S0632" trans="overlap">stuff I was carrying and in case it exploded and</u>
<u n="2424" who="S0635"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2425" who="S0632">I was like I'm pretty sure I'm not carrying but I</u>
<u n="2426" who="S0635" trans="overlap">it was just a lighter wasn't it?</u>
<u n="2427" who="S0632">it was the lighter or something and I suddenly started panicking about it after we took off</u>
<u n="2428" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2429" who="S0632">and I was like shit shit shit shit <vocal desc="laugh"/> but it was fine but</u>
<u n="2430" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="2431" who="S0632">yeah the cabin the cabin did decompress slowly and we had to <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> to land</u>
<u n="2432" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2433" who="S0632">and that was a bit scary and then we had that whole connecting flight</u>
<u n="2434" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2435" who="S0632">ended up talking to people on the plane and</u>
<u n="2436" who="S0635">yeah we sort of landed in Newark and er got a nice pilot sort of gave us a little speech and thanked us and said explained what had happened</u>
<u n="2437" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2438" who="S0635">I think and then</u>
<u n="2439" who="S0632">well yeah and it was all fine and we</u>
<u n="2440" who="S0635" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="2441" who="S0632">we made it and</u>
<u n="2442" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah we arrived a lot later than we meant to in Boston but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> still waited for us anyway</u>
<u n="2443" who="S0632">she did</u>
<u n="2444" who="S0635">which was really nice of her</u>
<u n="2445" who="S0632">she did cos we told her to go home <vocal desc="laugh"/> but</u>
<u n="2446" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah we thought we'd just get a hotel in Boston or something</u>
<u n="2447" who="S0632">but we didn't have to and she drove us back to their house</u>
<u n="2448" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2449" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and spent a day or two with the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>s</u>
<u n="2450" who="S0635">we did yeah we didn't do much I remember picking <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> up from work I remember doing to Cracker Barrel to get souvenirs</u>
<u n="2451" who="S0632">yeah to pick up the last few souvenirs</u>
<u n="2452" who="S0635" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> dropped by to see us and we gave her back her</u>
<u n="2453" who="S0632">her camping gear</u>
<u n="2454" who="S0635">her camping gear</u>
<u n="2455" who="S0632">and we ate <unclear>Caesar</unclear> salad with a</u>
<u n="2456" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2457" who="S0632">in the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s house cos we had it</u>
<u n="2458" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2459" who="S0632">to ourself for a bit</u>
<u n="2460" who="S0635">mm but I think we didn't do much <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came round for dinner one night</u>
<u n="2461" who="S0632">that was about it yeah it was</u>
<u n="2462" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2463" who="S0632">quite low key but that's probably what we needed at the end</u>
<u n="2464" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2465" who="S0632">and then just get put back on our our plane and</u>
<u n="2466" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2467" who="S0632" trans="overlap">fly home to the UK</u>
<u n="2468" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2469" who="S0632">and again there was a few delays in Iceland and stuff but on the whole it was pretty uneventful</u>
<u n="2470" who="S0635">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I guess and that was it and then my dad picked us up and we were completely knackered but my mum had been round our house to help tidy it a bit for us</u>
<u n="2471" who="S0632">she had yeah</u>
<u n="2472" who="S0635" trans="overlap">which was really sweet it was really nice actually</u>
<u n="2473" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2474" who="S0635" trans="overlap">but yeah we were totally zonked out</u>
<u n="2475" who="S0632">completely zonked yeah</u>
<u n="2476" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="2477" who="S0632">and it's just amazing we fit that much in was that a three-week from end to end from arriving</u>
<u n="2478" who="S0635" trans="overlap"><trunc>someth</trunc></u>
<u n="2479" who="S0632" trans="overlap">in the US to leaving the US?</u>
<u n="2480" who="S0635">yeah I think so yeah maybe a little longer something like that</u>
<u n="2481" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2482" who="S0635">yeah I'm pretty impressed actually <pause dur="short"/> I think don't think we forgot got much I mean</u>
<u n="2483" who="S0632">I <trunc>thi</trunc> it's hard to remember absolutely everything but it's interesting that we haven't forgotten too much and it's one of those things where you suddenly start to remember more about it when you start talking about it</u>
<u n="2484" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah I <trunc>tha</trunc> if you take it step by step but little animals we saw what was that funny thing we saw on the road?</u>
<u n="2485" who="S0632">was that like a a porcupine or something you saw on the road? or</u>
<u n="2486" who="S0635" trans="overlap">it was a</u>
<u n="2487" who="S0632">or was that in Kings Canyon?</u>
<u n="2488" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2489" who="S0632" trans="overlap">you saw some sort of</u>
<u n="2490" who="S0635">was it a pine marten or</u>
<u n="2491" who="S0632" trans="overlap">a pine marten <trunc>s</trunc>some</u>
<u n="2492" who="S0635" trans="overlap"><trunc>y</trunc> well I dunno</u>
<u n="2493" who="S0632">marmoset</u>
<u n="2494" who="S0635">yeah a <trunc>mar</trunc></u>
<u n="2495" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2496" who="S0635">oh the marmot I think</u>
<u n="2497" who="S0632" trans="overlap">a marmot</u>
<u n="2498" who="S0635">I think it was a marmot yes</u>
<u n="2499" who="S0632">yay</u>
<u n="2500" who="S0635">yeah and I can remember other meals and things</u>
<u n="2501" who="S0632" trans="overlap">or is it <trunc>c</trunc> was it Canada jays we saw at Ventana?</u>
<u n="2502" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah there's a few different kinds of jay that we saw</u>
<u n="2503" who="S0632">oh what the other kind of jay we saw? something jay</u>
<u n="2504" who="S0635">yeah I can't remember it now</u>
<u n="2505" who="S0632">with the funny head things</u>
<u n="2506" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2507" who="S0632">Steller's jay</u>
<u n="2508" who="S0635">Steller's jay that's it yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2509" who="S0632">yeah we did see quite a lot of wildlife and I was happy that our bear experience wasn't as terrifying as as my mind had made it</u>
<u n="2510" who="S0635">no it was very pleasant yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2511" who="S0632" trans="overlap">so I know you still need to be really careful around bears but I'd imagined the <trunc>b</trunc></u>
<u n="2512" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="2513" who="S0632">first and last bear</u>
<u n="2514" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2515" who="S0632">I would ever see with be a grizzly bear tearing its way into my tent rather than a black bear solemnly sloping off into the woods going</u>
<u n="2516" who="S0635" trans="overlap">oh he was sweet</u>
<u n="2517" who="S0632">leave me alone tourists</u>
<u n="2518" who="S0635">yeah well and we</u>
<u n="2519" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2520" who="S0635">were lucky like from speaking to other people like almost no one had seen a bear that year</u>
<u n="2521" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah people who were yeah</u>
<u n="2522" who="S0635" trans="overlap">I mean yeah</u>
<u n="2523" who="S0632" trans="overlap">people who work there in the camp were like</u>
<u n="2524" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="2525" who="S0632">yeah I haven't seen a bear yet this year</u>
<u n="2526" who="S0635">uhu uhu</u>
<u n="2527" who="S0632">so we were really lucky</u>
<u n="2528" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2529" who="S0632">even just to see one sloping off I got a fairly good view of it</u>
<u n="2530" who="S0635">yeah yeah we <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="2531" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I saw it for a good five minutes or so</u>
<u n="2532" who="S0635" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="2533" who="S0632">before it disappeared and</u>
<u n="2534" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2535" who="S0632">it's not like that moose that I never saw</u>
<u n="2536" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2537" who="S0632">from our last American trip</u>
<u n="2538" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="2539" who="S0632">but yeah it was dreamy completely dreamy</u>
<u n="2540" who="S0635">mm yeah it's hard to sum up really just when you're talking about it</u>
<u n="2541" who="S0632">all the different legs had quite a different feel like from from San Francisco or to driving down Highway one to LA to the Desert</u>
<u n="2542" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah I'm quite pleased by just the little things like the trees and the rocks and the</u>
<u n="2543" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2544" who="S0635">different birds and the smell and the sort of sense of everything just being bigger and</u>
<u n="2545" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2546" who="S0635">the music that we listened to and</u>
<u n="2547" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2548" who="S0635">it was just really good</u>
<u n="2549" who="S0632">I quite like in some ways that bits of it were hard it made it</u>
<u n="2550" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="2551" who="S0632">more of a more of a rollercoaster and</u>
<u n="2552" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2553" who="S0632">more of a full experience I guess</u>
<u n="2554" who="S0635">yeah I mean</u>
<u n="2555" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I mean not in the actual moment I could have like</u>
<u n="2556" who="S0635">you</u>
<u n="2557" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2558" who="S0635">can't expect to cram that much in and and</u>
<u n="2559" who="S0632" trans="overlap">not have hard moments</u>
<u n="2560" who="S0635">no yeah you can just stay in one hotel for two weeks by a pool</u>
<u n="2561" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2562" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and</u>
<u n="2563" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2564" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and not be taxed but <vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>ye</trunc></u>
<u n="2565" who="S0632" trans="overlap">well even our next holiday</u>
<u n="2566" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="2567" who="S0632">even though it's a traditional holiday in the sense of it's sun and sand</u>
<u n="2568" who="S0635">uhu</u>
<u n="2569" who="S0632">we're not sticking in one hotel we're</u>
<u n="2570" who="S0635">no we've got a lot to see</u>
<u n="2571" who="S0632" trans="overlap">hopping from island to island</u>
<u n="2572" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2573" who="S0632" trans="overlap">and making sure we fit in as much as possibly can it's like we can't have a relaxing holiday we have to</u>
<u n="2574" who="S0635">I think</u>
<u n="2575" who="S0632" trans="overlap">keep moving around</u>
<u n="2576" who="S0635" trans="overlap">this one will be probably more relaxing but yeah</u>
<u n="2577" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I would have thought so I mean</u>
<u n="2578" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="2579" who="S0632">I kind of hope so just because you know I just wanna spend a lot of time snorkelling</u>
<u n="2580" who="S0635">yeah</u>
<u n="2581" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2582" who="S0635">it's just hard I always feel a bit like I'm being I guess a bit like as is says you always feel a bit like you're being cheated out of a better or like another experience if you don't go and do something else and</u>
<u n="2583" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah you're worried that you're er</u>
<u n="2584" who="S0635">missing something or</u>
<u n="2585" who="S0632" trans="overlap">missing something amazing by by making a decision</u>
<u n="2586" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and you're gonna leave without ever seeing like the most ridiculous beach or something and it's like</u>
<u n="2587" who="S0632" trans="overlap">ah yeah it's really hard cos the world's so vast and</u>
<u n="2588" who="S0635">mm</u>
<u n="2589" who="S0632">and everyone's got a different opinion about what the important thing is to do in LA for example</u>
<u n="2590" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2591" who="S0632">and it's like you didn't do that? it's like no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2592" who="S0635"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2593" who="S0632" trans="overlap">we weren't there very long</u>
<u n="2594" who="S0635">yeah er but I I think the best thing is that like we didn't I didn't feel like we missed anything like I wasn't wanting for anything like I felt like we did great stuff every day</u>
<u n="2595" who="S0632">we did and</u>
<u n="2596" who="S0635" trans="overlap">and I was really pleased with all the like things we saw and</u>
<u n="2597" who="S0632">I well</u>
<u n="2598" who="S0635" trans="overlap">the memories we made and</u>
<u n="2599" who="S0632" trans="overlap">for us seeing erm the Watts Towers and Salvation mountain they're a huge deal</u>
<u n="2600" who="S0635">yeah like that once <trunc>th</trunc> like that was <trunc>ju</trunc>just two days but</u>
<u n="2601" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="2602" who="S0635">I was like I don't care what I see now like</u>
<u n="2603" who="S0632">it's like</u>
<u n="2604" who="S0635" trans="overlap">cos I've seen</u>
<u n="2605" who="S0632" trans="overlap">if if if I don't see anything else amazing this holiday then</u>
<u n="2606" who="S0635">I've still seen this sort of like my favourite things that I've ever seen <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2607" who="S0632">yeah that's pretty good <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2608" who="S0635">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2609" who="S0635" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="2610" who="S0632">oh</u>
<u n="2611" who="S0635" trans="overlap">yeah that's so true</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
