<text id="SEGU">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:43:04</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-02-25</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0041 S0084</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Friendships, relationships, clothes</topics>
		<activity>Drinking coffee, discussing friends</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0041">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Conference and Events Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0084">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lewisham, London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Production Controller</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0084">kidney stones</u>
<u n="2" who="S0041">that's the truth</u>
<u n="3" who="S0084">after the Christmas party yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0041">A private shindig</u>
<u n="5" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's why I've been having hot water and lemon every morning before work cos it's supposed to flush out your kidneys <pause dur="short"/> so I have it an hour before eating I think that's why I take cereal to work so I have that at seven thirty and then I have my cereal well whenever I feel like <unclear/> Anyway sorry if I'm rude but I keep forgetting I'm supposed to be recording my fecking conversations <pause dur="short"/> right Alex is mental</u>
<u n="6" who="S0041">yeah no he's actually nuts</u>
<u n="7" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0041">he's actually crazy so</u>
<u n="9" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="10" who="S0041">we're driving to <trunc>Car</trunc> and I realise this is now a one-way conversation that he's talking out to me</u>
<u n="11" who="S0084">is that cos you're hung-over or you just haven't had a chance to get any word in?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0041">yeah well or if I put words in <pause dur="short"/> you know I'm like I try and <pause dur="short"/> I'm not very good at the the touchy feeling conversations</u>
<u n="13" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0041">so he's saying to me that she <trunc>re</trunc> you know she's been on her on own for single for so long that she didn't eh <pause dur="short"/> she just wanted her independence back and <trunc>sh</trunc> he said you know we've just been seeing each other for twenty weeks <pause dur="short"/> I thought <trunc>t</trunc> so you worked out exact pinpoint twenty weeks like not a few months</u>
<u n="15" who="S0084">twenty weeks? When did he split up with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0041">no sorry I'm on about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="18" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0084">I thought this was the one in <anon type="place"/> right okay</u>
<u n="20" who="S0041">no right</u>
<u n="21" who="S0084">him and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> they've seen each other for twenty weeks</u>
<u n="22" who="S0041">what a strange way to quantify it</u>
<u n="23" who="S0084">who says that?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0041">I know</u>
<u n="25" who="S0084">wouldn't you just say four months or five months or whatever it was?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0041">yeah no <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="27" who="S0084">twenty weeks</u>
<u n="28" who="S0041">which I thought was weird in the first place</u>
<u n="29" who="S0084">like checking off on the calendar with red crosses</u>
<u n="30" who="S0041">exactly <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="31" who="S0084">mm okay</u>
<u n="32" who="S0041">em so I was like hmm that's a bit weird</u>
<u n="33" who="S0084">so she wants her independence</u>
<u n="34" who="S0041">anyway so she wants her independence back em and they were just you know seeing each other and having fun and you know it did seem to start to open up as if it was going to go somewhere and</u>
<u n="35" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0041">then she's run a mile and he said really I I just I thought to myself <pause dur="short"/> if her heart's not in it then there's no point you know what will be will be</u>
<u n="37" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0041">and so really it was kind of mutual <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't at all cos the conversation prior to that when he explained that she said it was all basically all her doing</u>
<u n="39" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0041">he's then tried to convince himself that he can have some say in this</u>
<u n="41" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="42" who="S0041">which was really weird <pause dur="short"/> and then he starts he says you know she she just she's got so many things that she wants to do as if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was now now now the way he's talking about her</u>
<u n="43" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0041">is as if she's this amazing fantastic person</u>
<u n="45" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="46" who="S0041">but they're just drifting apart and I said oh oh right em you know <trunc>wh</trunc> what type of stuff does she wants to do you know</u>
<u n="47" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0041">try and ask it about you know found out a bit about her try and put myself in his position a bit</u>
<u n="49" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0041">em you know well she just you know she wants to you know she wants to travel and you know and she's done the hairdresser thing and now she's doing the Premier Inn thing and</u>
<u n="51" who="S0084">the what?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0041">premier Inn <pause dur="short"/> she works for Premier Inn</u>
<u n="53" who="S0084">oh I thought we were premiering you know like <vocal desc="laugh"/> Chairman Mao or something she was out there you know in ruling countries <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> she works for Premier Inn <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="54" who="S0041">and that's the big dream</u>
<u n="55" who="S0084">that's the living living living the dream</u>
<u n="56" who="S0041" trans="overlap">as the hairdressing was the big dream</u>
<u n="57" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="58" who="S0041">and so I wasn't quite following and then I</u>
<u n="59" who="S0084">so she was a hairdresser for?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0041">maybe this is me being a snob right I don't know</u>
<u n="61" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0041">but she's like yeah now she's doing the Premier Inn thing and you know and I think maybe a year from now you know she probably you know <trunc>sh</trunc> she might even work abroad <pause dur="short"/> I mean she's already moving out of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="63" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0084">aw he's such a local boy</u>
<u n="65" who="S0041">I know and I said</u>
<u n="66" who="S0084">aw bless him</u>
<u n="67" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> I wait till you find out where to <pause dur="short"/> so I said oh right she oh right she <trunc>al</trunc> she's always lived in <anon type="place"/> then? </u>
<u n="68" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0041">well yes yeah oh oh I see <pause dur="short"/> I thought why the frig? Anyway I thought I can't say that cos you did too</u>
<u n="70" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="71" who="S0041">I said oh where is she moving to? Oh she's moving to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="72" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0084">that's it she's going up in the world</u>
<u n="74" who="S0041">she's moving to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0084">oh bless</u>
<u n="76" who="S0041">in with her auntie <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0084">oh kids</u>
<u n="78" who="S0041" trans="overlap">three strikes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0084">oh bless him he is special isn't he let's be honest</u>
<u n="80" who="S0041">it gets better <pause dur="short"/> it gets so much better <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0084">go on then</u>
<u n="82" who="S0041">and then he said you know and she says to me <pause dur="short"/> you know you've done the whole travelling thing you know <pause dur="short"/> you you went out there you know you went to New Zealand and I haven't had that</u>
<u n="83" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0041">it's the way</u>
<u n="85" who="S0084">yeah but</u>
<u n="86" who="S0041">he didn't go travelling <pause dur="short"/> he went on a three week holiday <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah and I just thought oh Jesus like I want to I want to be empathetic <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="87" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0041">but I'm just thinking what the fuck are these people for real? </u>
<u n="89" who="S0084">yeah no</u>
<u n="90" who="S0041">I I just really can't get on board with people that are like that <pause dur="short"/> I can't I just can't understand it</u>
<u n="91" who="S0084">bless them they live in a very small world</u>
<u n="92" who="S0041">really small</u>
<u n="93" who="S0084">though don't they?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0041">really small</u>
<u n="95" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> you know when you go back for a visit it's all very lovely you know you go to the village and you think oh nothing's changed all the same people you know it's lovely and you can just pretend that it's all sort of the same and it's em you know comforting</u>
<u n="96" who="S0041">yeah comforting yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0084">but then you leave</u>
<u n="98" who="S0041">that's it</u>
<u n="99" who="S0084">and you go and do your other life</u>
<u n="100" who="S0041">your real life</u>
<u n="101" who="S0084">you go and you know you're ambitious and do a job and you look at where you're going not not for them</u>
<u n="102" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0084">you know they're just going to go to the pub everyday and see the same people every day</u>
<u n="104" who="S0041">yes exactamundo</u>
<u n="105" who="S0084">their aspirations are moving from a two bedroomed house in <anon type="place"/> to a three bedroomed house in <anon type="place"/> maybe off the high street <pause dur="short"/> like you know</u>
<u n="106" who="S0041">that's it <pause dur="short"/> I've never known people like that</u>
<u n="107" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0041">I've never like</u>
<u n="109" who="S0084">quite a village mentality isn't it?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0041">yeah and it just really shocked me</u>
<u n="111" who="S0084">oh bless him <pause dur="short"/> I suppose like it doesn't worry me if that's what makes people happy</u>
<u n="112" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0084">if it but it you know if he was <trunc>d</trunc> I mean <pause dur="short"/> it's difficult to say whether he sounds unhappy cos it sounds like he's living in denial a little bit which probably means he is kind of a bit unhappy</u>
<u n="114" who="S0041">he said well you know I just don't want to lose a friend over it </u>
<u n="115" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0041">and I was like well to be honest I think I'm coming to the realization that perhaps you can't be friends with an ex </u>
<u n="117" who="S0084">not immediately</u>
<u n="118" who="S0041">you know <pause dur="short"/> and he said yeah we've got the same circle of friends we're always going to be bumping in to each other so hope we can be civil <pause dur="short"/> I said I'm sure you will at some point don't worry about it now </u>
<u n="119" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0041">and he said you know well just <pause dur="short"/> I'm having a realisation and just the clarity I really know what I want now <pause dur="short"/> and I was like oh right yeah so what you know what you thinking? Not em moving somewhere or travelling somewhere or getting a better job or improving his own job</u>
<u n="121" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> eh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a <anon type="place"/> girl</u>
<u n="123" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0041">I was like oh okay em</u>
<u n="125" who="S0084">so where did she come from?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0041">they've known each other for years <pause dur="short"/> eh I think it was his ex-girlfriends <pause dur="short"/> they met somehow through breaking up with people</u>
<u n="127" who="S0084">as you do</u>
<u n="128" who="S0041">yeah really kind of weird <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>ash <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>ish situation</u>
<u n="129" who="S0084">where everyone knows each other</u>
<u n="130" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="131" who="S0084">and everyone's cheating on each other</u>
<u n="132" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> and then she basically got screwed up screwed over by this guy</u>
<u n="133" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0041">and Alex got to know about her better he spent a lot of time with her and basically for three years they kind of pushed boundaries quite a lot <pause dur="short"/> and he said you know I just this is what I want and I don't want to rush into it <pause dur="short"/> I thought yeah cos he slept with her </u>
<u n="135" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And you left her in bed which you just declared in the kitchen earlier</u>
<u n="136" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and he was like you know we both you know we both you know our last serious partners are both younger than us and <pause dur="short"/> you know we've both been screwed over you know <trunc>t</trunc> these people came back into our lives and we welcomed them with open arms we got shit in again <pause dur="short"/> and we just both have been through very similar things I just think you know I think you know it might be something so <pause dur="short"/> and I'm think is there only me that's sat in the world right now screaming at people have you all gone fucking mad? </u>
<u n="137" who="S0084">well yeah <trunc>m</trunc> <trunc>ma</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I think it's the beginning of the year because think in January and February everyone says fuck I'm single <pause dur="short"/> I've had enough of being single I know I'll just throw myself at the nearest nut job and hope for the best <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="138" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0084">the two quite damaged mental people think do you know what would be a brilliant idea? Let's get into a relationship together and be mental together <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="140" who="S0041">together <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0084">at least they're not afflicting it on anybody else <pause dur="short"/> but surely that's just gonna end in disaster cos they're just gonna be more and more mental together so</u>
<u n="142" who="S0041">I know</u>
<u n="143" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">hi</u>
<u n="144" who="S0041">hi</u>
<u n="145" who="S0084">hi Anna</u>
<u n="146" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">are you going to have dinner now or?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0041">no no</u>
<u n="148" who="S0084">are we in your way? No come in</u>
<u n="149" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh thanks</u>
<u n="150" who="S0041">we can retire to the boudoir</u>
<u n="151" who="S0084">yes <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="152" who="S0041">well <trunc>w</trunc> what?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0084">and when really what they actually have to do is think I I just need to be single for a little while </u>
<u n="154" who="S0084">I know I know I just</u>
<u n="155" who="S0041">but surely</u>
<u n="156" who="S0084">it's actual nuttiness</u>
<u n="157" who="S0041">it's the same thing with that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> isn't it? She just needs to be single <pause dur="short"/> sounds like she's just lurched from one disaster to another</u>
<u n="158" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="159" who="S0041">in actual fact being in a relationship does you more damage <pause dur="short"/> oh well that's not as tidy as I want it to be</u>
<u n="160" who="S0084">well you've done well though considering when I poked my head in this morning <pause dur="short"/> I mean it really is em it's really not that bad</u>
<u n="161" who="S0041">urgh</u>
<u n="162" who="S0084">it's nice and warm though</u>
<u n="163" who="S0041">nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's <pause dur="short"/> I just the whole whole thing's oh dear <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0084">what is that?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0041">what is this on my head?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0084">where did this grow from? Oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came round earlier and I said about the shower and she said well last week I got a message saying it was cold so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came in and turned it up and well what can I do? I had to get him to take the regulator out of the shower cos you said it was cold I was like hang on A </u>
<u n="167" who="S0041">she took the regulator of the shower?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0084">yeah and the the <trunc>wat</trunc> it's fucking boiling <pause dur="short"/> and I said well mine was okay but it got hot <pause dur="short"/> by the time Anna who had the next shower came in it was too hot and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had to shower and said she had to keep getting out of it <pause dur="short"/> And <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said well you know let me know on Sunday but she wouldn't even really talk to me so that was quite interesting she was only really talking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and she said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> text me on Sunday </u>
<u n="169" who="S0041">I think it's because she knows that with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she gets somewhere like</u>
<u n="170" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0041">she doesn't have to be very committal she doesn't have to say much</u>
<u n="172" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="173" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will just let her get away with stuff</u>
<u n="174" who="S0084">basically yeah it's because I'm <pause dur="short"/> I just tell her how it is like no you're not getting <trunc>r</trunc> more rent from me <pause dur="short"/> these are days you will get rent from me <pause dur="short"/> this is what we agreed do not be mental <pause dur="short"/> what is in that bag you running away to sea?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0084">is this you joining the navy now?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0041">yeah this is it</u>
<u n="178" who="S0084">all in the bag</u>
<u n="179" who="S0041">eh this was my swimming stuff actually <pause dur="short"/> I really can't be bothered to pack my bag now I think I'm going to do it tomorrow</u>
<u n="180" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0041">which I always do this and then in the morning in the morning I think why the fuck did you do that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? Why didn't you just pack your bag? Maybe I'll just put my clothes in it</u>
<u n="182" who="S0084">oh could you just why don't you just make a pile <pause dur="short"/> make it like throw things here not throw them like fold the clothes that you want to take and then at least it's all out on the side and then you can just you know scoop and place in the bag</u>
<u n="183" who="S0041">em I really want to wear these</u>
<u n="184" who="S0084">was? Ah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0041">it's just not the weather yet</u>
<u n="186" who="S0084">not yet <pause dur="short"/> soon <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>tue</trunc> no yes Tuesday is going to be fourteen degrees <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna be a heat wave <pause dur="short"/> so em maybe you can wear them to work</u>
<u n="187" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="188" who="S0084">I think they're probably appropriate</u>
<u n="189" who="S0041">yes I can definitely do that</u>
<u n="190" who="S0084">yeah darling <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> Can't stop yawning today</u>
<u n="191" who="S0041">yeah I told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about the message that I sent to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like yes <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> She's like that's great what else can we do? Do you know what if you've been on her Facebook she'll have been on yours <pause dur="short"/> I said but she can't see mine cos it's private </u>
<u n="192" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="193" who="S0041">she just be on to the profile pictures</u>
<u n="194" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0041">she's like so what you need to do is take photographs put them on Facebook put them in profile pictures you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="196" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0041">so I'm gonna do it <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna do it</u>
<u n="198" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0041">she basically <trunc>thr</trunc> the through through all this crapple apple she just says I <trunc>do</trunc> I just don't <pause dur="short"/> it just makes me really sad he would behave that way <pause dur="short"/> cos she knows him quite well</u>
<u n="200" who="S0084">who does? Eve?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> em and she just said I just don't understand it and it's been just a tosser the way he's going about things <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="202" who="S0084">I think that blokes are like that though <pause dur="short"/> like when you're in a relationship with them they're nothing but as sweet as pie and then as soon as it's over they're like right well I can just be totally selfish which in their head means act like a twat which is unfortunate <pause dur="short"/> I mean not all blokes let's not all generalise <pause dur="short"/> but I think in his head he's like right well that's it now you told me that I'm single and that I just <trunc>s</trunc> that you don't want to be with me anymore and so I can just do what I like <pause dur="short"/> </u>
<u n="203" who="S0084">this is not appropriate dinner wear is it?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0041">the sex top <pause dur="short"/> have you got a blouse like em a vest top that you could wear underneath it or does it not really go with a vest top?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0084">I don't it doesn't really go but I'm going to take it just in case <pause dur="short"/> it's definitely not dinner wear <pause dur="short"/> I can't wear that to go out for a meal can I?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0041">no you can't <pause dur="short"/> I mean unless you don't take the eh the jacket off but you might wear something really warm?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0041">so that's a bit that's a bit dangerous</u>
<u n="209" who="S0084">I'll take the sex top and maybe I'll put the sex top on</u>
<u n="210" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0084">and wander round the room in it a little while and then say do you know what? I can't I really can't wear this to dinner I'm going to put my other top on</u>
<u n="212" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> fine</u>
<u n="213" who="S0084">just so then he can see the sex top but I just won't wear the sex top out</u>
<u n="214" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0084">that's fine</u>
<u n="216" who="S0041">I like it as a plan</u>
<u n="217" who="S0084">it's a definite plan</u>
<u n="218" who="S0041">so wear the wear the leather <trunc>trou</trunc> cos that that's the evening outfit <pause dur="short"/> the leather trousers I'm going to have to have taken in</u>
<u n="219" who="S0084">really? How exciting</u>
<u n="220" who="S0041">yeah but I'm keeping them <pause dur="short"/> I love them</u>
<u n="221" who="S0084">well obviously yeah <pause dur="short"/> so fourteen is too big now?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0084">winner</u>
<u n="224" who="S0041">I mean I think it's just the trousers I think obviously I don't know</u>
<u n="225" who="S0084">can you wash them though?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0041">maybe as I've worn them</u>
<u n="227" who="S0084">boil wash?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0041">you can't wash them</u>
<u n="229" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="230" who="S0041">wipe clean only <pause dur="short"/> I think all it would all it needs is just the darts</u>
<u n="231" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="232" who="S0041">doing a little but deeper cos they're not very deep at all</u>
<u n="233" who="S0084">no it's quite an easy job there's a woman at the market who does em tailoring</u>
<u n="234" who="S0041">yeah she could perhaps just take them they're not they're really not very much too much big it's literally just the waist band</u>
<u n="235" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0041">they're fine everywhere</u>
<u n="237" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0041">but the waistband they they slip down</u>
<u n="239" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0041">as I walk and I think I think because my legs just aren't fat enough to keep them tight to here so</u>
<u n="241" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="242" who="S0041">they slide down my thighs then my thighs then pull it down from the waist so</u>
<u n="243" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no you <trunc>ju</trunc> you just don't want to feel uncomfortable in them</u>
<u n="244" who="S0041">yeah I don't know I don't know what the best thing to do would be whether perhaps it might be better for her to take them in on the leg rather than the waist <pause dur="short"/> cos the last thing you want is muffin top bulge</u>
<u n="245" who="S0084">well that's not gonna happen cos you're gonna just gonna get smaller <pause dur="short"/> so but it's probably worth doing the leg and waist while she's there</u>
<u n="246" who="S0041">yeah maybe</u>
<u n="247" who="S0084">I mean it's difficult isn't it? Cos you kinda want her to do it not so you can wear them now <pause dur="short"/> but you're just if you're gonna get skinnier again you'll have to do it again</u>
<u n="248" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="249" who="S0084">I mean can you put up with it for now?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0041">I think so</u>
<u n="251" who="S0084">I would wait</u>
<u n="252" who="S0041">they didn't annoy me too much last night <pause dur="short"/> em I just have to it sounds ridiculous but I just have to make sure that this is on my skin and not on my underwear</u>
<u n="253" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="254" who="S0041">Cos against skin it tends to to go less</u>
<u n="255" who="S0084">yeah it sticks a bit doesn't it?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so cos they're they're just quite straight do you see what I mean?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="258" who="S0041">like they're not they're not large</u>
<u n="259" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0041">they're they're not a small pair of trousers it's not like they're ridiculously too small they're just very straight <pause dur="short"/> so they</u>
<u n="261" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="262" who="S0041">they should really go in at the waist to kind of hug on a bit</u>
<u n="263" who="S0084">yeah pick up <pause dur="short"/> well I'd just wait a few weeks <pause dur="short"/> like if you can put up with it for now and then eh</u>
<u n="264" who="S0041">yeah maybe</u>
<u n="265" who="S0084">see how you go <pause dur="short"/> see how you go with the old not eating</u>
<u n="266" who="S0041">we'll see how we go with that</u>
<u n="267" who="S0084">yeah are you going to see the GP this week? Make an appointment? I was going to send you that link actually <pause dur="short"/> got to dig that out the nutritionist link</u>
<u n="268" who="S0041">yeah I <trunc>do</trunc> I don't really know what to do <pause dur="short"/> cos I just I just feel like I'm being stupid</u>
<u n="269" who="S0084">you're not though are you? I mean you are eating quite healthily generally speaking you're not eating an awful lot <pause dur="short"/> I mean what it could be is you need to be eating more of smaller things</u>
<u n="270" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="271" who="S0084">to boost your metabolism</u>
<u n="272" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> more often</u>
<u n="273" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you need to just sort of reverse what you're doing</u>
<u n="274" who="S0041">sexy little top <pause dur="short"/> sexy little top</u>
<u n="275" who="S0084">so what are you going to wear down there tomorrow?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0041">I'm wearing this</u>
<u n="277" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="278" who="S0041">with this black vest and this top <pause dur="short"/> have you seen this?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0084">oh yeah you did show me that yeah it's cute</u>
<u n="280" who="S0041">em I'm gonna take this in my handbag</u>
<u n="281" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0041">just so if it's cold I'm just gonna shove it over</u>
<u n="283" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0041">em and black tights and my flat boots</u>
<u n="285" who="S0084">which are somewhere safe</u>
<u n="286" who="S0041">yeah god knows where the hell they are they might be in the hall</u>
<u n="287" who="S0084">I ate them</u>
<u n="288" who="S0041">you ate my beautiful black boots?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0084">so I was texting what I thought was your number earlier I think I have about four different numbers for you because I think I've got the old number which I thought I'd deleted</u>
<u n="290" who="S0041">did anyone reply?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0084">well someone did reply to your number they said this is the wrong number and I was like oh my god I've got the thief I've got the thief </u>
<u n="292" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0084">reply <pause dur="short"/> cos I sent you a message saying oh I was looking for my frying pan but the frying pan's dead </u>
<u n="294" who="S0041">oh shit yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0084"> Oh how I miss you frying pan who art in heaven rest in peace like this really stupid message and I sent it <pause dur="short"/> it sent twice for some reason and then and then I text you saying how how's the wedding going? But my stupid predictive text put like how's rhetorically wedding going life rather than the <pause dur="short"/> ridiculously so then I had to write I meant the wedding and are we having tonight? And at that point but I'd said like hi duck </u>
<u n="296" who="S0041">which we can have wine</u>
<u n="297" who="S0084">which we can have wine yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I put hi duck and then about ten minutes later em someone replies saying sorry duck wrong number <pause dur="short"/> and I was like oh my god I've got the thief this is brilliant I can track them down <pause dur="short"/> and eh and they they said and I'm also sorry about your frying pan <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like sorry about that <pause dur="short"/> em so I was like eh sorry who is this? And they said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and in my head I was like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> from Plymouth? Like what how would I have got his number? And I hadn't even thought it would be <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but and so I replied and I said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who? Without thinking but then because but it's saved as <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> in my phone <pause dur="short"/> but then when I looked for Stu's number it's not in my phone <pause dur="short"/> so my phone is doing some very interesting things</u>
<u n="298" who="S0041">how weird</u>
<u n="299" who="S0084">yeah but then I sent the message like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who? What are you talking about? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who? This is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and then he didn't reply <pause dur="short"/> he was probably quite insulted that I was like em</u>
<u n="300" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you're a liar</u>
<u n="301" who="S0084">who are you?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0041">where is my black vest? I didn't wear a vest yesterday did I? What did I wear yesterday? To the pub? Do we know? I can't remember</u>
<u n="303" who="S0084">nothing</u>
<u n="304" who="S0041">ooh</u>
<u n="305" who="S0084">birthday suit</u>
<u n="306" who="S0041">I definitely I didn't wear my vest <pause dur="short"/> which means I've I've lost a <trunc>ves</trunc> it's in the bag <pause dur="short"/> it's fine <pause dur="short"/> panic over <pause dur="short"/> so I wonder how many other numbers it's done it to?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0084">well it's a bit of a concern so I just that's what I deleted all the numbers that I had for you and when you text me saying I'm home I was like right that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> get that in <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> so I've got that number but because my numbers for some reason are all synced so all the details I've got your <trunc>Face</trunc> well I haven't got no I deleted everything <pause dur="short"/> so I had your Facebook I had your phone number but now see now I've got two three records for <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> because that's that's you know you can never have too many</u>
<u n="308" who="S0041">no well never</u>
<u n="309" who="S0084">but that but if I open it it says no additional information for this contact <pause dur="short"/> this phone is quite annoying <pause dur="short"/> open that one <pause dur="short"/> oh this is your number isn't it? It ends three six five?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0041">double three six three six five</u>
<u n="311" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so that's you and what's that one? That's yeah That's yeah Oh and what's four three four? Is that the old one?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0041">that sounds like an old a number I know so I'm guessing it must be the old one</u>
<u n="313" who="S0084">shall I try and call it? No cos that might be Stu <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="314" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="315" who="S0084">can't have that</u>
<u n="316" who="S0041">but I think that might be my old one</u>
<u n="317" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="318" who="S0041">so that's day number one outfit there</u>
<u n="319" who="S0084">lovely</u>
<u n="320" who="S0041">that's day number two outfit there and night outfit there <pause dur="short"/> pants</u>
<u n="321" who="S0084">pantaloons</u>
<u n="322" who="S0041">I'll have to put some washing later I think cos I <pause dur="short"/> I want <trunc>go</trunc> I want good pants I think I might have been silly an worn them <pause dur="short"/> you're a winner you're a winner <pause dur="short"/> well you Well you can be up yeah you you will have to be winners today I'm afraid <pause dur="short"/> em you can all you can all be winners I think <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah jamas jamas <pause dur="short"/> yes get jamas</u>
<u n="323" who="S0084">Don't forget jamas you need them in your life <pause dur="short"/> oh no I've deleted the wrong one</u>
<u n="324" who="S0041">fucking idiot</u>
<u n="325" who="S0084">for the love of god <pause dur="short"/> I am a fucking idiot it's true</u>
<u n="326" who="S0041">these really need ironing</u>
<u n="327" who="S0084">is that an issue? It's just your pjs <pause dur="short"/> I think you're probably alright <pause dur="short"/> don't well you you have to be cos you can't use that iron cos it will destroy everything you own</u>
<u n="328" who="S0084">oh that's true</u>
<u n="329" who="S0041">put them in the shower tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> not in the shower cos that would be mental</u>
<u n="330" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0041">oh god I don't know what to do</u>
<u n="332" who="S0084">well they're cute just wear those</u>
<u n="333" who="S0041">em yeah I was gonna wear these but I'm thinking about the situation we discussed earlier</u>
<u n="334" who="S0084">ah that is an issue</u>
<u n="335" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0084">that is a quite serious issue hmm</u>
<u n="337" who="S0041">I mean either way what I wear is really not going to save me much is it?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0084">well no</u>
<u n="339" who="S0041">come worst case scenario time</u>
<u n="340" who="S0084">at least there be no like no well I don't know I mean it's</u>
<u n="341" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0041">maybe maybe well tell you what we'll play it by ear so I'll take another pair</u>
<u n="344" who="S0084">take everything <pause dur="short"/> I mean you are only going for a couple of days so <trunc>yo</trunc> you know</u>
<u n="345" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0084">you aren't going to pack that much</u>
<u n="347" who="S0041">I really wish I had a dark pair <pause dur="short"/> but I don't <pause dur="short"/> like a black pair <pause dur="short"/> ah leggings I suppose?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0041">what am I talking about? You're dark <pause dur="short"/> I mean I had you on last night which is a bit of a killer</u>
<u n="350" who="S0084">you've only worn them a couple of nights though <pause dur="short"/> febreeze? I wouldn't even worry about them <pause dur="short"/> they're only a couple of days old</u>
<u n="351" who="S0041">still smell of em washing powder</u>
<u n="352" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0041">there we go so you're you're a winner and then</u>
<u n="354" who="S0084">got a pyjama top?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0041">pyjama top</u>
<u n="356" who="S0084">unless you're going to go breasticles out?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0041">probably gonna go breasticles out</u>
<u n="358" who="S0084">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> but you've got your growler covered so that's fine</u>
<u n="359" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That's great <pause dur="short"/> oh where is? Where are? There we go</u>
<u n="360" who="S0041">so you <trunc>hav</trunc> you haven't had had time time to check your Facebook then?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0084">did it at work</u>
<u n="362" who="S0041">and did he reply?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0084">nope fuck and</u>
<u n="364" who="S0041"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0084">he's been online</u>
<u n="366" who="S0041">oh really?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0084">so his <unclear/> not replied so em</u>
<u n="368" who="S0041">on the wall it goes</u>
<u n="369" who="S0084">on the wall it went</u>
<u n="370" who="S0041">and perfectly</u>
<u n="371" who="S0084">you put it?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> and perfectly Facebook because the message is quite long chops it</u>
<u n="373" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0041">to fit it on the wall <pause dur="short"/> the the the hotel room fits perfectly before the chop <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was looking at it she was like holy crap that's amazing that is great</u>
<u n="375" who="S0084">ah mate well I hope you know what you are doing</u>
<u n="376" who="S0041">well oh you're starting to get bobbly now <pause dur="short"/> I like you <pause dur="short"/> yeah I figure this with shorts is sufficiently non-sexy enough to just be my general standard jamas and I've not tried at all</u>
<u n="377" who="S0084">fine but it's still quite sexy</u>
<u n="378" who="S0041">but still quite sexy not wearing T-shirt or granny pants or something <pause dur="short"/> that's good <pause dur="short"/> shoes shoes now <pause dur="short"/> if I want to wear the heels it's going to have to be those even though they're just so old now <pause dur="short"/> they they're my old smelly shoes that I just don't want to wear them but</u>
<u n="379" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="380" who="S0041">can you imagine running through the underground and stuff?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0084">yeah you've got to have something that you're comfortable in</u>
<u n="382" who="S0041">it's gotta be comfy so</u>
<u n="383" who="S0084">do it</u>
<u n="384" who="S0041">you've got to be goers so I'll take you tomorrow that's fine <pause dur="short"/> make up can be done tomorrow that's fine <pause dur="short"/> jewellery <pause dur="short"/> I don't do you? I really don't wear jewellery at all do I?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't often see you in jewellery</u>
<u n="386" who="S0041">Cos I feel like a Christmas tree that's why <pause dur="short"/> I feel like a Christmas tree</u>
<u n="387" who="S0084">em only if you had like big Pat Butcher earrings <pause dur="short"/> but even then I'm I'm quite partial to a big earring <pause dur="short"/> I'm rubbish with jewellery I always lose one earring <pause dur="short"/> I always just have one like it really annoys me like I've got so many just one of <pause dur="short"/> but then actually you could start a trend couldn't you? Just wear all of them mismatching</u>
<u n="388" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I used to just wear one <pause dur="short"/> cos when I had my hair cut off it was shaved</u>
<u n="389" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0041">it was like an inverted bob when that went into fashion three years ago</u>
<u n="391" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0041">em and it was really long at this side but then short at this side so that side went behind my ear and that side was long <pause dur="short"/> so I always had one <trunc>ear</trunc> earring and this was always just a stud</u>
<u n="393" who="S0084">well that's what I was thinking yeah just have a stud on one side</u>
<u n="394" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0084">so that would be okay or just wear mismatching just wear like a yellow one and a red one</u>
<u n="396" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> or there's like ladybird one that's just like a dragon</u>
<u n="397" who="S0084">yeah?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0041">I'd love to have a dragon earring</u>
<u n="399" who="S0084">yeah how do you get dragon earrings? mm</u>
<u n="400" who="S0041">well it's probably not your standard</u>
<u n="401" who="S0084">I'd like ponies <pause dur="short"/> pony earrings <pause dur="short"/> like jumping ponies <pause dur="short"/> like jumping beans but not</u>
<u n="402" who="S0041">I really want I'm really pissed cos I really want to take my camera</u>
<u n="403" who="S0084">donde?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0041">to to London</u>
<u n="405" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0041">but it's full</u>
<u n="407" who="S0084">I know I meant where is it in here?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0041">it's at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="409" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="410" who="S0041">I know I know</u>
<u n="411" who="S0084">well you can take my <trunc>came</trunc> oh hang on wait a minute you're really clumsy</u>
<u n="412" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0084">I mean the frying pan issue is fresh in my mind <pause dur="short"/> I mean presumably you're not going to be whacking him on the side?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0041">well no no <pause dur="short"/> what I might do is</u>
<u n="415" who="S0084">you haven't oh you haven't got a special phone</u>
<u n="416" who="S0041">text <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to take his</u>
<u n="417" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0041">oh no he sold it</u>
<u n="419" who="S0084">well take mine</u>
<u n="420" who="S0041">so would you mind?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0084">no it's fine</u>
<u n="422" who="S0041">I promise I'll look after it I'll eh</u>
<u n="423" who="S0084">let me get it now while I remember cos you're if you're leaving early tomorrow I might not be up <pause dur="short"/> I'll go and find it</u>
<u n="424" who="S0041">let's hope you're not up</u>
<u n="425" who="S0084">well I might be but I hope not<pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0084">there might be some contraband Maltesers in my draw</u>
<u n="427" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="428" who="S0084">not just Yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0041">not contraband</u>
<u n="430" who="S0084">yeah but did I tell you the Lent doesn't em count on each Sunday of Lent?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0041">oh right</u>
<u n="432" who="S0084">so you can have a break every Sunday</u>
<u n="433" who="S0041">is that true or is that?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0084">no that no that's true that's according to Wikipedia and the Bible</u>
<u n="435" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="436" who="S0084">because <trunc>East</trunc> each Sunday obviously you go to Mass on a Sunday in the Catholic church only this is <pause dur="short"/> and each Sunday is a little Easter <pause dur="short"/> you celebrate it as if it's Easter <event desc="sound of dropping something"/> Whoa <pause dur="short"/> don't do that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> As if it's <pause dur="short"/> em Easter so it's not Lent so you can eat chocolate so tomorrow I'll be having chocolate milk on my chocolate cornflakes with chocolate on the side <pause dur="short"/> a bath of chocolate</u>
<u n="437" who="S0041">chocolate <unclear/></u>
<u n="438" who="S0084">chocolate chocolate chocolate chocolate chocolate <pause dur="short"/> oh my photos from Brighton are on here</u>
<u n="439" who="S0041">chocolate steak</u>
<u n="440" who="S0084">including the really filthy windows that we had <pause dur="short"/> that were disgusting</u>
<u n="441" who="S0041">dirty windows</u>
<u n="442" who="S0084">yeah do you see how dirty they are? Really like considering it's a hundred like seventy pounds a night and they bill it's up as a boutique hotel</u>
<u n="443" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="444" who="S0084">and then a wonky chandelier</u>
<u n="445" who="S0041">ah em <pause dur="short"/> we were looking at this hotel in Cornwall online</u>
<u n="446" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0041">em that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had heard about</u>
<u n="448" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0041">and em it's like for a spa package <pause dur="short"/> it's like three hundred and ten pound or something</u>
<u n="450" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0041">for a night but it's the most amazing hotel I've ever seen like</u>
<u n="452" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="453" who="S0041">not not flamboyant as in amazing cos it's massive and its all full of stuff but it's eco design so it's basically designed to be self-sufficient and everything <pause dur="short"/> I don't understand it but everything's like design should be in the design museum</u>
<u n="454" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="455" who="S0041">yeah it looks really good</u>
<u n="456" who="S0084">where is that? Cornwall?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0084">I think I've heard of that <pause dur="short"/> I think some of my</u>
<u n="459" who="S0041">it's called Scarlett</u>
<u n="460" who="S0084">yeah I think some of my friends stayed there</u>
<u n="461" who="S0041">Scarlett</u>
<u n="462" who="S0084">they put some photos on Facebook recently <pause dur="short"/> the New Year's Eve photos are on here</u>
<u n="463" who="S0041">are they? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm I'm trying to think about what of my clothes I have that I can wear for the wedding cos I'd just I'd love to buy a new dress <pause dur="short"/> I was in Warehouse today and there's some really nice things but realistically I just can't justify buying loads of new dresses for all the weddings</u>
<u n="465" who="S0041">I'm I allowed to wear this?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0084">was is das? <unclear/> you don't pull everything on your head</u>
<u n="467" who="S0041">can you see it from there?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0084">em</u>
<u n="469" who="S0041">if I don't pull it out</u>
<u n="470" who="S0084">is it the polka dot?</u>
<u n="471" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0084">what is it? Is it a dress?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0041">I really love it but I've just never found anything that I could possibly wear it for <pause dur="short"/> I wore it for a twenty-first actually</u>
<u n="474" who="S0084">oh did you?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> now I'll get it down</u>
<u n="476" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="477" who="S0041">ow what are you doing up there? How did you get up there? I've been wondering where you went</u>
<u n="478" who="S0084">oh you must have put it up there <pause dur="short"/> I wonder like I like the way you're asking the cushion how it got in the cupboard as if the cushion put itself in the cupboard <pause dur="short"/> oh I like the floral one that's very pretty</u>
<u n="479" who="S0041">I wore that one for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> twenty-first</u>
<u n="480" who="S0084">ow <pause dur="short"/> It's really nice</u>
<u n="481" who="S0041">so it's a balloon bottom</u>
<u n="482" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0041">so I do have some I do have some good dresses</u>
<u n="484" who="S0084">I can't really see the polka dot one yet <pause dur="short"/> I'm intrigued <pause dur="short"/> here you go look I'll put the camera on the top here</u>
<u n="485" who="S0041">thank you</u>
<u n="486" who="S0084">look after it with love</u>
<u n="487" who="S0041">look after it with love and joy</u>
<u n="488" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> don't take any naughty photos on it</u>
<u n="489" who="S0041">I don't think that's going to be an option</u>
<u n="490" who="S0084">no photos of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wanger please <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0041">that's that's that one</u>
<u n="492" who="S0084">oh that's so pretty <pause dur="short"/> is it silk?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0041">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0084">it's really nice</u>
<u n="495" who="S0041">em and that one</u>
<u n="496" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="497" who="S0041">it's just basically just a plain <unclear/> one but <pause dur="short"/> this goes round the middle but</u>
<u n="498" who="S0084">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> you look like a a cake</u>
<u n="499" who="S0041">it's em</u>
<u n="500" who="S0084">it's very nice</u>
<u n="501" who="S0041">looks like a cake <pause dur="short"/> it's a I call it my Carrie Bradshaw dress it reminds me of something crazy that she'd wear</u>
<u n="502" who="S0084">yeah it is a bit crazy isn't it? It's nice though so you've got stripes and circles</u>
<u n="503" who="S0041">yeah like I don't know where the hell you would wear it</u>
<u n="504" who="S0084">I have no idea</u>
<u n="505" who="S0041">I wore it I wore it to em</u>
<u n="506" who="S0084">tea parties?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> tea party <pause dur="short"/> I wore it <trunc>Jorna</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> final design show when he graduated</u>
<u n="508" who="S0084"><vocal desc="sneeze"/> Bless me</u>
<u n="509" who="S0041">they have like a final show <pause dur="short"/> you go and look round and everyone gets all dressed up in suits and</u>
<u n="510" who="S0084">so what accessories did you wear with it?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0041">I I don't I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I had a little white cardigan</u>
<u n="512" who="S0084">and what shoes did you wear?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0041">Silver ones <pause dur="short"/> I have a pair of when I buy a dress I buy a pair of shoes to go with it</u>
<u n="514" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0041">and then I'm not allowed to wear the shoes unless I wear the dress</u>
<u n="516" who="S0084">mm mm</u>
<u n="517" who="S0041">so the silver silver slingbacks <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I just love it I just never find <trunc>anyth</trunc> anywhere to wear it with <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>con</trunc> the concern is now I'm actually bit too old to wear this dress do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="519" who="S0041">like it's a really young dress</u>
<u n="520" who="S0084">it is a young dress yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0041">and I haven't em <pause dur="short"/> I haven't tried it on lately <pause dur="short"/> like I haven't had it on since I graduated and really I think I'm too old to wear this type of dress now <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? It's a very young print isn't it?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0084">the pattern on it is very young yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I mean it's</u>
<u n="523" who="S0041">it's a very young print</u>
<u n="524" who="S0084">it's the sort of thing you don't want to get rid of because it's you know because of the memories attached to it</u>
<u n="525" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="526" who="S0084">there's nothing to say that you have to get rid of it <pause dur="short"/> I mean your wardrobe is pretty bare</u>
<u n="527" who="S0041">summer tea party <pause dur="short"/> I could wear it to a summer tea party</u>
<u n="528" who="S0084">you could wear it to a tea party yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0084">you'd have a tea party</u>
<u n="531" who="S0041">we could do that</u>
<u n="532" who="S0084">we can have a tea party <pause dur="short"/> go punting</u>
<u n="533" who="S0041">we can have a tea party <pause dur="short"/> I think I could wear this to a summer tea party</u>
<u n="534" who="S0084">well to be honest I was looking at photos from last April Maz came over from Berlin and she stayed for the weekend and it was so hot <pause dur="short"/> it was about thirty degrees and we went on a punt down to Grantchester and it was so hot <pause dur="short"/> we had a barbeque in the back garden and it was the day before Easter Sunday it was Easter Saturday so it was the second of April and it was yeah it was like twenty-seven thirty degrees</u>
<u n="535" who="S0041">so I might even be able to wear it</u>
<u n="536" who="S0084">so for your birthday we might even be able to have a tea party</u>
<u n="537" who="S0041">that would be awesome <pause dur="short"/> I would love to have a tea party for my birthday</u>
<u n="538" who="S0084">you could have like a Mad Hatter's tea party <pause dur="short"/> you could be Alice</u>
<u n="539" who="S0041">that would be my favouritist thing ever</u>
<u n="540" who="S0084">it would be pretty fun</u>
<u n="541" who="S0041">Alice would probably wear something like this <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="542" who="S0084">I think she would wear exactly like that</u>
<u n="543" who="S0041">Alice in Wonderland is my favourite Disney film ever</u>
<u n="544" who="S0084">is it?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> I love I love the Mad Hatter's tea party <pause dur="short"/> I played the Mad Hatter once in a play <pause dur="short"/> it was great</u>
<u n="546" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="547" who="S0041">that would be my favourite birthday ever <pause dur="short"/> I was actually going to make it my wedding</u>
<u n="548" who="S0084">we might have to</u>
<u n="549" who="S0041">not just a tea party <unclear/></u>
<u n="550" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I know a few hens that have done it as a hen <trunc>p</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> in fact actually my friend this week has gone to a Mad Hatter's tea party and she's gone as the mock turtle you know in the story the book</u>
<u n="551" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="552" who="S0084">as opposed to the film they've got mock turtles <pause dur="short"/> and she got some paper plates and painted them green and a couple of years ago we had a Christmas party at work and she was went as Robin Hood <pause dur="short"/> because she bought a beautiful green dress and said right what can I wear it to? Fancy dress party <pause dur="short"/> em then we went in as Robin Hood really foxy Robin Hood so she wear this really sort of slinky green dress and she made a little felt hat and she had like a little toy bow and arrow and she's gonna wear the green dress and just like assemble the paper plates on her front and back</u>
<u n="553" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="554" who="S0084">so she looks like a turtle then obviously when they go so then they go out in the afternoon and have the tea party and she can be the turtle <pause dur="short"/> and then when they go out for dinner she can just pull that off</u>
<u n="555" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="556" who="S0084">and then she's looking hot to trot</u>
<u n="557" who="S0041">ah <pause dur="short"/> that is a good plan</u>
<u n="558" who="S0084">it's quite good <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> quite cheap as well not having to buy costumes all the time</u>
<u n="559" who="S0041">oh yeah</u>
<u n="560" who="S0084">but that hen party cost ninety pounds just for the day and the evening</u>
<u n="561" who="S0041">what are people doing?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0084">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> and then she cos she said it's up in did she say Chester? So the petrol it's going to take her four hours to get there em</u>
<u n="563" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="564" who="S0084">and then and that wasn't even including the dinner</u>
<u n="565" who="S0041">that's a lot of money</u>
<u n="566" who="S0084">or was it including dinner I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> mad <pause dur="short"/> I think I might actually boycott hen parties from now one</u>
<u n="567" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0084">now I've started a precedent now I think I might carry on</u>
<u n="569" who="S0041">that's that is extreme</u>
<u n="570" who="S0084">well I mean I thought Barcelona was pretty bad <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean really you just <pause dur="short"/> I don't wanna have to spend more than thirty forty quid realistically <pause dur="short"/> cos you're gonna go out aren't you and spend money on dinner and drinks <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's the having to travel to places isn't it? That's the problem</u>
<u n="571" who="S0041">you just reminded me of something then <pause dur="short"/> oh Michelle's wedding dress was absolutely beautiful</u>
<u n="572" who="S0084">oh was it?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0041">absolutely beautiful em <pause dur="short"/> but I didn't realise until <trunc>ha</trunc> the reception it was a plain white dress <trunc>ma</trunc> the wedding dress on top of my wardrobe</u>
<u n="574" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="575" who="S0041">is actually more like a wedding dress than her wedding dress</u>
<u n="576" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="577" who="S0041">it was completely plain <pause dur="short"/> literally bust top</u>
<u n="578" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0041">straight down and ivory white done</u>
<u n="580" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="581" who="S0041">nothing else <pause dur="short"/> no detail no <pause dur="short"/> oh there was a a lace back that was white</u>
<u n="582" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="583" who="S0041">like a the basque bit</u>
<u n="584" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="585" who="S0041">but she had this em thing made <pause dur="short"/> and it was like a completely here down to the floor a train <pause dur="short"/> it was like an overcoat idea</u>
<u n="586" who="S0084">oh okay</u>
<u n="587" who="S0041">but it was completely sheer</u>
<u n="588" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="589" who="S0041">with like loads of embroidery all over it all the way round the edges covered covered covered in embroidery</u>
<u n="590" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="591" who="S0041">A bit like you know the royal wedding? She used a bit of embroidery</u>
<u n="592" who="S0084">mm hm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0041">it was like that but all down her arms</u>
<u n="594" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="595" who="S0041">all down her arms to here <pause dur="short"/> and it didn't look grannyish at all it looked lovely</u>
<u n="596" who="S0084">oh my god</u>
<u n="597" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="598" who="S0084">it sounds nice <pause dur="short"/> so she had it made did she?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="600" who="S0084">cor that'd be expensive</u>
<u n="601" who="S0041">I wanted I meant to ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> actually em <pause dur="short"/> what size she thought Michelle was which I know is not a very nice thing to say about a bride but she's she's quite I think she's my size which is what I wanted to ask <pause dur="short"/> I think I've found someone</u>
<u n="602" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="603" who="S0041">that's probably about my build <pause dur="short"/> cos she you know it's always easier to see in somebody else isn't it?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="605" who="S0041">like she's quite she's a bit chubby but she's not <pause dur="short"/> you wouldn't look at her and go god she's big </u>
<u n="606" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="607" who="S0041">she's just a bigger person generally</u>
<u n="608" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="609" who="S0041">and she she wasn't suited to what she was wearing at all <pause dur="short"/> like once she took the em the the cover thing off</u>
<u n="610" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="611" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="612" who="S0084">oh really? That that that's what made it?</u>
<u n="613" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="614" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="615" who="S0041">really made it <pause dur="short"/> em which is a bit of a shame but she was happy</u>
<u n="616" who="S0084">yeah I can't em I can't imagine <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> dress at all <pause dur="short"/> she tried to describe it to me cos she's a bit of a hippy and she's quite arty <pause dur="short"/> she tried to describe this dress she said it was did she say it was lemon?</u>
<u n="617" who="S0041">lemon</u>
<u n="618" who="S0084">basically yeah it's like a sort of yellowy colour as opposed to white</u>
<u n="619" who="S0041">I feel a bit naked</u>
<u n="620" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0041">do I look naked? I'm butt naked aren't I? Can't really wear this</u>
<u n="622" who="S0084">you are quite naked</u>
<u n="623" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="624" who="S0084">but yeah it's not a traditional wedding dress by any means <pause dur="short"/> but I'm quite looking forward to it <pause dur="short"/> well you'll get to see it if you still want to come</u>
<u n="625" who="S0041">yeah I do</u>
<u n="626" who="S0084">we'll have to talk about it on Tuesday when you get paid</u>
<u n="627" who="S0041">yes I do</u>
<u n="628" who="S0084">we'll just sit down and work out logistics really but we could do it together because <pause dur="short"/> she's saying that we have to fly realistically we should fly into Belfast City rather than Belfast International cos it's so much easier to go to the hotel <pause dur="short"/> where we can get changed and then</u>
<u n="629" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="630" who="S0084">find our way to the wedding <pause dur="short"/> but in that case we can't fly from Stanstead and we might have to fly from Gatwick</u>
<u n="631" who="S0041">these match don't they perfectly?</u>
<u n="632" who="S0084">beautifully <pause dur="short"/> but em that's fine cos what we could do is stay with my friend Chrissy in Brixton on the Thursday night and then fly out on the Friday morning from Gatwick</u>
<u n="633" who="S0041">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0084">Cos I'm sure she'll be fine with that <pause dur="short"/> she's got space cos we'll just kip on the floor <pause dur="short"/> it'll probably mean getting the tube at some sort of ridiculous hour</u>
<u n="635" who="S0041">stupid o'clock</u>
<u n="636" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0041">my favourite time of the morning <pause dur="short"/> stupid o'clock</u>
<u n="638" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> but it's stupid o'clock from London or stupid o'clock from Cambridge <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="639" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="640" who="S0084">we're probably better off in Brixton</u>
<u n="641" who="S0041">I think that's as far as my packing effort goes I think</u>
<u n="642" who="S0084">it's pretty good <pause dur="short"/> I mean realistically tomorrow morning you have to wash yourself and put your toiletries in a bag</u>
<u n="643" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="644" who="S0084">which is doable <pause dur="short"/> so what bag are you going to take? You can take your swimming bag</u>
<u n="645" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> cos I was gonna take my little <trunc>s</trunc> excuse me suitcase but my little one's going to be a little bit too small</u>
<u n="646" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="647" who="S0041">and that one's going to be to big and that one's just easy to carry</u>
<u n="648" who="S0084">yeah if you don't ram it full of stuff</u>
<u n="649" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not going to weigh anything</u>
<u n="650" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="651" who="S0041">and I don't want <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to have to carry it</u>
<u n="652" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="653" who="S0041">I really don't know how I feel about this now <pause dur="short"/> now it's come to it</u>
<u n="654" who="S0084">getting nervous</u>
<u n="655" who="S0041">I'm not nervous I just don't especially because of the said situ and moods I'm just I don't want to I don't want to react to something badly</u>
<u n="656" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="657" who="S0041">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="658" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="659" who="S0041">I don't think I will <pause dur="short"/> but on the phone I felt I felt the same feeling that I'm scared is gonna happen <pause dur="short"/> cos basically he when I was on the phone to him about what we would do em <pause dur="short"/> he and he told me what he was getting for me for my birthday</u>
<u n="660" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="661" who="S0041">em which by the way you may you may want in</u>
<u n="662" who="S0084">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="663" who="S0041">you may want in <pause dur="short"/> I found out for my birthday <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="664" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="665" who="S0041">em there's an exhibition at the Design Museum Louboutin</u>
<u n="666" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="667" who="S0041">A retrospective exhibition</u>
<u n="668" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="669" who="S0041">of all the shoes</u>
<u n="670" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="671" who="S0041">and all the like design influences of the shoes</u>
<u n="672" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="673" who="S0041">em and pictures and all sorts of stuff</u>
<u n="674" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="675" who="S0041">and it's the first one that they've ever done and he's got me two tickets to go</u>
<u n="676" who="S0084">oh wow <pause dur="short"/> that sounds really fun</u>
<u n="677" who="S0041">I know <pause dur="short"/> so that's fun and he says I've just got to choose a date in May or June</u>
<u n="678" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="679" who="S0041">unless I want I wouldn't really want to go in May cos I'm gonna go to eh I might be going to a wedding with Liz so</u>
<u n="680" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="681" who="S0041">the extra money I have that month will go for that</u>
<u n="682" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="683" who="S0041">and he was like okay well just let me know when you're free and I said okay <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="684" who="S0084">but but is does he mean that he would take you though? Is that not what he means?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0041"><trunc>H</trunc> well yeah <pause dur="short"/> well he was kinda skirting around it so he doesn't obviously doesn't really want to go to the</u>
<u n="686" who="S0084">shoe</u>
<u n="687" who="S0041">the shoe bit</u>
<u n="688" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="689" who="S0041">so he was like so you might you know you might want to take someone else <pause dur="short"/> if I get you two tickets then perhaps take the one that's just going to enjoy that bit </u>
<u n="690" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="691" who="S0041">but you know and I'll go in something else and meet you afterwards</u>
<u n="692" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="693" who="S0041">which is fine</u>
<u n="694" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="695" who="S0041">em</u>
<u n="696" who="S0084">so what you do? Would you go down for the day do you think?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="698" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="699" who="S0041">but it was like and he just thought that would be nice cos that you know obviously cos I won't see you on your birthday</u>
<u n="700" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="701" who="S0041">and I said oh right why won't you? </u>
<u n="702" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="703" who="S0041">and he was like em well you know cos I said <pause dur="short"/> Oh no I've got to keep free on the twenty-eighth <pause dur="short"/> The more I think about it I think I might have done that</u>
<u n="704" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="705" who="S0041">I think I think I said keep free</u>
<u n="706" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="707" who="S0041">for the weekend before and the weekend after <pause dur="short"/> cos I remember saying to him that what about going to Nottingham</u>
<u n="708" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="709" who="S0041">and I said if we do that it'll prob it'll be a girls'</u>
<u n="710" who="S0084">weekend</u>
<u n="711" who="S0041">holiday <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> em but you know keep one or the other free cos whichever one we don't go for <pause dur="short"/> I'll we'll do something together <pause dur="short"/> so actually out of all my nitpicking of that I think I might have actually the person that said keep free</u>
<u n="712" who="S0084">but then he hasn't written it on the calendar <pause dur="short"/> he hasn't written like keep free <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says keep free <pause dur="short"/> so now he has no idea why he's keeping it free</u>
<u n="713" who="S0041">yeah and he's not asked <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> which is ridiculous</u>
<u n="714" who="S0084">he's still not asked her?</u>
<u n="715" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="716" who="S0084">that's a bit weird</u>
<u n="717" who="S0041">yeah I don't really understand what's going on with them like <pause dur="short"/> I don't know but anyway he said you know cos I've said I've got on the calendar keep free and you said it's not you so</u>
<u n="718" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="719" who="S0041">I don't know I just <pause dur="short"/> am I being stupid cos I kind of thought <pause dur="short"/> I thought to myself <pause dur="short"/> like I had a real sinking feeling cos I kind of thought <pause dur="short"/> even if Even if it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that asked you to keep it free <pause dur="short"/> I can't believe that you would keep both those weekends as weekends for her <pause dur="short"/> that are both around my birthday and not think to say like <pause dur="short"/> Actually it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> birthday that week <pause dur="short"/> she she might want me to do something at at one of those so <pause dur="short"/> can we just have one that's a keep free? Do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="720" who="S0084">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> well to be <trunc>ho</trunc> he might have done <pause dur="short"/> he might have thought that and now he just can't remember <pause dur="short"/> I think he might have done it a while ago if it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that actually was the one who said keep it free <pause dur="short"/> cos it could well be that it was you <pause dur="short"/> and it actually there's no need to get too worried about it cos it was you in in the first place</u>
<u n="721" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="722" who="S0084">but yeah I mean if if he did if he's just completely blocked out the rest of the next nine months to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> bearing in mind that you'll probably be gone within nine months it's a bit of a kicker</u>
<u n="723" who="S0041">innit?</u>
<u n="724" who="S0084">but then it's all supposed to be that way isn't it? Like typically you don't stay this close with your ex-boyfriend or girlfriends <pause dur="short"/> so you don't say</u>
<u n="725" who="S0041">yeah but it's birthday time</u>
<u n="726" who="S0084">yeah but then if you're seeing somebody else like you you don't know what you might be doing in April like you might be seeing somebody he might be more serious with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like <pause dur="short"/> you might have a a you know a group of people out that night say if we went on a girlie thing and he would definitely come and you and he would definitely be invited and you definitely would see each other but <pause dur="short"/> like to actually just spend time just one on one <pause dur="short"/> cos I've got nothing to compare it to so to me it seems a bit <pause dur="short"/> a little but strange but maybe it's not maybe it's completely normal just like it would be normal if you were all like best mates and you had never actually been in a relationship together</u>
<u n="727" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="728" who="S0084">like if you were just best mates maybe you would just hang out just the two of you but <pause dur="short"/> given that you've got history <pause dur="short"/> for anybody new that's coming in it's hard like it would be hard to break in to that relationship that you have <pause dur="short"/> the two of you <pause dur="short"/> like whatever it is now</u>
<u n="729" who="S0041">yeah whatever it is</u>
<u n="730" who="S0084">whatever is going on it's hard for anybody new <pause dur="short"/> I'm obviously not that my sympathies lie with her at all but <pause dur="short"/> and I don't think he's handling the situation at all well <pause dur="short"/> but you know this is the first time both of you have done this so you are gonna sort of <pause dur="short"/> it is a bit of a learning curve</u>
<u n="731" who="S0041">and he said em <pause dur="short"/> and you know <trunc>na</trunc> you know I haven't been invited to anything so <pause dur="short"/> and then he tried to have a dig at me as it was my fault</u>
<u n="732" who="S0084">Good job you said it was a girlie thing</u>
<u n="733" who="S0041">yeah and that we'd do something else <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I just thought it was really weird really odd</u>
<u n="734" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> he is a bit of a strange one isn't he?</u>
<u n="735" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I you know that awful kind of sinking feeling <pause dur="short"/> I don't I really don't want anything else to come up this weekend that gives me that kind of <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="736" who="S0084">it hurts</u>
<u n="737" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos I don't want to <trunc>re</trunc> I don't want to react <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="738" who="S0084">mm mm mm <pause dur="short"/> well yeah</u>
<u n="739" who="S0041">I just want it to go smoothly without a hitch and then</u>
<u n="740" who="S0084">walk away</u>
<u n="741" who="S0041">have some nice photographs <pause dur="short"/> it'll be a nice memory <pause dur="short"/> and then if if actually that's it then</u>
<u n="742" who="S0084">well I don't you know I don't think it needs to be it <pause dur="short"/> you just need to you know at the end of this weekend just give yourself some space <pause dur="short"/> and that's what you'd already you've already laid that groundwork with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you've already said that's what you need <pause dur="short"/> so it shouldn't come as a shock to him</u>
<u n="743" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="744" who="S0084">so yeah all being well you know you'll have a nice time and then you'll just come back and <pause dur="short"/> it'll be as it is this week you know <pause dur="short"/> not actually seeing each other all the time and try and keep a bit of distance</u>
<u n="745" who="S0041">yeah but before said space I want to leave <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to leave with a nasty taste do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0084">mm yeah of course</u>
<u n="747" who="S0041">so</u>
<u n="748" who="S0084">well this is what we were saying though like <pause dur="short"/> if something does come up it's gonna really hurt and it's gonna make you feel sick <pause dur="short"/> and you're not going to enjoy it</u>
<u n="749" who="S0041">yeah I know</u>
<u n="750" who="S0084">but you went it to this with your eyes open didn't you like <pause dur="short"/> I remember you saying like you wanted to do this because you feel like it's going to help you move on <pause dur="short"/> like it is going to be make or break like it's</u>
<u n="751" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="752" who="S0084">if something does come up you can't <pause dur="short"/> depending on what it is it's gonna be hard to react hard not to react cos you can't really <pause dur="short"/> cos if he's like of whatever if he says something about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and it it hurts <pause dur="short"/> he's sort of within his rights to talk about her</u>
<u n="753" who="S0041">no he's no</u>
<u n="754" who="S0084">I know it's hard <pause dur="short"/> cos your you know it'll be a really nice time and you'll just fall back into the routine of <trunc>ju</trunc> it just being the two of you really easy</u>
<u n="755" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="756" who="S0084">but you'll have a nice time you know</u>
<u n="757" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="758" who="S0084">when was When was his birthday?</u>
<u n="759" who="S0041">it's on Tuesday</u>
<u n="760" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> I see</u>
<u n="761" who="S0041">I was just about to say oh god I haven't got you a birthday present well yeah you have</u>
<u n="762" who="S0084">you've got quite quite a decent one</u>
<u n="763" who="S0041">fucking eejit</u>
<u n="764" who="S0084">quite nice</u>
<u n="765" who="S0041">yes thanks</u>
<u n="766" who="S0084">A little jolly <pause dur="short"/> so what are you going to do on Monday? You're gonna go to HMS Belfast?</u>
<u n="767" who="S0041">it's closed</u>
<u n="768" who="S0084">ah what? Why?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0041">till further notice</u>
<u n="770" who="S0084"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="771" who="S0041">yeah I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I'm really pissed off</u>
<u n="772" who="S0084">shit</u>
<u n="773" who="S0041">so going for the egg hunt</u>
<u n="774" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="775" who="S0041">I'm going to make go the egg hunt <pause dur="short"/> I'll print us off I've printed off the maps at work they're in the car</u>
<u n="776" who="S0084">ah that's pretty fun</u>
<u n="777" who="S0041">yeah so that should be a nice thing to do <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna go to the market tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> em I'm gonna go to the Tate Modern cos I've never been and he hasn't either <pause dur="short"/> I basically just gave him a list of things</u>
<u n="778" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="779" who="S0041">I said just have a look and we'll see what you want to do and we'll do we'll do it <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="780" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> it'll be quite a whistle-stop</u>
<u n="781" who="S0041">yeah I think it's going to be a bit of a whistle-stop tour</u>
<u n="782" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="783" who="S0041">which is good</u>
<u n="784" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> knackering but but good</u>
<u n="785" who="S0041">yeah I don't I don't want to get too too knackered like I'm thinking <pause dur="short"/> perhaps go to the market tomorrow then go back to the hotel and have a bit of a kip</u>
<u n="786" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="787" who="S0041">you know a bit of a just a rest a breather</u>
<u n="788" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="789" who="S0041">and then go and do the egg hunters you know a couple of hours</u>
<u n="790" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="791" who="S0041">and then the have a leisurely just wander around the Tate Modern get on the train do you know?</u>
<u n="792" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="793" who="S0041">not let's do all this and run around cos I can't be arsed with that shit</u>
<u n="794" who="S0084">what it's just very knackering and I don't think you actually see anything in any great detail you know if you wanted to go the Tate Modern you should just take half a day or a whole day</u>
<u n="795" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="796" who="S0084">then do it <pause dur="short"/> and then the next time you go to London do something else cos otherwise it's not <pause dur="short"/> sort of pointless really</u>
<u n="797" who="S0041">that's what I thought</u>
<u n="798" who="S0084">it's a pretty a pretty impressive place</u>
<u n="799" who="S0041">is it?</u>
<u n="800" who="S0084">the Tate Modern yeah yeah cos there's an old turbine hall so it's massive</u>
<u n="801" who="S0041">is it?</u>
<u n="802" who="S0084">it's really massive yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've forgotten the last one I went to see I can never remember his name <pause dur="short"/> it was a Chinese artist who was imprisoned for like forty years for speaking out again the Chinese regime</u>
<u n="803" who="S0041">oh yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0084">and he's supposed to be like on the run now <pause dur="short"/> em what is his name? Pass <pause dur="short"/> and he had tiny grains of sand and each one of them was hand painted in the turbine hall <pause dur="short"/> when you see the turbine hall you'll see how big it is and it each grain of sand was painted by Chinese workers <pause dur="short"/> and but they're painted like with lead and so health and safety came and took them all away because they said oh it's you know because people were going in and walking on them <pause dur="short"/> so it's like walking on like westerners walking on the work of what people do in the east <pause dur="short"/> so how much time and effort goes into work that they produce and <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was quite it was quite a statement and but they took it all away and they said you couldn't go in</u>
<u n="805" who="S0041">there was sand all over the floor?</u>
<u n="806" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and you</u>
<u n="807" who="S0041">and this a massive hall?</u>
<u n="808" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> was it sand or was it rice? It might have been rice grains of rice <pause dur="short"/> but even still it's pretty fucking small and it's all over the turbine hall you know <pause dur="short"/> it was amazing</u>
<u n="809" who="S0041">wow</u>
<u n="810" who="S0084">yeah and you could go walk on it and then they said you couldn't walk on it and then they just took it all away <pause dur="short"/> it's really sad</u>
<u n="811" who="S0041">motherfuckers <pause dur="short"/> there's a photography exhibit on there at the minute <pause dur="short"/> I don't really know cos I'm really not an art person at all <pause dur="short"/> I like it I enjoy it like I appreciate it but I just have no knowledge of at all</u>
<u n="812" who="S0084">yeah no well I'm the same particularly like modern art <pause dur="short"/> I think it's all a bit em a bit silly</u>
<u n="813" who="S0041">yeah em</u>
<u n="814" who="S0084">I'd rather go and watch a play watch a movie read a book</u>
<u n="815" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="816" who="S0084">I don't really understand art <pause dur="short"/> unless I can the talent in it and you can't it's difficult to quantify modern art isn't it? It's difficult to for people to say that's good that's bad</u>
<u n="817" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="818" who="S0084">unmade bed <pause dur="short"/> pile of brick</u>
<u n="819" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="820" who="S0084">knocked down shed etcetera</u>
<u n="821" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what is that?</u>
<u n="822" who="S0084">what is that? Light on and off</u>
<u n="823" who="S0041">it's yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's why I like the graphic design thing cos <trunc>y</trunc> you get the bit with it the tells you the the story behind it the thought process</u>
<u n="824" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="825" who="S0041">that's why I used to like looking at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> work going through <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> work with him because you didn't just see the poster or the other whatever</u>
<u n="826" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="827" who="S0041">the thought process behind it was the interesting bit that I liked</u>
<u n="828" who="S0084">you could see how he'd got there <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="829" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="830" who="S0084">I like when you go and see art now and they've got like a little accompanying note and it's just words put together in a sentence <pause dur="short"/> and you you you think but that doesn't make any sense</u>
<u n="831" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="832" who="S0084">you've just put that into a sentence that's not actually making any sense for anybody</u>
<u n="833" who="S0041">no which is stupid stupid <pause dur="short"/> yes so <pause dur="short"/> oh and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I I said I asked him to book em somewhere for dinner</u>
<u n="834" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="835" who="S0041">he booked Cte</u>
<u n="836" who="S0084">what's Cte?</u>
<u n="837" who="S0041">you know eh the French bistro thing? There's one in Cambridge</u>
<u n="838" who="S0084">cte? No I don't know</u>
<u n="839" who="S0041">yeah C O T E with a little hat on the E</u>
<u n="840" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm like the eh French word yeah no <pause dur="short"/> oh actually is it the one off <anon type="place"/> <trunc>Str</trunc> on <anon type="place"/> Street?</u>
<u n="841" who="S0041">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="842" who="S0084">oh okay yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I've never been in <pause dur="short"/> looks nice though</u>
<u n="843" who="S0041">yeah well I've</u>
<u n="844" who="S0084">it's look nice from the outside</u>
<u n="845" who="S0041">I went there once and we just had like a sandwich cos it was lunch time</u>
<u n="846" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="847" who="S0041">but it wasn't much to write home about <pause dur="short"/> maybe we ordered the wrong stuff</u>
<u n="848" who="S0084">is that the one on the corner on <anon type="place"/> Street?</u>
<u n="849" who="S0041">it's the one it's</u>
<u n="850" who="S0084">Cos they're a few that opened</u>
<u n="851" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="852" who="S0084">the last couple of years and there's one that's on the corner that looks quite nice</u>
<u n="853" who="S0041">I don't know</u>
<u n="854" who="S0084">Cos it used to be an American diner and you used to sit in like old nineteen fifties cars when we first moved to Cambridge about four or five years ago <pause dur="short"/> it's a proper American diner and I really <trunc>lik</trunc> I though it but cheesy as hell</u>
<u n="855" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="856" who="S0084">but it was quite fun and obviously like playing Elvis records all the time but I think it was an independent and it just closed down and then yeah</u>
<u n="857" who="S0041">I can't remember if it's the corner one</u>
<u n="858" who="S0084">but like a brasserie type place opened up and it was on the corner but I never I never looked that closely</u>
<u n="859" who="S0041">there's a couple in a row <pause dur="short"/> there's two or three</u>
<u n="860" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> there's two</u>
<u n="861" who="S0041">they blur into one</u>
<u n="862" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="863" who="S0041">Cos they <trunc>brou</trunc> they're both red</u>
<u n="864" who="S0084">Cos then cos you've got Chez Gerard and you've got Café Rouge then you've got a couple more</u>
<u n="865" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="866" who="S0084">and there that sort of stretch of restaurants</u>
<u n="867" who="S0041">so I was a bit like oh</u>
<u n="868" who="S0084">so it's not something special then?</u>
<u n="869" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> well I don't think so <pause dur="short"/> he might cos he's never been there before</u>
<u n="870" who="S0084">I mean it's difficult isn't it? Somewhere like London where you've got so much choice <pause dur="short"/> it's really hard <pause dur="short"/> so at least you know like if you do book at chain but like a good chain at least you know what you're getting</u>
<u n="871" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="872" who="S0084">maybe he knows that the dinners there are quite nice</u>
<u n="873" who="S0041">God knows <pause dur="short"/> and then I thought well the dinner in the hotel should be fantastic</u>
<u n="874" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="875" who="S0041">but then it seems a shame to go to London and eat in the hotel</u>
<u n="876" who="S0084">yeah really <pause dur="short"/> a bit of a waste</u>
<u n="877" who="S0041">so even though we do only pay fifty percent for it so the food is just like it's basically á la carte dining for next to nothing</u>
<u n="878" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="879" who="S0041">for two people two courses you're looking at a hundred and twenty quid</u>
<u n="880" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="881" who="S0041">we pay sixty</u>
<u n="882" who="S0084">that's really good</u>
<u n="883" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="884" who="S0084">really good</u>
<u n="885" who="S0041">you kind of should do it for the just to be able to but it's there's no point</u>
<u n="886" who="S0084">mm hmm</u>
<u n="887" who="S0041">there's no point in going down to London if you're just going to stay in the hotel <pause dur="short"/> and we get canapés and champagne before we leave anyway so</u>
<u n="888" who="S0084">that's pretty sweet</u>
<u n="889" who="S0041">that's a winner</u>
<u n="890" who="S0084">and you get half the price on the bar as well don't you?</u>
<u n="891" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cocktails may be required</u>
<u n="892" who="S0084">cheeky cocktail</u>
<u n="893" who="S0041">I think cheeky vino may be required</u>
<u n="894" who="S0084">I don't know if I don't <trunc>mi</trunc> don't mind if I do</u>
<u n="895" who="S0041">em</u>
<u n="896" who="S0084">are you <trunc>off</trunc> oh are you offering me vino now?</u>
<u n="897" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="898" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="899" who="S0041">red vino</u>
<u n="900" who="S0084">red vino <pause dur="short"/> I think I'll have red vino <pause dur="short"/> I have a date tomorrow</u>
<u n="901" who="S0041">oh do you?</u>
<u n="902" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if I'm going to go though</u>
<u n="903" who="S0041">why?</u>
<u n="904" who="S0084">I don't I don't know I don't know if he what he's going to be like <pause dur="short"/> I suppose that's why you go</u>
<u n="905" who="S0041">eh who's he? Who is he?</u>
<u n="906" who="S0084">eh his name's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> he is a roofer but he also writes screenplays <pause dur="short"/> naturally the two thing go together</u>
<u n="907" who="S0041">go</u>
<u n="908" who="S0084">go?</u>
<u n="909" who="S0041">he might act</u>
<u n="910" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> We need to start writing these <trunc>thi</trunc> these don't we? So if we've got one that sings one that acts the next one is what dancing?</u>
<u n="911" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="912" who="S0084">mime possibly <pause dur="short"/> that would be quite good</u>
<u n="913" who="S0041">well that would be the winner if someone mimed</u>
<u n="914" who="S0084">or and then then drawing <pause dur="short"/> maybe some sort of eh graffiti or stroke</u>
<u n="915" who="S0041">or</u>
<u n="916" who="S0084">caricature artist</u>
<u n="917" who="S0041">yeah pull out paper and just</u>
<u n="918" who="S0084">mm I don't they freak me out those things but yes</u>
<u n="919" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="920" who="S0084">so it was</u>
<u n="921" who="S0041">we have tea now?</u>
<u n="922" who="S0084">tea? Shall we make tea?</u>
<u n="923" who="S0041">no I don't mean cup of tea I mean eating tea</u>
<u n="924" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="925" who="S0041">I had <trunc>lu</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> oh my god I've haven't eaten <pause dur="short"/> I haven't eaten anything</u>
<u n="926" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> What the hell is the matter with you? You must be starving</u>
<u n="927" who="S0041">I think I just felt I just thought I felt a bit sick then that's probably why</u>
<u n="928" who="S0084">you haven't eaten all day you absolute maniac no wonder if you're hungry <pause dur="short"/> I haven't stopped eating today <pause dur="short"/> I've eaten so much <pause dur="short"/> I've had porridge for breakfast then I had some <unclear/> for midmorning snack <pause dur="short"/> then I had an omelette the most successful omelette I've ever made in my life <pause dur="short"/> not out of a frying pan not that I'm harping on about my frying pan <pause dur="short"/> em my my frying pan that's in heaven <pause dur="short"/> and then in the afternoon I went into town and then I came back and I made fajitas that actually weren't fajitas at all it was just some corn in a wrap that wasn't even fajita mix because I didn't have any so I just put loads of spices on it <pause dur="short"/> em random spices with salad</u>
<u n="929" who="S0041">Good</u>
<u n="930" who="S0084">so just some sort of wrap really not a fajita in any sense shape or form</u>
<u n="931" who="S0041">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="932" who="S0084">I had two of those <pause dur="short"/> and a yoghurt</u>
<u n="933" who="S0041">goodo</u>
<u n="934" who="S0084">I've eaten loads of food <pause dur="short"/> I've eaten my dinner and your dinner <pause dur="short"/> I've eaten everyone's food</u>
<u n="935" who="S0041">goodo <pause dur="short"/> I feel</u>
<u n="936" who="S0084">where's your food? No wonder you feel sick</u>
<u n="937" who="S0041">I feel like I <pause dur="short"/> well I need to make my soup but I just keep putting it off cos I can't be arsed but now</u>
<u n="938" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="939" who="S0041">everything there's gonna go off if I don't use it</u>
<u n="940" who="S0084">get it in <pause dur="short"/> put it all in <pause dur="short"/> no cos the last time you did that you made the inedible you make the inedible soup</u>
<u n="941" who="S0041">yeah I can't do that</u>
<u n="942" who="S0084">Don't do that</u>
<u n="943" who="S0041">no it's just minestrone again I just can't be able to make it <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Maybe I'll feel more inclined to do it in the morning</u>
<u n="944" who="S0084">it seems unlikely given that you've only got an hour to get ready <pause dur="short"/> you should get up like in an hour's time</u>
<u n="945" who="S0041">oh dear</u>
<u n="946" who="S0084">em did the house smell when you came home?</u>
<u n="947" who="S0041">eh I wasn't smelling I wasn't prepared to smell</u>
<u n="948" who="S0084">but I think if it had smelt you would have smelled it</u>
<u n="949" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I've got a really bad sense of smell</u>
<u n="950" who="S0084">oh have you?</u>
<u n="951" who="S0041">yeah really really bad</u>
<u n="952" who="S0084">you've got to be aware of smelling have you?</u>
<u n="953" who="S0041">no sometimes I don't smell I can't smell like I can't smell now <pause dur="short"/> I know that sounds ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <trunc>wh</trunc> I've always had it so I didn't realise that it was a problem</u>
<u n="954" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="955" who="S0041">em basically if I I think I don't know how I worked this out but I think I only have a sense of smell up one nostril</u>
<u n="956" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="957" who="S0041">so like I'm a bit snotty today</u>
<u n="958" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="959" who="S0041">Cos I I automatically am from smoking the night before</u>
<u n="960" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="961" who="S0041">I can't really smell very much <pause dur="short"/> I don't notice that my sense of smell isn't there</u>
<u n="962" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="963" who="S0041">Cos I don't I don't know I just don't cos I've always had it <pause dur="short"/> I've always had this</u>
<u n="964" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="965" who="S0041">it's so weird isn't it?</u>
<u n="966" who="S0084">well I suppose it's like my not thinking that I could possibly be allergic to apples until you said that your face gets hot and tingly and hot and red when you eat chocolate and you think that's probably because you're allergic to it <pause dur="short"/> that's always happened to me when I eat apples <pause dur="short"/> any type of apple my face goes really hot <pause dur="short"/> I sweat loads and it tingles and I just thought oh that's a bit weird <pause dur="short"/> why is it that apples do that to you? Oh well and carried on</u>
<u n="967" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="968" who="S0084">never flagged it as an issue and now I think god</u>
<u n="969" who="S0041">I just <pause dur="short"/> I can't really smell</u>
<u n="970" who="S0084">well I can't smell at the moment because of the cold but</u>
<u n="971" who="S0041">I must be able to smell cos part of your taste and smell</u>
<u n="972" who="S0084">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="973" who="S0041">and I can just taste so it's just it's very</u>
<u n="974" who="S0084">it's just lessens</u>
<u n="975" who="S0041">it's I don't know</u>
<u n="976" who="S0084">than everyone else's maybe? It's just not hyper-sensitive</u>
<u n="977" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but the other day when I came back I could smell it so</u>
<u n="978" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="979" who="S0041">if I'm clear if I'm nasally clear <pause dur="short"/> I think it might be cos I've got quite bad sinuses</u>
<u n="980" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="981" who="S0041">like <pause dur="short"/> I've <pause dur="short"/> what's the thing I've got?</u>
<u n="982" who="S0084">sinusitis</u>
<u n="983" who="S0041">rhinoitis</u>
<u n="984" who="S0084">what the fuck is that?</u>
<u n="985" who="S0041">it's called Rhinusitis but it's basically</u>
<u n="986" who="S0084">rhinoitis <pause dur="short"/> rhino you are a rhino</u>
<u n="987" who="S0041">turn in to rhino <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="988" who="S0084">turn it to rhino <pause dur="short"/> horns will come out your nose</u>
<u n="989" who="S0041">it's em <pause dur="short"/> yes it's just the sinus <pause dur="short"/> basically I'm allergic to dust air con changes in temperature like everything <pause dur="short"/> it's just stupid</u>
<u n="990" who="S0084">that's madness</u>
<u n="991" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it just makes me snotty <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit like hay fever</u>
<u n="992" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="993" who="S0041">A bit like hay fever <pause dur="short"/> but I haven't had it very bad for years and years</u>
<u n="994" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="995" who="S0041">so I just assumed it's gone away but I think the non smell thing</u>
<u n="996" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="997" who="S0041">is probably part of that which is a bit weird</u>
<u n="998" who="S0084">it is a bit weird isn't it?</u>
<u n="999" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> can you smell it? Have you smelt it?</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0084">I smelt it the other day one day <pause dur="short"/> and I opened the window and then everyone smelt the fridges and I took the bin out today and I threw away some chicken and I hoovered actually</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0041">I put loads of bleach down the drain <pause dur="short"/> I think it was the drain <pause dur="short"/> I think it was when I eh emptied out the soup the mouldy soup</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0041">I think it was something stuck in the drain</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0084">possibly cos it doesn't <pause dur="short"/> I don't really can't really smell it <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said when he went out this morning and came here he could smell like that it was like smelly in the house but like when I came back from town earlier I couldn't smell anything</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0041">did you get anything from town</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0084">eh just some birthday cards and oh <vocal desc="yawn"/> excuse me and some stuff from Boots <pause dur="short"/> nothing exciting</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0084">I did <pause dur="short"/> I get emails from InStyle magazine and em they send one to me every day and yesterday they had feature that was fifty dresses for under fifty quid <pause dur="short"/> they had this T-shirt dress from River Island I thought it was <pause dur="short"/> I'm never sure about River Island cos I think it's like almost chavy and</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0041">right</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0084">it's quite young</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0041">it's got a lot better recently</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0084">we'll it always used to be okay and then it got quite chav and now I think it might be it's like borderline <pause dur="short"/> there's some stuff that you can get away with</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's quite</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0084">but it's also quite young <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0041">yeah it's very young and I think now it's really overpriced <pause dur="short"/> it never used to be <pause dur="short"/> river Island</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0041">used to be less expensive than Topshop</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0041">and now they're on pretty an even par but there's not the same design or the same quality</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0084">yeah I think and the yeah the quality of the material is just not there <pause dur="short"/> but it was em like a long T-shirt dress like round neck like crew neck or whatever they call it <pause dur="short"/> em black and white pattern like A sort of paisley pattern it's a bit weird and like a brighter trim around the bottom like bright like orange and blue floral pattern at the bottom</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0084">so it was quite interesting and it looked like sort of gold finishing on the sleeve and I could see it online and it was twenty quid so I thought that would be quite good I'd wear it with leggings and heels maybe if I go out or just slobbing around or whatever <pause dur="short"/> it's quite quite good for twenty quid <pause dur="short"/> and I went in to have a look at it and the the what do you call it? Like lamy? Lamy? like gold just like a really cheap synthetic material like</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0041">like that skirt?</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0084">it's not cotton <pause dur="short"/> no your skirt's nice whatever your skirt is <pause dur="short"/> it's really cheap <pause dur="short"/> it's almost like that but like thicker if you can imagine it?</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0041">like thick satin or?</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0084">yeah but just really cheap <pause dur="short"/> really cheap</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0084">and so it sticks out and just looks really weird and like the I quite like the the clash of the monochrome and the floral coloured pattern at the bottom <pause dur="short"/> and it might be that you could get away with the sleeves you know if you just teamed it with some nice big gold earrings or something fake or the real gold whatever <pause dur="short"/> but I didn't try it on because I don't wanna or no I could I couldn't really justify buying any clothes I said I wasn't going to buy any clothes for a while so <pause dur="short"/> and I don't really need it so I just thought if it's really nice for twenty quid and I'll get it but I was a bit like hmm might be nice I if try it on <pause dur="short"/> can I be arsed? It's <unclear/> me</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0041">ah <pause dur="short"/> lost all love</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0084">and everyone was just stopping in my way and I wanted to punch everybody in the head</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0041">Saturday's in town are just the worst</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0084">yeah I every weekend you know every time I go in on a Saturday I think why do I do this to myself? </u>
<u n="1033" who="S0041">no bad</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0084">if I go <pause dur="short"/> I normally try to go for nine AM and I'm home by ten thirty and it's</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0041">that's fine</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0084">done <pause dur="short"/> but I couldn't make myself go in this morning</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0041">no that no <pause dur="short"/> oh god I hate town on Saturday so bad <pause dur="short"/> bad bad bad bad</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0084">I don't know you were <unclear/> I don't know why I did it <pause dur="short"/> I didn't really need to go <pause dur="short"/> I just sit <pause dur="short"/> I mean it was sunny I think <pause dur="short"/> I thought I'll just have a little potter <pause dur="short"/> and it was really nice</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0041">A little potter around</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0084">little bit of a potter</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh I brought the bottle of Prosecco home from work</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0041">em to take for the weekend which I thought would be nice</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0041">I mean the more I think about it I think in actual fact what's what's really happening here is <pause dur="short"/> that without cos I've subconsciously put quite a lot of effort into this weekend</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah you have</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0041">and I really don't think whatever the outcome is I'm going to be satisfied with it really</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0041">so I think I probably need to prepare for that a bit</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0084">well I think realistically at this point you want him to just turn around and say I love you let's get back together </u>
<u n="1051" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0084">because</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0041">but it's not going to work that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what's going on in my head is if he said that to me I'd be really happy but I'd also be thinking no because</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0041">that the way you're behaving</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0041">is not a person that I want in my want to be with</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0084">well absolutely yeah <pause dur="short"/> he can't he's a completely different person it seems from how he was when he was with you</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0084">and also you know the fact that he would jack in something with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that quickly like obviously he's saying that she doesn't mean anything to him but you know it's a worry with people that do that like he is very much in sort of two minds it seems the more you've got somebody like that you just can't really trust him</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know why I think it I don't know why</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0084">but</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0041">I don't know why I think it</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0084">yeah I think you have to prepare yourself that really there's a good chance that something's going to happen this week that's going to hurt</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0084">you know yeah</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0084">Cos worst you know the best <trunc>t</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> yeah the best outcome is you have a really nice weekend</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the best outcome is we have a lovely weekend <pause dur="short"/> do you know that I just want him to realise</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0084">but that's still going to hurt though <pause dur="short"/> you know like you know you come back whenever it is Monday and you say your goodbyes and you think well that was a really nice weekend and then that's gonna hurt because then you've got to walk away <pause dur="short"/> and you know</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0084">if you have anything less than a good weekend that's gonna hurt for whatever reason makes it a not good weekend</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a lose lose situation</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0084">yeah which is what I've been saying for weeks</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0041">yes I know</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but that said I can I understand why you're doing it <pause dur="short"/> and maybe this is a way of re-establishing your friendship rather than whatever weird thing is going on between you two at the moment</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0084">so</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0041">I <pause dur="short"/> I just feel a bit I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the thing is I just don't feel like he's <pause dur="short"/> after all the things he was saying about how special what we had was I just don't think I feel like he's treating it like it was</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0041">because he's not behaving well towards me so I kinda think that that just tarnishes</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0041">tarnishes what we had and I don't think he's really <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="sound of phone"/> Hello?</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0084">I'm British Gas calling <pause dur="short"/> you're through to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> how may I direct your call? Em I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it's like he doesn't realise that but and that's the weird thing</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0041">and like the when we're going away like Navyness and whatever I kinda think like he doesn't care that he's not going to see me</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> well I mean he probably does he just hasn't it's like isn't any comprehension he just doesn't see</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0084">long term <pause dur="short"/> like he's just I think he thinks that it's just a pipe dream on a pipe dream that's wrong though</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0084">it's just you know that your plan for today</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0084">today I will oh I know I'll join the navy <pause dur="short"/> and tomorrow you'll get to be a hot air pilot or whatever <pause dur="short"/> hot air? Are they pilots? Whatever they are</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0084">it don't know if it's a <unclear/></u>
<u n="1095" who="S0041">I've always like to do that <pause dur="short"/> I've never been on a hot air balloon before?</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0084">no I haven't I mean I think I might shit myself a tiny tiny bit <pause dur="short"/> shit my pants man</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0041">would you?</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0084">I hate flying <pause dur="short"/> so <unclear/> just being like up in a plane</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0041">oh yeah of course</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0084">but loose <pause dur="short"/> and just like the <trunc>pos</trunc> the possibility of like falling out of the plane at any point</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0041">no I probably wouldn't do that if I were you</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> which is why I will not be throwing myself out of any planes <pause dur="short"/> I mean I would quite like to go to on a hot air balloon but I think I would have to sit down in the basket <pause dur="short"/> cos I think</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0041">but then you wouldn't get to see very much</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0084">oh no cos I'm quite tall <pause dur="short"/> I'm quite long in the torso if you think the basket is probably here</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0084">so I could sit here</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0084">it is <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="1109" who="S0041">is it?</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0084">I don't know I've</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0041">are they that shallow?</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0084">I've never been on one <pause dur="short"/> I think it's quite that's my fear that it would be so shallow that I would if I leant over I would fall out because it would only come to my midriff or lower</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0084">in which case I'd want to sit down</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0041">I think it comes to the boobage</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0084">yeah but that's <trunc>ha</trunc> depending on what height <pause dur="short"/> like that might come to your boobs but that's like still in <trunc>m</trunc> mine not my waste cos you're not a munchkin</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I think I think it would come to your boobage <pause dur="short"/> I think to me I think I get the feeling that it would be about here on me</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0084">okay well that would make me feel more secure</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0041">it would probably be about here on you</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0084">okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah that would be okay</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0041">ish</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0084">I'd still want some sort of harness</u>
<u n="1123" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1124" who="S0041">strap yourself into the hot air balloon</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0084">yeah exactly and then I can't be used as a ballast <pause dur="short"/> right get her off</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0084">throw her out <pause dur="short"/> we need more height throw her out</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0041">what was that? Oh my just that you reminded me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> made a really funny you at work made a really really funny comment the other day <pause dur="short"/> they were asking me about the Navy thing and I was telling them that that I passed my exam on that <pause dur="short"/> and em I said but obviously I've got to send my paperwork back when I have my eye test on Wednesday and the doctor's clearly going to tell me off for sending in my weight as it is now</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0041">and I was like they can't you know you say you can't join the Navy like because you're fat <pause dur="short"/> you know you come sorry you can't come on this ship because and he was like <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then he just quickly went cos it'll sink</u>
<u n="1131" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1132" who="S0041">it was really funny <pause dur="short"/> it was really quick <pause dur="short"/> this guy is like quite a serious person at works with like numbers yeah cos it will sink <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1133" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0041">that was funny</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0084">devastating</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0041">I need I need this make up off my face <pause dur="short"/> it's driving me freaking mad</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0041">em <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0084">oh I saw your moisturizer on discount at Boots but I remembered you said it smelled like porridge <pause dur="short"/> so I didn't buy it</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0041">oh this one?</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0041">yeah it smells like porridge but it's really good though</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0084">is it? Does it smell of porridge?</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I mean</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0084">I like porridge <pause dur="short"/> I might start nibbling on myself in the night <pause dur="short"/> that's a bit dangerous</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0041">it em <pause dur="short"/> they're not in there Char the makeup wipes not in there <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what you've done with them</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0084">so no sign of the car key then so you couldn't go in the house?</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0041">go around the house <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0084">Nofo's</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0041">it's really good it just it's a bedtime one like it</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0041">once it's <trunc>so</trunc> soaked in it doesn't smell</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0084">oh okay</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0041">and the next day I don't smell of <trunc>po</trunc> porridge</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0084">right so not one for first thing in the morning</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> but I don't do that anyway</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0084">I do I moisturize normally when I get out of the shower so that might sometimes be in the morning <pause dur="short"/> I try and shower in the evening but sometimes I feel really</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0041">I em <pause dur="short"/> I can't <pause dur="short"/> I really wanted to go on the sunbed</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0084">I saw Ten Years Younger today</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0041">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0084">oh my god the woman she had a chemical peel and laser surgery around her lips because her skin was so bad like obviously her lips were really puckered from where she'd been smoking all those years</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0041">yeah my mum's are not horrendous but bad</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0084">and she was from Glasgow you know they have like the highest rate em of skin cancer there <pause dur="short"/> it's like tripled in the last five years because people go on sun beds</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0041">really?</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> em cos they said cos obviously it's so fucking depressing in Glasgow cos everyone's like on smack and there's no jobs or whatever <pause dur="short"/> everyone lives in high rise <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0041">everyone's on smack</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0084">everyone's on smack they like deep fried Mars bars</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0041">have you ever had one?</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0084">etcetera etcetera <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0041">I haven't either</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0084">it sounds like hell <pause dur="short"/> absolute hell</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0041" trans="overlap">it does sound like hell</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0084">em I my worry would be that I'd get addicted and I'd need one every day and then my heart would go bye bye</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0041">bye bye now</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> So</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0041">and delete</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0084">okay <pause dur="short"/> bye and delete <pause dur="short"/> poor heart she's already under enough stress <pause dur="short"/> to be adding layers of Mars bars to the eh to the arteries <pause dur="short"/> went for sausage club yesterday which was delicious</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0041">I went for sausage club yesterday</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0084">it was so good <pause dur="short"/> like we had em we always make a joke cos like every time we go it's a different price depending on who's on the till because you're all fucking special And the last time I went it was the big guy who fancies all the women so he undercharges all the girls <pause dur="short"/> so me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> my colleague <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had the same breakfast but mine was one pound seventy and his was two pound twenty-four <vocal desc="laugh"/> Because the bloke undercharges women which was hilarious and all the boys were like that's fucking sexist if it was the other way round they'd be like you know the union will be getting involved blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> and I was like oh shut up whatever <pause dur="short"/> and eh this week it was the guy in charge it was Michael and you know like as soon as you walk you're like right everyone get out your loans</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0041">yeah?</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0084">get a second mortgage on that house to pay for your breakfast <pause dur="short"/> and he tried to charge me and I always have the same thing <pause dur="short"/> so bearing in mind it was one pound and seventy last time three pound twenty-four</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0041">shut up</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0084">and I was like hold the phone Michael <pause dur="short"/> what the hell? Two sausages beans and two eggs and he was like three pound twenty-four <pause dur="short"/> and I was like are you sure that's right Michael? And he said are you doubting me? And I said well I <trunc>w</trunc> I wouldn't dare Michael I wouldn't dare but it is quite early in the morning I just wonder whether you accidentally slipped on the button for sausage and pressed it ten times rather than two times because that's a bit obscene <pause dur="short"/> Em and I said if you're gonna recalculate it as more I wanna just have that price please <pause dur="short"/> eh and he did it again and it came out at two pounds and I was like right <pause dur="short"/> so how did we get the three pounds twenty-four? and he was like yeah I <trunc>n</trunc> I'm so sorry about that <pause dur="short"/> such a piss take if he didn't I think he does it on purpose because obviously he's the manager so he just overcharges everybody</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0084">probably cos he knows the rest are fucking retards and they undercharge</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0041">and you'll just say alright</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1190" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1191" who="S0084">doing him out of shit loads of money all the time anyway so he's like well I've got to make it back somehow </u>
<u n="1192" who="S0041">oh yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0084">it's really funny <pause dur="short"/> like when I went <pause dur="short"/> there's a big guy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who undercharges the women like he's serving on Thursday I had some sort of weird chicken crumble <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty mental</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0041">chicken crumble?</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0084">yeah so it was crumble but with like a like imagine like a chicken pie <pause dur="short"/> so chicken and bacon and mushrooms in a you know</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0084">sauce or whatever</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0084">and then you'd have a pie on top or around it <pause dur="short"/> well without the pie instead of the pie you've got crumble so it was mental but pretty nice <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't a sweet crumble it was a savoury crumble but it was <trunc>goo</trunc></u>
<u n="1200" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like a crust</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0084">it was good <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was really nice with like some tatties and eh like carrot and swede mash or something <pause dur="short"/> and he was oh yeah that's two pounds <trunc>no</trunc> and I know knew for one it should be like three ninety-nine <pause dur="short"/> and I was like oh that's really great and he was like oh I didn't see your veg on your way out <pause dur="short"/> thanks <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> it's so bad like obviously the feminist in me is like oh you should you know shouldn't allow it you shouldn't allow it  <pause dur="short"/> and then I'm like well I'm fucking poor </u>
<u n="1202" who="S0041">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1203" who="S0084">so that's just gonna have to eh</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0041">that's in order</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0084">be ignored <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's pretty good <pause dur="short"/> that's who you want on the till <pause dur="short"/> I mean I it's already pretty subsidised so even like the the the full meal is yeah is like four quid so it's not it's not going to break the bank <pause dur="short"/> but it does make you really frugal like to think the difference between two like two fifty or four pounds</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0041">that's a big difference isn't it?</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0084">it is a big difference like you can have a bowl soup <pause dur="short"/> a small bowl of soup is forty P or a big bowl of is ninety P I think? So even that's really cheap</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0084">like a small bowl of soup there's not actually that much difference in quantity</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0084">but it's its price so you might as well get a small bowl <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0041">they say that at work <pause dur="short"/> they say you know we <trunc>sh</trunc> we can't really complain about the quality of the food that they serve because it's free</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0041">but</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0084">did you not get the food they serve to the guests?</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0041">oh no do we fuck</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0084">who cooks your food then? Have they got a special company in do they?</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> it's the chefs but em</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0084">it's the same chefs then?</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it's just like cos obviously the stuff that's served in the restaurants is the restaurant's open in the evening and it's a la carte</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0041">so it's like monkfish and duck and</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0084">nice</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0041">other shit</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0041">and the lunch bar it's like well burgers or pizza are fine <pause dur="short"/> but they couldn't afford to give us that cos I think they're allocated something stupid like forty P a head?</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0084">for their staff?</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> which it just doesn't make sense to me <pause dur="short"/> and I'm sure it can't be that low <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure it can't but basically you know the food that's given to a a guest is allocated at ten pound a head or something</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0041">so it's a really really vast different <pause dur="short"/> em for example today's menu which I I walked past was em potato wedges peas and sweet corn mixed together</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0041">and fried chicken</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0041">the junk food only gets <trunc>s</trunc> like that type of junk food only gets served at a weekend</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0041">which I don't understand <pause dur="short"/> treat time <pause dur="short"/> em or but they'd put like a chicken curry on which was just shit like you wouldn't eat it <pause dur="short"/> it's bad</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0041">and then the other two options to go with it would be rice and naan bread</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0041">where's the vegetable?</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0041">there's no healthy option if you wanted to eat healthily you can't</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0084">that's really bad</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0041">or the the other day lasagne</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0041">with chips</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0084"><trunc>P</trunc> so carbs on carbs?</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0041">carbs on carbs with</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0084">garlic bread</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0041">garlic bread</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0084">was it really?</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0084">that's hilarious <pause dur="short"/> what wrong with a salad?</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0041">and they're like the housekeepers need that stodge to keep them going cos they do a really physical job no they don't <pause dur="short"/> nobody needs that</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0084">bollocks <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0041">nobody's body is made for that</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no no <pause dur="short"/> there's absolutely no need for it <pause dur="short"/> and you really should be you know supplying alternatives</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0084">you know</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0041">but they just don't</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0084">I mean I can't really complain about our canteen it is it is good <pause dur="short"/> they do have quite a lot of stuff on <pause dur="short"/> they've got like a bistro bar and a traditional bar and so they'll have like two mains and then they'll be a veggie option and then they'll have soup plus a hot veg and then a cold salad bar and there's the sandwiches and then there's the cold meats section there's pies and then there's you know all your other stuff like your crisps and your fruit and your yoghurts and your and your dessert</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0041">all that shit</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0084">it's massive but you are feeding over a thousand people</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0084">so the you <trunc>o</trunc> so you can get more in because obviously you've got more people paying</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0084">so it's easier to feed more people so</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0041">yeah I know this is absolute cack although I must admit because of all the complaining I've been doing <pause dur="short"/> eh it has got better for the past couple of weeks</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0084">and you're on that board thing are you? The gossip board?</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0041">the gossip board <pause dur="short"/> that's where I complained</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0084">Good</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0041">I went did I tell you I went to Holiday Inn last week with the gossip board?</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0084">oh you said went to the Holiday Inn? Yeah</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0041">yeah that was because of the gossip board</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0041">that was quite nice</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0084">that was a whole day out was it or part of the day?</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0041">three hours I think <pause dur="short"/> yeah three hours</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0041">yeah it was a bit a bit of a change of scenery <pause dur="short"/> have I told you that they made me go and <trunc>ch</trunc> be on the charity board as well?</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0084">oh so what does that mean? Like finding a charity to sponsor or doing campaigns to raise money?</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> each year IHG yeah <pause dur="short"/> each year IHG have a</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0084">sponsors a</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0041">sponsors a charity <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0041">this year I can't even tell you what it is <pause dur="short"/> shelter in the storm</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0041">have you heard of this before?</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0084">I've heard of Shelter is it different?</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0041">it's it's <trunc>af</trunc> It's everything it's Africa</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0084">it's everything it's Africa <pause dur="short"/> eh is it everything or is it Africa?</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0041">it's it's <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc> what's that really big charity?</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0084">Oxfam? Cafod? Water Aid?</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0041">eh eh</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0084">save the Children NSPCC</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0041">it's it's something like that it's one of those but it's not those</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0084">cancer Research?</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0084">RSPCA? RNIB?</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0041">it helps</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0084">RNLI</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0041">it helps loads of <trunc>peo</trunc> loads of different things</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0084">UN no not UN? Oh</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0041">oh I can't fucking remember <pause dur="short"/> but I should know this being on charity border calls</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0084"><trunc>Prob</trunc> probs yeah</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0041">but yeah anyway it doesn't do that like last year <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>whi</trunc> they sponsored Whizz Kids right</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0041">which is basically the charity of the children with chairs <pause dur="short"/> and I think we I think we bought two our hotel bought two and they were six pound a go</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0041">because people could really relate to it so when you're doing things you knew you could quantify what you're giving to somebody <pause dur="short"/> you know how much that would change their way of life</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0041">so people really got into it</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0041">but now it's like well what does the charity do? I don't really know <pause dur="short"/> you know it's in Africa and if there's a natural disaster or any type of disaster war or something they provide shelter for people who lose their homes</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0041">which is the part that I've we're supposedly going in as shelter in a storm</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0084">mm well that's good</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0041">but then</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0084">that's what they need</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0041">well yeah but <trunc>th</trunc> the logic being that we provide luxury accommodation for people</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0041">all over the world</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0041">these people provide accommodation no matter what</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0041">all the time like that's just as <trunc>in</trunc> just as luxurious to somebody with nothing</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0041">it <pause dur="short"/> I think that's supposed to be the the kind of link</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0084">tenuous link <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but this other <trunc>char</trunc> because it does so much stuff <pause dur="short"/> it helps fight AIDS in Africa <pause dur="short"/> it's malaria jabs it's children in India they're getting married off at eight years old and raped</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0084">is it Amnesty International?</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> frig <pause dur="short"/> it's it's like it's really like Amnesty International but and I think it's called Community community oh</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0084">world is it like The World Aid Organisation or World or something? Mate you probably should know this</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0041">I know <pause dur="short"/> but it's like that and you know you just think well <trunc>y</trunc> you no you can't quantify do they want do they want us to give clothes? Do they want us to give money? Do what? I just it just doesn't make sense</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0084">the thing is they've probably have you this and you've probably gone yeah it's interesting</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0041">no they haven't actually</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0084">have they not?</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0041">I don't know if they've told the management team but they certainly haven't told us yet</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0084">because that's well that's what you need to know isn't it? Otherwise there's no point</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0041" trans="overlap">there's no direction <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what I said</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0041">so it just it just seems a waste of time <pause dur="short"/> but yeah check that on the CV board board for charity borders</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0084"><trunc>Lit</trunc> literally bored to tears</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0041">yes to death <pause dur="short"/> and the worst part is we have to send someone from the department and obviously no one volunteered to go but I can't do charity stuff <pause dur="short"/> like I really can't</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0084">what? Why?</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0041">have I told you that? I think Africa is just like I can't even don't even know what's going on there</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0084">what <unclear/></u>
<u n="1350" who="S0041">I have told you this before <pause dur="short"/> this makes me sound really mean but you know starving kids in Africa?</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0041">I can't really accept that that's real and I know it is but because I've just I find it so horrific</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0041">I've just <pause dur="short"/> I I it's just so far away from anything l I can possibly understand <pause dur="short"/> it I feel like when I see it on TV it's not real</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0041">which makes me sound awful</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0041">and I know it does but it's just it's so it's so bad <pause dur="short"/> I just can't understand how I just can't I just can't fathom it</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0041">it's like space you know I just I</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0084">well I mean it's horrific and it is difficult to understand that in this day and age you know in Somalia kids are dying every day</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0084">hundreds and thousands of people are dying every day and yet there's absolutely no need for it <pause dur="short"/> every day like what is it every three seconds somebody dies in Africa <trunc>beca</trunc></u>
<u n="1364" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0084">you know needlessly through lack of water through drinking dirty water through lack of immunization you know it's it's happening all the time at at a time when we've cured all of these diseases</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0084">but we let it run wild out there because it's just not financially viable for us to do anything about it <pause dur="short"/> it is disgusting and it is really far away but the worry is obviously what with television being everywhere in our lives is we are desensitized to everything</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0084">so if we see something we're like oh that's just the TV I'll just block that out <pause dur="short"/> but they but that's so much more important it's like when people are like oh we've got to help ourselves before we help anybody else and you think well that's not really what it's all about it's about helping the people who need it the most </u>
<u n="1370" who="S0041">but do you not think and this is this makes me sound like Hitler</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0041">which I know that <pause dur="short"/> so do you know prepare yourself <pause dur="short"/> but do you not think that <pause dur="short"/> like if these if we these people should be able to should <trunc>wa</trunc> they're just not evolved <pause dur="short"/> do you not think? Like the only reason they're they're genetically different to us because okay so they're not educated cos we were given an education</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0041">but we weren't educated we were cavemen too</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0041">and it's just because our environment is habitable that we've been able to evolve and learn these things like <pause dur="short"/> I I <trunc>ca</trunc> I find it really weird it's like aliens to me <pause dur="short"/> honestly it's like aliens to me <pause dur="short"/> like they live in an environment that can't really readily or easily for the for the vast part of it anyway their land can't grow things</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0041">it's not it's not <trunc>cru</trunc> it's not supposed to sustain life</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not It's not yeah it's not sustainable yeah</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0041">it's not supposed to so no matter how much <trunc>m</trunc> money you throw at the problem</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0041"><trunc>th</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> it's perpetual because they shouldn't be living there</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0041">and really I can't I can't help but think right that if maybe if maybe no one was throwing money at it</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0041"><trunc>w</trunc> which is where the Hitler comes in they would all be dead</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0041">anyway <pause dur="short"/> which isn't that I wish all the people dead</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0041">I just wish that maybe thousands of years ago hundreds of years ago when people started throwing money at the problem they didn't throw money at it so it never developed <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean like I</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0084">I <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0041">I can't understand how it got to this now</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0084">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I mean my history is pretty bad as well <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why <pause dur="short"/> obviously we all come from Africa <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>even</trunc> like</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0084">through the last thousands of years as man's evolved we've all come from Africa <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>every</trunc> we are from them</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0084">so why it happened that you know obviously in the west we evolved more quickly we maybe it was because our terrain was much more habitable and we were able to do that <pause dur="short"/> as as we evolved we then went to these countries and then enslaved them and we took religion and we took our culture and enforced it on these countries <pause dur="short"/> so like for example when you go to New Zealand and you learn about the Maori culture and you learn about how they'd had to come over from you know Polynesian Islands and they and and you know <trunc>in</trunc> invaded New Zealand and the Maoris had made it their own land <pause dur="short"/> and when the whites came like the missionaries came they came and taught them religion <pause dur="short"/> so they taught them that God had created the earth in seven days and on the seventh day he rested and the seventh day was a sacred day <pause dur="short"/> so they laid down their weapons on the seventh day and they rested and the white man came and they brutally murdered them all <pause dur="short"/> because they knew that they'd lay down their weapons</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0041">are you being serious?</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah they did <pause dur="short"/> that's how they That's how they went there and took over the land <pause dur="short"/> it's probably what they did in America but I can't remember but I know it's definitely what they did in New Zealand <pause dur="short"/> that's what the missionaries did <pause dur="short"/> so there they're preaching the word of God but in an actual fact</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0041">fuck</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0084">they're there on behalf of you know the pillaging armies now they're gonna go</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0041">holy</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0084">the women are going to be raped the children are going to get killed and the men are gonna be enslaved <pause dur="short"/> so it's all very well to say that we're the evolved western world when in actual fact we're less humane than anybody else</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0084">though the issue I have is this idea of natural selection <pause dur="short"/> a certain number of people have to die because the planet can only sustain a certain number of people</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0084">and obviously because of their they they don't have access to condoms men <trunc>don</trunc> men rape women</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0084">so they're constantly having babies <pause dur="short"/> there's no way that they can't not <pause dur="short"/> because there's no consensual sex there <pause dur="short"/> they're being raped</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0084">they're constantly having babies they're more and more babies being brought into a world that that can't sustain them <pause dur="short"/> it's so it just beggars belief that we can have money and they can't <pause dur="short"/> our world is evolved but there's hasn't <pause dur="short"/> like how and it's because it seems so alien now because it's been allowed this gulf has been allowed to get bigger and bigger and bigger and bigger</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0084">at a time when we could have done something about it</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0084">nothing was really done</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0084">and so now it's got to a point where I we can't really fix it <pause dur="short"/> because the gulf is so huge between us</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0084">so really it's really hard but technology has come so far that you could actually transform the landscape if you wanted to <pause dur="short"/> companies could go out there and they could build irrigation in the fields</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0041">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0084">they could you know</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0084">greenhouses whatever it takes <pause dur="short"/> they can make the land more habitable than they have right now <pause dur="short"/> you can You can</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0041">but you can't you can't give that</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0084">invent clouds to come over <trunc>y</trunc> you can you know there are cloud buster machines now <pause dur="short"/> you can actually cause rain like people can now actually cause it to rain</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0041">but you can't <trunc>rea</trunc> give that to someone who is so <trunc>wh</trunc> so <trunc>n</trunc> so backward which sounds awful but they are</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0084">no but they're not stupid do you know what I mean? They just haven't been afforded the opportunity because we we're in the west and we're special and we've got the tools and we want to make our money ourselves <pause dur="short"/> we don't want to give anybody else what we've got</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0041">well someone must say to those men to rape is wrong and they don't understand that</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0084">but no But no I don't think anybody is because they're just being left to their own devices <pause dur="short"/> there's no one really there There's no one really there to help them</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0041">but how can they think that's right? Like in our in in England</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0084">because they're because they are barbaric in the sense that they haven't got they haven't been through the same civilization that we have <pause dur="short"/> but that doesn't mean that we're any more humane cos we did terrible things as well</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0041">but they must talk to each other</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0084">our armies go in and pillage</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0041">like they they can communicate so</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0084">it's not about</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0041">so when the woman says no don't do that </u>
<u n="1437" who="S0084">and he thinks that that's okay much like in a country that we think is more developed for example Saudi Arabia like they they stone women in the middle east still <pause dur="short"/> they'll chop off your hands you're not allowed to sunbathe in a in a bikini</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0084">you know everyone every country really is at a different level of development civilization <pause dur="short"/> em and we're still incredibly backward and we still don't help each other in the way that I think we should <pause dur="short"/> there's that's what I find so sickening about national identity and divides and borders is that this these gulfs between us are getting bigger all the time when in actual fact we should just be one</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0084">we shouldn't be however hundreds of countries there are because we're not helping each other</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0084">do these these people in Somalia are dying and it's so unnecessary <pause dur="short"/> I mean obviously it's not just Somalia but that's where the drought is at the moment</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0084">and obviously you've got people in Haiti you know and they're still in Port Au Prince they're still living in shanty towns</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0041">in fucking New Orleans they're still living in tents</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I mean and this is like a whole country you know Haiti <pause dur="short"/> it's awful</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0041">yeah I don't really get it <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>do</trunc> I don't I can't really fathom it to be honest and</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0084">well no that's and I think that's why people have such a have such difficulty in in relating to it because it is so far away <pause dur="short"/> it's so far removed from what we understand but that's you know it's not a reason not to do something about it</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0041">and then I have to go and then put the video on and I start crying <pause dur="short"/> I can't watch it <pause dur="short"/> I can't even watch the adverts on TV</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0084">I know I can't watch the adverts on TV <pause dur="short"/> I cry</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0041">and then we had to watch this video and I'm sat there bawling</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0041">and I thought to out of everyone to send to the charity meeting</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0041">really <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't me</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0041">I was the wrong person to send to the charity meeting <pause dur="short"/> it was a fucking piss take</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0084">that is just really moving though isn't it? I mean that I mean that that's why they do it</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0084">because they want to affect you <pause dur="short"/> you know they they need to get your attention</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0041"><trunc>W</trunc> why <pause dur="short"/> oh I just don't I don't think I'll ever get it <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I'll ever understand it</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0084">well I mean that's a good enough reason to try and understand it isn't it? You know if you think well I don't understand that maybe maybe I should read something more about it like I think if I watch something on TV <pause dur="short"/> but the thing is my memory is like a goldfish <pause dur="short"/> like I might watch a film about the troubles in Northern Island and I think I don't understand that I don't really understand what happened there and what and the history like the history goes back like hundreds of years between the Irish and the English and I why where does it come from? And I've read about it and I've gone online and I've watched movies and I think it's really interesting and how how has this come to be and I learn it and I think oh my god this is really bad <pause dur="short"/> a week later I'm interested in something else and I've forgotten about that and it's gone <pause dur="short"/> I couldn't tell you any of it now <pause dur="short"/> you know I just think it's so hard but something like that <pause dur="short"/> it's really important isn't it? Like</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0084">the idea that someone is dying every three seconds unnecessarily</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0041">yeah like you saying it and I know you're not lying but it just sounds like a lie</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0084" trans="overlap">I'm not lying no <pause dur="short"/> no no no <pause dur="short"/> I mean that was the whole idea of doing behind doing World Aid again in two thousand and eight or whenever it was two thousand and five when Live Eight <pause dur="short"/> what was it called? Live Eight?</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0041">yeah Live Eight</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0084">and they all those advert the all the celebrities clicking every three seconds</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0084">do you remember?</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0084">that was it <pause dur="short"/> that's another person dead <pause dur="short"/> and it's really powerful but then as soon as that's gone everyone's forgotten about it because that's what you do you sort of go about your daily lives don't you?</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0084">unless you are the Bob Geldof's of this world going out and championing it in Ethiopia and Somalia and Botswana</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0041">what I don't really get as well is that like <pause dur="short"/> there are <trunc>pe</trunc> there are people that can afford to give a lot of money</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0041">like I'm not talking well I'll give my one pound a week</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0041">I'm talking just take your interest out of what you had</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0041">this year and give them half a million quid</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0041">so I if I don't actually believe that the government really wants to do anything about it because if they did</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0041">there's enough money going round</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0041">people have got enough money</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well if you think that they could have cleared the third world debt em you know over and over and over and over and over and over and over easily so then they just won't do it <pause dur="short"/> because it just doesn't make any sense and obviously the the people who can can afford to and can afford to make a little difference are the pharmaceutical companies</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0084">the ones that are out there</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0084">pushing their drugs peddling their drugs <pause dur="short"/> creating more problem and actually they're the ones who are rich they're the ones actually who would be like the what do you call it? Those horrible creatures? Cockroaches the ones who never die</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0084">you know they'll be an apocalypse</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0084">they'll be a nuclear war and it'll be the fucking pharmaceutical companies who will survive <pause dur="short"/> they're fucking devils <pause dur="short"/> cos it's just</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0041">Cos I thought that as well <pause dur="short"/> so I said okay so you can't you can't make them wear condoms</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0084">they try and they're constantly given they're there they're giving them out obviously because you've got an AIDS epidemic haven't you?</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0041">so why don't they just give all the women the pill?</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0084">you can't make them take it</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0041">but you would take it</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0084">you <trunc>tr</trunc> well I suppose you'd try <pause dur="short"/> I mean obviously you've got</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0041">you do if you lived in a country where you're going to be raped</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0041">you would think they would take it</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well again you've got to get the pharmaceutical companies to agree to it and I don't think they would</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> did you see a while ago actually? I don't know why but I just remembered this <pause dur="short"/> a while ago there was an <trunc>a</trunc> an article about a woman em in the news and they thought <trunc>t</trunc> she'd be she was immune to HIV</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0084">bloody hell</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what happened with that how long ago was it? About a <trunc>y</trunc> a year ago?</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0084">she's immune? Oh my god</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0041">yeah she lived in all these places where she must have been raped a zillion times</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0041">and because it's so rife</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0041">that <trunc>sh</trunc> she'd not got it</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0084">she developed an immunity</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0041">she's not and she's not got it</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0041">yeah so they want cos they were doing tests on her DNA and stuff</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0084">I bet <pause dur="short"/> god can you imagine? It reminds me of em you know the comedian Bill Hicks? Have you seen his stand up? He died He died actually on stage <pause dur="short"/> but he was a comedian in the eighties and nineties American <pause dur="short"/> and he was he was quite controversial at the time <pause dur="short"/> he always reminds me of the day they find a cure for HIV people are just going to be fucking in the street</u>
<u n="1522" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1523" who="S0084">he does a skit of like man and woman are like oh hi how's it going like on the lawn outside and everyone would just be fucking all the time <pause dur="short"/> I thought that was quite funny <pause dur="short"/> he does this bit like have you seen Human Traffic?</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't remember it though</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0084">okay there's a bit in the beginning where what's his name? Kip? Jip? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? One of the mean the main guys?</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0041">it's like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1527" who="S0084">whatever his name is and his he goes home and he's getting ready for the party of the century the Friday night and he puts on a DVD of the comedian and he's like yeah I've done drugs <pause dur="short"/> yeah I drink but I just go home and I light a spliff and I go about my day <pause dur="short"/> I don't kill anybody I don't get in a rage <pause dur="short"/> I just get a bit high and I have a lovely time <pause dur="short"/> it's quite funny <pause dur="short"/> and you think that's fair enough <pause dur="short"/> if you get high on a bit of weed you very rarely are gonna get smash a beer bottle over somebody's head in a pub fight are you?</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> well that's the thing how the hell is alcohol legal and weed isn't?</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> does seem mental isn't it?</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0041">it just doesn't make any sense</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0084">you think about the A and E admissions <pause dur="short"/> every Friday night</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0084"><trunc>W</trunc> with like from people smoking weed versus people who have been out drinking <pause dur="short"/> it's a no brainer</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0041">yeah that's true actually</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0084">I might make a cheeky hot chocolate rather than vino bed vino <pause dur="short"/> you should eat some food</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0041">oh I'm not</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0084">everything? Everything in the world</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0041">all food <pause dur="short"/> might just make a slice of toast</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but once you start eating you might find that you're really hungry</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0041">right <pause dur="short"/> eighty slices of toast</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0084">and then have the whole loaf <pause dur="short"/> that would be pretty funny <pause dur="short"/> I would like that <pause dur="short"/> I'd like to see that</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0041">I didn't notice what time it was</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0084">Bedfordshire o'clock <pause dur="short"/> I loves it I do bed <pause dur="short"/> I do know what I'm going to wear for my date tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna go over to my mum's for the day</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0041">where are you going?</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0084">we said we'd meet at the Boathouse</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0041">the Boathouse the Boathouse?</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0084">Down by <anon type="place"/> corner</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0084">Cos he lives on <anon type="place"/> Road</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0084">so I just I thought</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0041">how old is he?</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0084">thirty-six</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's got quite a good body from the the photos <pause dur="short"/> and he's a <unclear/></u>
<u n="1556" who="S0041">why do you think you're not going to enjoy it?</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0084">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> he just seems a bit em his spelling's really bad <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm so ridiculous</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0041">no you're not my spelling's bad and I'd still judge somebody else on it cos I know it's wrong do you know what I mean? I don't think it's right <pause dur="short"/> I mean check it</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0084">or like and part of it is like text language as well it's it so</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0084">could be that he's not stupid it's just it's just writing quickly</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0041">could be <pause dur="short"/> could be that he's stupid</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0084"><vocal desc="cough"/> The coughing has started <pause dur="short"/> right let's get some water</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0041">could be a bit stupid though</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0084">could be a bit stupid <pause dur="short"/> I mean it could be quite good crack <pause dur="short"/> if in doubt just go and see for the fun for the laugh <pause dur="short"/> go for the shits and giggles <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0041"><unclear/> the kitchen again</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0084">yeah to <pause dur="short"/> I don't think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has come home <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1568" who="S0041"><shift new="singing"/>fantastic<shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1569" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0041"><shift new="singing"/><unclear/><shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1571" who="S0084">oh can I even have chocolate? Yeah it's practically Sunday</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0041">it's practically Sunday</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's definitely fine <pause dur="short"/> so has Emily got a parking space outside her house?</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0041">has she?</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0084">got a parking spot outside her house?</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0084">oh that's nice and easy <pause dur="short"/> have you spoken to her since she had that thing with her mum the other night?</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> I didn't ask about that though</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0084">alright</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0041">she's fine</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0084">Good</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0041">well she's fine <pause dur="short"/> I like that somebody's been helping myself to my bread</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0084">oh really? Who? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1584" who="S0041">I don't know</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0084">he's a bit of a one <pause dur="short"/> at least he don't come from me <pause dur="short"/> I don't like white bread <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> I went back on my bike today for the first time in about two weeks <pause dur="short"/> it felt so strange <pause dur="short"/> it felt really small</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0041">did it?</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0084">yeah when I was pulling out <unclear/> corner I feel a bit on edge <pause dur="short"/> but it was fine quite hard work but It was nice it was nice and sunny</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the first time back on the bike's the hardest isn't it? That's was a bit of a chicken</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0041">and cycled home as opposed to <unclear/> and that's downhill across Midsummer Common</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0084">oh really?</u>
<u n="1592" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1593" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't really have to do much <pause dur="short"/> I just sit there</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0084">yeah it's much easier on the way back <pause dur="short"/> it's nice It's nice cycling along the river cos I don't cycle to work anymore so it's quite pretty <pause dur="short"/> that is nice <pause dur="short"/> I like <pause dur="short"/> oh I Sacha Baron Cohen has got a new film coming out cos they've banned it</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0041">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0084">from the Oscars because they didn't they've said that they haven't banned it cos you know it's tomorrow night <pause dur="short"/> and they said the organiser said that they haven't banned it but his website this blogger website in America said they have because he's got this new film coming out called The Dictator <pause dur="short"/> and he plays this character which is like a cross between Saddam Hussein and em Gaddafi <pause dur="short"/> so you can imagine it's quite controversial and basically the idea is like tips for a dictator who wants to keep his country under a regime <vocal desc="laugh"/> and they've said you can't come cos there was that year when he at that MTV awards and he lowered himself into Eminem's face as Bruno like his buttocks in a man's face</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0041">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0084">I think Eminem was in on that wasn't he? Whatever his name is <pause dur="short"/> em and I think they think that he's just you know he'll he'll do something ridiculous something that's really <trunc>flam</trunc> flamboyant and you think</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0084">well you know and America should be used to it by now <pause dur="short"/> they get Ricky Gervais to host their whatevers they are every year <pause dur="short"/> he always does the is it the Grammys he always does? And he always says really controversial things that everyone's like I don't think you can really say that but okay </u>
<u n="1601" who="S0041">but's it too late cos it's out your mouth</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0084">yeah but he's been doing it for a few years now <pause dur="short"/> I think it smells of like mouldy cheese or something in here <pause dur="short"/> I noticed it earlier ah that Carmen is so heavy I see what you mean about her being heavy footed <pause dur="short"/> cos she came in slammed the door stomped in here like stomped really stomped up the stairs and I thought it must have been <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> with his heavy boots or something</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0041">yeah I thought it was</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0084">man alive <pause dur="short"/> I've never heard anything like it</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0084">maybe she's got a like steel hub-capped boots or something</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0041">em em and I I was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> she em she's woken me up twice this week</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0084">really? <trunc>W</trunc> what like during the night?</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0041">eh yeah <pause dur="short"/> em she cos she comes in here <pause dur="short"/> she pushes that door to and doesn't close it and she puts her earphones on <pause dur="short"/> so she can't hear her bashing around</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0041">her own slap bashing around <pause dur="short"/> and she's on the phone then so she's shouting</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0041">through the earphones and I'm just like oh for fuck's sake like you're actually taking the piss </u>
<u n="1614" who="S0084">spanish people are loud aren't they? You like when they talk like the conversation</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0084">and they are quite loud I think they just must not realise</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0041">and you think that after the she's woken me up once</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0041">yeah the day later she might think to close the door <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0084">when now after you <trunc>s</trunc> stomped in there and said thanks very much for that </u>
<u n="1621" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0084">well no I'm sorry for waking you up this morning</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0041">alright doesn't matter</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0084">honestly didn't realise</u>
</body>
</text>
