<text id="SEM7">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:00:00</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-12-16</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0539 S0557</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc></rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Future plans, Relationships, Trip to Edinburgh/London, Flooding in the Lakes, Christmas, Present buying, Family. </topics>
		<activity>Talking whilst on the way to Edinburgh. </activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, complaining, announcing, anecdote telling, making arrangements, apologising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0539">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lancaster</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cumbrian/Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Carnforth</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Masters Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0557">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Liverpool</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Kirby Lonsdale</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0557">so I'm glad we're finally on the train after a twenty minute delay</u>
<u n="2" who="S0539">I know well the tracks at <anon type="place"/> are really bad at the moment so we'll probably be delayed on the way back as well I think the flooding's eroded part of the track so when I was going to <anon type="place"/> it was delayed by half an hour</u>
<u n="3" who="S0557">yeah I can't believe like how much the flooding's like affected us like I had no idea how bad it was</u>
<u n="4" who="S0539">I know</u>
<u n="5" who="S0557">erm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0539">well I've never ever seen it flooded in <anon type="place"/> before</u>
<u n="7" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="8" who="S0539">it's so sad and when you drive through <anon type="place"/> there's so many like houses that have all been flooded</u>
<u n="9" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0539">and like all the sofas and</u>
<u n="11" who="S0557" trans="overlap">businesses</u>
<u n="12" who="S0539">everything in just in the middle of the streets it's so bad</u>
<u n="13" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah like my friend's er dad owns a business and all of his work that er was due to be shipped out has been ruined so obviously that's not good is it?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh god and so close to Christmas as well</u>
<u n="15" who="S0557">I know</u>
<u n="16" who="S0539">there was this family that posted on Facebook looking for a erm house to rent</u>
<u n="17" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0539">because their son's in hospital with cancer and he can come home now for Christmas but they don't have anywhere to live so it's awful</u>
<u n="19" who="S0557">yeah I think the only positive thing to come out of it is the deadline's <vocal desc="laugh"/> been moved back <unclear/></u>
<u n="20" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0539">I know well I didn't I didn't have to do my stats exam</u>
<u n="22" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0539">because they've postponed it all which I think the stats teacher's quite annoyed at but</u>
<u n="24" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I know well even my I've got two essays in for January I didn't think they'd be affected and they've been moved back two weeks afterwards so <pause dur="short"/> didn't think they'd be affected</u>
<u n="25" who="S0539">no no that's good <vocal desc="laugh"/> in some ways I just can't believe like <anon type="place"/> was flooded</u>
<u n="26" who="S0557">I know cos I thought it was just near me <unclear>though</unclear> when I was coming back</u>
<u n="27" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0557"><unclear/> <anon type="place"/> way <unclear>didn't we</unclear></u>
<u n="29" who="S0539">like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were driving through and they had to leave <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s car in erm in the middle of <anon type="place"/> and he's got like a</u>
<u n="30" who="S0557">has he got it back now or anything?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0539">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0539">he's got like a brand new BM so I don't think he'd've</u>
<u n="34" who="S0557">oh it wasn't the one near the car wash was it? I saw loads of pictures on Facebook and that was a fifteen BMW</u>
<u n="35" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah no I think it oh maybe it was no no I don't think it was</u>
<u n="36" who="S0557">right by the car wash like in the middle of <unclear>the road</unclear></u>
<u n="37" who="S0539" trans="overlap">no no it was up <anon type="place"/> it must've flooded up there as well cos the river <anon type="place"/> like burst its banks didn't it?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="39" who="S0539">it's awful there's so many animals that have been killed as well there was this</u>
<u n="40" who="S0557">ah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0539">poor little cat that was on a fence</u>
<u n="42" who="S0557">mm?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0539">and erm this woman saw it and it'd just dropped into the floodwater so she just managed to get it out it was such a shame</u>
<u n="44" who="S0557">ah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0539">but then she had dogs at her house so she said she couldn't keep it so erm she was like appealing for someone to take this little cat in and then this other girl on Facebook said that she'd take it in</u>
<u n="46" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="47" who="S0539">so they had to like wade through floodwater to meet her and</u>
<u n="48" who="S0557">mm well there was that dog on Facebook people were saying erm it fell in the river and it just got swept off cos obviously the current was too fast</u>
<u n="49" who="S0539" trans="overlap">ah and did you see that <vocal desc="laugh"/> donkey that got rescued?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0557">a donkey? no</u>
<u n="51" who="S0539">yeah like the erm animal rescue team wanted to rescue it but the police told them not to it was too dangerous but they did and then it had the cheesiest grin</u>
<u n="52" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah oh yeah I saw that it was like proper smiling wasn't it?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0539" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it was hilarious poor little thing</u>
<u n="54" who="S0557" trans="overlap">ah that was funny <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was so happy</u>
<u n="55" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0539">it looked like a person</u>
<u n="57" who="S0557"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I thought you meant like round here but no sorry on Facebook</u>
<u n="58" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0557"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0539">so what do you want to do in <anon type="place"/> today?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0557">erm well I think it depends on the weather but obviously well we've eaten now haven't we? so if we have a wander round we'll go and get a drink I'll leave it to you cos obviously you know it better than me really don't you? but</u>
<u n="62" who="S0539">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0557">erm obviously look round the markets</u>
<u n="64" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0557"><unclear>for nice</unclear> Christmassy things</u>
<u n="66" who="S0539">we'll have to go to</u>
<u n="67" who="S0557">mulled wine</u>
<u n="68" who="S0539">yeah we'll have to go to the dome that's really nice</u>
<u n="69" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0539">it has like a massive Christmas tree inside <unclear>it's lovely</unclear></u>
<u n="71" who="S0557" trans="overlap">erm where are we booked in for food again?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0539"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0557">yeah what did your mum call it? <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="74" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0557">yeah that's meant to be well known well obviously my friend went there last night so she must've</u>
<u n="76" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah did you ask her if it was good?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0557">well she said I'd love it cos it's all Christmassy like</u>
<u n="78" who="S0539">yeah erm yeah I'm glad we booked there instead of <anon type="place"/> actually because</u>
<u n="79" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah it does it does look really good inside <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah I was looking at some reviews there and they said it was a bit like overrated and the service wasn't great and the food wasn't that good</u>
<u n="81" who="S0557">did you enjoy it for your graduation <unclear>though</unclear>?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah it was really nice but</u>
<u n="83" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0539">I think <anon type="place"/> is a bit better when did you last come to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0557">oh a long time ago like a couple of years ago</u>
<u n="86" who="S0539">mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0557">I've been wanting to go for like weekends away and stuff in fact I almost booked a wedding but <unclear/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh did you?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0539">ah yeah I love <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah it's so like historical and stuff could we go erm near the castle and stuff?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0539">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0539">yeah you've got to pay if you want to go round</u>
<u n="95" who="S0557">yeah but we don't need to do that do we? but we could go and look</u>
<u n="96" who="S0539">yeah I erm I never went round it when I was at uni in <anon type="place"/> because</u>
<u n="97" who="S0557" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0539">if well they there was like this old wives' tale that if you went round the castle while you were studying there it was like bad luck so</u>
<u n="99" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="100" who="S0539">I thought I'd better not risk it</u>
<u n="101" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah oh no I need all the help I can get <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0539" trans="overlap">so I never went round I know so have you applied to do like your masters now?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0557">erm almost I've half applied I'm gonna apply to <anon type="place"/> I think but I'll leave it till January</u>
<u n="104" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0557">but <anon type="place"/> <trunc>lo</trunc> it'd be lovely wouldn't it? and where's <anon type="place"/>? whereabouts is that? <unclear/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0539">erm that's like an hour and a half</u>
<u n="107" who="S0557">yeah I might apply there as well</u>
<u n="108" who="S0539" trans="overlap">like north of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0557" trans="overlap">is there stuff to do round it? like is there?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0539">I don't really I've never been to <anon type="place"/> I don't think it's as lively as <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> but</u>
<u n="111" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah I <unclear>wanna</unclear> apply there as well but erm like the big cities I think and also stay at <anon type="place"/> possibly</u>
<u n="112" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0557">cos obviously the funding continues so that'd be an easy option</u>
<u n="114" who="S0539">oh that's good</u>
<u n="115" who="S0557">yeah and obviously it's a good reputation isn't it?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0557" trans="overlap">it is good to stay there</u>
<u n="118" who="S0539" trans="overlap">so do you get discount from <anon type="place"/> then because you did your undergrad there?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0557">no I think you know how student finance covers four years?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0557">I think it instead of me paying like eleven grand to do my LPC in <anon type="place"/> I can just continue with the funding on do you see what I mean?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0539">oh that's good</u>
<u n="123" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I think it's six grand it works out as</u>
<u n="124" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0557">how much did you pay for yours? was it six thousand?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0539">I think it was like six thousand eight hundred but then I got an a thousand grand scholarship</u>
<u n="127" who="S0557">oh yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0539">so that helped a little bit but</u>
<u n="129" who="S0557">I got a two thousand pound scholarship first year but erm for the grades and stuff but</u>
<u n="130" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah well mine was for academic performance</u>
<u n="131" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0539"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on my course she erm did her undergrad at <anon type="place"/> though</u>
<u n="133" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0539">so she gets a nine grand scholarship for her masters because</u>
<u n="135" who="S0557" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0539">yeah she started uni when the fees were higher</u>
<u n="137" who="S0557">yeah so did I though</u>
<u n="138" who="S0539">yeah so</u>
<u n="139" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><unclear>mm</unclear> oh</u>
<u n="140" who="S0539">so that more than covers her fees and she's got like a bit extra in the bank which is really good</u>
<u n="141" who="S0557" trans="overlap">why did she get that then?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0539">at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0557">why?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0539">just because she paid the higher fee rates and I think her your family income has to be so much and whatever it's worth looking into though</u>
<u n="145" who="S0557" trans="overlap">oh see that's where <unclear/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0539">like there's certain criteria you have to fill fulfil to get it but</u>
<u n="147" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah just so expensive now you know?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0539">oh yeah well nine grand a year's a lot</u>
<u n="149" who="S0557">yeah and after when I graduate next year I'm gonna be like <unclear>sixty thousand pounds in debt</unclear></u>
<u n="150" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh I know don't even talk about it <pause dur="short"/> I know when I went to <anon type="place"/> the fees were only like</u>
<u n="151" who="S0557">three thousand was it?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0539">I think it was like three thousand</u>
<u n="155" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0539">or less than I think it was a bit cheaper</u>
<u n="157" who="S0557">I think yeah cos I applied to erm where did I apply to in Scotland? I can't remember and erm it was cheaper</u>
<u n="158" who="S0539">yeah oh yeah it is</u>
<u n="159" who="S0557" trans="overlap">it's like Scottish universities are cheaper aren't they? even</u>
<u n="160" who="S0539">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0557">but don't erm if you were born in Scotland you get it for free don't you?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0539" trans="overlap">but then you've got an extra year yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0557">that's so good</u>
<u n="164" who="S0539" trans="overlap">and and if you live in the EU it's so bad <vocal desc="laugh"/> they just hate the English <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear>yeah I know I know</unclear></u>
<u n="166" who="S0539">there's definitely a bit of hatred there still</u>
<u n="167" who="S0557"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0539">so er what did you do last night? did you go out for tea in the end?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah went for a nice meal I ended up having a Christmas dinner I was just gonna get the pizza and then erm and then there was the turkey dinner <unclear>on</unclear> so that was really nice and it was lovely presented you know? it was like apricot stuffing erm and the gravy was gorgeous it was like thick red wine gravy on the turkey</u>
<u n="170" who="S0539" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0557">meat was a bit fatty though</u>
<u n="172" who="S0539">mm</u>
<u n="173" who="S0557">it was good</u>
<u n="174" who="S0539">and who did you meet up with?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0557">erm my old work colleague she's working somewhere else obviously and I am now but erm yeah we like to catch up occasionally</u>
<u n="176" who="S0539">mm nice how's she doing?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0557" trans="overlap">so yeah yeah good I think yeah she's really enjoying like her workplace and stuff</u>
<u n="178" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0557">she actually went for a Christmas party the night after our old work do and they hired out you know the <anon type="place"/> showground opposite <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0539">oh yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0557">it was like teepees</u>
<u n="182" who="S0539">oh</u>
<u n="183" who="S0557">and it's nice it's all lit up inside and stuff so <unclear/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh lovely yeah I went to see Elton John <vocal desc="laugh"/> there</u>
<u n="185" who="S0557">oh yeah you did didn't you?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0539">I hope they get like more big acts there it's good cos we don't get anyone near us</u>
<u n="189" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0539">and it's like a really good venue it can fit like loads of people in</u>
<u n="191" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0539">although we were just like sat on plastic chairs</u>
<u n="193" who="S0557" trans="overlap">how close would that be though?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0539">yeah yeah I know it would <unclear/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><unclear/> instead of going to the <anon type="place"/> and stuff</u>
<u n="196" who="S0539">yeah well I don't really like Elton John myself but he's such a big name and he was so close I think you've got to like support it</u>
<u n="197" who="S0557">oh yeah you might as well</u>
<u n="198" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0557">well I was gonna go but I think the tickets were a bit <unclear>fucking</unclear> ridiculous</u>
<u n="200" who="S0539">yeah so is?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I would really like to see Michael McIntyre there <unclear/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0539">oh yeah that would be great</u>
<u n="203" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah his new tour <unclear/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0539">I was gonna book tickets actually he was on in October in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0557">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0539" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="207" who="S0557">well I saw him with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and my mum like two thousand and eight so I wanna see his new tour</u>
<u n="208" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0557">we could go actually we could have a look for tickets</u>
<u n="210" who="S0539">yeah that'd be good</u>
<u n="211" who="S0557">I bought his new DVD as like a little stocking filler for my parents <unclear/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0539">oh nice what you gonna get your mum and dad for Christmas?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0557">I've got my mum a spa day</u>
<u n="214" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0557">at the <anon type="place"/> cos we both love the <anon type="place"/> and she goes on about it all the time</u>
<u n="216" who="S0539" trans="overlap">the <anon type="place"/> in?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0557"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0539">oh lovely</u>
<u n="219" who="S0557">erm I wish it included lunch really but it was just erm a treatment use of facilities and then <pause dur="short"/> erm a cupcake <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0557"><unclear>we'll</unclear> have lunch there</u>
<u n="222" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0557">and then I've also got her a top from Zara</u>
<u n="224" who="S0539">oh nice</u>
<u n="225" who="S0557">erm and I might get her some like Liz Earle moisturiser as well dad I got him oh I got him this really nice erm TK Maxx I love TK Maxx especially for Christmas shopping it's like a real leather Ipad case</u>
<u n="226" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="227" who="S0557">and it's got like a notepad and stylus and stuff <unclear/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh lovely</u>
<u n="229" who="S0557">and it was down from like a hundred and ten to twenty-four ninety-nine</u>
<u n="230" who="S0539">that's really good</u>
<u n="231" who="S0557">so I got him that some Ralph Lauren pyjamas in TK Maxx again</u>
<u n="232" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0557">they were like twenty quid</u>
<u n="234" who="S0539">oh very nice</u>
<u n="235" who="S0557">and then erm some L'Oréal post shave balm that he likes</u>
<u n="236" who="S0539">yeah I got a erm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0557" trans="overlap">what have you got?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0539">well I got a <vocal desc="laugh"/> Ted Baker Ipad case</u>
<u n="239" who="S0557">for your mum? or for?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0539">no no for me like last year or the year before</u>
<u n="241" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> for you? <unclear>oh okay</unclear></u>
<u n="242" who="S0539">erm but I've just <trunc>ne</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0557">from TK Maxx?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0539">no no no it was from Ted Baker</u>
<u n="245" who="S0557">oh right</u>
<u n="246" who="S0539">but I haven't been able to afford the Ipad yet so it's just <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="247" who="S0557"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0539">sitting there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0557">so you bought the case with no Ipad?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0539">yeah well I really liked the case and I was gonna get the Ipad but then</u>
<u n="251" who="S0557" trans="overlap">mm I <trunc>g</trunc> I got the mini and it's not too bad really</u>
<u n="252" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0557">it was like two six nine or something</u>
<u n="254" who="S0539">er yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0557">it's not too bad</u>
<u n="256" who="S0539">yeah my mum gave me like money towards it but then I was in a bit of</u>
<u n="257" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0539">yeah I was in debt then from uni so I was like oh right you can just pay that off so</u>
<u n="259" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0539">yeah I haven't got one yet I'll get one one day I'm sure</u>
<u n="261" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0539">and then my dad just wants like a log basket because <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="263" who="S0557">what?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0539">well he hates like pointless Christmas presents</u>
<u n="265" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so he wants practical <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah like he's he's very honest about it and like if he doesn't like them he's just like what is this you have given me?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0557" trans="overlap">what has he got in the past that he doesn't like?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0539">oh just like nice little gifts like clothes and things like that he's just like mm the zip doesn't fit over my nose and <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0557" trans="overlap">what? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0539">well he's got a big nose so he's like really paranoid about zips and things</u>
<u n="271" who="S0557"><vocal desc="laugh"/> doesn't fit over his <unclear/></u>
<u n="272" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0539"><unclear>ridiculous</unclear> so yeah he wants a log basket this year and then</u>
<u n="274" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0557">have you got that yet?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0539">no no we need to find one with strong enough handles</u>
<u n="277" who="S0557" trans="overlap">where are you gonna get one? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0539">cos he <vocal desc="laugh"/> has a lot of logs apparently so erm we're still searching for the perfect basket</u>
<u n="279" who="S0557" trans="overlap">how do you wrap that?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0539">don't</u>
<u n="281" who="S0557"><unclear/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0539">probably put like a big ribbon round it or something?</u>
<u n="283" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0539">a few holly berries on top very Christmassy</u>
<u n="285" who="S0557"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0539"><unclear/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0557">what are you getting your mum then?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0539">I think she wants like a spa day or something I don't know she's hard to buy for because she just likes her bargains and things and</u>
<u n="289" who="S0557">yeah spa <unclear>date's are</unclear> that's a nice gift like I don't want to just give her that I got her like the top to go with it but</u>
<u n="290" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0557">erm yeah do that you like your spa dates don't you?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0557">I really wanted to take her to that place you went <anon type="place"/> but</u>
<u n="294" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0557">you know? sixty pounds each or whatever it was</u>
<u n="296" who="S0539">I know</u>
<u n="297" who="S0557">that's a bit ridiculous</u>
<u n="298" who="S0539">it is really pricey it's lovely though</u>
<u n="299" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0539">I mean that's quite a good deal for there really because I was looking into it and if if you just stay overnight there you've still got to pay thirty pounds for the spa which is crazy</u>
<u n="301" who="S0557">yeah you said didn't you? it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="302" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah but with that package you get like the spa and then the afternoon tea</u>
<u n="303" who="S0557" trans="overlap">did you get? oh you get afternoon tea</u>
<u n="304" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0557">well that one I did was just lovely</u>
<u n="306" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0557">erm</u>
<u n="308" who="S0539">where was that at?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0557"><anon type="place"/> like <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0539">oh right</u>
<u n="311" who="S0557">so like you got erm like fruit on arrival like erm a two course lunch and stuff</u>
<u n="312" who="S0539">oh</u>
<u n="313" who="S0557">it was so nice</u>
<u n="314" who="S0539">yeah the one me and my mum went to was nice that was <vocal desc="cough"/> like thirty something</u>
<u n="315" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0539">for erm <pause dur="short"/> for a treatment and I got like a back massage and then access to the spa and a three course dinner the dinner was really nice the spa wasn't like great it was a bit</u>
<u n="317" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0539">like run down it could've done with a refurb but yeah it was nice there's some good offers around</u>
<u n="319" who="S0557">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah just got an email from the BT <unclear>legal grad</unclear> scheme thing it's like an in house thing that sounded really good didn't get that</u>
<u n="320" who="S0539">oh</u>
<u n="321" who="S0557">it's just so hard like all the psychometric tests that they expect you to do and then</u>
<u n="322" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh my god I know</u>
<u n="323" who="S0557">the assessment centres and stuff I just don't know how anyone gets employed I really don't</u>
<u n="324" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah well the psychometric tests I <trunc>h</trunc> I don't know they're a bit strange really aren't they? and so abstract</u>
<u n="325" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I know yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0539">like didn't you say you got that that weird question?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0557">yeah it wasn't anything to do with law it was just like palm reading but it was really hard like a massive paragraph and the amount I know it's all meant to be how you deal with time pressure and stuff</u>
<u n="328" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0557">but it was about fifty questions in twelve minutes like massive paragraphs and then like and then the actual question itself was like four lines long</u>
<u n="330" who="S0539">mm</u>
<u n="331" who="S0557">it was just ridiculous</u>
<u n="332" who="S0539">well <anon type="place"/> uni when I was applying to there they said well I didn't know this but I wanted to go to the open day</u>
<u n="333" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0539">but it was fully booked I only found out about it like a month before it was</u>
<u n="335" who="S0557" trans="overlap">the postgrad open day?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0539">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0539">and they didn't like tell us it was happening on our course which was quite annoying when I'm like a student there</u>
<u n="339" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0539">and I can't even attend cos it was fully booked but erm because I <trunc>sa</trunc> I'd in expressed an interest in it</u>
<u n="341" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0539">they like emailed me to say erm like to give me the information on like the Powerpoints and stuff that they'd</u>
<u n="343" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0539">presented in the open day and</u>
<u n="345" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0539">they said that they don't even read your application so you spend like so long on your personal statement and everything like that</u>
<u n="347" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0539">and they don't even look at it it's all based on this psychometric test and they</u>
<u n="349" who="S0557">it shouldn't just be that that should be in addition to</u>
<u n="350" who="S0539" trans="overlap">I know well they justify it by saying that like they don't want to erm you know advantage students that come from like wealthier backgrounds but I don't understand <unclear>the <trunc>y</trunc></unclear></u>
<u n="351" who="S0557">no it should just be as a whole</u>
<u n="352" who="S0539">yeah surely students that come from</u>
<u n="353" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0539">more privileged backgrounds will be able to get people to answer the questions <vocal desc="laugh"/> for them you know?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0539">it should be based on the experience you have and things</u>
<u n="357" who="S0557" trans="overlap">it should be everything overall like you know? you might not be as strong as that but you might have loads of experience to talk about</u>
<u n="358" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0557">so cos I have quite a lot of experience I think but</u>
<u n="360" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0557">obviously not</u>
<u n="362" who="S0539">no I think the application itself and your personal statement is a pretty a good indicator rather than your answers on a test really</u>
<u n="363" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah it shows how you like you really want it and stuff and what you can offer to the course doesn't it?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0557">I dunno I think I'll do the masters for a year and that gives me a bit longer to decide what I'm actually gonna do</u>
<u n="366" who="S0539">mm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0557">yeah so erm what did you do this weekend did you say?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0539">oh I went to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="369" who="S0557">oh yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0539" trans="overlap">erm yeah with erm me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got the train down because</u>
<u n="371" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0539"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have moved there now cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was living in <anon type="place"/> but erm she met this guy from Holland on her year abroad in Vienna</u>
<u n="373" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0539">and he he was just like trying to get jobs in <anon type="place"/> but he couldn't so he managed to get one in <anon type="place"/> erm so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s like working for <anon type="place"/> now and they have like an office in <anon type="place"/> and</u>
<u n="375" who="S0557" trans="overlap">oh I applied to them</u>
<u n="376" who="S0539">oh did you?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0557">yeah and what was really good about them actually going off what we were saying</u>
<u n="378" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0557">erm they go off just psychometric tests they don't look at even if you're on like a third which I I don't I'm obviously not on they erm just go off your test and how er you er are in the interview so I don't know how that <trunc>in</trunc> how I feel about that but <unclear/></u>
<u n="380" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0557">but anyway carry on</u>
<u n="382" who="S0539">erm yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got her boyfriend to do the test actually <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0557">oh really <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0539">so erm yeah he managed to get a job in London so he's moved there now and</u>
<u n="385" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0539">I don't think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was that keen on moving to London actually but she sort of had to because he'd made the big journey over here and</u>
<u n="387" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0539">everything so she's moved down there now but she had like an amazing flat in Glasgow in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="389" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0539">it was so nice and she's still got like a nice flat but it's a lot smaller than the one in Glasgow</u>
<u n="391" who="S0557">well it's just not the same value for money is it?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0539">no not at all</u>
<u n="393" who="S0557">you'd literally get a studio flat in London for like eight hundred pounds a month</u>
<u n="394" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah yeah well she was paying I think like three fifty in Glasgow for a really nice <trunc>si</trunc> a really nice flat like right in the centre</u>
<u n="395" who="S0557" trans="overlap">how much was she paying sorry?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0539">three fifty I think</u>
<u n="397" who="S0557">and she was halving that</u>
<u n="398" who="S0539">with all the bills in no she wasn't halving it that was</u>
<u n="399" who="S0557">that was just what it was?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="401" who="S0557">no way really?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0539">her sharing it with someone else for three fifty each</u>
<u n="403" who="S0557" trans="overlap">oh I was gonna say <unclear/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0539">but erm but now she's in <anon type="place"/> I think she pays like seven hundred</u>
<u n="405" who="S0557">yeah <pause dur="short"/> each?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0539">yeah each for a one bed</u>
<u n="407" who="S0557" trans="overlap">that's ridiculous</u>
<u n="408" who="S0539">flat and quite a way out of the centre</u>
<u n="409" who="S0557" trans="overlap">is she happy there though?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0539">I think she is yeah I mean there's plenty going on all the time and stuff and she's with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> now which is good like</u>
<u n="411" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0539">they only used to see each other like every few months or whatever so</u>
<u n="413" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0539">yeah but she's still having to travel quite a lot up to <anon type="place"/> like</u>
<u n="415" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0539">we stayed at erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s on</u>
<u n="417" who="S0557">er <trunc>a</trunc> did you ever get get a taxi back to hers then? like how much was that?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah we oh <vocal desc="sigh"/> I can't remember I don't think it was too bad because they have this app called like Uber</u>
<u n="419" who="S0557">oh Uber yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah I'd never heard of it</u>
<u n="421" who="S0557">yeah it's meant to be really good yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0539">yeah so it's</u>
<u n="423" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I don't know what it is really it's just</u>
<u n="424" who="S0539" trans="overlap">well it's like people that have like cars and are free that evening I think and like they check them out</u>
<u n="425" who="S0557" trans="overlap">oh is it? I thought it was just like a an er just a different taxi service</u>
<u n="426" who="S0539" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="427" who="S0557">and like you can just do it on your phone and then you see who's available I didn't know it was like random people</u>
<u n="428" who="S0539" trans="overlap">I don't I don't know I think it is</u>
<u n="429" who="S0557" trans="overlap">is that safe?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0539">I don't <trunc>kn</trunc> <vocal desc="sigh"/> I I think it's random people anyway I mean they must like check them out</u>
<u n="431" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I dunno we'll we'll google it later</u>
<u n="432" who="S0539">I'm not sure so yeah we stayed at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s on Sunday night</u>
<u n="433" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0539">cos she's moved there too cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had to fly early to Glasgow on Monday morning so it wouldn't've really been fair for us to stay there</u>
<u n="435" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0539">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s living</u>
<u n="437" who="S0557">oh she flies there then?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0539">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0557">is that not a bit of a faff with like security and stuff? does?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0539">oh I think it's a lot quicker than getting the erm the train there so</u>
<u n="441" who="S0557">really though? cos you have to get there like two hours before then wait and then</u>
<u n="442" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah well I think when it's a short haul flight you don't have to be there as</u>
<u n="443" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0539">long before</u>
<u n="445" who="S0557">so erm what did you actually do in London then?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0539">erm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0557">you were there for two nights weren't you?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0539">yeah well the first night we arrived quite late cos the train was delayed</u>
<u n="449" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0539">erm so we just went round to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s and met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I think that was the first time I've actually met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0557">is he nice?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0539">yeah yeah he was really nice actually quite quiet but I guess he was a bit nervous and</u>
<u n="453" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0539">like English is his second language so that must be like a bit difficult</u>
<u n="455" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0539">but yeah he was really nice really friendly blew up our little blow up bed for us which was nice</u>
<u n="457" who="S0557" trans="overlap">ah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="458" who="S0539">erm and then we went out in <anon type="place"/> that night</u>
<u n="459" who="S0557">yeah I thought you were tagged in yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah which is like <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0539">erm yeah so that was good</u>
<u n="463" who="S0557">was it nice there?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0539">yeah it was really expensive though</u>
<u n="465" who="S0557">yeah I bet</u>
<u n="466" who="S0539">cost us like twenty pounds just to get into the club and then</u>
<u n="467" who="S0557">that's ridiculous</u>
<u n="468" who="S0539" trans="overlap">it was eight pounds for a single vodka and like mixer</u>
<u n="469" who="S0557" trans="overlap">that's like Ibiza prices isn't it?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0539">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="471" who="S0557">how can you <trunc>d</trunc>? you know? you can justify Ibiza cos you're paying for like big names but London</u>
<u n="472" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0557" trans="overlap">that's just</u>
<u n="474" who="S0539">it wasn't a particularly nice club either there was a club in Edinburgh that we always used to go to called the <anon type="place"/> and it's just <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0557">oh yeah</u>
<u n="476" who="S0539">underground and like really horrible and</u>
<u n="477" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="478" who="S0539">but that was like free entry and like really cheap drinks I think it cost us like</u>
<u n="479" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0539">two pounds for like a double vodka or something so you can sort of understand that but but yeah it was nice to like see them and catch up with them but it was so expensive I couldn't believe it I mean I know <anon type="place"/>'s expensive but</u>
<u n="481" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I just don't think it's worth it it's too fast paced and stuff you know what I mean? and if I'm like <unclear>staying in a</unclear> nice city like Manchester Liverpool Edinburgh even</u>
<u n="482" who="S0539">yeah yeah it's just so busy everywhere you go isn't it? and then on the Sunday</u>
<u n="483" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="484" who="S0539">we went to we woke up quite late actually we woke up at like half eleven <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then we went into <anon type="place"/> which was nice</u>
<u n="485" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah oh <unclear>I love it there</unclear></u>
<u n="486" who="S0539">we had lunch there <pause dur="short"/> and then we went we met up with erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="488" who="S0539">and went to the erm winter wonderland</u>
<u n="489" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="490" who="S0539">which was awful <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0557">why? I thought it was meant to be nice</u>
<u n="492" who="S0539" trans="overlap">it it <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="493" who="S0557">it's not like a full on thing I think it's just like <unclear/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0539" trans="overlap">no it was just absolutely crammed with people</u>
<u n="495" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0539">it was horrible and it's just like a massive cheap fairground really</u>
<u n="497" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0539">and I wasn't very impressed with it at all so</u>
<u n="499" who="S0557">did they like it? or not?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0539">no so then we went to erm <anon type="place"/> and like round there</u>
<u n="501" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0539">so we had like a few drinks there and then we went to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0539">which has like loads of gay bars and things and then</u>
<u n="505" who="S0557">I <trunc>di</trunc> I liked <anon type="place"/> in New York as well that was my favourite <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="506" who="S0539">yeah I think it's a bit different in London</u>
<u n="507" who="S0557">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0539" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0557">did you like it there?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0539">yeah it was fun erm we went in this one <trunc>ba</trunc>bar and we saw the you know the gay couple off Gogglebox?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0557">oh yeah were they in that bar?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0539">yeah they were like outside</u>
<u n="513" who="S0557"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0539">erm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0557">you should've gone and said hello</u>
<u n="516" who="S0539" trans="overlap">so yeah I know they're really <trunc>ni</trunc></u>
<u n="517" who="S0557"><unclear>cool</unclear></u>
<u n="518" who="S0539">well they seem really nice on Gogglebox</u>
<u n="519" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0539">erm and then we had an early night and then we booked to go to the erm <anon type="place"/> which is</u>
<u n="521" who="S0557" trans="overlap">oh I was gonna say you'd have to book probably wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0539"><trunc>y</trunc>yeah in the <anon type="place"/> we wanted to go to erm the <anon type="place"/> to begin with</u>
<u n="523" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0539">to erm</u>
<u n="525" who="S0557">I really wanna go to the <anon type="place"/> as well I think that's in the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0539">there's a reference there's a restaurant called <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="527" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> sorry that's what I'm on about</u>
<u n="528" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah I really want to go there</u>
<u n="530" who="S0539">yeah that's supposed to be really nice but that was all fully booked</u>
<u n="531" who="S0557"><unclear>oh yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="532" who="S0539">I think you could go at like six forty-five or something but</u>
<u n="533" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0539">we weren't willing to get up at like five <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0557"><unclear/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0539">in the morning to go so we erm</u>
<u n="537" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="538" who="S0539">we booked in the <anon type="place"/> instead</u>
<u n="539" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0539">it was really nice had eggs benedict</u>
<u n="541" who="S0557">ah</u>
<u n="542" who="S0539">and like a fruit smoothie it was delicious and then we went to the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0557"><trunc>h</trunc> was it expensive?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0539">erm I think the eggs benedict was like twelve quid</u>
<u n="545" who="S0557">oh wow</u>
<u n="546" who="S0539">and the fruit smoothie was like three fifty</u>
<u n="547" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="548" who="S0539">but it was really good</u>
<u n="549" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="550" who="S0539">and</u>
<u n="551" who="S0557">it's nice for a weekend though</u>
<u n="552" who="S0539">yeah a little treat</u>
<u n="553" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="554" who="S0539">and then we went to erm <pause dur="short"/> the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="555" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0539">which was good very weird though there was like one canvas that just had like a rip in the middle of it <vocal desc="laugh"/> and just think like yeah what's the point of that?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0557" trans="overlap">mm oh oh my gosh yeah</u>
<u n="558" who="S0539">it was bizarre</u>
<u n="559" who="S0557">I love erm natural history museum and the science museum</u>
<u n="560" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="561" who="S0557">in like Washington New York I er assume it would be like the same in <anon type="place"/> <unclear>won't it</unclear>?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0539">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I haven't been to the <anon type="place"/> one</u>
<u n="564" who="S0539">yeah it's <unclear>cool</unclear></u>
<u n="565" who="S0557" trans="overlap">oh actually yes I have been to the <anon type="place"/> one actually</u>
<u n="566" who="S0539">when did you go to <anon type="place"/> then?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0557">erm I went with school I think</u>
<u n="568" who="S0539">did you?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0557">yeah erm on a school trip don't know what it was for but I think it was English or something I can't remember <unclear>that was like</unclear> a couple of years ago</u>
<u n="570" who="S0539" trans="overlap">I went I went to the <anon type="place"/> with school</u>
<u n="571" who="S0557">did you?</u>
<u n="572" who="S0539">I went to see the Cirque du Soleil</u>
<u n="573" who="S0557">oh nice</u>
<u n="574" who="S0539">that was really good actually</u>
<u n="575" who="S0557">I'd love to see like a show like Wicked or something</u>
<u n="576" who="S0539">oh yeah Wicked's really good actually</u>
<u n="577" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear>that'd be good</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="578" who="S0539">me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went to see erm The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time</u>
<u n="579" who="S0557">what's that?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0539">last year it's erm a play about a boy with autism</u>
<u n="581" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="582" who="S0539">and he like finds this dog that's been killed in his backyard</u>
<u n="583" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah I wouldn't like that</u>
<u n="584" who="S0539">with like a fork through the middle of it</u>
<u n="585" who="S0557">yeah no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="586" who="S0539">no it's <trunc>n</trunc> it's not that graphic</u>
<u n="587" who="S0557"><unclear/></u>
<u n="588" who="S0539">it's just it's really good really clever</u>
<u n="589" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0539">I really enjoyed the book so I was thinking like the play might not be quite as good but</u>
<u n="591" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0539">it was really really good I loved it</u>
<u n="593" who="S0557" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="594" who="S0539">and then we went to Gordon Ramsay's restaurant that was amazing</u>
<u n="595" who="S0557">I love erm do you watch Masterchef?</u>
<u n="596" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="597" who="S0557">my <trunc>paren</trunc> me and my parents have really got into Masterchef Australia we've been watching it like every night whatever erm Marco Pierre White was like the mentor the past week I really wanna go to his restaurant <unclear>as</unclear></u>
<u n="598" who="S0539" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="599" who="S0557">I just find Gordon Ramsay like shouts too much like surely if you go to a restaurant you don't want him shouting in the kitchen cos you can hear him can't you?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0539" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well he's he's not in</u>
<u n="601" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><unclear>you're here for a relaxing time</unclear></u>
<u n="602" who="S0539">he's not actually in the restaurant unfortunately</u>
<u n="603" who="S0557">well he'll be in one of them surely? like the <anon type="place"/> one doesn't he actually <unclear>cook</unclear> there?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0539" trans="overlap">I think he like pops in from time to time but</u>
<u n="605" who="S0557">oh does he?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0539">yeah he's like trained them all yeah he doesn't come across and shout at you unfortunately I don't really like him himself</u>
<u n="607" who="S0557"><vocal desc="cough"/> mm</u>
<u n="608" who="S0539">but his food is really good</u>
<u n="609" who="S0557">what did you have? was it like is it super expensive?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0539">oh yeah</u>
<u n="611" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0539">it wasn't like mega mega money but yeah it was quite a lot</u>
<u n="613" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="614" who="S0539">I had like this seven course tasting menu so I think we had</u>
<u n="615" who="S0557">seven courses?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0539">yeah we had like <trunc>l</trunc> oh they were only like really tiny though</u>
<u n="617" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="618" who="S0539">had like lobster and duck and oh and then they brought these truffles out at the end which were like smoking what's it called? the like dry ice stuff which is quite cool</u>
<u n="619" who="S0557" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="620" who="S0539">and then erm we had like this chocolate dessert yeah it came out as like this big erm like chocolate sphere thing</u>
<u n="621" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="622" who="S0539">and then you got this like erm liquid chocolate sauce stuff</u>
<u n="623" who="S0557">oh wow</u>
<u n="624" who="S0539">like pour on top and then it like all dissolved it was really fancy</u>
<u n="625" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah I would love that I think like for a special occasion just my parents don't really like erm spending a lot cos we eat out so much we can only afford to like</u>
<u n="626" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0557">you know we can't do that all the time but yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0539">yeah well we don't eat out very much so</u>
<u n="629" who="S0557">I see yeah special</u>
<u n="630" who="S0539">it was a special little treat</u>
<u n="631" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="632" who="S0539">I don't think I'll be going back again any time soon though unfortunately</u>
<u n="633" who="S0557" trans="overlap">might do that for like graduation or something that'd be nice</u>
<u n="634" who="S0539">oh yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0557" trans="overlap">what shall we do for graduation? I wanna do something special</u>
<u n="636" who="S0539">I don't know there aren't like that many nice places to eat in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="637" who="S0557">well no I'd maybe we could go away for the weekend to celebrate</u>
<u n="638" who="S0539">yeah that'd be nice</u>
<u n="639" who="S0557">erm I don't know where to go <unclear/></u>
<u n="640" who="S0539">for my graduation we went to erm the <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="641" who="S0557">I thought you went to the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0539">yeah we went to the <anon type="place"/> the night before</u>
<u n="643" who="S0557">oh yeah</u>
<u n="644" who="S0539">and then we went to the <anon type="place"/> the day of our graduation</u>
<u n="645" who="S0557" trans="overlap">ah where did your parents stay that night?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0539">we all stayed in the erm <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="647" who="S0557">ah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0539">which was oh it was awful actually</u>
<u n="649" who="S0557">was it?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0539">cos it's it was like quite expensive</u>
<u n="651" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="652" who="S0539">and erm woke up at I er well I couldn't sleep actually I don't know why I was just like</u>
<u n="653" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="654" who="S0539">really nervous and excited</u>
<u n="655" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="656" who="S0539">and erm woke up to this really loud thudding noise on the ceiling I'm like what is that? and it was like the gym above like someone was on the running machine and it was so loud</u>
<u n="657" who="S0557" trans="overlap">no way <unclear/></u>
<u n="658" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah oh it was absolutely awful</u>
<u n="659" who="S0557">did you complain?</u>
<u n="660" who="S0539">yeah we did cos my my mum couldn't sleep because of it as well so</u>
<u n="661" who="S0557">what did they say?</u>
<u n="662" who="S0539">they just moved us to like another room</u>
<u n="663" who="S0557">what? at like five A M?</u>
<u n="664" who="S0539">it was like three in the morning and just constant for hours</u>
<u n="665" who="S0557" trans="overlap">you moved at three A M?</u>
<u n="666" who="S0539">oh no no we complained the next day</u>
<u n="667" who="S0557">oh I see</u>
<u n="668" who="S0539">and then they moved us <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah they just gave us like a complimentary bottle of wine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="669" who="S0557" trans="overlap">it's ridiculous cos you could like drop like weights on the floor or anything do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I don't know why they didn't have the gym at like the bottom of the hotel really</u>
<u n="671" who="S0557" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="672" who="S0539">no that was really annoying but the meal was really nice at the <anon type="place"/> my dad hated it though</u>
<u n="673" who="S0557" trans="overlap">ah why? what did he have?</u>
<u n="674" who="S0539" trans="overlap">well it was just we had like the taster menu again</u>
<u n="675" who="S0557">yeah so</u>
<u n="676" who="S0539"><unclear/></u>
<u n="677" who="S0557">does he quite like simple?</u>
<u n="678" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="679" who="S0557">yeah can imagine him being like that</u>
<u n="680" who="S0539" trans="overlap">he just yeah he just likes meat potatoes and veg</u>
<u n="681" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0539">like nice massive portions mountains of mashed potato</u>
<u n="683" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="684" who="S0539">but erm yeah he wasn't that impressed</u>
<u n="685" who="S0557">oh</u>
<u n="686" who="S0539">but me and my mum really enjoyed it <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0557">I'd love to be able to cook <unclear>like that it's so good</unclear></u>
<u n="688" who="S0539" trans="overlap">it was nice yeah so when?</u>
<u n="689" who="S0557">I'm looking forward to tonight's food</u>
<u n="690" who="S0539">yeah it should be good</u>
<u n="691" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="692" who="S0539">have you decided what you're having?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0557">I think so well there's erm let me just get the menu up <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna have well there's the confit chicken terrine but I'm not really sure if he said it's like hard harder than a pâté</u>
<u n="694" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah yeah it is</u>
<u n="695" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I've never had it before but the meat</u>
<u n="696" who="S0539">it's just like meat in like like solidified it sounds like really weird it's nice though</u>
<u n="697" who="S0557">is it? mm</u>
<u n="698" who="S0539">I think you'd like it I don't know you're funny with meat though</u>
<u n="699" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I think I might <trunc>prefe</trunc> yeah I might get the honey roasted parsnip soup with truffle oil cos I love truffles are you getting the salmon or the beef then? carpaccio what is that?</u>
<u n="700" who="S0539">erm that's like raw beef it's quite nice</u>
<u n="701" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="702" who="S0539">I can't go down <pause dur="short"/> I think I might get the turkey actually</u>
<u n="703" who="S0557">that's for main though what are you getting for starter?</u>
<u n="704" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh for starter I think I'll get the salmon yeah or the beef</u>
<u n="705" who="S0557" trans="overlap">salmon? and then turkey?</u>
<u n="706" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="707" who="S0557">I might get risotto</u>
<u n="708" who="S0539">and then I'm gonna get the chocolate thing for pudding</u>
<u n="709" who="S0557">yeah chocolate mousse honeycomb ice cream that sounds amazing</u>
<u n="710" who="S0539">mm</u>
<u n="711" who="S0557">although cheese I love cheese and biscuits</u>
<u n="712" who="S0539">yeah but you can get cheese anywhere</u>
<u n="713" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="714" who="S0539">they will be nice though</u>
<u n="715" who="S0557" trans="overlap">had mousse last night though</u>
<u n="716" who="S0539">did you?</u>
<u n="717" who="S0557">yeah did I show you the photo?</u>
<u n="718" who="S0539">no</u>
<u n="719" who="S0557">it's like erm</u>
<u n="720" who="S0539">oh yeah you got pudding as well yeah</u>
<u n="721" who="S0557" trans="overlap">ah yeah it was like chocolate brownie with peanut butter and salted caramel ice cream this is like salted caramel sauce homemade chocolate and a comb with mousse in</u>
<u n="722" who="S0539">mm that looks good</u>
<u n="723" who="S0557">so good</u>
<u n="724" who="S0539">I haven't eaten there in ages actually</u>
<u n="725" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0539">it does look really nice so is your friend seeing anyone at the moment?</u>
<u n="727" who="S0557"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="728" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="729" who="S0557">yeah yeah she's erm she's been with him for like four or five years I just get the impression that he's a bit sort of controlling</u>
<u n="730" who="S0539">oh is he?</u>
<u n="731" who="S0557">yeah like erm on what she like you know? she can't even have a Facebook account which is fair enough cos I mean Facebook does cause a lot of trouble but it's not for him to say do you know what I mean? <unclear/></u>
<u n="732" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="733" who="S0557">erm so yeah</u>
<u n="734" who="S0539">no that's not very good is it?</u>
<u n="735" who="S0557">no</u>
<u n="736" who="S0539">I think yeah if he if she cheated on him then maybe you could understand it but</u>
<u n="737" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="738" who="S0539">it's a bit odd so when's erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s wedding?</u>
<u n="739" who="S0557"><unclear/></u>
<u n="740" who="S0539">have they sorted it all out yet?</u>
<u n="741" who="S0557">twenty-ninth</u>
<u n="742" who="S0539">twenty-ninth of?</u>
<u n="743" who="S0557">December</u>
<u n="744" who="S0539">oh really? well that's really soon</u>
<u n="745" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah I know I really don't know what to wear because I was gonna buy a new dress for the occasion but I mean <pause dur="short"/> but I mean you know? it's a lot of money just for one day and I really can't afford to with it being just after Christmas</u>
<u n="746" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="747" who="S0557">so I think can you wear black to a wedding?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0539">yeah I guess oh</u>
<u n="749" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I just I didn't I thought you were meant to wear colours cos I might wear this or my blazer</u>
<u n="750" who="S0539" trans="overlap">you could</u>
<u n="751" who="S0557">with my black dress I wore for the law ball <unclear/></u>
<u n="752" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah that'd be nice</u>
<u n="753" who="S0557">with my fake Valentino shoes</u>
<u n="754" who="S0539">yeah if you like dress it up a bit with a nice necklace or something I'm sure that'd be fine</u>
<u n="755" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah I don't wanna spend money just to</u>
<u n="756" who="S0539">I need to get a dress for my mum and dad's wedding <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="757" who="S0557">oh yeah what are you gonna wear to that then?</u>
<u n="758" who="S0539">I don't really know yet <pause dur="short"/> it's like typical whenever you need a dress you can never find it yeah that's really nice</u>
<u n="759" who="S0557">so er is that alright then?</u>
<u n="760" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="761" who="S0557">okay and I'll wear the shoes I wore to the law ball</u>
<u n="762" who="S0539">yeah yeah I don't really know what to wear at all</u>
<u n="763" who="S0557">are you gonna go like proper fancy?</u>
<u n="764" who="S0539">well I'd like to wear like a nice dress but I don't think my mum's gonna wear a wedding dress or anything</u>
<u n="765" who="S0557">no</u>
<u n="766" who="S0539">she'll just wear like a nice eveningy dress</u>
<u n="767" who="S0557">I'll wear erm <pause dur="short"/> those shoes or I could wear this dress which do you prefer?</u>
<u n="768" who="S0539">no they're both nice I don't know</u>
<u n="769" who="S0557">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah will she wear like cream or?</u>
<u n="770" who="S0539">I don't know</u>
<u n="771" who="S0557">probably not white cos obviously</u>
<u n="772" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="773" who="S0557"><unclear/></u>
<u n="774" who="S0539">no I think she's quite open to colours really</u>
<u n="775" who="S0557">ah</u>
<u n="776" who="S0539">she wants to go on like a crash diet first though so</u>
<u n="777" who="S0557" trans="overlap">does she?</u>
<u n="778" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="779" who="S0539">I don't think she'll be buying a dress soon although it's only February it's not that long away</u>
<u n="780" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah you'll have to go shopping with her</u>
<u n="781" who="S0539">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="782" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I need a coffee to wake me up a bit</u>
<u n="783" who="S0539">yeah I'm feeling quite sleepy I don't drink tea or coffee though that's the only problem</u>
<u n="784" who="S0557">I think I think I'm like allergic to caffeine cos it makes me really ill</u>
<u n="785" who="S0539" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="cough"/> does it? like how?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0557" trans="overlap">like I love it I love coffee but I just get really headachey and feel like car sick with it and</u>
<u n="787" who="S0539">mm</u>
<u n="788" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="789" who="S0539">my mum gets really bad headaches actually</u>
<u n="790" who="S0557" trans="overlap">but I love it</u>
<u n="791" who="S0539">she has to have like a coffee to get rid of the headache <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="792" who="S0557">what?</u>
<u n="793" who="S0539">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="794" who="S0557" trans="overlap">that's a bit strange <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="795" who="S0539">it's not very good really</u>
<u n="796" who="S0557">that is really weird</u>
<u n="797" who="S0539">so where's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> getting married at?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0557">erm <anon type="place"/> church and then the reception's at <anon type="place"/> green</u>
<u n="799" who="S0539">ah</u>
<u n="800" who="S0557">so that'll be really nice cos it's a nice er golf club isn't it? <unclear>it's a fancy one</unclear></u>
<u n="801" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0557">I love it there</u>
<u n="803" who="S0539">oh that'll be nice</u>
<u n="804" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="805" who="S0539">yeah I wonder if erm if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'ll still get married this year or not</u>
<u n="806" who="S0557" trans="overlap">oh yeah I personally like obviously I'd prefer to before I had a baby but I wouldn't while I was pregnant you'd wanna be like your <trunc>be</trunc> looking your best wouldn't you? and</u>
<u n="807" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="808" who="S0557">I dunno I'd feel a bit</u>
<u n="809" who="S0539">yeah I know what you mean</u>
<u n="810" who="S0557">I'd do it afterwards I think</u>
<u n="811" who="S0539">oh my god I can't believe it a guy in my year his girlfriend's had a baby and they didn't even know she was pregnant <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="812" who="S0557">yeah that's insane you find you hear about that a lot don't you?</u>
<u n="813" who="S0539">I don't know</u>
<u n="814" who="S0557">like you go to the toilet and then just pop out a baby</u>
<u n="815" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="816" who="S0557">like could you imagine?</u>
<u n="817" who="S0539" trans="overlap">I think it's like quite rare</u>
<u n="818" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="819" who="S0539">but yeah it's in the news a bit</u>
<u n="820" who="S0557">I feel like I'd know I I feel like I'd have some kind of inkling surely?</u>
<u n="821" who="S0539" trans="overlap">I know it's hard to believe really isn't it?</u>
<u n="822" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="823" who="S0539">but I mean they'd they'd just got a house together and they're engaged and everything so I think it was like a welcome surprise but</u>
<u n="824" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah how long have they been together for?</u>
<u n="825" who="S0539">oh er like just over a year so not that long yeah</u>
<u n="826" who="S0557" trans="overlap">so not long so yeah I feel like obviously I was with someone for seven years but I it annoys me when people are together for like six months and then jump into everything and then they wonder why it doesn't work out</u>
<u n="827" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="828" who="S0557">but I mean I I <trunc>c</trunc> I I don't think there's like a one set time for everyone but <unclear/></u>
<u n="829" who="S0539" trans="overlap">no no but at the same time there's like no need to rush into things I don't think</u>
<u n="830" who="S0557" trans="overlap">do you know what I mean? cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like they rushed into it they got like they lived together and everything and</u>
<u n="831" who="S0539">why? how long have they been together for?</u>
<u n="832" who="S0557">maybe like two years</u>
<u n="833" who="S0539">mm that's not long is it?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0557" trans="overlap">but they've they've had a <trunc>ba</trunc> they've got a baby that's almost a year old</u>
<u n="835" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="836" who="S0557">and they're living together and stuff I don't know I mean they seem happy but</u>
<u n="837" who="S0539">yeah well it works out sometimes</u>
<u n="838" who="S0557">I just feel like I like I didn't show much like he's done the honeymoon period for like six months do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="839" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="840" who="S0557">I just think people don't know the real <trunc>s</trunc>selves</u>
<u n="841" who="S0539">yeah well looking after <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has definitely proven to me that I don't want children any time soon <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="842" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="843" who="S0539">like it's really nice looking after them but it's lovely giving them back again</u>
<u n="844" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I kind of don't know if I want them ever</u>
<u n="845" who="S0539">really?</u>
<u n="846" who="S0557">well I feel like sometimes I do like when I think of names I'm like oh that'd be kind of nice</u>
<u n="847" who="S0539"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="848" who="S0557">but they just annoy me</u>
<u n="849" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="850" who="S0557">like fitting in with school the boring school routine like every morning you can't just have a spontaneous weekend away and just takes the excitement out of everything</u>
<u n="851" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="852" who="S0557">it's just boring and mundane like I feel like there's a lot of good things out of it you know it's obviously a very rewarding experience but</u>
<u n="853" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="854" who="S0557">I don't know</u>
<u n="855" who="S0539">no I definitely don't want children yet I want to go travelling and things I know you can take like children with you obviously but it's a lot harder</u>
<u n="856" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah not really well can you imagine in the heat and stuff them whining? I can't deal with that</u>
<u n="857" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah oh did you get that video I sent you of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> reading?</u>
<u n="858" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="859" who="S0539">she's such a cutie</u>
<u n="860" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="861" who="S0539">yeah when we were on holiday</u>
<u n="862" who="S0557">see it is nice like in that sense isn't it?</u>
<u n="863" who="S0539">yeah when we were on holiday she was just like recognising like word <trunc>l</trunc></u>
<u n="864" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="865" who="S0539">the word letters and things</u>
<u n="866" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="867" who="S0539">erm but yeah it's crazy how fast she's</u>
<u n="868" who="S0557" trans="overlap">would she <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="869" who="S0539">no no no it's crazy how fast she's come on</u>
<u n="870" who="S0557">ah</u>
<u n="871" who="S0539"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s like the top of her class for reading and everything</u>
<u n="872" who="S0557" trans="overlap">really? oh wow</u>
<u n="873" who="S0539">yeah yeah she's a little brainbox I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s more of the comedian there</u>
<u n="874" who="S0557">yeah she is like the class clown isn't she?</u>
<u n="875" who="S0539"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="876" who="S0557">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="877" who="S0539">I don't know how she'll be getting on at school on her first day I like took her in cos I we were down there which was nice</u>
<u n="878" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="879" who="S0539">and erm straight away she was like out in the play yard bit and there was like this big sandpit filled with water and she like persuaded her little friend to start splashing in it so <vocal desc="laugh"/> like</u>
<u n="880" who="S0557" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="881" who="S0539">they got covered in water before they'd even started the school day it was quite funny</u>
<u n="882" who="S0557"><unclear/> that sounds like her doesn't it?</u>
<u n="883" who="S0539">yeah they've sent us over a massive Christmas list of everything they want</u>
<u n="884" who="S0557">what?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="886" who="S0557">isn't that a bit cheeky?</u>
<u n="887" who="S0539"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I thought so</u>
<u n="888" who="S0557">cos I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for her wedding invite said I know this seems to be the thing at the minute asking for money towards a holiday</u>
<u n="889" who="S0539">really?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0557">and I think that's really cheeky</u>
<u n="891" who="S0539"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="892" who="S0557">like and and also like have you seen in America they <trunc>ha</trunc> they go round with the barcode scanners?</u>
<u n="893" who="S0539">oh yeah</u>
<u n="894" who="S0557" trans="overlap">like you put they put it on your list or whatever what's it called? there's a name for it</u>
<u n="895" who="S0539">oh I don't know but yeah I know what you mean</u>
<u n="896" who="S0557" trans="overlap">you know what I mean? and I think that's rude to let you</u>
<u n="897" who="S0539">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="898" who="S0557">I I think it's just what I I dunno I'm not gonna contribute to their holiday like if they can't afford to have a holiday then don't get married like</u>
<u n="899" who="S0539">no you shouldn't request unless it's like erm money towards charity or something instead of a gift you can sort of understand that but</u>
<u n="900" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear>but no</unclear> I personally I I've just got them a voucher</u>
<u n="901" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="902" who="S0557">erm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="903" who="S0539">yeah well I think that's fair enough</u>
<u n="904" who="S0557" trans="overlap">so yeah</u>
<u n="905" who="S0539">I don't I don't think my mum and dad will be asking for any wedding gifts at all</u>
<u n="906" who="S0557">oh it's polite though to get something isn't it?</u>
<u n="907" who="S0539">mm they're all there now aren't they?</u>
<u n="908" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><unclear>what do you think they'd want? a voucher</unclear>?</u>
<u n="909" who="S0539">a log basket probably <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="910" who="S0557">where on earth are you gonna get that from? you'll have to google maybe Amazon they have everything</u>
<u n="911" who="S0539">well <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> like sent <unclear/> but we have them like next to the fire so it needs to like look quite nice</u>
<u n="912" who="S0557">oh yeah</u>
<u n="913" who="S0539">so she sent us this one that was like</u>
<u n="914" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I don't know where we got ours from actually</u>
<u n="915" who="S0539">she sent us this one that was just like a black plastic bucket <vocal desc="laugh"/> which was</u>
<u n="916" who="S0557">what?</u>
<u n="917" who="S0539">yeah and then this one that was like made out of fabric</u>
<u n="918" who="S0557" trans="overlap">you want a nice wooden one like you seen in the in the <anon type="place"/> and stuff</u>
<u n="919" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah well we've had a wicker one for ages and it's been really good but</u>
<u n="920" who="S0557">yeah but ours is wicker I think</u>
<u n="921" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="922" who="S0557">it looks really like modern</u>
<u n="923" who="S0539">but it's starting to break away now it's very sad</u>
<u n="924" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><unclear/> my mum was saying her friend <vocal desc="laugh"/> her friend who works with her husband the first year they were married he got her a a waste paper bin</u>
<u n="925" who="S0539"><vocal desc="laugh"/> god</u>
<u n="926" who="S0557">and a mop</u>
<u n="927" who="S0539">how romantic</u>
<u n="928" who="S0557">and he was like oh it's for the house you know? you said you wanted one and she was like yeah for the house but not for me</u>
<u n="929" who="S0539"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's awful</u>
<u n="930" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I would I would just be like what is this?</u>
<u n="931" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="932" who="S0557">take your present back then</u>
<u n="933" who="S0539">well my dad doesn't really do presents I think my mum just buys herself something and</u>
<u n="934" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="935" who="S0539">then he gives it to her</u>
<u n="936" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I just find men really hard to <trunc>pa</trunc> like buy for</u>
<u n="937" who="S0539">mm</u>
<u n="938" who="S0557">mum's fine like I'll get her skincare or something but dad I just he doesn't use anything like we got him this really expensive like eighty pound leather like bag for work and it'd be really nice you know? to take his work in and stuff</u>
<u n="939" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="940" who="S0557">and he just takes it in like erm plastic bags</u>
<u n="941" who="S0539">well I think yeah men are just a lot more practical aren't they?</u>
<u n="942" who="S0557" trans="overlap">doesn't appreciate it yeah <unclear>mm</unclear></u>
<u n="943" who="S0539">yeah I never know what to get my brother he's a hard one to buy for got no idea at all <pause dur="short"/> he's like asked for a leather jacket but I don't think I could really afford a leather jacket</u>
<u n="944" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah again that's cheeky like assuming</u>
<u n="945" who="S0539">yeah well that I think that was more</u>
<u n="946" who="S0557" trans="overlap">unless you look on Asos in the</u>
<u n="947" who="S0539">it was more <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> than him really</u>
<u n="948" who="S0557">oh was it?</u>
<u n="949" who="S0539">but then I think they're they asked what we wanted as like an afterthought I <trunc>th</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think they're getting me like a coat from Zara</u>
<u n="950" who="S0557">oh yeah</u>
<u n="951" who="S0539">for my birthday and Christmas</u>
<u n="952" who="S0557" trans="overlap">did you send them it?</u>
<u n="953" who="S0539">yeah so that'll be quite handy I still haven't</u>
<u n="954" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I wouldn't be like just in case like I was planning on spending twenty quid on <unclear/> do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="955" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="956" who="S0557">I'd find that awkward</u>
<u n="957" who="S0539">well they've got me pretty awful presents for the past</u>
<u n="958" who="S0557">oh yeah obviously yeah</u>
<u n="959" who="S0539" trans="overlap">ten years so I think I</u>
<u n="960" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="961" who="S0539">deserve a jacket last year was awful I opened it up and I'd got these pink fluffy earmuffs with sequins all over it I was like oh my god what do I say?</u>
<u n="962" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="963" who="S0539">I was like oh thanks and then I think I sort of like just put it erm on like the side of the carpet</u>
<u n="964" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="965" who="S0539">next to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s presents and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like picked them up and she was like oh mummy are these for me? and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like yeah I think so like they <vocal desc="laugh"/> they just they were obviously</u>
<u n="966" who="S0557" trans="overlap">would you not know that she wrapped it for you?</u>
<u n="967" who="S0539">well I don't they were obviously more suited to a younger</u>
<u n="968" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="969" who="S0539">child like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="970" who="S0557">she just got you that?</u>
<u n="971" who="S0539">oh and some other things but yeah that they were the <trunc>o</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> that was the present that really stood out</u>
<u n="972" who="S0557"><unclear/></u>
<u n="973" who="S0539">it was awful</u>
<u n="974" who="S0557">and my nan used to go to the market and get me like plastic battery operated airplanes and helicopters</u>
<u n="975" who="S0539"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="976" who="S0557">I was just like I was like</u>
<u n="977" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="978" who="S0539"><unclear/></u>
<u n="979" who="S0557">my mum used to hate my nan's gifts it was so funny she used to give them to charity</u>
<u n="980" who="S0539">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="981" who="S0557">and then nan used to make it really obvious that she didn't like <unclear>them</unclear></u>
<u n="982" who="S0539">did she?</u>
<u n="983" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="984" who="S0539">why? what would she be like?</u>
<u n="985" who="S0557">she'd just be like have you got the receipt? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="986" who="S0539">ah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="987" who="S0557">so</u>
<u n="988" who="S0539"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying she bought her erm boyfriend's parents</u>
<u n="989" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="990" who="S0539">like she spent ages trying to find like a nice present in John Lewis</u>
<u n="991" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="992" who="S0539">she got them like this like posh candle thing</u>
<u n="993" who="S0557">ah <unclear/></u>
<u n="994" who="S0539">and then erm like this set of like pâté and like chutney and stuff she thought like surely they'll use that?</u>
<u n="995" who="S0557" trans="overlap">oh that's nice mm yeah</u>
<u n="996" who="S0539">and then anyway a <trunc>f</trunc> a couple of months later I think they're building their own house or something so they were moving out of their other house</u>
<u n="997" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="998" who="S0539">and erm her boyfriend returned home with like all this pâté and chutney that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had bought them</u>
<u n="999" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0539">and erm he was like oh yeah they they they weren't really using it so they thought it might come in handy for us like that's so rude <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1001" who="S0557">did she say you do know I bought that then?</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0539">well yeah I think like they knew it was her like</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0557">why would you give it back?</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0539">I know to the person that bought it you</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0557">unless they forgot</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0539">no no they can't've forgotten</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0557">you wouldn't do that though would you?</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0539">I'm like pâté and chutney it's quite a <trunc>n</trunc></u>
<u n="1009" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah that's a nice gift yeah</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0539">yeah and they could've always given it to someone else</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0557"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1012" who="S0539">and now she's like I don't have a clue what to get them like</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0557">why doesn't? yeah she should just ask him and get er him to ask or</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0557">something I used to do all the shopping for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s family</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0539">did you?</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0557">and I enjoyed it but like he just he just never did it so I was like fine I'll do it cos it's a joint thing anyway so I just did it anyway</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0557">and then he was like all offended cos they loved it and like he wasn't getting any credit and I was like well you didn't help in the first place</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0539" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0557">so</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0539">oh I still haven't got a birthday card off my brother and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1023" who="S0557">really?</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0557">that's awful like if you didn't give them one or something</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0539" trans="overlap">I know yeah</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0557">all hell would break loose</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0539">I know I sent we sent them a Christmas card to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0539">they'll probably've received that but they still haven't sent my birthday card</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0557">that's really bad</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0539">yeah I thought so it would've <trunc>b</trunc>been nice for <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to make me like a little card</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0539">I think they'd've quite enjoyed doing that too <pause dur="short"/> oh well</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0557" whoConfidence="low">oh well it's not worth it anyway</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0539" whoConfidence="low">it'll be nice to see them at Christmas what are you doing for Christmas?</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0557">I'm going to the same place I did last year the <anon type="place"/> like it's a nice chain the <anon type="place"/> it's not quite as nice as the <anon type="place"/> but it's a nice hotel chain near <anon type="place"/> it's not the nicest area but erm on nothing's open on Christmas Day so we literally just stay in the hotel anyway</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0557">erm we're there for three nights like we got a good deal and like all the food's included so there's like afternoon tea on arrival and like carols</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0539">ah</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0557"><unclear/> evening <unclear/> buffet and then there's obviously a fry up in the morning</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0557">er like a four course Christmas lunch and then like cheese and crackers and stuff</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0539">oh that'll be nice</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0557" trans="overlap">and then on Boxing Day I'll go to the gym like I did last year and like erm get a massage and go in the spa</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0539">oh lovely</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0557">erm and we'll <trunc>g</trunc> walk round the grounds and stuff so it's really nice nicer than being at home to be honest</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0539">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0557">cos I have such a small family but it's nice for you with the girls isn't it?</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0557">but I don't have that so</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0539"><vocal desc="cough"/> well I don't it's lovely being at home but my mum just gets so stressed over Christmas dinner</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> dad did he got up at half four last <unclear>the other</unclear> year</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh my god I mean it's just it's like any other meal really like there's no need to get</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0557" trans="overlap">there is a lot to do but yeah</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0539">so stressed out about it it just sort of spoils <vocal desc="laugh"/> the day really</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I know that's why I insist on going away now because it was quite cold actually and we spent all that time</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0539">ah</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0557">and I was just like it's there's no point really it's nice to be waited on</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0557">we were gonna go back to New York like cos we er got a good deal but</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0539">did you go to New York at Christmas then the last time you were? oh wow</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah like actually this was like a couple of years ago</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0539">I've always wanted to go to New York</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0557">two thousand and eleven or something?</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0557">something like that two thousand and ten maybe it was quite a long time ago</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0539">mm</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0557">but it was just amazing we went to the Hilton on Christmas Day</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0539">oh wow</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0557">erm and ice skating and stuff Central Park</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0539">ah lovely</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0557">but erm yeah I'll do it again</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0539" trans="overlap">and was it really? was it really cold?</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0557">there was a snowstorm so like all the cars were covered up completely</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0539">oh wow</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0557">and we couldn't go to the Statue of Liberty that's why I wanna go back cos we didn't get to do quite a lot of stuff cos the weather</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1079" who="S0557" trans="overlap">all the subways were covered in ice</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0539"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to live in New York actually</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0557">really?</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0539">for quite a long time she just said it was so cold</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0557" trans="overlap">oh wow</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0539">like you just couldn't warm up</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0539">in the winters obviously</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0557">yeah it's boiling during the summer it's like proper seasonal there</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0557">I like that having actual seasons</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0557">whereas it's just all cold here</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0539">and how much were flights to New York?</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0557">well <vocal desc="sigh"/> got we got a good deal <vocal desc="sigh"/> looking for this year but when we went it was probably about four hundred five hundred</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0539">mm</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0557">it's quite a lot isn't it?</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0539">yeah it is quite expensive</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0557" trans="overlap">that's why I was like kicking myself because it was fifteen hundred for a four star hotel right by the Empire State and flights</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0539">wow</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0557">for like four nights this year but obviously travel with like the whole ISIS thing isn't <unclear>great</unclear></u>
<u n="1100" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah it is a bit</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0557">so</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0539">dodgy I was a bit weird about going to <anon type="place"/> actually which <trunc>s</trunc> which sounds a bit silly but I guess it is</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0557">well yeah</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0539">a likely spot for an attack</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0557" trans="overlap">there's loads going on like there isn't there?</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><unclear>you hear of something</unclear> every other week</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0539">yeah like the building we went for breakfast in is like one of the really high  rise buildings so</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0539">they have like security scanners and</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0539">you know? like walk through scanning machines which is good</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0539">like it makes you feel a bit more secure</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0539"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s going with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> actually to see erm The Nutcracker in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1117" who="S0557" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0539">just before <trunc>Chris</trunc></u>
<u n="1119" who="S0557" trans="overlap">just <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0539">yeah just <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think it was I <trunc>d</trunc> I don't know why <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s not going really it seems</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0557">she's probably quite young <unclear>she'll probably make</unclear></u>
<u n="1122" who="S0539" trans="overlap">I think she goes to the cinema and stuff and she went to the theatre with us when</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0557">did she?</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0539">it was funny actually <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1125" who="S0557" trans="overlap">does she not get really bored though?</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0539">no no she was fine actually</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0557" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0539">yeah we went to see a play and erm it was a bit of an odd play actually it wasn't really for children it was like marketed towards children but it was a bit scary</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0539">and they had like people like coming up the aisles like going over to the children and stuff</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0557"><unclear>god</unclear></u>
<u n="1132" who="S0539">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was terrified <vocal desc="laugh"/> she like jumped from her seat like over to her dad's seat</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0539">and left little <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to like face the baddie like</u>
<u n="1135" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1136" who="S0539"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was fine she just sat there like sipping on her drink <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1137" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah I can imagine her yeah I can imagine her doing that</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0539">it was funny</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0557"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1140" who="S0539">but yeah they were both really good</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would probably be like hi</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0539"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah she was fine</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0539"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was terrified yeah it was really scary I was a bit scared actually</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0539">a bit creepy</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0557">well I find that with erm what was I watching the other day? oh you know Wallace and Gromit? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1148" who="S0539">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1149" who="S0557">I was watching that and it's actually really dark like I didn't really realise</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0557">I haven't seen it in a while for like for children to watch it</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0557"><unclear>just just a bit</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1154" who="S0539">yeah a few like children shows are like that</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0557" trans="overlap">Disney movies they're quite dark messages Disney movies</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0539">yeah I really want to see Krampus at the cinema that's like a Christmassy film</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I'm sorry but Christmas is a joyous time not for a horror movie</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0539" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but it looks good I think we should go see it</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><unclear/> no <unclear/></u>
<u n="1160" who="S0539">yeah it'll be good</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0557" trans="overlap">it's not for me at all</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0539">you're such a little scaredy cat</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0557">I hate horror movies literally watched House of Wax when I was like twelve</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0539" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1165" who="S0557">and I still have nightmares about it I really do not like it</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0557">I find torture like chopping off limbs so unnecessary</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1169" who="S0557">like the James Bond movies have just got so violent there's no point like</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0557">I just don't get how people can do that to other people it's horrible</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0557">hate it</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0539">no I used to be fine with horror movies but they do scare me a little bit</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0557" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0539">now it's like The Ring and stuff like that</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0557" trans="overlap">some of them are fine it's just the chopping off limbs I hate</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0539"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1179" who="S0557">like you know? like Saw can't deal with that</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0557">but if it's just like I don't know <pause dur="short"/> like The Exorcist I found hilarious</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0539">did you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1183" who="S0557">I was laughing the whole way through it was like</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0539">well some of them are just pretty stupid aren't they?</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0539">no I think we should go and see it</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0557">yeah no I won't be</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0539"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1189" who="S0557">no Christmas is meant to be like you know? health and oh The Holiday was on last night I was watching that</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh was it?</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0539">oh I missed that</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0557" trans="overlap">it's my favourite Christmas movie</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0539">oh oh I love all the Christmas films</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0557">yeah oh I'm just gonna actually remind my mum to record Masterchef <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1196" who="S0539">oh is that on tonight?</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0557">yeah it's on every night</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0539">oh right</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0557">she's got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> today</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0539">oh does she?</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0539">what's she doing with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0557">well I don't know what the weather was like over there but they they trust us that much they've given us a key to their house how nice is that?</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0539">oh that's good</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0539">do they live in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0557">erm what's it called? <pause dur="short"/> outside just outside on the way to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1208" who="S0539">erm</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0557">you know? just outside <anon type="place"/> literally <pause dur="short"/> oh what's it called?</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0539">I never drive up that way</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0557" trans="overlap">thingy bridge</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0539">I really don't know</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I really er my <trunc>mi</trunc> the name's slipped</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0539">it's not like <vocal desc="sigh"/> oh <anon type="place"/> bridge?</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0557">no no it's like just er just past <anon type="place"/> bridge like maybe five miles from there past <anon type="place"/> and then you turn left</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0539">and not it's not <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0557">no it's before you get to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1218" who="S0539">oh I don't know I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> is do they have a nice house?</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0557">yeah well they own their own business don't they? but it's erm</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0557">it's lovely it's so nice it's probably like eight hundred thousand</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0539" trans="overlap">mm good grief do they just?</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0557" trans="overlap">they have like a pond and <unclear>it's</unclear> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="1224" who="S0539">do they just have the <anon type="place"/> then? or do they have any other?</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0557">just the <anon type="place"/> as far as I know</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0539">mm</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0557">but that's doing well obviously as you know</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0539">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0557">so yeah</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0539">I'm still waiting for our free meal there</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0557">yeah I know well we get free coffee but</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0539">yeah free meal would be nice</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I mean I don't know if we went in for dinner they'd probably give us a discount I'm sure</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0557">but erm yeah</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0539">ah so how often are you seeing her now? it seems to be all the time</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0557">well <vocal desc="sigh"/> when I'm at uni mum sees her erm <pause dur="short"/> she sees her Monday Thursday sometimes at the weekend</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0539">mm</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0557">and then obviously when I'm home erm I'm only <trunc>h</trunc> back for a month <unclear>aren't I</unclear>? till the eighth so I'm just gonna see her as much as I can in this month while I can and then obviously mum brings her up at the weekend occasionally to see me in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1242" who="S0539">ah</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0557">but yeah it's a nice little arrangement</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0539">do you think you'll get like a dog any time soon if <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0557">think it'll have to be when I move out because obviously the renting situation</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0557">so that's a shame</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0539">so did they say a definite no then?</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0557">she didn't no she just didn't get back to us</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0539">oh</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0557">so I assume erm you know? for the amount we're paying and like we're obviously really close like my mum buys them Christmas presents</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0539">does she?</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0557">like they're really close like they they meet up and stuff because</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0557">like her and her husband and my mum and dad like you'd think she'd you know?</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0539">yeah be a bit more laid back</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah exactly she knows like we're not gonna do anything that's gonna oh well it's fine</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0539">oh that's a shame</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I'll just get one myself</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0557">but she's so funny <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's such a wuss like she's scared of the dark <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1262" who="S0539">ah</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0557">a little puppy came in yesterday erm to the <anon type="place"/> mum was saying and she just ran away she's so funny</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0539" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="1265" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1266" who="S0557">she's a lovely dog</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0539">I really want a dog</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0539">so have you thought about where you're gonna live next year if you stay in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0557">er grad college</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0539">are you?</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0557">I wasn't gonna pay but I I think <pause dur="short"/> I dunno I'd prefer to be close to the library</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0539">mm</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0557">cos my internet's so bad I just can't really do you know what I mean? and er I <trunc>c</trunc> I don't drive at the minute so I think I'll just be at grad college</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0539">yeah is it expensive?</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0557">er I think it's just the same really as the dorms but it's it's a nicer standard</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0539">yeah it looks really</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0557" trans="overlap">you've got the <unclear>balcony thing</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1279" who="S0539">is it quite new? the grad college?</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0557">yeah yeah I think so they've updated it yeah</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0539">yeah yeah I haven't been in but it looks nice</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0557">you know? it's a couple of thousand pounds more in debt than I already am so it won't make much difference</u>
<u n="1283" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1284" who="S0557">to be honest I probably won't pay it back anyway</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0539" trans="overlap"><trunc>s</trunc> so how much is the masters?</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0557">erm <pause dur="short"/> six thousand I think isn't it? in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1287" who="S0539">oh right okay so similar to mine then?</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0539">what? and then you'll do your LPC after that will you?</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0557">well the LPC qualifies me as a solicitor but erm the masters isn't a full masters so you're paying for that with the element of risk that you might not get a training contract</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0539">right</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0557">so if I do a masters I can do anything with that and then if I get a training contract then they'll pay for me to do the LPC</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0539">yeah that's good</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><unclear>if you see what I mean</unclear></u>
<u n="1295" who="S0539">so you'll apply</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0557" trans="overlap">so I think I'd prefer to do that really than the <anon type="place"/> one</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0539">you'll apply for the training contract before you do your masters will you?</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0557">but you have to do <unclear/> schemes and they're so competitive for like a two week placement you have to do the assessment centre and all that stuff</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0557">it's a bit ridiculous</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0539">I'll have to erm start applying for assistant psychologist post</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0557">yeah when are you doing that?</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0539">well <vocal desc="sigh"/> there's no point at the moment</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0539">I think I <vocal desc="sigh"/> teaching finishes in March and then I've just got my dissertation to do</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0539">then we graduate in September so I guess like over the summer I can start sort of applying for things</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0539">and see if anything comes up there's actually been I I actually got two interviews like just I'd I applied for them like just before I started my masters cos I thought</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0539">well if I did get one</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0539">like I'd probably go for that instead of doing my masters</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0539">but yeah as soon as I started I got two interviews in like the same week</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0539">it's just typical isn't it? like you</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0557">did you not go? no?</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0539">well no there was no point then cos I'd paid all my fees and everything</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0557" trans="overlap">just yeah but you don't know though that you they could've said well we'll have you after your masters if you impressed them</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0539">no I don't it it doesn't really work like that</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1327" who="S0539">I think they needed someone there and then really</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0557"><unclear>yeah</unclear> that's fine</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0539">but yeah yeah it was</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0557">where were where were they at then?</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0539">I think one was in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1332" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0539">and then oh I think one might've been in like <anon type="place"/> or somewhere like that</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0557">oh you said that</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0557">oh right yeah would you move there then?</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0539">I don't know like it's a bit of a commute isn't it? but</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0557" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0539">yeah maybe</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0557">yeah people like live in <anon type="place"/> and commute nowadays</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0539" trans="overlap">I think</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0557">cos it's so much cheaper <unclear/> commute to London <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1343" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's crazy</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0557"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1345" who="S0539">I think I'll just have to apply like everywhere after I graduate though and see</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0539">but there has there's there's been more jobs available round here lately I've noticed</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0557">has there?</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0557"><unclear>I'm not really looking</unclear></u>
<u n="1351" who="S0539">for assistant psychologist posts</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0557">oh right whereabouts then? like round Edinburgh way or?</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0539">no round us like</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0557">oh right</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0539"><anon type="place"/> well no no I haven't seen any in Lancaster actually <anon type="place"/> and</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0539">like <anon type="place"/> and erm yeah there <trunc>wa</trunc> there was one in <anon type="place"/> actually with like <anon type="place"/> uni I think that was more research though</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh really</unclear>? <unclear/> good</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0539">yeah so it's looking a bit more promising really</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0557">I think it's improving now isn't it? cos <unclear/> in the in the in the decline or whatever it's getting better <unclear/> the job market</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0539">yeah hopefully</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0557">mm</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0539">we'll have to see and then I think a few people on my course are like gonna do PhDs but</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0557">oh yeah? do you not? oh no you're doing your</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0539">yeah well if I did a PhD that would be like three years</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0557">is that different to the doctorate?</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0557">would you pursue that if you didn't do the <unclear>NHS</unclear>?</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0539" trans="overlap">no er I think if you want to do PhD you're kind of er wanting to go into <trunc>acade</trunc>academia so like lecturing and things like that but</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0557">oh really?</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0539">yeah but the doctorate is for your clinical or educational training</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0557">oh right</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0539">so you're training to be an educal educational clinical psychologist so</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0557">yeah I would not want to be a lecturer</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0539">no</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0557" trans="overlap">have you even got to <anon type="place"/> yet?</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0539">I'm not <trunc>su</trunc> no no cos <anon type="place"/>'s like literally just outside <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1378" who="S0557">oh is it?</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0539">but we weren't stopped</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I might nip to the loo as well <unclear/></u>
<u n="1381" who="S0539">yeah we weren't really stopped for that long were we?</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0557" trans="overlap">no I thought it was gonna be half an hour</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0539">yeah</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0557">maybe it means like near the we have to stop <unclear/> <unclear>I don't know</unclear></u>
<u n="1385" who="S0539">the train erm back will probably be delayed by a bit as well I think</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0557">I hope not cos it's gonna be quite late isn't it when we get in?</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0539">do we change on the way back?</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0557">I don't think so</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0539">no er I didn't think it said a change but</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0557">I think it's just direct</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0539">yeah you used to have to change at <anon type="place"/> but maybe they've changed that now</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0557" trans="overlap"><trunc>w</trunc>will we find out like when we get back on or <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0539">we can just look it up on our phone it'll say if there's any changes or not</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0557">yeah okay</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0539">but I didn't think there was</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0557" trans="overlap">I think no I don't think so I'll have a look but</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0539">is your mum okay to</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0557">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0539">pick us up then?</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0557">that's fine I just didn't want it too late if it's delayed by lots it should be fine</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0539">yeah they generally catch up time anyway though actually</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0557">yeah</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0539">it's generally not too bad <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1404" who="S0557">erm would it say if there's changes?</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0539">yeah it should do you <trunc>m</trunc> you might have to go onto like the actual</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0557">just <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> no it doesn't say anything about</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0539">yeah oh that's good then</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0557">we'll have a look nearer the time</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0539">yeah <pause dur="short"/> is your dad doing another PhD?</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0557">er no he's got er oh no he's just handed in his dissertation for his er like fourth masters or whatever he's on</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0557">so yeah</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0539">oh what's this one in?</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0557">and then I think he's doing a <trunc>P</trunc> his PhD I think it's occupational health and safety</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0539">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0557">so yeah</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0539" trans="overlap">so what does your dad actually do?</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0557">oh <vocal desc="sigh"/> it's I think his official title is superintendent but he like runs the whole of the <trunc>med</trunc>medicine and health department <anon type="place"/> or like helps to run it I don't really know</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0539">oh that's cool</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0557">and then he like does health and safety and he lectures at times and stuff</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0539">oh</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0557">so he does quite a lot like it's quite varied</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0557">and he's in the labs and stuff occasionally</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0539">ah</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0557">so a bit of everything really so that's good</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0539">yeah I saw him actually the other day at uni I don't er</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0557" trans="overlap">oh I think he said he saw you actually</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0539" trans="overlap">oh did he?</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0557">yeah did you say hi?</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0539">oh I was going to but he he didn't seem to be looking my way</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0557">oh he maybe like sensed you were there but like didn't really it didn't didn't register until</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0539" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I thought maybe you didn't like him saying hello to you</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
