<text id="SF2F">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:32:40</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Plants, hairstyles, the NHS, A-Level reforms, petrol crisis </topics>
		<activity>ANON and ANON talking while watching TV</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0115">Brian Moore UK Border Force</u>
<u n="2" who="S0037">sorry?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0115">that's Brian Moore from the UK Border Force</u>
<u n="4" who="S0037">I do like a bit of <trunc>U</trunc> <trunc>li</trunc> the programme you mean? Or the <trunc>comp</trunc> the institution <vocal desc="laugh"/>?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the he's from the actual the you know institution like um</u>
<u n="6" who="S0037">you can have  YOU CAN HAVE  that end piece of biscuit as compensation for that bit that triple bluff that I did the other day when I swapped the biscuits round so many times and I ended up</u>
<u n="7" who="S0115">it was breakable <pause dur="short"/> you know none of us knew what was going on</u>
<u n="8" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> just naughty aren't I?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0115">well quite</u>
<u n="10" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but um so I'm gonna get my hair cut on Friday <pause dur="short"/> I'm going back to the same place I think</u>
<u n="11" who="S0115">oh yeah what you gonna are you gonna dye it blue?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0037">what?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0115">are you gonna have it blue?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0037">um perhaps <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> That wasn't in the plan but maybe</u>
<u n="15" who="S0115" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> no no I didn't I I was just I just wondered um</u>
<u n="16" who="S0037">D'you think I should have it blue?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> no uh just that would be an interesting different colour</u>
<u n="18" who="S0037">it would be</u>
<u n="19" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> no I wouldn't uh</u>
<u n="20" who="S0037">that wouldn't be my first choice</u>
<u n="21" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well I wouldn't uh insist <trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> you know like I wouldn't try to force you change your hair to blue um</u>
<u n="22" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> that might be a bit like a <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="23" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and uh you gonna have it based similar to what it was or uh shorter?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0037">I think so <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I keep thinking like should I get it cut a bit shorter because it grows very fast <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="25" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah maybe</u>
<u n="26" who="S0037">I quite like it <trunc>lo</trunc> like I like being able to tie it up</u>
<u n="27" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0037">specially in the summer <pause dur="short"/> like it's nice having short hair in the summer if it's really short but if it's like kind of medium it's <trunc>u</trunc> it's annoying because it's hard to tie up</u>
<u n="29" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> isn't there a way you could sort of do that uh tie it up sort of half tied up</u>
<u n="30" who="S0037" trans="overlap">not <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> there is but it sort of tickles me neck like if it's that's the bit that's the worst <pause dur="short"/> I don't really mind the other bits <pause dur="short"/> shall we halve this?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> well we can't have that can we? I mean you can't have</u>
<u n="32" who="S0037">tickled neck?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0115">you can't have your neck being tickled</u>
<u n="34" who="S0037">na <pause dur="short"/> not by the own hot hair <pause dur="short"/> so yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0037">so I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I'm going back to the same guy <pause dur="short"/> but he was quite sort of <pause dur="short"/> like he's really <trunc>ov</trunc> like camp</u>
<u n="37" who="S0115">that does tend to happen with uh hairdressers doesn't it?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0037">oh uh</u>
<u n="39" who="S0115">and um</u>
<u n="40" who="S0037">quite camp</u>
<u n="41" who="S0115">is what like does that bother you? I mean is it  is it  just too too camp for <pause dur="short"/> too camp to to to cut hair</u>
<u n="42" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no no no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> handle? No <pause dur="short"/> well the hairdresser that I had before when I first came here <pause dur="short"/> like he was young and like the salon was quite hip</u>
<u n="43" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0037">it was recommended to us <pause dur="short"/> I went there <pause dur="short"/> ooh careful</u>
<u n="45" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0037">but the salon was quite sort of like <pause dur="short"/> no turn it up if you want to</u>
<u n="47" who="S0115">no no it's it's on</u>
<u n="48" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh is it?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0037">I already closed the window</u>
<u n="51" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="52" who="S0037">but it's extra closed now</u>
<u n="53" who="S0115">are these? Hopefully those aren't dead you know there huh</u>
<u n="54" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think they're looking better <pause dur="short"/> in fact the ones outside are looking even better like</u>
<u n="55" who="S0115">really? That's not even I I didn't even <trunc>s</trunc> expect that to</u>
<u n="56" who="S0037">what?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0115">I didn't expect the other ones to</u>
<u n="58" who="S0037" trans="overlap">they look like they've grown to me</u>
<u n="59" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0037">have you had a look at them?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0115">no uh well we did pour some uh some feed on there so</u>
<u n="62" who="S0037">I think that was the answer</u>
<u n="63" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so so so what were you saying about your uh?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0037">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah so the one that I went to when I first came here like the music in the salon was on really loud</u>
<u n="65" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the guy was really sort of trendy</u>
<u n="67" who="S0115">yeah like uh just uh in <trunc>en</trunc> sort of entertaining then was he?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and it was a bit like a date like he was uh like he was trying to find like a <pause dur="short"/> ah it's an unusual picture on the TV</u>
<u n="69" who="S0115">ah see I've seen them that's one of the um <pause dur="short"/> it's not  it's not  Bin Laden it's one of his mates</u>
<u n="70" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="72" who="S0037">but um</u>
<u n="73" who="S0115">he's in he's the one who's in prison in America and he's um confessed to various things or something like that</u>
<u n="74" who="S0037">oh</u>
<u n="75" who="S0115">is it  is it?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0037">I saw in the news</u>
<u n="77" who="S0115">I don't know if it's <trunc>A</trunc></u>
<u n="78" who="S0037">I saw in the news something like coming to a town near coming to <trunc>Holly</trunc> coming to New York soon as if it was a trailer and it was like Al Qaida</u>
<u n="79" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah sorry <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Where was that?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that was in the news <pause dur="short"/> al Qaida released it in the news</u>
<u n="81" who="S0115">what they released like a trailer for themselves did they?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> supposedly</u>
<u n="83" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they didn't but did they release it or or did someone just sort of you know do it on their Apple and then uh</u>
<u n="84" who="S0037">I don't know</u>
<u n="85" who="S0115">put like by Al Qaida on it or something</u>
<u n="86" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I've had a bit more than <trunc>h</trunc> half because it's narrow at the top and there's not even any cream in the top of the Crème Egg</u>
<u n="87" who="S0115">oh right no actually that's it's great it's nice</u>
<u n="88" who="S0037">mm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0115">so you you preferred your previous hairdresser then</u>
<u n="90" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah sorry <pause dur="short"/> no no so <pause dur="short"/> yeah the first guy I went to it was like a date and he was like he was trying to find common ground <pause dur="short"/> he was like D'you like Lady Gaga? and I was like Uhh cut my hair please <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0037">this guy was sort of like he was he's totally camp but he was more like he was just easier to get on with and he did my hair nice a few times <pause dur="short"/> though I didn't really like it as much last time but <pause dur="short"/> hopefully he'll get to know it and</u>
<u n="93" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0037">you know</u>
<u n="95" who="S0115">get to know a little</u>
<u n="96" who="S0037">its intricacies and flatness</u>
<u n="97" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Um and they might just camp it up</u>
<u n="98" who="S0037">I don't mind if he camps my hair up <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't mind that <pause dur="short"/> make it nice and big <pause dur="short"/> and fluffy</u>
<u n="99" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> but yeah as I said before uh you could've had a perm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0037">I'm not sure I'm wild about that idea</u>
<u n="101" who="S0115">um it's sort of interesting</u>
<u n="102" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think I'll just get it trimmed and like <pause dur="short"/> and then I've got some dye so I might dye it a bit more <pause dur="short"/> just a slightly different colour</u>
<u n="103" who="S0115">like Julia Roberts in uh?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0037">sorry? The colour of?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0115" trans="overlap">she had  she had  a perm didn't she?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0037">did she?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0115">didn't she have one in um Pretty Woman or something?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0037">I'm not party to Julia Roberts's hair treatments</u>
<u n="109" who="S0115">well there was a lot of them in the eighties anyway I dunno if it was um</u>
<u n="110" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well Kevin Keegan had a perm but I'm not gonna get one</u>
<u n="111" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0037">like</u>
<u n="113" who="S0115">well</u>
<u n="114" who="S0037">I could go in and imagine if I went the hairdressers and just took a picture of Kevin Keegan and was like Can I have this please?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0115">oh yeah it used to go all round</u>
<u n="118" who="S0037">aha and like they're quite long though as well like</u>
<u n="119" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0037">your hair gets a bit like that sometimes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0115">mm well <pause dur="short"/> um you you actually so I suppose that's</u>
<u n="122" who="S0037">I know <pause dur="short"/> no I just mean when it grows like it grows <pause dur="short"/> cos it's curly</u>
<u n="123" who="S0115">well <pause dur="short"/> sort of <pause dur="short"/> it it's thick isn't it I mean <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's too I I'll get it  I'll get it  cut I'll have it uh um</u>
<u n="124" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no you don't need to get it cut it's nice</u>
<u n="125" who="S0115">I'll have it shaved shaved off</u>
<u n="126" who="S0037">I'm not sure that's that would be very nice but</u>
<u n="127" who="S0115">might do</u>
<u n="128" who="S0037">well might do</u>
<u n="129" who="S0115">which uh <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> no I could have a crew cut</u>
<u n="130" who="S0037">you could have a crew cut <pause dur="short"/> I could have a crew cut maybe <pause dur="short"/> be nice for the summer</u>
<u n="131" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you? Well um</u>
<u n="132" who="S0037">just have to rub a flannel on me head and that'll be done</u>
<u n="133" who="S0115" trans="overlap">not not sure if uh</u>
<u n="134" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0115">if if <unclear/> it would suit you <pause dur="short"/> crew cut</u>
<u n="136" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think it would be beautiful that lovely forehead and uh the bit lumpy bit at the back of my head <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="137" who="S0115">so would you will you change the colour of it then <pause dur="short"/> maybe red?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I've got uh <pause dur="short"/> I've bought some dye which is more or less the same colour as my normal hair</u>
<u n="139" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0037">sometimes dying your hair like it gives it a bit of like makes it nice to nice conditioning <pause dur="short"/> nice and <trunc>condition</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I dunno what I was <trunc>say</trunc> what am I saying? Makes it</u>
<u n="141" who="S0115" trans="overlap">maybe gives it a nice texture?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0115">yeah so I might do and it's also a little bit more a little bit <trunc>ji</trunc> different so for the spring it's like a bit more gingery</u>
<u n="143" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0037">on my already quite gingery hair <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> red</u>
<u n="145" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is there already? Whose whose is your favourite celebrity hair?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0037">who's my favourite celebrity hair?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> is it like one of those Greek ones?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0037">which Greek ones?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0115">mm like most most of them you know the the big big Greek hair</u>
<u n="150" who="S0037" trans="overlap">um Kate Middleton's got nice hair hasn't she? She always has it done nice</u>
<u n="151" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="152" who="S0037">I do like um Cheryl Cole when she has it really massive</u>
<u n="153" who="S0115" trans="overlap">what's it like?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0037">Kate Middleton hair <pause dur="short"/> kate Middleton's hair is like just brown but it always looks really glossy and nice <pause dur="short"/> but it's got like it's her who always has it uh sort of curled towards the ends? Like bit sort of big big sort of curls though</u>
<u n="155" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and curled at the end? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> like so she's got fat hair and she curls it yeah?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0037" trans="overlap">she definitely has it done yeah <pause dur="short"/> well no um maybe she's got hair that's a bit wavy but it's not <trunc>w</trunc> not curly</u>
<u n="157" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="158" who="S0037">but she's got sort of straightish hair but <pause dur="short"/> she just well she the that's <trunc>cu</trunc> she always looks nice like cos her hair she's obviously got like a fulltime pardon me a fulltime hairdresser <pause dur="short"/> but um and I quite like any of the ones where they have like <trunc>mas</trunc> when they have it really big like Cheryl Cole sometimes has her hair quite big</u>
<u n="159" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I guess um someone um <unclear/> like</u>
<u n="160" who="S0037">um and also who else's hair? I don't know <pause dur="short"/> but I like sort of quite big hair but my hair's just the very very opposite <pause dur="short"/> it's quite</u>
<u n="161" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><trunc>I</trunc> could is there a way that you could get it big?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> you can like back comb it stuff uh which I do do when I go out but I don't wanna do that every time cos I don't wanna like knack the texture of it</u>
<u n="163" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0037">like snap it all or anything but <pause dur="short"/> I shouldn't complain because people who have like frizzy hair say they wanna have straight hair <pause dur="short"/> like I'm lucky I can go out with wet hair in the morning and it'll just be fine it'll just like my normal looks like I've blow dried it <pause dur="short"/> I only blow dry it to save time</u>
<u n="165" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0037">like my hair's not really any different</u>
<u n="167" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="168" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you know especially for work I just <trunc>dr</trunc> I just like blast it I don't like do it with a brush or anything <pause dur="short"/> so I'm half the time I just don't even do that I just leave the towel on me head while I'm pottering around in the morning and then just take it off and <pause dur="short"/> I normally dry me fringe bit and then just let the rest dry itself</u>
<u n="169" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0037">so</u>
<u n="171" who="S0115">right</u>
<u n="172" who="S0037">am I boring you with my hair stories? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0115">um well no I was asking um <pause dur="short"/> I was just uh</u>
<u n="174" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so um yeah so I'm quite lucky cos some people  some people  just can't like me friend Lucy she's got lovely hair and if I was her I'd just leave it but she like full-on straightens it and that every single day</u>
<u n="175" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Cos you  cos you  <unclear/> Covered up <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0037">which is crackers if you ask me</u>
<u n="177" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="178" who="S0037">but each to their</u>
<u n="179" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I think a lot of people uh <trunc>pr</trunc> probably more than um more straighten than uh otherwise um</u>
<u n="180" who="S0037" trans="overlap">curl? Yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0115">but some people uh if you straighten the hair it would grow like in a  in a  mushroom shape</u>
<u n="182" who="S0037">yeah that'd be good</u>
<u n="183" who="S0115">um like um</u>
<u n="184" who="S0037" trans="overlap">maybe I should straighten yours one time</u>
<u n="185" who="S0115">I think mine</u>
<u n="186" who="S0037">in fact I don't even know if I've got any straighteners any more</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I think mine mine might go in a mushroom shape um but uh</u>
<u n="188" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh it'd be nice mushroom</u>
<u n="189" who="S0115">I think it probably would actually <pause dur="short"/> a and E uh <pause dur="short"/> survey</u>
<u n="190" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh it's like some sort of survey</u>
<u n="191" who="S0115">about the NHS <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> increase rationing</u>
<u n="192" who="S0037">do you think it should be privatized?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0115">um well it's not being properly uh <pause dur="short"/> I don't  I don't  um <pause dur="short"/> uh no I don't  I don't  understand enough about it but uh I believe that uh they're if if <trunc>Ameri</trunc> if if it became more like America's one there's a risk it could become more America's is</u>
<u n="194" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I knowing it's not being privatized as such by name but <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I think like for what</u>
<u n="195" who="S0115">but it's not the same as America's one and it's it's always gonna have that sort of centralized feel I <trunc>su</trunc> I suppose um <pause dur="short"/> but uh</u>
<u n="196" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="197" who="S0115">but it it I believe there's a problem in certain companies with certain private <pause dur="short"/> there's a lot of outsourcing to private companies</u>
<u n="198" who="S0037">mm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0115">part of the problem with that is the sort of monopoly aspect of uh</u>
<u n="200" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0115">or um it it's not quite a monopoly but it you know the thing with the <trunc>T</trunc> well we did think we we've talked before about the uh the like the TV the entertainment stuff and the internet stuff</u>
<u n="202" who="S0037">oh yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0115">um like <pause dur="short"/> about how <trunc>y</trunc> you're you're um a captive audience and you have to pay  you have to pay  uh a <trunc>v</trunc> a really uh extortionate fee fee to just to be able to watch TV um</u>
<u n="204" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh it's horrible I hate all that thing <pause dur="short"/> and also like <pause dur="short"/> I think <pause dur="short"/> and also the the thing about like</u>
<u n="205" who="S0115" trans="overlap">which so but of course there's there's no way that the customer can can choose uh different services there there's only that one private service possibly available from that bed and they can't go anywhere since they're they're stuck in the bed so they're that is a forced monopoly which is always um</u>
<u n="206" who="S0037" trans="overlap">feeding the <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and like <trunc>f</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's horrible <pause dur="short"/> and like feeding the patients shit but then giving them the guests like the in the canteen having all like nice food</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah the the sort of desperation to raise um money is is the problem that that hits that like if you  if you  make um</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0115">if you make uh <trunc>m</trunc> um if you want to introduce like obviously uh a lot of money making um strategies it would you're gonna you um you aren't gonna find things like um <trunc>de</trunc> you know desperation to make money and and raising <trunc>ev</trunc> all possible</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115">any any price that would possibly be able to go up would go up <pause dur="short"/> and uh and yeah charging charging a patient ten pounds a day to watch TV for example is uh is is uh is it's partly desperation and also of course it's very unfair because they can't um have they have no ability to to to choose another service although I don't know what they do with laptops if they allow them um which they probably should do</u>
<u n="212" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know shocking <pause dur="short"/> opt out like <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think you weren't <trunc>be</trunc> allowed them before but I think you sort of are now but I'm not sure</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115">um so yeah well I think I already talked about that but I mean if I I don't understand like what they were doing with the uh NHS now I don't  I don't  um</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037">I think it was gonna be that they would let let doctors choose how they should spend the money <pause dur="short"/> I dunno the for me the government seems to the Conservative government seems to really like like it can't be arsed like it's just putting the onus on everyone else like did you read that thing about A levels in the news?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115">uh no I didn't</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037">so Michael Gove the absolute <trunc>n</trunc> the absolute I can't even use the words <trunc>u</trunc> on a tape cos it's just I don't wanna you know</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they're privatizing that as well? He's got a funny old face hasn't he? I think he's been been <trunc>lo</trunc> locked up  locked up  in an attic as a child for a while</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but he's horrible isn't he? Oh he's just I just really dislike the man <pause dur="short"/> anyway Michael Gove um said that he wants universities to set A levels like <trunc>t</trunc> to pose the questions you know?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115">uh no I've <pause dur="short"/> does he want that or or?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what he says he wants</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115">why is he doing that to save money?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115">what's the advantage of it?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037">well he's saying he said he wants them to be more rigorous <pause dur="short"/> he wants to do away with the option to do modules <pause dur="short"/> he wants to</u>
<u n="225" who="S0115">whereas <trunc>mo</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> no I would've thought modules were could be a good thing cos then you'd have a wider range of um knowledge that probably it's likely to help you get a job and probably likely to help you in university</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037" trans="overlap">of course I mean <pause dur="short"/> but it's presumptuous to think that A levels are <trunc>on</trunc></u>
<u n="227" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I don't  I don't  know I don't see why they're changing it <pause dur="short"/> are they just changing  are they just changing  things simply for the sake of it or they are they doing this to make money <trunc>s</trunc> to to save money somewhere um?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> probably <pause dur="short"/> but I think <pause dur="short"/> he's just being elitist by saying that <pause dur="short"/> like he said that the Russell Group you know the Russell Group should set A levels so he's offended not only like all other universities in the United Kingdom but for example like A level teachers who perhaps have a better place to know what's working and what's not um</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> I don't know though because this is this actually gonna? Well the Russell not all the Russell Groups are that that great anyway is it I mean?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0037">well who's in the Russell Group that's not that great? Warwick <pause dur="short"/> warwick are alright</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115">no I you  I you  can't insult a whole university but you can say that there may be they're not <trunc>alway</trunc> it's not always that um</u>
<u n="232" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well <anon type="place"/>'s not in the Russell Group but there's another group of like the <trunc>r</trunc> the best the most sort of research intensive and <anon type="place"/>'s in that one <pause dur="short"/> but but anyway</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I mean <trunc>w</trunc> I just uh how does I mean where do they even you know where do they get these these ideas <trunc>u</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>p</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> is this just the university themselves proposed that idea?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037" trans="overlap">basically <pause dur="short"/> no not all it's they're like ooh we're a bit surprised by that and we're like there was a woman on This Morning saying you know universities are so overstretched and now they want us to set the A level things as well and <pause dur="short"/> you know it just seems a bit weird <pause dur="short"/> it's just like some Daily Mail view like exams are easy that's basically what that's come from <pause dur="short"/> you know?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115"><trunc>R</trunc> really has it come from that?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037">well that's my opinion</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115">why but but how many uh but <trunc>w</trunc> why wouldn't they want their? Wouldn't people want their exams to be? Wouldn't people want exams to be easier for their own children but harder for everyone else? Sort of in a not my not in my back yard sort of thing</u>
<u n="238" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well older older people think that A levels are easier now don't they? Oh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> but I just thought that was stupid I just thought he was just trying to put it onto other people like they're not tackling any problems</u>
<u n="239" who="S0115">I I don't know I mean I don't know the whole of the</u>
<u n="240" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think he's just putting problems onto like</u>
<u n="241" who="S0115" trans="overlap">ah I don't know that I wonder <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="242" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but anyway maybe that's just</u>
<u n="243" who="S0115">there's been</u>
<u n="244" who="S0037">maybe that's not the case</u>
<u n="245" who="S0115">yeah so the main story in the on this one seems to have been the introduction of something called uh um Big Society Capital I mean <trunc>w</trunc> what is? You obviously haven't you haven't heard of that have you?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what Cameron? No not really I mean I I've heard of his Big Society ideas <pause dur="short"/> none of which I've been particularly like bowled over by but that's just me</u>
<u n="247" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc> the it's not easy to just sort of tell people to do stuff for free <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="248" who="S0037">Cos the people who want who are gonna be inclined to do that are already doing that I bet</u>
<u n="249" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="250" who="S0037">ooh sorry <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>sor</trunc> ooh I'm sorry</u>
<u n="251" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it yeah well if you can force people but it doesn't always work does it because</u>
<u n="252" who="S0037">sorry</u>
<u n="253" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh because they would say that <pause dur="short"/> you know like with the uh where they tried to get people to to work for nothing um</u>
<u n="254" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah thank you <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah in the  in the  shops?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah in fact so that didn't work that didn't sort of</u>
<u n="256" who="S0037">thank you</u>
<u n="257" who="S0115">that didn't work very well they they all pulled out of it</u>
<u n="258" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no it didn't <pause dur="short"/> because yeah they were just like taking advantage of people weren't they? Really</u>
<u n="259" who="S0115">I dunno well the companies pulled out so um if the companies pulled out then somebody uh well the customers must've complained <trunc>o</trunc> or</u>
<u n="260" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0115">someone scared <trunc>u</trunc> cos like some of those companies like Tesco are are you know as powerful if not more powerful than the government itself <pause dur="short"/> so if when they if they change their minds then they must've really been scared by it <pause dur="short"/> uh probably <trunc>s</trunc> some aspect of the media were yeah maybe media sort of <trunc>s</trunc> tried to scare them out of it but</u>
<u n="262" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it was just bad press wasn't it? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm all for people being given chances though but if they're just being taken advantage of then I mean that's obviously not cool</u>
<u n="263" who="S0115">uh well it just appeared I mean <pause dur="short"/> because on the one hand it it seems like a good thing to</u>
<u n="264" who="S0037">so we didn't <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="265" who="S0115">to to try and get people into into jobs but <pause dur="short"/> I would  I would  think if you wanna force somebody to work you can at least force them and then pay them not not force them and then give them the same that they had before that that's a difficult issue it's different here <trunc>o</trunc> than in America isn't it because like they're not  they're not  really cutting in the same way are they?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> um I don't know</u>
<u n="267" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I guess it depends on the state obviously but here the message is absolutely you know um austerity and cutting everything whereas in uh I think in America they they've they've decided to <trunc>s</trunc> to put in loads more um money <pause dur="short"/> they've basically not currently um</u>
<u n="268" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what's that called again?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0115">they're not cutting  they're not cutting</u>
<u n="270" who="S0037" trans="overlap">to stimulate growth you mean? What's that called I'm sure it's got like a</u>
<u n="271" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh well there's different things aren't there? you know <trunc>q</trunc> is there there's quantitative easing</u>
<u n="272" who="S0037" trans="overlap">quantitative easing? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0115">and then that's uh I think that just means printing money um</u>
<u n="274" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I wish they'd just say that</u>
<u n="275" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like <pause dur="short"/> but um <pause dur="short"/> and it's it uh it bonds um like bonds are issued <pause dur="short"/> uh that's the Bank Of England loans the government money then gets takes the bond or something like that <pause dur="short"/> and then as the Bank Of England has loaned the money then</u>
<u n="276" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0115">um that means the money gets to be printed <pause dur="short"/> it's injected <pause dur="short"/> another yeah they did there were three hundred billion or something recently <pause dur="short"/> the um extra money was printed</u>
<u n="278" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I find it <pause dur="short"/> I find I</u>
<u n="279" who="S0115">but it America though they're more sort of <pause dur="short"/> I think they've increased <pause dur="short"/> they had the bailout package which which was uh something that was um there was a lot of news about that I think back in whenever it was <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> and they're so they they have a really enormous amount of money that was injected into um into their economy</u>
<u n="280" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0115">um which is the world's biggest um and uh that seems to me to be a slightly different technique to what's going in over in Europe it's seems to be always um apart from maybe some of the more successful countries like Germany pretty much everyone's just um basically chopping the</u>
<u n="282" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0115">it uh just just reducing um spending and and cutting um cutting government spending cutting funding for things um so just struggling to sort of define that</u>
<u n="284" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I dunno I find it hard to follow like I suppose it's not <pause dur="short"/> I suppose that it's got I'm not like really massively interested in um economics</u>
<u n="285" who="S0115">yeah I know well it it can be <trunc>ver</trunc> it can be very boring I understand why people find it boring because they it's quite technical and <pause dur="short"/> it's also depressing as well but I  but I  think it has uh a huge <trunc>u</trunc> impact on people's daily lives</u>
<u n="286" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0115">from the number of buses to uh <trunc>ho</trunc> how much it costs to buy food to fuel to everything <trunc>y</trunc> it's all like connected in in the economics isn't it? Um</u>
<u n="288" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh no I can  I can  see why</u>
<u n="289" who="S0115">and I I mean obviously uh you know fuel prices are a good example of uh</u>
<u n="290" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah the fuel crisis as well</u>
<u n="291" who="S0115">well we just had  we just had  the panic didn't we so uh panic panic buying</u>
<u n="292" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I liked it that like other things were jumping on the band wagon and saying like oh panic buy beer and like <vocal desc="laugh"/> panic buy you know shoes or whatever</u>
<u n="293" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean that was  that was  cos they thought it was gonna be a strike which was never confirmed um but uh that's</u>
<u n="294" who="S0037" trans="overlap">has there even been a strike like they</u>
<u n="295" who="S0115">no no there <trunc>wa</trunc> there wasn't but there was</u>
<u n="296" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'm sure they were just trying to get some extra revenue in before the end of the tax year</u>
<u n="297" who="S0115">oh yeah something like that I mean they tried to get the guy to resign but he didn't um he didn't resign uh I think they were just trying to like sensationalize it and put the blame on um you know sort of uh attack the strikers hadn't actually started striking yet so um</u>
<u n="298" who="S0037">hadn't struck? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0115">they they they <trunc>so</trunc> he sort of wanted I suppose he wanted to attack them before they'd  before they'd  <trunc>e</trunc> actually before they thought of starting the strike um yeah perhaps to scare them out of starting the strike</u>
<u n="300" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0115">which which worked in that way but but it also meant that there was massive like panic and and uh one person did die actually so there was one uh</u>
<u n="302" who="S0037">oh was that the woman who was <trunc>de</trunc> decanting that? In her next to her gas cooker or something?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0115">I don't know but um someone someone there well there <pause dur="short"/> one person died basically from the  from the  panic from the panic buying sort of</u>
<u n="304" who="S0037" trans="overlap">which who d'you mean died? What of? What did she die of though it wasn't just sheer panic <vocal desc="laugh"/>?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0115">uh being burnt by petrol I imagine</u>
<u n="306" who="S0037">yeah that was the woman who'd I think who'd stockpiled the petrol and she was decanting it from one like jerry can into another while her oven was on</u>
<u n="307" who="S0115">well it's above the oven or something?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0037">no like I think she was just splashing it around while a gas flame was on in her <pause dur="short"/> well it's like the vapour'll ignite won't it?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> yeah I never  I never  thought of it <pause dur="short"/> I mean I didn't I didn't  think like <pause dur="short"/> I suppose you when you say oven you don't you mean the actual uh? You mean a gas hob you mean like a hob?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like she was cooking her dinner yeah yeah a gas hob like a <trunc>fl</trunc> naked flame yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0115">yeah yeah uh that's that's like <unclear/> naked flame yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I mean that's like Darwinism that is if you ask me</u>
<u n="313" who="S0115">but if it weren't for the  if it weren't for  the panic then she she wouldn't have got burnt</u>
<u n="314" who="S0037" trans="overlap">D'you know what I mean? I feel <pause dur="short"/> I feel very sory for her family and everything</u>
<u n="315" who="S0115">she wouldn't have been um she wouldn't have been decanting</u>
<u n="316" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I really do <pause dur="short"/> I do feel sorry for her family and stuff cos it's you know it's not very nice but at the same time like that's like you know safety like one oh one that if you ask me</u>
<u n="317" who="S0115">well it I guess it is</u>
<u n="318" who="S0037" trans="overlap">bit of natural selection there I think</u>
<u n="319" who="S0115">yeah but people just make mistakes man if they're  if they're  if they're in a hurry if if you're in a panic</u>
<u n="320" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="321" who="S0115">then then you you you you may make a mistake like because cos they're not normally  they're not normally  doing that are they?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well if you're gonna get into</u>
<u n="323" who="S0115">you don't normally handle fuel in the house do you so?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0037">well <trunc>n</trunc> you shouldn't either <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's no good reason to</u>
<u n="325" who="S0115">yeah but if you can  you can  pour it in the um living room can't you? Or can't you I mean</u>
<u n="326" who="S0037">well you can</u>
<u n="327" who="S0115">you're saying that even the  even the  vapour of it is gonna catch fire</u>
<u n="328" who="S0037">well I wouldn't do it I mean I don't</u>
<u n="329" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you'd have to yeah decant it outside</u>
<u n="330" who="S0037">oh uh yeah exactly</u>
<u n="331" who="S0115">yeah so I don't know why she didn't decant it outside that's something that we don't  we don't  know</u>
<u n="332" who="S0037" trans="overlap">in your garage or something innit? Ah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0115">um perhaps she didn't have an outside</u>
<u n="334" who="S0037">well most people have an outside <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> So no I don't know whether that was uh <pause dur="short"/> but uh <pause dur="short"/> uh yeah so everyone's feeling the pinch</u>
<u n="336" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="337" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> it was it does feel like it has since the crisis or whatever felt like a</u>
<u n="338" who="S0037">A <trunc>pr</trunc> a fuel crisis?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that everyone's like <trunc>every</trunc> everything's getting <trunc>sh</trunc> everything's shrinking or being raised in price</u>
<u n="340" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and now they're saying <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> and now they're like oh you can't water your garden or whatever</u>
<u n="341" who="S0115">well that's annoying <pause dur="short"/> that's an old one that is</u>
<u n="342" who="S0037">no no but like from today it's a if you get caught watering your garden it's a thousand pound fine</u>
<u n="343" who="S0115">that's quite  that's quite  bizarre you know</u>
<u n="344" who="S0037">ridiculous isn't it?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0115">it's quite strange considering the amount the sheer enormous quantity of rain that falls in England</u>
<u n="346" who="S0037">I know <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> well we've got a rainwater thing haven't we? So can just collect it</u>
<u n="347" who="S0115" trans="overlap">why are they sort of doing all this  all this  stuff anyway about? It's raining now</u>
<u n="348" who="S0037">I know it's raining now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0115">are you supposed to collect your own water or something?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think it hasn't been raining for a while though</u>
<u n="351" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> I mean can they not take water from the sea somehow?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0037">well I don't know</u>
<u n="353" who="S0115">yeah uh I suppose like that that's the most efficient that you know with the with um <trunc>reserv</trunc> <trunc>r</trunc> reservoirs presumably you have to store water in a reservoir you can't store it in in in some way to prevent it from evaporating</u>
<u n="354" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't think plants like sea water that much <pause dur="short"/> in the sea? <vocal desc="laugh"/> Don't know</u>
<u n="355" who="S0115">I guess</u>
<u n="356" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="357" who="S0115">A <trunc>l</trunc> a lidded reservoir?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0037">no I suppose it always does evaporate <pause dur="short"/> it would be quite a big lid for the reservoir</u>
<u n="359" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0037">so</u>
<u n="361" who="S0115">but it's just is it's just not <pause dur="short"/> perhaps that that possibility's there isn't you know it would be too expensive to uh</u>
<u n="362" who="S0037">put a lid on the reservoir? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0115">to <trunc>l</trunc> to lid the reservoir</u>
<u n="364" who="S0037">I think it most definitely would be <pause dur="short"/> they could store it underground maybe</u>
<u n="365" who="S0115" trans="overlap">depends what you lid it with though doesn't it?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0037">could store it underground</u>
<u n="367" who="S0115">yeah I mean presumably there's some reason why they <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>b</trunc> because they collect the rainwater but um <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0037">I dunno</u>
<u n="369" who="S0115">I suppose there could  there could  be able a method of of trying to keep <unclear/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but you're right it's rained all day today</u>
<u n="371" who="S0115">Cos cos it's it seems that the volume is there you I mean</u>
<u n="372" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0115">somehow anyway</u>
<u n="374" who="S0037">but I bet they'll still water the grass at King's and all that <pause dur="short"/> they'll just pay it won't they?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> I don't know uh they they they would be pretty exempt I imagine cos they're a public um institution or something</u>
<u n="376" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> is it just private homes then?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0115">guess so yeah <pause dur="short"/> I imagine you could get round it if you if you're a public institution <pause dur="short"/> no that's never well it used to be hosepipe like um</u>
<u n="378" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0115"><trunc>Th</trunc> they always used to have those things but but um uh it it's pretty wasteful I suppose innit all the getting a hosepipe and just like sort of letting it  letting it  run</u>
<u n="380" who="S0037" trans="overlap">squirting it around? Yeah I suppose it is but <pause dur="short"/> if you're growing stuff like we're growing vegetables I mean I'm not gonna be like letting them dry out am I?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well part of it they'd have to prove  they'd have to prove  that you  that you  watered your garden or something they'd have to come round and I mean sort of</u>
<u n="382" who="S0037" trans="overlap">look at your garden? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> see if it's wilting? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0115">and then um <pause dur="short"/> you could  you could  be framed though someone could uh</u>
<u n="384" who="S0037">ah and like neighbours taking pictures of you? Like the uh Stasi?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0115" trans="overlap">get get a hose hose pipe and sort of spray <pause dur="short"/> like could get their hose pipe and spray it on your garden then <unclear/> like</u>
<u n="386" who="S0037" trans="overlap">then you can <pause dur="short"/> like remember</u>
<u n="387" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well that that's like one of those  one of those  stupid petty garden wars where</u>
<u n="388" who="S0037">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0115">where neighbours chop each others' trees down</u>
<u n="390" who="S0037">that's right yeah <pause dur="short"/> or argue over like spend hundreds of thousands of pounds on legal costs about like like land the size of like a stamp or something</u>
<u n="391" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like border border <pause dur="short"/> that happens quite a lot I think you know when <pause dur="short"/> having worked in litigation there are a lot of cases you know the fees are enormous like</u>
<u n="392" who="S0037" trans="overlap">why do people do it? People've just got more money than sense haven't they?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0115">well yeah basically I think that's that's mainly um but they're also just <pause dur="short"/> some people are just genuinely bad people so you have to do something to <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="394" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah but if it was like a tiny strip of land then you would just be like d'you know what? Have it like</u>
<u n="395" who="S0115">well I mm <pause dur="short"/> I it's not  it's not  been something that <pause dur="short"/> well some that I ever really thought of <pause dur="short"/> but you've got a kind of neighbour that decides to sort of rebuid a fence and then sort of you know put his fence sort of</u>
<u n="396" who="S0037">yeah right on your bit</u>
<u n="397" who="S0115">like a a metre further in?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0037">they did that to me nana like me nana used to um have</u>
<u n="399" who="S0115">I think it's just bad people isn't it?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0037">me nana had daffodils</u>
<u n="401" who="S0115">person who's always got to</u>
<u n="402" who="S0037">had all these tulips and daffodils a massive big load of them against against that fence in her old garden where we where she used to live <pause dur="short"/> and the council came and replaced the fence <pause dur="short"/> um cos the <trunc>h</trunc> her neighbours were horrible</u>
<u n="403" who="S0115">yeah I know yeah I remember you saying</u>
<u n="404" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and they replaced the fence cos um when it was me <trunc>n</trunc> Marge used to live next door they had a lower fence cos they would chat over it but they got it she had it replaced when these horrible neighbours came and had like a high one</u>
<u n="405" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0037">so then they moved it though and like <trunc>w</trunc> she lost all of her flowers <pause dur="short"/> they all went on the other side of the fence <pause dur="short"/> they moved it over like by</u>
<u n="407" who="S0115" trans="overlap">how <trunc>di</trunc>? Who who moved it?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0037">the council moved the fence by about you know</u>
<u n="409" who="S0115">but how? I mean that can't just happen can it or was there some corruption or something?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0037">dunno just by mistake I think <pause dur="short"/> not on purpose</u>
<u n="411" who="S0115">so she <trunc>w</trunc> she wasn't there to see <pause dur="short"/> see it happening?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I don't think you realize until the spring time came and all the flowers were on the <vocal desc="laugh"/> getting eaten by the like horrible <trunc>la</trunc> like Staffies and that next door</u>
<u n="413" who="S0115">fuh</u>
<u n="414" who="S0037">never mind</u>
<u n="415" who="S0115">there um uh <pause dur="short"/> they're I guess some them sorts of families cos like we were watching the uh that um that gypsies program weren't we?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh <pause dur="short"/> I suppose when if you see <trunc>tho</trunc> those sorts of Staffie type families it <trunc>rem</trunc> it reminds you of the similarity to some of the um gypsy families like a cultural similarity</u>
<u n="418" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I mean <pause dur="short"/> you can't say that anybody anyone with a Staffordshire bull terrier's bad I mean it's not the dog's fault like you said before</u>
</body>
</text>
