<text id="SFCW">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:32:16</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-05</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0263 S0264</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Dhaba Café, University of Sussex</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Colleagues</relationships>
		<topics>Work</topics>
		<activity>Colleagues talking about work</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, requesting</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0263">
				<exactage>39</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hastings</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>France</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0264">
				<exactage>60</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Crickhowell</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South Wales/Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>23</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>tutorial fellow</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate; Dutch -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0263">International Corpus you've decided to help them out</u>
<u n="2" who="S0264">yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> I think by the time you <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah you've gotta well you have to sign er a form just</u>
<u n="3" who="S0263">I'm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0264"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0263">I've signed up for the erm <pause dur="short"/> corpus MOOC starting in September</u>
<u n="6" who="S0264">oh yeah that</u>
<u n="7" who="S0263" trans="overlap">just to add to my <vocal desc="laugh"/> things to do</u>
<u n="8" who="S0264" trans="overlap">that's the the the repeat</u>
<u n="9" who="S0263">it's the repeat</u>
<u n="10" who="S0264">of the one that I signed up for and never carried on with yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0263" trans="overlap">yeah I'm going to I'm going to maybe not do all of it but look at some of it</u>
<u n="12" who="S0264">the first week or two is is quite straightforward cos you just watch a video and they they make sure it's all bite size and you and you click when something is done it gives you a great feeling you've you click through all these things but then it starts getting more demanding</u>
<u n="13" who="S0263" trans="overlap">after a bit yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0264">the problem <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="15" who="S0263" trans="overlap">so what other grievances oh yes oh I had you know the <unclear>Miage</unclear> students?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0264">yes</u>
<u n="17" who="S0263">they were quite tricky</u>
<u n="18" who="S0264">yes</u>
<u n="19" who="S0263">do you remember?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0264">I do er</u>
<u n="21" who="S0263">er <pause dur="short"/> so I went to the end of year sort of examiners' meeting <pause dur="short"/> and a got a few emails beforehand from the head of that</u>
<u n="22" who="S0264">their kind of tutor their course tutor?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0263">yeah and she said I need to speak to you so I said okay so from the email I thought well it's going to be something negative <pause dur="short"/> so I was expecting the worst I had got <trunc>m</trunc> I had got them to do some transcription <vocal desc="laugh"/> do you remember? so I thought it was gonna be about that</u>
<u n="24" who="S0264">oh your transcriptions?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0263">I had got them to do some work on the <unclear>Furasso</unclear> law and things like that</u>
<u n="26" who="S0264">well they agreed</u>
<u n="27" who="S0263">they agreed and they all so they seemed happy enough anyway <pause dur="short"/> and they liked they liked having you they said</u>
<u n="28" who="S0264">oh</u>
<u n="29" who="S0263">and erm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0264" trans="overlap">that's unexpected after the last session</u>
<u n="31" who="S0263"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0264">they nearly</u>
<u n="33" who="S0263">well they were not they weren't great were they? anyway</u>
<u n="34" who="S0264">I thought that it was very French I mean that's what I I told told you when you told me about the riots and how the kids upturned the cars</u>
<u n="35" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0264">I thought this I liked this about France they they can say what they feel <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0263">yeah they're very</u>
<u n="38" who="S0264" trans="overlap"><event desc="unintelligible"/> demonstrative</u>
<u n="39" who="S0263">the opposite of what the experience I had here</u>
<u n="40" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0263">and the oh <pause dur="long"/> and erm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0264">so you went along</u>
<u n="43" who="S0263">she said yes erm <pause dur="short"/> you've got to change your course you know the students are not happy with it and I was <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>th</trunc>they er they want to do a they want to do more things like CVs and I said oh but we did CVs and we did video CVs</u>
<u n="44" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah and why didn't they tell you anyway?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0263">cos I got this CV idea from you the video CV</u>
<u n="46" who="S0264">can't remember</u>
<u n="47" who="S0263" trans="overlap">you film yourself doing sort of presentation well it <trunc>w</trunc> I think it was I don't know</u>
<u n="48" who="S0264">somebody else but</u>
<u n="49" who="S0263" trans="overlap">anyway</u>
<u n="50" who="S0264">a good idea yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0263">I said oh well okay and er <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> then she said well I suppose <pause dur="short"/> I said well <trunc>sh</trunc> I I need some more concrete sort of feedback shall I <trunc>wr</trunc>write to the students and say would you mind giving me some feedback?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0263">and then so I sent them that</u>
<u n="54" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0263">and the feedback that I got was absolutely lovely they said we really appreciated it</u>
<u n="56" who="S0264">oh</u>
<u n="57" who="S0263">cos it's not at all their style to sort of say that they like things when they don't</u>
<u n="58" who="S0264">no cos they</u>
<u n="59" who="S0263" trans="overlap">they said</u>
<u n="60" who="S0264" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="61" who="S0263" trans="overlap">we really like doing the workshops</u>
<u n="62" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0263">erm one guy said I don't usually like English but as you let you let us a lot of you let us have a lot of freedom and <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I was happy to you know I thought I thought that's what they needed to not to be sort of mithered too much they been wanted a lot of freedom</u>
<u n="64" who="S0264" trans="overlap">it wouldn't work with them would it?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0263">no</u>
<u n="66" who="S0264">they'd just rebel</u>
<u n="67" who="S0263" trans="overlap">and I got really nice and the last after you left we went to the to the pub with some of them and I gave them all my second hand books that I don't want anymore and they were really touched by that</u>
<u n="68" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0263">and they said I'm reading er I'm reading some of the books you gave us and</u>
<u n="70" who="S0264">you mean novels or what?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0263">novels yeah <pause dur="short"/> and the feedback didn't at all correspond to what this woman had said</u>
<u n="72" who="S0264">but did you make this woman read the feedback? did you <trunc>gi</trunc> er send send the feedback to her?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0263">no cos she doesn't read English she doesn't speak English she's always going on about how <trunc>sh</trunc>she doesn't speak a word of English</u>
<u n="74" who="S0264" trans="overlap">well I reckon it would be worth translating that feedback <pause dur="short"/> cos it's so such a contrast isn't it? I</u>
<u n="75" who="S0263">thought so it made me feel pretty low <trunc>al</trunc>already just having a low <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0263">end of term and then I got this criticism and I was thinking oh no and then I got the feedback from those students which was really nice which really cheered me up</u>
<u n="78" who="S0264">yeah but it makes you wonder where did she where is she coming from? where does she get this <pause dur="short"/> idea from? it must have been one student on one morning <pause dur="short"/> or maybe she said what don't you like about er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s course?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0263">and also it was interesting you know when you give feedback you usually say one well the the sort of practice is to say one nice thing and then</u>
<u n="80" who="S0264">one thing for improvement say</u>
<u n="81" who="S0263">and she didn't say she went straight into you know <pause dur="short"/> negative negative negative as if the whole thing had been a <trunc>disa</trunc> and I was thinking well that's not the impression that I got at all</u>
<u n="82" who="S0264">I think you've gotta be quite clever to manage that group because it's a it's quite a large group and they're not linguists they're IT so they don't perceive language to be necessarily the most useful thing for them</u>
<u n="83" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0264">and so if you can manage that <pause dur="short"/> which you have which you did <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0263">so I'm a bit I'm sort of erm a bit fed up with er</u>
<u n="86" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0263"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> university</u>
<u n="88" who="S0264">yes <pause dur="short"/> would you like some fruit I've got a whole bag of stuff here?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0263">but I could imagine it's erm the same anywhere</u>
<u n="90" who="S0264">within reason I think that's I think that's true but I</u>
<u n="91" who="S0263" trans="overlap">thank you</u>
<u n="92" who="S0264">I once worked in erm <anon type="place"/> and</u>
<u n="93" who="S0263">thanks</u>
<u n="94" who="S0264"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but now I was well actually the staff were alright but he was very good because he was very mm what's it called? democratic he he put people into er little committees er with a revolving chairperson and said okay you're in charge you're you this group is in charge of IT procurement or IT development for the department</u>
<u n="95" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0264">and so he would delegate decisions <pause dur="short"/> it was quite clever really</u>
<u n="97" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0264">so you felt involved I think</u>
<u n="99" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0264">you felt that it was a kind of more a flatter organisation <pause dur="short"/> rather than having say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> making all the management decisions <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0263">mm <pause dur="short"/> anyway <pause dur="short"/> and then I've had a horrible shock cos I've seen er the accommodation here and last time it seemed to me that I paid a hundred and something for the week</u>
<u n="102" who="S0264"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0263">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0263">and erm I got a bill for two hundred and eighty a week <vocal desc="laugh"/> the only difference is that I've got a pull out bed that you can pop up <pause dur="short"/> it's the same room</u>
<u n="106" who="S0264">but that's erm you should be paying less not more if it's pull up shouldn't you? more like a studio <pause dur="short"/> than <trunc>bef</trunc></u>
<u n="107" who="S0263" trans="overlap">well I've got one bed and the pull up before it just had</u>
<u n="108" who="S0264">well why don't you ask them to change to er the other room?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0263">well I asked for a sort of family room for</u>
<u n="110" who="S0264">oh that's why</u>
<u n="111" who="S0263">for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to come</u>
<u n="112" who="S0264">that's why</u>
<u n="113" who="S0263">but actually here I'm all on my own</u>
<u n="114" who="S0264">is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not coming?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0263">he's gone off cycling</u>
<u n="116" who="S0264">where?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0263" trans="overlap">but he'll be coming down then</u>
<u n="118" who="S0264">oh <pause dur="short"/> is he in the UK?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0263">no he he <trunc>wen</trunc> he went back <pause dur="short"/> yesterday he stayed one night here <pause dur="short"/> so I oh I've got eight hundred and something <vocal desc="laugh"/> bill</u>
<u n="120" who="S0264">oh my gosh that's a lot</u>
<u n="121" who="S0263">well three weeks</u>
<u n="122" who="S0264">gosh</u>
<u n="123" who="S0263">erm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0264" trans="overlap">why couldn't you okay why don't you negotiate with them and erm <pause dur="short"/> move into <pause dur="short"/> a small room for two of the weeks? <pause dur="short"/> I mean er when is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gonna stay with you is that whole time or</u>
<u n="125" who="S0263">next week</u>
<u n="126" who="S0264">for one week or?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0263">every other night <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0264">oh I see you why every other night? that'll <trunc>disor</trunc>disorientate him</u>
<u n="129" who="S0263">because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> works every other day</u>
<u n="130" who="S0264"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> er is his <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="131" who="S0263" trans="overlap">my my brother</u>
<u n="132" who="S0264">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0263">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mum mum is too old to look after him on her own <pause dur="short"/> so she can only</u>
<u n="134" who="S0264" trans="overlap">so that's the deal</u>
<u n="135" who="S0263" trans="overlap">look after him when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> works Monday Friday Wednesday Friday <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0264">that's annoying because erm <pause dur="short"/> if you could persuade <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to have <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for a whole week then</u>
<u n="137" who="S0263">well they are this week</u>
<u n="138" who="S0264">then you could go into a smaller room</u>
<u n="139" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0264">save some money and then move back into the family room</u>
<u n="141" who="S0263">mm <pause dur="short"/> there's no difference in the size <pause dur="short"/> it's just</u>
<u n="142" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0263" trans="overlap">but it's got a slide it's you know it's those beds that fit underneath you know?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0264">yeah but they obviously make a well ask them</u>
<u n="145" who="S0263">I will I feel a bit embarrassed cos I got given the bill <vocal desc="laugh"/> sort of stood there and looked at the figure</u>
<u n="146" who="S0264">your jaw dropped</u>
<u n="147" who="S0263">and then I went off</u>
<u n="148" who="S0264"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you probably didn't even take it in did you right at that moment?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0263">I didn't take it in and then I spoke to my mother and she's last <trunc>yes</trunc> this morning and she went <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0264" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0263">ah you how are you gonna pay for that? and I was like I don't know she no <vocal desc="laugh"/> she was saying how are <trunc>y</trunc> how are you gonna pay for all these extravagances?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0264">well except it isn't <pause dur="short"/> it isn't such an extravagance is it? it's not like you're staying at I don't know the Holiday Inn or something</u>
<u n="153" who="S0263">well it would be a hundred a night if I was staying in a hotel</u>
<u n="154" who="S0264">mm <pause dur="short"/> and what what is it here? fifty something</u>
<u n="155" who="S0263" trans="overlap">thirty-seven</u>
<u n="156" who="S0264">thirty-seven that's good <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0263">so it's still quite cheap isn't it?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0264">yeah I mean it's cheaper than er <pause dur="short"/> er what do you call that chain? erm not Ibis the other one with the moon the half moon</u>
<u n="159" who="S0263">Holiday Inn?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0264">no but it's one like that</u>
<u n="161" who="S0263"><unclear/>?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0264">similar</u>
<u n="163" who="S0263">Premier Inn?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0264">yeah Premier</u>
<u n="165" who="S0263"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0264">Premier that one</u>
<u n="167" who="S0263">so</u>
<u n="168" who="S0264" trans="overlap">that's quite cheap</u>
<u n="169" who="S0263">the thing is a did get you know I pestered them to have that room with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when I was last here in March so they did they've made a sort of compromise cos I'm not really supposed to have children in there</u>
<u n="170" who="S0264">oh I see</u>
<u n="171" who="S0263">so I don't feel I want to sort of quibble now about</u>
<u n="172" who="S0264">no but you could er you could ask rather than quibble</u>
<u n="173" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0264" trans="overlap">I mean it could be a question</u>
<u n="175" who="S0263">so I could say</u>
<u n="176" who="S0264">can I check something?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="178" who="S0264">that's like how it was originally put it</u>
<u n="179" who="S0263">I was surprised at the figure cos it was I have to go back to my old emails or <pause dur="short"/> from March and see how much I paid then</u>
<u n="180" who="S0264">well</u>
<u n="181" who="S0263">it was <trunc>mu</trunc> it's this is my own fault because I didn't get the firm price through the from them it was all up in the air</u>
<u n="182" who="S0264">well you wouldn't think would you because you you've stayed there only last year <pause dur="short"/> so why would you think it would be different?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0263">well not last year er <pause dur="short"/> a few months ago</u>
<u n="184" who="S0264">oh yes it is only a few months ago</u>
<u n="185" who="S0263"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's er</u>
<u n="186" who="S0264" trans="overlap">well there you are</u>
<u n="187" who="S0263" trans="overlap">feels like a year ago</u>
<u n="188" who="S0264">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0263">so I'm gonna go back and see how much I've paid and say you know <trunc>wh</trunc> why is it double the price? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0263">and</u>
<u n="192" who="S0264" trans="overlap">no I think that's perfectly reasonable</u>
<u n="193" who="S0263" trans="overlap">it could be yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0264">I was gonna say that one of the erm <pause dur="short"/> the you know one of the changes about this place is the erm outsourcing</u>
<u n="195" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0264">but <anon type="place"/> is er independent isn't it?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0264">so</u>
<u n="199" who="S0263">what's happened about that? have they <pause dur="short"/> still all well the same staff or so it seems have they er outsourced or not?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0264">yeah they've taken the same staff on I think the existing ones are supposed to be more or less under the same conditions but all the new ones presumably under worse conditions and also <pause dur="short"/> the room at the end of my corridor with the erm researchers in there's one very dejected because he spent most of last year <pause dur="short"/> helping with the campaign</u>
<u n="201" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0264">and so he got a he didn't get his he didn't submit his PhD on time and now he's in overtime you know when you pay</u>
<u n="203" who="S0263">continuous?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0264">yeah so he pays a low fee but <pause dur="short"/> got no money coming in so</u>
<u n="205" who="S0263" trans="overlap">a continuation</u>
<u n="206" who="S0264">yeah so he's looking very sorry and</u>
<u n="207" who="S0263" trans="overlap">I didn't know you had researchers at the end you've got a study room have you at the end of your corridor?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0264">on the right hand side opposite the language study room is the researchers' room</u>
<u n="209" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0264">for the philosophy students</u>
<u n="211" who="S0263">philosopher</u>
<u n="212" who="S0264">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0263">philosophy <trunc>stu</trunc></u>
<u n="214" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's that sort of mixed corridor <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> in fact it's quite a strange corridor</u>
<u n="215" who="S0263">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="216" who="S0264">he's got some teaching coming up <pause dur="short"/> autumn term that'd bring some money in <pause dur="short"/> but until then probably living on nothing</u>
<u n="217" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0264">don't think he he's</u>
<u n="219" who="S0263" trans="overlap">I was thinking maybe I could do some work <pause dur="short"/> if it's in the summer <vocal desc="laugh"/> not that I particularly want to but</u>
<u n="220" who="S0264" trans="overlap">no and what could you do anyway? <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> it'd erm <pause dur="short"/> it could be something <pause dur="short"/> horrible like <pause dur="short"/> you know some service type thing</u>
<u n="221" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0264">well you could just be teaching and go and see erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0263">mm mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0264">and offer to <pause dur="short"/> poison the water supply</u>
<u n="225" who="S0263"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0264">and erm do some teaching cover</u>
<u n="227" who="S0263">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="228" who="S0264">I think that was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s job <pause dur="short"/> cover</u>
<u n="229" who="S0263">cover?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0264">but</u>
<u n="231" who="S0263" trans="overlap">for people who are sick</u>
<u n="232" who="S0264">yeah but if two people were sick</u>
<u n="233" who="S0263">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="234" who="S0264">or there might be some development work to do you could offer to erm <pause dur="short"/> write some materials or something</u>
<u n="235" who="S0263">mm uhu I'll have a think I'll have a look at my finances</u>
<u n="236" who="S0264">I think that's the <pause dur="short"/> that would be the best option and the better paid option compared to <pause dur="short"/> working behind a counter somewhere</u>
<u n="237" who="S0263">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="238" who="S0264">you could try the library by the way <pause dur="short"/> that wouldn't be so well paid <pause dur="short"/> often in the summer they take on people usually undergrads I think to do various weird things they don't have time for in the year</u>
<u n="239" who="S0263">oh right</u>
<u n="240" who="S0264">like vacuuming books</u>
<u n="241" who="S0263"><vocal desc="laugh"/> vacuuming books?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0264" trans="overlap">cos yeah they did that all last summer it was horrible</u>
<u n="243" who="S0263">oh yeah I tell you what after spending three weeks with my in laws I when I go back to <anon type="place"/> I'm gonna have the biggest tidy up they live</u>
<u n="244" who="S0264" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="245" who="S0263">they live <pause dur="short"/> in such clutter you can't believe it you cannot you can't even walk in and they've got both got crutches and rollators and things</u>
<u n="246" who="S0264">why?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0263">there are piles of paper every Guardian that they get and they get it every day they don't they keep they keep <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0264">every garden they? garden?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0263">every Guardian</u>
<u n="250" who="S0264">Guardian</u>
<u n="251" who="S0263" trans="overlap">paper newspaper <pause dur="short"/> so that you've got piles</u>
<u n="252" who="S0264">yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0263" trans="overlap">like ten piles of Guardians nearly like this high</u>
<u n="254" who="S0264">what does that say about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? that explains a lot doesn't it?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0263"><vocal desc="sigh"/> it's bonkers</u>
<u n="256" who="S0264" trans="overlap">I thought you can</u>
<u n="257" who="S0263">it's really bonkers <pause dur="short"/> like old estate agents magazines from nineteen eighty-five like and just clutter broken things things that are broken</u>
<u n="258" who="S0264">which they are going to repair one day</u>
<u n="259" who="S0263">so I'd say do you want to keep this? they've got three or four of everything as well <pause dur="short"/> which is very bizarre <pause dur="short"/> five potato peelers erm <pause dur="short"/> I said well shall I throw this away it's broken oh</u>
<u n="260" who="S0264">no</u>
<u n="261" who="S0263" trans="overlap">no no no no no anything you show them a piece of dirty tissue almost shall I throw this away?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0264">no recycle</u>
<u n="263" who="S0263" trans="overlap">no no no which all the erm cereal packets all the egg cartons <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's all kept which means that you just can't move er</u>
<u n="264" who="S0264" trans="overlap">when when you started that I thought you were gonna say they were hyper organised and hyper and so you were shamed into thinking you must tidy up at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0263">no well this made me think like I'm gonna <pause dur="short"/> purify my home to such an extent that there's no cos my office is a bit <vocal desc="misc"/> you know piles of paper and it's really made me want to sort of</u>
<u n="266" who="S0264">but nothing like that nothing like you what you described in</u>
<u n="267" who="S0263">no</u>
<u n="268" who="S0264"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0263"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0264"><anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> that sounds <pause dur="short"/> quite serious</u>
<u n="271" who="S0263">it's so serious</u>
<u n="272" who="S0264">cos people do get more untidy as they get older anyway</u>
<u n="273" who="S0263">do they?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0264">well I think so I read about well Iris Murdoch and her husband</u>
<u n="275" who="S0263"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0264">and they had bottles everywhere <pause dur="short"/> you know on table tops</u>
<u n="277" who="S0263">there's not a table top there's not a table top free</u>
<u n="278" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0263">er also to add to that there's mice scuttering around and pooing everywhere</u>
<u n="280" who="S0264">oh</u>
<u n="281" who="S0263"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0264">well</u>
<u n="283" who="S0263" trans="overlap">it's really really serious</u>
<u n="284" who="S0264">well it's a</u>
<u n="285" who="S0263" trans="overlap">I felt quite sick and I'm I'm quite glad I came away alive and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> too</u>
<u n="286" who="S0264">you didn't get sick?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0263">I got sick a bit actually yeah <pause dur="short"/> but we are okay and I I we tried to clean up and help but they they said that we were bullying them</u>
<u n="288" who="S0264">oh gosh</u>
<u n="289" who="S0263">they</u>
<u n="290" who="S0264" trans="overlap">how old are they?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0263">er <trunc>eigh</trunc> seventy-nine and eighty-seven</u>
<u n="292" who="S0264">eighty-seven? <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0263" trans="overlap">so they said we we were bullying them <pause dur="short"/> I thought they'd say thanks I spent hours cleaning up the kitchen</u>
<u n="294" who="S0264">we used to do the same with my mum I think my brother had a go at reorganising tidying things and er her response I think was she may have accepted when he did it but when I tried to it was very much very similar very defensive so I'd feel that I was <pause dur="short"/> almost well <pause dur="short"/> attacking her so I I you stopped</u>
<u n="295" who="S0263">mm yeah I did stop eventually cos it it's it's not a it's not something you particularly want to do is cleaning I don't particularly get much joy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0263" trans="overlap"><trunc>esp</trunc> it and you do expect a bit of thanks</u>
<u n="298" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0263">but er anyway</u>
<u n="300" who="S0264">are they erm in good health or <pause dur="short"/> despite the mice?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0263">er well for their age <pause dur="short"/> they can hardly they can't move very well they're both on crutches</u>
<u n="302" who="S0264">yeah you mentioned the crutches <pause dur="short"/> well all the more reason</u>
<u n="303" who="S0263">to <trunc>t</trunc> have</u>
<u n="304" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0263">have a clear <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0264"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0263">well</u>
<u n="308" who="S0264">well what if there's a fire or something?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0263">oh</u>
<u n="310" who="S0264">actually the</u>
<u n="311" who="S0263" trans="overlap">oh my gosh</u>
<u n="312" who="S0264">more reason why there should be a fire with all the Guardians piled up <pause dur="short"/> one drop of lighter fuel and a match <pause dur="short"/> the whole lot could go up</u>
<u n="313" who="S0263">but I I'm interested in this erm <pause dur="short"/> this hoarding what does it mean?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0264" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0263">what why? why?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0264" trans="overlap">it's called old age <pause dur="short"/> must be some genetic <pause dur="short"/> like squirrels <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0263">I realised though when I was at er a meeting I used <pause dur="short"/> the work interesting wrong in France</u>
<u n="318" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="319" who="S0263">because some somebody there was some teacher was moaning about a student you know these these Miage students they do two weeks at university and two weeks in a company?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0264" trans="overlap">company yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0263">anyway one of these guys well who well you never saw and nor did I he never turns up</u>
<u n="322" who="S0264">oh</u>
<u n="323" who="S0263">apparently at his at his job his IT job they're really happy with him and want to keep him on</u>
<u n="324" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0263">but he doesn't come to any of the courses at uni so the teachers were going oh <vocal desc="misc"/> well it's a disgrace he doesn't turn up blah blah <pause dur="short"/> but I said ah <foreign lang="fre"/> and I said <foreign lang="fre">intéressant</foreign> and I</u>
<u n="326" who="S0264">well that's the same use isn't it?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0263">it's not because one woman looked at me as I started and she went <foreign lang="fre"/> because I'd used it in a way you know one of my supervisors would have used it oh that's really interesting</u>
<u n="328" who="S0264" trans="overlap">well <trunc>curio</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0263" trans="overlap">the the dichotomy between all the contradiction</u>
<u n="330" who="S0264"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0263">you know or that's an interesting you know contradiction or something and <foreign lang="fre">intéressant</foreign> in French means that you can have gained something from it</u>
<u n="332" who="S0264">oh</u>
<u n="333" who="S0263" trans="overlap">it's interesting either <trunc>fina</trunc> you know it's that it's <trunc>g</trunc> you <trunc>s</trunc> got you get some gain or it's <trunc>g</trunc> it's worthy of some</u>
<u n="334" who="S0264" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="335" who="S0263">benefit</u>
<u n="336" who="S0264" trans="overlap"><trunc>becau</trunc>because there's that line on on the CDs I'm listening to in the car</u>
<u n="337" who="S0263">yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0264">one of the actors says so the oh <foreign lang="fre">ce est intéressant</foreign> and I thought he just meant oh that's interesting but it must be the sense that you've mentioned there</u>
<u n="339" who="S0263">well I suppose in a beginner French something maybe <pause dur="short"/> but in general it <trunc>mea</trunc> if something's <foreign lang="fre">intéressant</foreign> like a price you can say that price is interesting is French you can say <foreign lang="fre">ce prix est intéressant</foreign> it means oh I'm getting good value for money although</u>
<u n="340" who="S0264">oh</u>
<u n="341" who="S0263" trans="overlap">if it's in English you can't say that price is interesting</u>
<u n="342" who="S0264">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0263" trans="overlap">you go well there's nothing interesting about that price</u>
<u n="344" who="S0264"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0263">but in French it really means</u>
<u n="346" who="S0264">value</u>
<u n="347" who="S0263">there's a value it's it's valuable</u>
<u n="348" who="S0264">oh</u>
<u n="349" who="S0263">so when she</u>
<u n="350" who="S0264" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="351" who="S0263" trans="overlap">when I said it and I or I immediately realised my error but I then I thought I can't <pause dur="short"/> cos it was meeting of course</u>
<u n="352" who="S0264" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="353" who="S0263" trans="overlap">well I can't go on and say well the meaning in England I'm sorry I've misused the term so they were absolutely horrified</u>
<u n="354" who="S0264">of course</u>
<u n="355" who="S0263"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0264">so it's related to the English sense of interest like the interest on something</u>
<u n="357" who="S0263">yes</u>
<u n="358" who="S0264">yes</u>
<u n="359" who="S0263">yes</u>
<u n="360" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="361" who="S0263">but I'd used it wrongly in this</u>
<u n="362" who="S0264"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0263">it's not what I meant to say and what I meant to say that it was it it was in the English sense</u>
<u n="364" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah curious or</u>
<u n="365" who="S0263">curious</u>
<u n="366" who="S0264">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0263" trans="overlap">of how he could be so different how</u>
<u n="368" who="S0264"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="369" who="S0263">you know in ones milieu he was really appreciated and the other you know</u>
<u n="370" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0263">detested by</u>
<u n="372" who="S0264" trans="overlap">I <trunc>kn</trunc></u>
<u n="373" who="S0263"><vocal desc="cough"/> and</u>
<u n="374" who="S0264" trans="overlap">I didn't</u>
<u n="375" who="S0263" trans="overlap">they all looked at me or after getting my bad feedback and then <vocal desc="laugh"/> they looked at me when I said this</u>
<u n="376" who="S0264">the outcast</u>
<u n="377" who="S0263">how can <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> think this guy is a great you know? to them it was as if I was saying he was really you know great <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="378" who="S0264">a paragon</u>
<u n="379" who="S0263"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="380" who="S0264">I didn't realise they were supposed to be spending two weeks in either in both base level they were doing both at once or something</u>
<u n="381" who="S0263">two weeks on two weeks it's two weeks on and two weeks off</u>
<u n="382" who="S0264" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="383" who="S0263">yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0264">cos they weren't coming to uni everyday were they? it was just two days a week or two like erm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0263" trans="overlap">no yeah every day for two weeks</u>
<u n="386" who="S0264">oh but the rest of the time they were doing other things other classes?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0263">yeah mm</u>
<u n="388" who="S0264" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="389" who="S0263">so er</u>
<u n="390" who="S0264" trans="overlap">like IT mm</u>
<u n="391" who="S0263">I thought that was very interesting <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0264"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0263">how I'd made that error</u>
<u n="394" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="395" who="S0263">because I've been you know thinking in English</u>
<u n="396" who="S0264" trans="overlap">coming back on yeah</u>
<u n="397" who="S0263" trans="overlap">than French and I I find I do that in both languages and get misunderstood <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0264">but last last time we talked I don't mean er I mean back in April <pause dur="short"/> I I think you'd taken the decision or you felt you were becoming more French</u>
<u n="399" who="S0263">er I'd taken a decision?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0264">almost it was almost conscious or you well you were aware let's say you were self aware you were seemed to recognise that</u>
<u n="401" who="S0263">well maybe</u>
<u n="402" who="S0264">you were going into that mode or role</u>
<u n="403" who="S0263">well er yeah</u>
<u n="404" who="S0264">not surprising it <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="405" who="S0263">especially when I get a lot of erm <pause dur="short"/> a lot of my writing has to be rephrased I get a lot of style <pause dur="short"/> style errors from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0264">but that's that would happen anywhere I think <pause dur="short"/> I don't know tend to think it's a necessarily</u>
<u n="407" who="S0263">what? even if I was living in England?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0264">to an extent</u>
<u n="409" who="S0263">oh right</u>
<u n="410" who="S0264">all of us and that could have</u>
<u n="411" who="S0263" trans="overlap">yeah I think some of it's more that it's informal it's er she says it's <trunc>prob</trunc> it's probably not French it's informal she says you know</u>
<u n="412" who="S0264" trans="overlap">cos I just went through a colleague's erm it's called a scholarly piece for her PG cert at HE and they were just said you they were just personality they were just habit</u>
<u n="413" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="414" who="S0264">er I was</u>
<u n="415" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="416" who="S0264">noticing <pause dur="long"/> I'm surprised it's not more like busier I think August must be the down month</u>
<u n="417" who="S0263">oh I think it's quite busy compared to last August</u>
<u n="418" who="S0264">do you?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0263">yeah could be really quiet at night time</u>
<u n="420" who="S0264" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="421" who="S0263" trans="overlap">it's really quiet</u>
<u n="422" who="S0264">yeah of course you know there's this summer at <anon type="place"/> or whatever it's called you know these Americans doing this undergraduate</u>
<u n="423" who="S0263">oh yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0264">physics or oh</u>
<u n="425" who="S0263">last year when I was at <anon type="place"/> we these students at night were like screaming and shouting</u>
<u n="426" who="S0264">what partying and sort of</u>
<u n="427" who="S0263" trans="overlap">partying and really drunk <pause dur="short"/> I think they were the visiting</u>
<u n="428" who="S0264">probably</u>
<u n="429" who="S0263">students</u>
<u n="430" who="S0264">they seem very young <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="431" who="S0263" trans="overlap">are you working for the whole of August?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0264">yeah but</u>
<u n="433" who="S0263" trans="overlap">and then straight into the new term?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0264">no there's two weeks I have two weeks erm what's called erm <pause dur="short"/> compulsory leave you er cos you have to use it up</u>
<u n="435" who="S0263" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> so what are you going to do?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0264">well I'm going to Toulouse for</u>
<u n="437" who="S0263" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="438" who="S0264">three days</u>
<u n="439" who="S0263">three days?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0264">I decided that's all I could afford well you know the <trunc>s</trunc> it's exactly the same look at well it was gonna be Strasbourg</u>
<u n="441" who="S0263">yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0264">that that they go Gatwick to Strasbourg as well</u>
<u n="443" who="S0263">uhu</u>
<u n="444" who="S0264">and maybe I was wrong but erm <pause dur="short"/> it seemed a bit more a bit er more expensive it probably is for accommodation and cos I <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="445" who="S0263" trans="overlap">alright you alright</u>
<u n="446" who="S0264" trans="overlap">it's it's a single room it's the same idea you know gosh erm if you were two people it would cost more or less the same</u>
<u n="447" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="448" who="S0264">it's just breakfast is more</u>
<u n="449" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="450" who="S0264">erm <pause dur="short"/> so Toulouse the it is just cheaper so it probably isn't as quaint as Strasbourg</u>
<u n="451" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="452" who="S0264">so going there</u>
<u n="453" who="S0263">for three days</u>
<u n="454" who="S0264">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0263">what are you going to do just</u>
<u n="456" who="S0264" trans="overlap">three or four days</u>
<u n="457" who="S0263">walk around the town or?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0264">well it's got er the Michelin guide it's got three stars or something so <pause dur="short"/> there's lots of things to do to see apparently and you and <pause dur="short"/> my French Argentinian friend says there's places you can go to by rail or you could hire a car</u>
<u n="459" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="460" who="S0264">erm all sorts of places of interest around Toulouse</u>
<u n="461" who="S0263">mm well it's quite big I've been to Toulouse</u>
<u n="462" who="S0264">bit like Bristol isn't it I suppose? aero aero industries</u>
<u n="463" who="S0263">mm yeah it's nice it's it nice huge sort of erm <pause dur="short"/> er <trunc>squ</trunc> you know a <foreign lang="fre"/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0264">oh what the cathedral?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0263" trans="overlap">just in the centre yeah</u>
<u n="466" who="S0264">oh it sounds a bit like erm <pause dur="short"/> what's the place on the west coast of France in the middle? Bordeaux <pause dur="short"/> that's got a cathedral and a big square</u>
<u n="467" who="S0263">mm mm</u>
<u n="468" who="S0264">well I suppose most French cities <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="469" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="470" who="S0264">are like that</u>
<u n="471" who="S0263">oh well that's good</u>
<u n="472" who="S0264">yeah and the rest of the time I'm going to <anon type="place"/> for a day editing and <anon type="place"/> examining for some board and oh examining in London a couple of days <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="473" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="474" who="S0264">just the odd day to get ready for and then a week before the new term term starts <pause dur="short"/> when do you start again?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0263">er <pause dur="short"/> I'm supposed to be back on the twenty-sixth of August for a <pause dur="short"/> <foreign lang="fre">rattrapage</foreign> which is sort of when they fail they get a second chance</u>
<u n="476" who="S0264">oh yeah resits</u>
<u n="477" who="S0263">resits and erm <pause dur="short"/> I I'm actually travelling back on the twenty-sixth <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0264"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0263">so I'm not gonna be there</u>
<u n="480" who="S0264">gosh what did your but you won't be timetabled will you for</u>
<u n="481" who="S0263">I have been timetabled</u>
<u n="482" who="S0264">for that day?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0263">yes so I've got to now say sorry I'm not like gonna be there</u>
<u n="484" who="S0264">so</u>
<u n="485" who="S0263" trans="overlap">and then August as everybody just <trunc>l</trunc> isn't</u>
<u n="486" who="S0264" trans="overlap">nobody's there yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0263" trans="overlap">everything's shut it's shut <pause dur="short"/> so no one's responded to my mails and nobody knows that I'm not gonna be there</u>
<u n="488" who="S0264">but hang on this is the twenty-sixth of August</u>
<u n="489" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="490" who="S0264" trans="overlap">so it's legitimate for you not to be there because nobody is anyway in France</u>
<u n="491" who="S0263" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="492" who="S0264" trans="overlap">in August</u>
<u n="493" who="S0263">it's criminal to</u>
<u n="494" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0263"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know what he's thinking of so erm</u>
<u n="496" who="S0264">who is this person?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0263">another person who organises Miage</u>
<u n="498" who="S0264">oh</u>
<u n="499" who="S0263">well for the student who never <vocal desc="laugh"/> turned up</u>
<u n="500" who="S0264">oh is that what it is? yeah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0263">it's for this same person</u>
<u n="502" who="S0264">it's yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0263">er so I've got to <pause dur="short"/> sort that out</u>
<u n="504" who="S0264" trans="overlap">so it has to be you really because you're the one who was teaching that group <pause dur="short"/> it'll just have to be rescheduled for the next day or something</u>
<u n="505" who="S0263">yeah but I'm always a bit worried you know when you don't get a response to your email so I think oh the you know</u>
<u n="506" who="S0264" trans="overlap">have you clicked the red exclamation mark for important?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0263">no I never I've never done that before</u>
<u n="508" who="S0264">oh</u>
<u n="509" who="S0263">well I'll do the I'll send them another one</u>
<u n="510" who="S0264">yeah because if when he comes back <pause dur="short"/> if he starts from the top down instead of the bottom up then your message might be buried</u>
<u n="511" who="S0263">mm</u>
<u n="512" who="S0264">it might him several days to reach it</u>
<u n="513" who="S0263">mm that's true <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <pause dur="short"/> not looking forward to going back at all</u>
<u n="514" who="S0264">no</u>
<u n="515" who="S0263" trans="overlap">considering how bad <vocal desc="laugh"/> the <trunc>li</trunc> end of term was <pause dur="short"/> so I'll see</u>
<u n="516" who="S0264">why don't you take them some Cadbury's what do you call those things? erm assortment things <pause dur="short"/> and you get them in little boxes and tins Quality Street</u>
<u n="517" who="S0263">I've tried that approach with gifts and things</u>
<u n="518" who="S0264">doesn't it work?</u>
<u n="519" who="S0263">postcards gifts <pause dur="short"/> could try again you think that I should try?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0264"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0263"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="522" who="S0264">it er looks very</u>
<u n="523" who="S0263" trans="overlap">you're buying your friends</u>
<u n="524" who="S0264">yeah well it looks very much like a peace offering but erm it wouldn't do any harm would it?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0263">no</u>
<u n="526" who="S0264">er especially if you're going to be a day <vocal desc="laugh"/> a day late</u>
<u n="527" who="S0263">oh they're different they're different people</u>
<u n="528" who="S0264">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0263">it's not the same <pause dur="short"/> yeah could try</u>
<u n="530" who="S0264" trans="overlap">no I think you could because erm</u>
<u n="531" who="S0263">bribe them</u>
<u n="532" who="S0264">you've been away three weeks so it's like er people do don't they when they've been on holiday <pause dur="short"/> from</u>
<u n="533" who="S0263">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="534" who="S0264">yes in your room</u>
<u n="535" who="S0263" trans="overlap">yeah he edited my French article</u>
<u n="536" who="S0264">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0263">cos he's very good at French <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so I have well got that just got accepted with a few final edits</u>
<u n="538" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="539" who="S0263" trans="overlap">so he <trunc>c</trunc> recorrected that for me a second time which was really kind so he <pause dur="short"/> actually his response after this criticism of me was <pause dur="short"/> he said just very quietly <foreign lang="fre">vivre la révolution</foreign> <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's very French</u>
<u n="540" who="S0264">in the meeting?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0263">just afterwards</u>
<u n="542" who="S0264">oh I see he means <foreign lang="fre"/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0263">I don't know</u>
<u n="544" who="S0264" trans="overlap">and I'm sure it's a</u>
<u n="545" who="S0263" trans="overlap">so I and he and then he phoned me up in the evening to <trunc>s</trunc> to ask if I was okay</u>
<u n="546" who="S0264">oh maybe he wasn't meaning I see yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0263">so maybe he thought I was being sort of rebellious sort of thing</u>
<u n="548" who="S0264">oh no maybe he meant that there should be a rebellion</u>
<u n="549" who="S0263">I don't know anyway he was very kind and</u>
<u n="550" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0263" trans="overlap">he's been kind by you know doing this <trunc>e</trunc>editing for me</u>
<u n="552" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="553" who="S0263">very kindly so</u>
<u n="554" who="S0264">put this off</u>
<u n="555" who="S0263">is that enough time?</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
