<text id="SFER">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:14:51</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-02-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>4</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0012 S0013 S0278 S0370</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Relations, mistresses, party, shopping, life without power, Big Brother, dogs, church, heating.</topics>
		<activity>General chat</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inviting</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0012">
				<exactage>70</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Costessey, Norfolk</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Norfolk</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mattishal, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>38</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0013">
				<exactage>63</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harrow, Middlesex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>36 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Childminder (retired)</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0278">
				<exactage>66</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Middlesex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>9</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>proprietor</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_1</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0370">
				<exactage>62</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harrow</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Harrow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>35 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Quality &amp; Curriculum Reviewer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0278">we all had something different and two of them <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said could could we have one knickerbocker glory and two two spoons please? yeah I can do that <pause dur="short"/> well yeah yeah we had a good night why am I telling you about this? oh yes but it but it was that's she'd just had the operation done that day and there was no signal it was no it was no mobile phone in the thing or</u>
<u n="2" who="S0012" trans="overlap">didn't they?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0278">it was too low there's no mobile signal</u>
<u n="4" who="S0012">oh yeah it is very low over there innit? yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0278">there was no signal erm and erm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0013">there's there might be a</u>
<u n="7" who="S0278" trans="overlap">so anyway we we we recorded we stood up in the pub and we all sung happy birthday to her and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's she's older than me I think she had one of these tablets and propped it up at the end of the table and we stood there and and we sung happy birthday to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the pub</u>
<u n="8" who="S0012">oh lovely</u>
<u n="9" who="S0278">isn't that lovely?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0278">but the landlord brought out <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had brought a game the erm Liar Dice <pause dur="short"/> which is good fun game isn't it? except I got it all wrong at one point I shouted out seventy-four <vocal desc="laugh"/> and they all go no no you can't have seventy-four can you?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0012">no you can't</u>
<u n="14" who="S0278">there's only seven on the dice <vocal desc="laugh"/> so</u>
<u n="15" who="S0370">oh right</u>
<u n="16" who="S0278">you say er so we had another cos people hadn't played that and I oh I was about seventy-one the last time I played Liar Dice <pause dur="short"/> so so we were doing that and then the landlord came out he said I've got a better one here and it was naughty quiz game <vocal desc="laugh"/> they were all not naughty but it was slightly strange questions you know erm and yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0278">and so we we the <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> started reading I'll tell you what he said I'll hand one to each of them and one of the girls said I can't read that <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know you know things things like and what is it? who is it illegal to have intercourse with? your cousin your uncle or your grandma?</u>
<u n="19" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0278">and then we had a conversation well are you a male or a female?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0370">it would be your grandma</u>
<u n="22" who="S0278">it is your grandma yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0278">it is your grandmother</u>
<u n="25" who="S0370">it's genetic you see more than half</u>
<u n="26" who="S0278">erm so so <unclear/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0370" trans="overlap">if your combination makes more than half of the same genetics</u>
<u n="28" who="S0278">yeah but there was you know which emperor insisted that his army was followed by a load of prostitutes? well I knew the answer to that one but it it it's in they the the they were all slightly</u>
<u n="29" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0012" trans="overlap">I don't</u>
<u n="31" who="S0013">I don't</u>
<u n="32" who="S0278">pardon? you know it don't you?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="34" who="S0013" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="35" who="S0278">it's Napoleon</u>
<u n="36" who="S0012">oh course it was course it was yes</u>
<u n="37" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0278" trans="overlap">keep the soldiers keep the soldiers happy and actually it wasn't emperors I think the German army had them all following round as well during the war</u>
<u n="39" who="S0012">did they?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0278">yes they did</u>
<u n="41" who="S0370">yeah but not the same as Napoleon did</u>
<u n="42" who="S0278">not the same as Napoleon no</u>
<u n="43" who="S0012">not the same people as Napoleon</u>
<u n="44" who="S0370" trans="overlap">cos it's it's still that French that's that's that's the problem with France isn't it? they've still got this acceptability of having a mistress</u>
<u n="45" who="S0012">that's right they do yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0370">it's absolutely fine you know you can have a mistress and that's why a lot of them get themselves in to trouble still but still the French concept is it's it's okay</u>
<u n="47" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0278">so we played that quiz for a while and then and then a couple of us said no I can't read that one no no no no give me another one <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="49" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="50" who="S0370">there was that guy wasn't there? the erm the the French guy who was erm</u>
<u n="51" who="S0012">president?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0370">no no no no not the president the the one for the world wide bank or something</u>
<u n="53" who="S0012">oh yes</u>
<u n="54" who="S0370">who got into trouble?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0012">mm yes he did</u>
<u n="56" who="S0370">right and he's had another one that he's got into trouble with</u>
<u n="57" who="S0278">oh oh</u>
<u n="58" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0370" trans="overlap">cos he he going along to these parties where everybody was having sex and he didn't realise the women were paid to be there and I thought god you arrogant little old fart if somebody actually wants to go to bed with you if they're not paid</u>
<u n="60" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="62" who="S0370">he think he's a well you dirty old man basically isn't he?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0012">well they yeah they are</u>
<u n="64" who="S0370" trans="overlap">and the fact that he he actually thought these young nubile women wanted to go to bed with him</u>
<u n="65" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0012">what about that Italian president then he's just as bad ain't he?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0370">oh well they're the same in <trunc>n</trunc> it's the Italians as well you're allowed to have mistresses it's absolutely fine yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0278">but yeah that was that was a good fun evening then and and it was worth <pause dur="short"/> it was a bit of a recce cos I think you know perhaps some sometimes <unclear/> out there cos there's such a wide range of stuff they did I mean there's bits scribbled all over the place half the puddings are up above the bar and there's a board over there and we we said I can't see that board that's the board he said I'll solve that and he lifted it off the wall put the table in chair at the end of the table there you go can you see it from there? <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> but not many people there they had a fire not an <trunc>o</trunc>open one but it was</u>
<u n="71" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a lovely pub</u>
<u n="72" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0278">yeah it does</u>
<u n="74" who="S0012">you should have lived there shouldn't you?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0013" trans="overlap">that that that place we went to see there</u>
<u n="76" who="S0278" trans="overlap">bit worrying the road going there though</u>
<u n="77" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0278">it's a dodgy road</u>
<u n="79" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0013" trans="overlap">it's a hundred thousand right? a hundred thousand</u>
<u n="81" who="S0278" trans="overlap">no there's no bus is there?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0013" trans="overlap">at the back of it there's allotments</u>
<u n="83" who="S0370" whoConfidence="low">I see <unclear/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0013" trans="overlap">over the road fields absolutely stunning place it's a beautiful it's a beautiful village</u>
<u n="85" who="S0278" trans="overlap">it's a beautiful place <unclear/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0013">we were there last week we went to <unclear/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0278">when I arrived I got immediately accosted in the car park erm some oh are you on the toad watch? I said no I'm not into toad watching oh you're not toad watching? okay if you see anybody else on the toad watch we're meeting up in the in the hall because there's quite a few people in the pub tonight</u>
<u n="88" who="S0370">what in toad hall was it?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0278">no they were toad watching</u>
<u n="90" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0370">toad hall</u>
<u n="92" who="S0278">there was a whole crowd of them looking for toads</u>
<u n="93" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> he never gets a joke you know?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0278">no</u>
<u n="95" who="S0012">never ever get the joke do you?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0278">yes I do</u>
<u n="97" who="S0012">well you don't take any notice of it</u>
<u n="98" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0278">so what they were doing they they all <pause dur="short"/> er making sure the toads get across the road cos there's three big lakes around there</u>
<u n="100" who="S0370">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0278">and they're heading back <unclear>to the lakes</unclear></u>
<u n="102" who="S0370" trans="overlap">but did you not explain to them there aren't any toads out at that moment? they're all hibernating</u>
<u n="103" who="S0278">apparently they no they're on they're on the move cos</u>
<u n="104" who="S0370" trans="overlap">oh are they? alright <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0278">they wouldn't be they wouldn't be out there</u>
<u n="106" who="S0012">do do they do the <trunc>fro</trunc> the the the watch of the little ones coming over the when they when they're all born?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0278">I guess so I guess so</u>
<u n="108" who="S0012" trans="overlap">cos there are millions of them</u>
<u n="109" who="S0370">they they obviously haven't got anything worthwhile to do with their lives have they? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0278">well they all meet in the pub and have a few beers it's a and it's a good it's a social thing isn't it?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0370">well if you've had a few beers you'd probably see lots of toads then don't you?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0012" trans="overlap">but there is there is a a society the toad scraper society where they scrape them off the road and fry them up and</u>
<u n="115" who="S0278">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0370">road kill</u>
<u n="117" who="S0012">road kill yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0278">he's joking now isn't he? that is a joke isn't it?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="120" who="S0012">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0278">but <trunc>the</trunc> that's I think of all of the places well I haven't been to many places out for a meal but that that was a lovely friendly the atmosphere was lovely</u>
<u n="122" who="S0012">mm mm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0370">did they have toad in the hole then on the menu?</u>
<u n="125" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0278">no he didn't he didn't but</u>
<u n="127" who="S0012"><unclear/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0278">but</u>
<u n="129" who="S0013">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0370">he he could have put that on specially for them</u>
<u n="131" who="S0278">yeah we suggested it we suggested it</u>
<u n="132" who="S0012">did you?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0278">and he said oh d'you know I haven't thought of that</u>
<u n="134" who="S0013"><unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="135" who="S0278"><unclear/> you've just given me an idea and also when we said <pause dur="short"/> we said well well how how do you all know each other? and he said well we're all bell ringers oh we said handbell ringers <pause dur="short"/> he said oh right so what d'you do? well</u>
<u n="136" who="S0370">we ring bells</u>
<u n="137" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0278">yeah and erm you've just given me another idea when can you come back again? it was so funny</u>
<u n="139" who="S0012">did he? yeah yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="141" who="S0278">well he'll probably have an evening of bell ringers</u>
<u n="142" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0370" whoConfidence="low">that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0278">what we could do is go and just go and practise there you see</u>
<u n="145" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0370">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0278">go on <trunc>s</trunc> instead of Thursday instead of practising in the hall at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0370">he can pay you a pint each</u>
<u n="150" who="S0278">and he can pay us</u>
<u n="151" who="S0370">pint each <unclear>on</unclear> practise</u>
<u n="152" who="S0278" trans="overlap"><unclear/> and we can practise cos he's got a a games area then there's the restaurant bit's in the pub as well and then there's a pubby bit</u>
<u n="153" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0278">you know it's all but it's all open plan the whole thing</u>
<u n="155" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0370">cos if he pays you in pints that's great cos that's</u>
<u n="157" who="S0012">that'd be lovely</u>
<u n="158" who="S0370">pre tax you see so he doesn't have to pay the tax on his profit</u>
<u n="159" who="S0278">but no no no they don't nobody oh it's only <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0013">it's a lovely village it's it's one of the prettiest villages on the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0012" trans="overlap">that's a lovely little village</u>
<u n="162" who="S0278">yeah it is</u>
<u n="163" who="S0012">we went for a party there last week</u>
<u n="164" who="S0013">yeah we went to a twenty-first</u>
<u n="165" who="S0012">twenty-first one one of the children we used to <trunc>ch</trunc> to child mind</u>
<u n="166" who="S0278">oh I remember I remember where they lived</u>
<u n="167" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0278">I remember where they lived on the bend on the bend there</u>
<u n="169" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0278" trans="overlap">yeah I remember the house</u>
<u n="172" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0013">you remember? oh yeah did we come and see you?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0278">no we came past it when we were looking</u>
<u n="175" who="S0013">oh right yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh it was lovely it was really nice she was so pleased to see us</u>
<u n="176" who="S0012" trans="overlap">mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah and we got a great big hug</u>
<u n="177" who="S0013" trans="overlap">she'd been she'd just arrived home for a weekend at home</u>
<u n="178" who="S0278" trans="overlap">brilliant brilliant</u>
<u n="179" who="S0013">and celebrate her birthday cos they hadn't seen her cos she's at uni in <anon type="place"/> so but so she'd said goodbye to all her friends and come down here they followed her down</u>
<u n="180" who="S0012">they all followed all the friends followed her down</u>
<u n="181" who="S0013">they followed her down</u>
<u n="182" who="S0012">she didn't know they were all going to be there</u>
<u n="183" who="S0013" trans="overlap">she didn't know anything about it</u>
<u n="184" who="S0370">oh right</u>
<u n="185" who="S0013">and a whole crowd of them weren't there?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0012" trans="overlap">great big crowd of friends and then we walked in and she screamed didn't she?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0013" trans="overlap">and then and then we came in</u>
<u n="188" who="S0012">she went oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then she come running up to me and give me the biggest bear hug of the lot didn't she? she's so</u>
<u n="189" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> lovely</u>
<u n="190" who="S0012">yeah she is lovely</u>
<u n="191" who="S0013">that's good</u>
<u n="192" who="S0012">lovely girl lovely family er weren't they?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm yeah they're French</u>
<u n="194" who="S0012">yeah she is she is</u>
<u n="195" who="S0013" trans="overlap">well her mother's French mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0012">she came when she came over <pause dur="short"/> er to <pause dur="short"/> to England she had an accident or something didn't she?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0013">yeah that's how they met</u>
<u n="198" who="S0012"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> looked after her</u>
<u n="199" who="S0013">he helped</u>
<u n="200" who="S0012">he helped</u>
<u n="201" who="S0013">he helped her after the accident</u>
<u n="202" who="S0012">yeah helped her after the accident and then they got together and got two children</u>
<u n="203" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0012">but er he said she couldn't remember that much English she couldn't understand much English and er somebody went up to her and said can you tell me where the loos are?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0013">and she <trunc>c</trunc> she said do you want to spend a penny?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0012">do you want to make a spend a penny? do you want to spend a penny?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0013" trans="overlap">she thought <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> penny</u>
<u n="208" who="S0012">penny for what she says?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0278">ah dear</u>
<u n="210" who="S0013">things like that yeah she comes up with quite a few</u>
<u n="211" who="S0012">well when we come out with all all these silly sayings that we have</u>
<u n="212" who="S0278" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0370" trans="overlap">do you want to spend a penny?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0278">mm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0013">in hospital</u>
<u n="217" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0278">this doesn't it doesn't taste <pause dur="short"/> erm well it tastes very healthy it's got a very healthy taste but it doesn't seem to have a <unclear/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0370" trans="overlap">well basically it's biscuit butter sugar and egg and cheese</u>
<u n="220" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0013">mm all good stuff</u>
<u n="222" who="S0278">well it is all good stuff but it's it's got it has got fat in it but it doesn't it doesn't taste</u>
<u n="223" who="S0370" trans="overlap">oh I think it's probably over fifty per cent fat <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0278" trans="overlap">that's what I was going to say it's a bit bit naughty for me but I <trunc>do</trunc> it doesn't when you eat it it doesn't <pause dur="short"/> feel that way</u>
<u n="225" who="S0370">yes it's nice</u>
<u n="226" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0278">it's lovely</u>
<u n="229" who="S0013">and lemon you got lemon</u>
<u n="230" who="S0278">and lemon</u>
<u n="231" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> lemon <unclear>will</unclear> cut through the fat so that's that's <unclear/> milk</u>
<u n="232" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> compensate for it</u>
<u n="233" who="S0370" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah real lemon?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0370">real lemon zest</u>
<u n="236" who="S0012">yeah that's cut through <unclear>even fat</unclear> so it's minus fat now <unclear>for the real</unclear></u>
<u n="237" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0278">it's lovely</u>
<u n="240" who="S0012">brought that up especially for us</u>
<u n="241" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0012">and we're sharing it with you</u>
<u n="243" who="S0278" trans="overlap">no no you can't you now see I understand what you said but when you say somebody brought that up especially for you it could mean totally different</u>
<u n="244" who="S0012">well you could have brought it all all over the table you know?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0013">what could have been different?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0278">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had brought brought this up specially</u>
<u n="247" who="S0013">oh dear</u>
<u n="248" who="S0012">he he did and we reconstituted when it was here and we put it all back together again this when we took the <unclear/> to <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0013" trans="overlap">don't make it worse</u>
<u n="250" who="S0370">I wondered why that bottom was so thick that's been bugging me that</u>
<u n="251" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="252" who="S0370">never mind <pause dur="short"/> I baked that when did I bake it? it wasn't last night the night before last</u>
<u n="253" who="S0012">night before yes</u>
<u n="254" who="S0278">bit <unclear/> isn't it really?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0370"><unclear/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got a heart shaped one</u>
<u n="257" who="S0370">has she? oh</u>
<u n="258" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she she</u>
<u n="259" who="S0370" trans="overlap">she's got it yeah she said I'm I'm sneaky</u>
<u n="260" who="S0012">you're sneaky? why?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0370">she said the the email back was that was sneaky</u>
<u n="262" who="S0013">why?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0012">why was that sneaky?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0370">cos she <unclear/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0013" trans="overlap">cos you agreed not to give each other things</u>
<u n="266" who="S0370">no no she said that was sneaky and no chocolate exclamation mark cos she's given up chocolate this month</u>
<u n="267" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="268" who="S0370">she gave up alcohol last month she's given up chocolate this month</u>
<u n="269" who="S0013">really?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0278">that's good</u>
<u n="271" who="S0012">but she hadn't given up alcohol altogether that was just</u>
<u n="272" who="S0370" trans="overlap">I think she needs to join the Methodists or the Baptists or something like that</u>
<u n="273" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah well January was</u>
<u n="274" who="S0278" trans="overlap">you don't miss it <trunc>near</trunc> as much as I I mean the half of us didn't well most of us didn't drink anything in this pub <pause dur="short"/> tonic water or water one lady didn't even have the coffee she said could I just have some hot water please? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0013">oh dear</u>
<u n="276" who="S0278">well it's alright they did alright out in <unclear/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0013" trans="overlap">well if they'd want you to come back?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0278">no they did alright after the meal and actually it didn't half brighten the place up</u>
<u n="279" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh no no no no</u>
<u n="280" who="S0278" trans="overlap">we brightened the place up</u>
<u n="281" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0012">they they'd</u>
<u n="283" who="S0370" trans="overlap"><unclear/> be hoping for a quiet evening without too much work to do these people turn up they want the menu moved here the menu moved there <pause dur="short"/> they want some different things that aren't on the menu</u>
<u n="284" who="S0278" trans="overlap">we were we were we <pause dur="short"/> we were wondering though we'd sat there for ages you see we <unclear/> nothing coming up well we all had different <pause dur="short"/> so they had you know they were sorting out all these different things the veg was <trunc>fan</trunc> fabulous it was spot on the way it was cooked just crunchy you know perfect</u>
<u n="285" who="S0370" trans="overlap">well microwave probably</u>
<u n="286" who="S0278">well it was perfect</u>
<u n="287" who="S0370">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0278">and erm we were going to say oh you know when <unclear/> bit hungry sort of thing you know? and the lady who was sat behind I was sat that way and the fire was there and there was a two ladies sat on the table there eating one was quite rotund and she said well she said I do the washing up here and erm they're probably waiting for my plate cos they haven't got enough round the back for you</u>
<u n="289" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0278">so and just then her plate got collected</u>
<u n="291" who="S0012">did it?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0278">yeah it did we said you'll get it any moment now and sure enough it came out yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0370">it's well if you do veg in a in a in a you know those steam bags you get in the microwave they come out beautiful</u>
<u n="294" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0278">right a steam bag that is why I'm going wrong where do I get a steam bag from?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="298" who="S0370">erm Safeway's Tesco's</u>
<u n="299" who="S0278">oh okay</u>
<u n="300" who="S0370">no sorry not Safeway's <pause dur="short"/> morrisons <pause dur="short"/> no I <unclear/> Safeway's</u>
<u n="301" who="S0278" trans="overlap">you can't get them in Sainsbury's I like Sainsbury's now the stuff is is nice</u>
<u n="302" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0370">overpriced <pause dur="short"/> lidl</u>
<u n="304" who="S0013">they are overpriced</u>
<u n="305" who="S0278">no it's not if you're there at eight o'clock in the morning as you're going round they put out they put out all the stuff they want to reduce and they're mixed in with everything else they don't put it separate</u>
<u n="306" who="S0370">oh right</u>
<u n="307" who="S0278">and so if you're the first you know it's the early bird who'll the worm</u>
<u n="308" who="S0370">oh I see but cos the Lidl's stuff's probably cheaper than their old <unclear>stale</unclear></u>
<u n="309" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0370">stuff no seriously Lidl vegetables are really are really good</u>
<u n="311" who="S0278">they are yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0012">Tesco's vegetables</u>
<u n="314" who="S0278">Morrisons don't seem to last</u>
<u n="315" who="S0012">Tesco's vegetables</u>
<u n="316" who="S0278">oh I think they're awful yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0013">I've got no complaints about Morrisons</u>
<u n="318" who="S0370">but <trunc>Tes</trunc>Tesco's terrible shocking</u>
<u n="319" who="S0012">we like Morrisons don't we?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0370">yes</u>
<u n="321" who="S0278">they I I I think where Tesco's have gone wrong is they they became too big</u>
<u n="322" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0278">management had become slack</u>
<u n="324" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0278">and they're used to having a job now which is not hugely demanding</u>
<u n="326" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0278">cos it wasn't and they swan around doing nothing the the when you go to a Tesco's store there are always too many people doing nothing</u>
<u n="328" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0370">you know and you go to pay for something and there are two people there in the Tesco garage on the way to <anon type="place"/> I went to the Tesco's in Watford to fill up with petrol two people there that were supposedly serving plenty of people filling their cars up outside only one person was taking the money so there was a queue and the other one was counting up the money in the till well I'm sorry if there are customers</u>
<u n="330" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0370">you put that to the side you serve the customers and then you carry on when it's quiet you know and she just ignored us</u>
<u n="332" who="S0013" trans="overlap">that's not what they do</u>
<u n="333" who="S0370">and I thought that is just typical Tesco</u>
<u n="334" who="S0012" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0370">you know you go to you do the you're own scanning and you go to check out and you need somebody to okay that you're over eighteen for your bottle of wine right? erm</u>
<u n="336" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0370">you would think they could scan you wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0012">you would wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0370">and make a rough guess but anyway so you're waiting for that the red light's flashing right? and these other peoples are stood around Tesco staff are stood there doing nothing</u>
<u n="340" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/> yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0278">mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0370">while you wait for the one who is meant to be doing who has probably gone off to the loo or something and finally comes back and starts doing something else and suddenly finally notices that you've got a red light flashing</u>
<u n="343" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0370">and deals with it to my mind if the red light's flashing right they should be multi talking trained you haven't got a customer over there at customer services you come straight over and say right are you?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yes that's right</u>
<u n="347" who="S0370"><unclear/> do that and go back</u>
<u n="348" who="S0012" trans="overlap">sometimes you have to wait ages when that light's flashing</u>
<u n="349" who="S0370">yeah yeah and that that's that's that's wrong you see and they get that wrong all the way along</u>
<u n="350" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0012">that's funny cos this morning</u>
<u n="352" who="S0370">and it is that that they do wrong</u>
<u n="353" who="S0278">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0370">yeah a lot of staff</u>
<u n="355" who="S0012" trans="overlap">this morning on</u>
<u n="356" who="S0370">I'm I haven't finished yet</u>
<u n="357" who="S0012">yeah okay</u>
<u n="358" who="S0370" trans="overlap">they think the store is there for them to have a job <pause dur="short"/> not that they have a job because there are customers in the store</u>
<u n="359" who="S0012">can I now speak?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0370" trans="overlap">yeah you can now I've finished now</u>
<u n="361" who="S0012">sir please? no</u>
<u n="362" who="S0370">I wanted to get that bit in</u>
<u n="363" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><unclear/> finished <unclear/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0370">have you forgotten it?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0012">on <trunc>Tes</trunc> on on the television this morning was a a programme called Click now Tesco's and other supermarkets and the police and they're now going to have facial recognition <pause dur="short"/> in their <pause dur="short"/> in the shops</u>
<u n="366" who="S0370">right</u>
<u n="367" who="S0012">and the police have got facial recognition all outside like in cameras all outside</u>
<u n="368" who="S0370">right</u>
<u n="369" who="S0012">so Tesco's will now recognise your face know what you're buying</u>
<u n="370" who="S0370">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0012">and then you get it all sorted out for you all the time</u>
<u n="372" who="S0370">what do you mean sorted out for you?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0012">well you get when you go in there he is again</u>
<u n="374" who="S0370">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0012">it's all straight they got all the stuff that you buy all stacked up and done</u>
<u n="376" who="S0013">oh that's silly</u>
<u n="377" who="S0370">oh I see</u>
<u n="378" who="S0013">bought it this week</u>
<u n="379" who="S0012" trans="overlap">well they <unclear/> it all in</u>
<u n="380" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="381" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0370">so they'll have it there ready for you just to pay with the card and go</u>
<u n="383" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah that's it yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0370">oh</u>
<u n="385" who="S0012">supposedly</u>
<u n="386" who="S0013">but you don't want things every week</u>
<u n="387" who="S0370">yeah but you can probably select them can't you?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0278">a lot of people shopping is the only exercise they get you know I make a point of parking away if I can and walk in and walk then the the more well the well taken to the ultimate stage people stay at home and it all gets brought to them</u>
<u n="389" who="S0012">that's great</u>
<u n="390" who="S0278" trans="overlap">you know that's no good</u>
<u n="391" who="S0012">that's great</u>
<u n="392" who="S0278">yeah but it's no good if people need to do a little bit of exercise in their life so they're not just sat watching the box all day</u>
<u n="393" who="S0370" trans="overlap">well no if you have shopping delivered you can be at the gym while it's</u>
<u n="394" who="S0012">yeah you can</u>
<u n="395" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0278" trans="overlap">yeah and pay to exercise rather than doing just</u>
<u n="397" who="S0012">all round the <unclear>aisles</unclear></u>
<u n="398" who="S0370">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> pays for the whole year you see so she goes as many times as she wants</u>
<u n="399" who="S0012">and she goes running <unclear/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0370" trans="overlap">and gets the parking gets a free parking ticket</u>
<u n="401" who="S0278">no there's there's a friend of mine in the TA old <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he he was a erm barristers' clerk in in <anon type="place"/> and he lived in <anon type="place"/> and</u>
<u n="402" who="S0370">and he jogged to work?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0278" trans="overlap">and it's expensive no it's really expensive parking in Leeds so it it was cheaper for him to buy a year's subscription to to a gym he used to park in the gym he used to go for a swim have a have a have a shower get changed</u>
<u n="404" who="S0370">then go to work</u>
<u n="405" who="S0278" trans="overlap">go and walk into work from there leave his car there come back and he can have a shower at the end of the day before he went home as well</u>
<u n="406" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="408" who="S0278">and so he got free parking for the whole day</u>
<u n="409" who="S0013">wow</u>
<u n="410" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0370">yeah yeah I could see that probably working actually yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0012">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0278">that could work well you wouldn't get free parking for a long time in <anon type="place"/> would you if you did that <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0012">well the nicest thing about living here is we can just get this</u>
<u n="415" who="S0278" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0012">park up the road get on the bus and go to Norwich for nothing</u>
<u n="417" who="S0278">that's right yeah I I got one of them cards too</u>
<u n="418" who="S0012">yeah you haven't used yours yet have you?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0278">yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0278">are you?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0012">yeah but you travel to <anon type="place"/> and get on the bus</u>
<u n="423" who="S0278" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="424" who="S0370">have you got a basket on wheels?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0013" trans="overlap">no no he doesn't no</u>
<u n="426" who="S0278" trans="overlap">no there is a no there</u>
<u n="427" who="S0013">no he goes to the park and ride</u>
<u n="428" who="S0278">I'll work it out for you one day but erm <pause dur="short"/> the</u>
<u n="429" who="S0012">there is no need that don't matter how long it takes to get there we get there free we don't have to drive to the park and ride pay for your park and ride get on the bus</u>
<u n="430" who="S0370">have you got a a a a basket on wheels for your shopping?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0012">no we haven't not yet not yet</u>
<u n="432" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0370">no I think they're a good idea actually</u>
<u n="434" who="S0278">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0370">mum had a superb one didn't she that you pushed?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0013">I suppose she did yeah that's alright if you're walking everywhere isn't it?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0278" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">it is yeah yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0370">but when I stop working I've got my bike all set up cos I've got my I've got by bike on this cycle to work scheme</u>
<u n="439" who="S0012">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0370">this was ages ago it was when I was at <anon type="place"/> centre</u>
<u n="441" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0013">yeah <unclear/> can do that</u>
<u n="443" who="S0370">they had this scheme so I did this cycle to work scheme</u>
<u n="444" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="445" who="S0370">and they</u>
<u n="446" who="S0012">free bike</u>
<u n="447" who="S0370">they took months to process the blasted thing months and months I I was leaving and they</u>
<u n="448" who="S0278" trans="overlap">by the time they</u>
<u n="449" who="S0370">when they processed it you see and I said well I'm not going to be cycling to <anon type="place"/> so do I need to you know pay it off? and they said no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that's fine</u>
<u n="450" who="S0012">oh wow</u>
<u n="451" who="S0370">so I got my bike at half price and tax free</u>
<u n="452" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0278" whoConfidence="low">mm mm</u>
<u n="454" who="S0013">that's what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't they? they got their bikes</u>
<u n="455" who="S0012">yes they did yeah yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0370" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="457" who="S0012">it's a good idea</u>
<u n="458" who="S0013">they just took off so much per week anyway didn't they?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0013">out of their wages</u>
<u n="461" who="S0012" trans="overlap">you can pick up a bike ride it to where you want leave it there somebody else will come along and pick up the bike ride it where you wanna go leave it there somebody else come along pick up the bike ride it leave it there you can leave your bikes all</u>
<u n="462" who="S0370" trans="overlap">oh the white bike scheme?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0370">yeah they did that in Oxford as well but the people started nicking them by the lorry load</u>
<u n="465" who="S0012">did they?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0370">well they turned up at night and just loaded them on the lorry and drove off</u>
<u n="467" who="S0012">did they? oh god</u>
<u n="468" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0370">you see which is a shame cos that's a nice way of doing it</u>
<u n="470" who="S0012">yes it is</u>
<u n="471" who="S0013" trans="overlap">it is lovely yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0012">yeah well they still they still</u>
<u n="473" who="S0013" trans="overlap">well usually they're so old looking aren't they?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0370">yeah but they've <unclear/> out to eastern Europe or something so?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0013">mm yeah</u>
<u n="478" who="S0370">they wouldn't have been sold in this country</u>
<u n="479" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="480" who="S0370">they all <unclear>out to</unclear> Africa</u>
<u n="481" who="S0278" trans="overlap">they sent they sent a load out to erm Gambia once cos the kids walked about sort of four miles to school and four miles back</u>
<u n="482" who="S0370" trans="overlap">that's right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0278">so they gave them to kids but when they left the school they had to hand them in they were for kids to use at the school</u>
<u n="484" who="S0012" trans="overlap"><unclear/> they give them puncture outfits?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0370" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> school <anon type="place"/> school now give every single pupil a erm <pause dur="short"/> a Samsung equivalent to a er a a Chromebook</u>
<u n="486" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0370">every pupil gets one</u>
<u n="488" who="S0012">Samsung help with that</u>
<u n="489" who="S0370">right they pay a deposit and they have to return it when they leave right?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0278">mm</u>
<u n="491" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="492" who="S0370">alright? the thing is they buy them in bulk you you can get them now for probably forty forty pound I should think</u>
<u n="493" who="S0012">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0370">if you buy in bulk yeah? erm and what's brilliant about it they've all got a Chrome book right? so they can all log onto Google Drive</u>
<u n="495" who="S0012">mm</u>
<u n="496" who="S0370">yeah? as an educational establishment if you join Google Drive <pause dur="short"/> right? you have limitless storage</u>
<u n="497" who="S0012">wow</u>
<u n="498" who="S0370">okay? and all your pupils you can set them up with a Gmail account in advance and you can do that on the you can't do that unless you you've enrolled</u>
<u n="499" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="500" who="S0370">it doesn't cost anything</u>
<u n="501" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="502" who="S0370">right? all Google wants is to people to be thinking Google</u>
<u n="503" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0370">there's nothing else in it for them</u>
<u n="505" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="506" who="S0370">no advertising on it at all so when they log on to Google drive you don't have to have any there's no software on a Chromebook you see? cos you go in the cloud and you use the word processor and the Excel well not Excel but the spreadsheet the presentation software that's on Google Drive so it's all in the cloud right?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0278" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="508" who="S0370">erm all their they have access to folders cos if you if you set up Google Drive you can give different people access to different folders to see different folders of yours you can share the access with them so those who are on the geography GCSE course the head of geography shares or somebody on the behalf of them shares all the folders that they need for their geography work so the reading material the assignments the homework it's all there</u>
<u n="509" who="S0012" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="510" who="S0278">clever innit?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0370">right so you don't need to hand out you don't need to print off homework sheets</u>
<u n="512" who="S0278">yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0370">so all that photocopying during the year you don't have to do assignments are handed in online</u>
<u n="514" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0370">you don't have it's absolutely superb yeah</u>
<u n="516" who="S0013" trans="overlap">brilliant <pause dur="short"/> absolutely brilliant</u>
<u n="517" who="S0278">but how do you know the person who's got that book is actually the the lad that's supposed to be doing the work to hand in the assignment could he?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0370" trans="overlap">you don't no</u>
<u n="519" who="S0278">could he give it to his brother to do all the work and then put</u>
<u n="520" who="S0370" trans="overlap">yes but they can do you can do that anyway <pause dur="short"/> once you word process it at home and print it out what's the difference?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0278">homework</u>
<u n="523" who="S0370">there's no difference</u>
<u n="524" who="S0012">homework</u>
<u n="525" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0012">you get homework from the teacher</u>
<u n="527" who="S0370">you know do you have samples of their handwriting when you're marking to check it's their hand writing? no</u>
<u n="528" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0278">but you you get to know a lot of people's handwriting</u>
<u n="530" who="S0370">precisely so that's all you need so if the work clearly is way above their ability</u>
<u n="531" who="S0278">then I suppose how <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah you have to question it</u>
<u n="533" who="S0370" trans="overlap">and lots of schools and colleges they use what's called turn it in which will scan <pause dur="short"/> will scan a piece of work and say whether it's all been written by the same person</u>
<u n="534" who="S0278">oh I see right</u>
<u n="535" who="S0370">right? well it sometimes works and sometimes doesn't but it it's reasonably reliable at picking out passages that have been copied off the internet</u>
<u n="536" who="S0278" trans="overlap">didn't they they do that for the end of of uni don't they I think?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0370" trans="overlap">yeah unis use turn it in as well yeah yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0278">so they so they know you haven't pinched it all off the internet</u>
<u n="539" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="540" who="S0370">that's right <pause dur="short"/> unless you pinched it all off the same place on the internet <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="542" who="S0278">the only only thing I'd <trunc>si</trunc> brilliant idea and the thing is are we gonna end up with a whole load of kids who <trunc>fi</trunc> who won't be able to write?</u>
<u n="543" who="S0012">this is a problem</u>
<u n="544" who="S0370" trans="overlap">well the question is do you need to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0278" trans="overlap"><unclear/> won't be able to work to that <pause dur="short"/> well you yes you do if the whole lot goes completely tits up and packs in</u>
<u n="546" who="S0370">well how can it?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0278">if there's a big war and infrastructure gets zapped then it'll all pack up <pause dur="short"/> I doubt if it's working in the Ukraine at the minute</u>
<u n="548" who="S0012" trans="overlap">plus</u>
<u n="549" who="S0370">the Ukraine <unclear/> I mean you can you're your computer you at a guess they could easily design computers that run off battery actually well they do don't they? laptops sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="550" who="S0278">but you need power to charge them</u>
<u n="551" who="S0370">huh?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0278">you need power to charge them if if you so what do you do?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0370" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="554" who="S0012">but there's also</u>
<u n="555" who="S0370" trans="overlap">generator generator</u>
<u n="556" who="S0012">there's also a growing sun spot</u>
<u n="557" who="S0278" trans="overlap">no fuel</u>
<u n="558" who="S0370">what?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0278">no fuel</u>
<u n="560" who="S0370">well in that case you're kaput anyway <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> you know forget about that</u>
<u n="561" who="S0278" trans="overlap">but if you <unclear/></u>
<u n="562" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0370">you know if if so if you're down to the level where you've got no electricity no fuel nothing</u>
<u n="564" who="S0278">mm</u>
<u n="565" who="S0370">well everything's gone</u>
<u n="566" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="567" who="S0370">you know? forget about technology your food processing won't take place <pause dur="short"/> nothing will happen your food won't be able to be packaged <pause dur="short"/> nothing will work</u>
<u n="568" who="S0278" trans="overlap">well that's true but but but it's getting you at the minute we could go back to basics couldn't we? the real basics we've still got cash we can still write <pause dur="short"/> you know we we we could go right back to basics couldn't we?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0370">yeah</u>
<u n="570" who="S0278">and we we we know how to cook we know how to forage we know the things we</u>
<u n="571" who="S0370" trans="overlap">sorry no gas I thought you said no fuel?</u>
<u n="572" who="S0278">no no we wood</u>
<u n="573" who="S0013">no yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0278">wood</u>
<u n="575" who="S0370">yeah but</u>
<u n="576" who="S0278">pot outside</u>
<u n="577" who="S0370">yeah but</u>
<u n="578" who="S0013">it would be <trunc>di</trunc>difficult but</u>
<u n="579" who="S0278">it would be difficult but we could cope and we could cope and we could keep warm and we could survive but when you get <trunc>ev</trunc>everybody relies completely on the technology and it can't be done without it</u>
<u n="580" who="S0013">I still think</u>
<u n="581" who="S0278">then</u>
<u n="582" who="S0370">they could still go out in the wood and chop some wood</u>
<u n="583" who="S0278"><unclear>what to cook?</unclear></u>
<u n="584" who="S0013" trans="overlap">still most most people would <unclear/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0370" trans="overlap">you'd do the basics you'd just forget about the rest but the rest will go anyway you know but I mean everything will go if you've got no fuel nobody is going to be delivering food to the shops</u>
<u n="586" who="S0278">no</u>
<u n="587" who="S0370">there'll be no food moving around</u>
<u n="588" who="S0012">no</u>
<u n="589" who="S0370">you'd have to go forage for yourself so</u>
<u n="590" who="S0278" trans="overlap"><unclear/> can you imagine what it be like say I know we talked about this about the fuel about er electricity the network feeding in but if it all went if London lost its power completely <pause dur="short"/> erm for for say a week because of some disaster something got flooded or you know erm I don't know what would happen say the Thames went into the flooded into the underground system well I mean it's up above it anyway isn't it?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0370">mm</u>
<u n="592" who="S0278">and if that got into it and then the whole all the electrics went <vocal desc="misc"/> and and it</u>
<u n="593" who="S0370" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well the underground have got their own electricity</u>
<u n="594" who="S0278">I know but but once it's flooded then you can't you've got to unflood it to get it going again haven't you? and then and then that would probably knock out other bits so</u>
<u n="595" who="S0370" trans="overlap">no it won't cos it's their own</u>
<u n="596" who="S0278">oh okay well</u>
<u n="597" who="S0013">yeah but if everything did go</u>
<u n="598" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="599" who="S0278">if everything did go in the whole of London</u>
<u n="600" who="S0370">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="601" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="602" who="S0278">erm there's no power at all in the whole of London</u>
<u n="603" who="S0278">mm</u>
<u n="604" who="S0278">absolute chaos wouldn't that be?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0013">it would be</u>
<u n="606" who="S0370" trans="overlap">it would be yeah yeah</u>
<u n="607" who="S0278">cos everything would stop nothing would be able to work cos it has to be <unclear/> everything</u>
<u n="608" who="S0012" trans="overlap">there's one of the thing that can wipe out just about every computer in the world and that's the sun</u>
<u n="609" who="S0278">well there's the what is it they taught us in the army? there's electromagnetic force</u>
<u n="610" who="S0012">there's sun spots</u>
<u n="611" who="S0278" trans="overlap">EMF yeah which comes from the sun</u>
<u n="612" who="S0012" trans="overlap">sun spots which come from the sun and they</u>
<u n="613" who="S0278" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="614" who="S0012">they they can they can wipe out all the satellites the whole lot of them</u>
<u n="615" who="S0278" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well they could do the satellites but they they did all the main computers are protected they're inside a screen so the EMF can't get in</u>
<u n="616" who="S0012">yeah but you wouldn't you wouldn't get the cloud anymore you wouldn't get all the because that'll work from the satellites</u>
<u n="617" who="S0370">no it doesn't the cloud is nothing I thought that</u>
<u n="618" who="S0012">did you?</u>
<u n="619" who="S0370">the word <trunc>clou</trunc> no they're not</u>
<u n="620" who="S0278">it's not <unclear/> no they're not</u>
<u n="621" who="S0370">they're all on the ground</u>
<u n="622" who="S0278">mm</u>
<u n="623" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="624" who="S0278">a lot of the the the</u>
<u n="625" who="S0012" trans="overlap">nevertheless that would wipe out a lot of</u>
<u n="626" who="S0370" trans="overlap">I <trunc>th</trunc>that's exactly what I thought they said in the cloud I assumed it was a satellite</u>
<u n="627" who="S0012">yes</u>
<u n="628" who="S0370">and it's not no in actual fact they tend to be in the cold areas of of of the world</u>
<u n="629" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="630" who="S0370">right? near the poles so that they don't have to cool them</u>
<u n="631" who="S0012">have you seen Google's?</u>
<u n="632" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="633" who="S0278">it's not one there's lots of them lots of them all working together yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0370" trans="overlap">oh there's loads of them all over the place</u>
<u n="635" who="S0012">have you seen Google Google's stuff that they got their their their er what do you call them? <pause dur="short"/> er hard drive things they're bigger than several football pitches put together</u>
<u n="636" who="S0278">right</u>
<u n="637" who="S0012">and the heat that's why the keep them up there up there the heat is so intense coming off they have to keep them</u>
<u n="638" who="S0278">that's why</u>
<u n="639" who="S0012">cool</u>
<u n="640" who="S0278">the <trunc>no</trunc> the poles are are melting</u>
<u n="641" who="S0012" trans="overlap">are melting</u>
<u n="642" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="643" who="S0370">it's the hard drive Google's hard drive</u>
<u n="644" who="S0278">yes</u>
<u n="645" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="646" who="S0278">yes it is <trunc>i</trunc> I it kind of I I do we we're getting right away from the way we were meant to be</u>
<u n="647" who="S0370" trans="overlap">I don't think I don't think it I think the <trunc>technol</trunc> we're we're in the technology age aren't we?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0278" trans="overlap">yes we are</u>
<u n="649" who="S0370">okay</u>
<u n="650" who="S0278">but we've been in both</u>
<u n="651" who="S0370" trans="overlap"><unclear>well</unclear> the computer age but when the industrial age started I bet people said</u>
<u n="652" who="S0278" trans="overlap">it's exactly the same thing</u>
<u n="653" who="S0012">they had riots</u>
<u n="654" who="S0370">you know we use to have potters and weavers and so on it's all now done in a factory what happens if the factory shuts down? nobody is gonna have any shoes or any pots or any clothes</u>
<u n="655" who="S0278" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="656" who="S0370"><trunc>e</trunc>exactly the same thing</u>
<u n="657" who="S0012">yeah oh</u>
<u n="658" who="S0278" trans="overlap"><unclear/> now what was it? I I read just yesterday the guy that invented the world wide web</u>
<u n="659" who="S0012">yeah he's English</u>
<u n="660" who="S0278" trans="overlap">he's he's worried about he's worried about some of the erm</u>
<u n="661" who="S0012" trans="overlap">or British</u>
<u n="662" who="S0278">of the way the way it's going and I can't remember what it was it was it was yesterday I read it</u>
<u n="663" who="S0370">oh right</u>
<u n="664" who="S0278">I read it on the BBC News on the internet and he's <trunc>wo</trunc> he's worried about the way one particular area is going</u>
<u n="665" who="S0012">he actually gave it to the world</u>
<u n="666" who="S0278">mm</u>
<u n="667" who="S0013"><unclear/> social <unclear/></u>
<u n="668" who="S0278" trans="overlap">maybe it was to do with erm these television these Samsung televisions that actually could listen in to your conversation</u>
<u n="669" who="S0012">oh isn't that terrible?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0278">yeah but but how do we know there's not loads more things like that?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0370">they could well</u>
<u n="673" who="S0278" trans="overlap">how do we know they're not listening in on the cloud to what's going on here there and everywhere?</u>
<u n="674" who="S0012">well they probably do</u>
<u n="675" who="S0370">they do</u>
<u n="676" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="677" who="S0370">every single mobile call is recorded</u>
<u n="678" who="S0278">oh and yeah yeah</u>
<u n="679" who="S0012" trans="overlap">and every single email can be read by the GHQ in England or in America</u>
<u n="680" who="S0278" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well that's fair enough cos if you're not up to mischief then you you shouldn't have any worries about it <pause dur="short"/> but I dunno</u>
<u n="681" who="S0013">we thought a long time ago that television <unclear/></u>
<u n="682" who="S0370" trans="overlap">they they don't seem to do it very well do they? cos <unclear/> but the the I I I think quite often the the the secret service or whoever it is you know they do this little bit of publicity about you know well in actual fact you know there were thirty-five terrorist risks that were you know prevented because of our work and I think oh yeah that's what you say you just to make that you're still getting the <unclear/> for sitting around nothing</u>
<u n="683" who="S0012">well yeah and what they do is look for key words</u>
<u n="684" who="S0370" trans="overlap"><unclear/> around yeah</u>
<u n="685" who="S0012">key words if they look at we we have a programme well we've probably told you about this we had a programme on our first IBM computer right? and we could talk and it was voice recognition and everything and we talked into it didn't we?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0370" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="687" who="S0013">we talked into it and it prints out</u>
<u n="688" who="S0012">and then it printed out what we said</u>
<u n="689" who="S0370">yeah</u>
<u n="690" who="S0012">well according to what we'd said we'd said that Reagan and Margaret Thatcher were getting ready for a world war <pause dur="short"/> and that was all on</u>
<u n="691" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><unclear/> and we and we were only</u>
<u n="692" who="S0012">and we were only talking like what you and I are talking now</u>
<u n="693" who="S0013">yeah and then we thought we'd read out of a book like Jack and the Beanstalk</u>
<u n="694" who="S0012">yeah Jack and the Beanstalk</u>
<u n="695" who="S0013">and it was the same kind of thing</u>
<u n="696" who="S0012">and it came out the same thing</u>
<u n="697" who="S0278" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh right</unclear></u>
<u n="698" who="S0370">well there we are</u>
<u n="699" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="700" who="S0012">and this was an IBM computer so you know nowadays we'd have had the FBI round here with guns and what have you <pause dur="short"/> because they'd thought we'd have said something wrong <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="701" who="S0013">obviously it's more sophisticated now</u>
<u n="702" who="S0012">well that is more sophisticated now but it weren't then were it?</u>
<u n="703" who="S0013" trans="overlap">you can ask them questions can't you?</u>
<u n="704" who="S0012">but don't it make you wonder what's going to happen in twenty thirty years time?</u>
<u n="705" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="706" who="S0012">where will the world be then?</u>
<u n="707" who="S0278">ah I dread to think with the way things are going</u>
<u n="708" who="S0012" trans="overlap">we'll have chips on like like your dog</u>
<u n="709" who="S0278">mm? <trunc>wha</trunc></u>
<u n="710" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah I'm sure we will</u>
<u n="711" who="S0012">we'll have chips</u>
<u n="712" who="S0013">chips</u>
<u n="713" who="S0278" trans="overlap">that <unclear>went</unclear> ever so quick you know with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> with the but it's it's it's like a grain of rice apparently and and the machine is like it's like that</u>
<u n="714" who="S0370">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0278">and and the tube is cut at a slant a sharp slant and she just got down on the floor with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and said come on</u>
<u n="716" who="S0370" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> pokes it in</u>
<u n="717" who="S0278">just just er pinched his skin together and went <vocal desc="misc"/> done</u>
<u n="718" who="S0370">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="719" who="S0278">you see</u>
<u n="720" who="S0370">well when did you get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> done?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0278">recently it was free when <unclear/></u>
<u n="722" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="723" who="S0278">was it when were you there with?</u>
<u n="724" who="S0370">it was free?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0278">no no day day before yesterday <unclear/> cos yesterday <unclear/> okay</u>
<u n="726" who="S0370">why was it free?</u>
<u n="727" who="S0278" trans="overlap">it's it's it's being paid for by the dog's homing trust <pause dur="short"/> my vet did it</u>
<u n="728" who="S0013">if you have something else <unclear/></u>
<u n="729" who="S0278">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh and they just</u>
<u n="730" who="S0013" trans="overlap">annual check or something</u>
<u n="731" who="S0278">they just you know it was fifty pound for the annual check and all the stuff</u>
<u n="732" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="733" who="S0278">erm forty-five and then it's fifty pounds for his wormer and stuff</u>
<u n="734" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="735" who="S0278" trans="overlap">wasn't it? this last time erm they they've now just sent out a thing that it it all fell to bits that veterinary practice cos the two key people went off and set up another one they wanted to buy it they weren't allowed to they set up another one in <anon type="place"/> and they drew all the customers along to <anon type="place"/> cos they like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> you see so all the ladies have followed <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to <anon type="place"/> but what they've got there now is a lovely lady she's really <trunc>s</trunc> erm what's her name? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="736" who="S0013">I don't know</u>
<u n="737" who="S0278">lovely lady and there's a Polish lass as well there's two others so they've got four vets and they've just put out another bumf about who they are all the new vets are there and I met the two of them and they're brilliant and they they're starting a healthy pet club and for nine ninety-nine per that's the lowest maybe it goes up with the age of the dog nine ninety-nine a month you get everything you get your flee your worm two annual checks erm and a few other things on the list erm and that'll work out far cheaper cos at the minute you know before lots of just before lots of medicine for Tobyover the year every three months you've got to do him that comes to erm that's a hundred two hundred pound</u>
<u n="738" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="739" who="S0278">that's two hundred pound and this this if it's nine ninety-nine a month what's that that's?</u>
<u n="740" who="S0370" trans="overlap">sounds a bargain</u>
<u n="741" who="S0278">it's an absolute bargain <unclear/> month</u>
<u n="742" who="S0370" trans="overlap">okay get signed up</u>
<u n="743" who="S0278">hundred <trunc>t</trunc> one hundred and twenty is it?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="745" who="S0278">hundred a twenty for the lot</u>
<u n="746" who="S0013" trans="overlap">as long as it includes everything you're used to</u>
<u n="747" who="S0278">oh it'll be the same stuff cos they that's what they <unclear/> same stuff yeah</u>
<u n="748" who="S0013">good</u>
<u n="749" who="S0012">sounds good</u>
<u n="750" who="S0278">so so that sounds good so I think I'm going to go for that <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does it for her two dogs but she's gone to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="751" who="S0013">but don't do it yet</u>
<u n="752" who="S0278" trans="overlap">which is no good what's the point in having a vet in <anon type="place"/> if your dog cuts himself?</u>
<u n="753" who="S0013" trans="overlap">don't join them yet</u>
<u n="754" who="S0012">well that's just <unclear/></u>
<u n="755" who="S0278" trans="overlap">and is bleeding you've got to got to drive to <anon type="place"/> you're going to drive to the nearest vet aren't you?</u>
<u n="756" who="S0012">that's the same with er what's the point in having a dentist in London <pause dur="short"/> you know?</u>
<u n="757" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="758" who="S0370">we'll leave that one I think</u>
<u n="759" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="760" who="S0278" trans="overlap">oh there is there is a good reason for that <pause dur="short"/> it's alright</u>
<u n="761" who="S0012"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah</u>
<u n="762" who="S0278">he's fantastic he's very good <pause dur="short"/> and this time when I go down and take <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> back I'm going to the dentist so it doesn't cost</u>
<u n="763" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="764" who="S0013">you do seem to go more often than we do we only go every nine months</u>
<u n="765" who="S0278" trans="overlap">it's twice <pause dur="short"/> it's twice a year that you should have a check</u>
<u n="766" who="S0370">well I went to the dentist last <pause dur="short"/> monday</u>
<u n="767" who="S0012">yeah?</u>
<u n="768" who="S0370">and he did that you know that very high white grating ultra cleaning thing</u>
<u n="769" who="S0012">oh right oh sounds horrible</u>
<u n="770" who="S0370" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> I hate that yeah</u>
<u n="771" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="772" who="S0370">yeah and then <vocal desc="laugh"/> Monday evening one of my fillings fell out</u>
<u n="773" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="774" who="S0370">and he said oh everything's absolutely fine I'll just give them a quick clean for you and I think the vibrator just loosened it all up</u>
<u n="775" who="S0013" trans="overlap">well I I won't have it and <pause dur="short"/> I haven't had it in years have I?</u>
<u n="776" who="S0370" trans="overlap">so I'm gonna go back again</u>
<u n="777" who="S0012" trans="overlap">no you don't no</u>
<u n="778" who="S0013">the cleaning cos I don't like it anyway cos it hurts my teeth for about three weeks <pause dur="short"/> and erm I told her I didn't want it again she said well you really should have so I <pause dur="short"/> agreed cos it was a new dentist <pause dur="short"/> and it and it <pause dur="short"/> cracked I've got a crack in my tooth now and and I now</u>
<u n="779" who="S0278" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah mine puts a funny brush in the paste</u>
<u n="780" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="781" who="S0278">he has a brush and he dips it in some paste and and he does it he's he's not he's not the hygienist it's not something they normally do they have a separate hygienist cos he knows I come his parents live at <anon type="place"/> so he knows how far I come and erm and he always cleans them for me as well</u>
<u n="782" who="S0013">yeah well I don't</u>
<u n="783" who="S0278" trans="overlap">part of the inspection</u>
<u n="784" who="S0013">I'm not going to have it er done again cos I <trunc>ken</trunc> I know they pick out all the little <pause dur="short"/> particles if there's anything there's gonna come out they pull it out</u>
<u n="785" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="786" who="S0278">well you want it come out so that the</u>
<u n="787" who="S0013" trans="overlap">not really no</u>
<u n="788" who="S0370" trans="overlap">it was probably loose anyway <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="789" who="S0278">it would have come out eventually</u>
<u n="790" who="S0013" trans="overlap">well I don't <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> full time</u>
<u n="791" who="S0012">yes well you're you're filling fell out was that? vibrated out?</u>
<u n="792" who="S0370" whoConfidence="low">probably yeah</u>
<u n="793" who="S0012">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and that's why they do it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="794" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="795" who="S0370"><unclear/></u>
<u n="796" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><unclear/> get some work</u>
<u n="797" who="S0012" trans="overlap">let me see what <unclear/> we can find out what went wrong and maybe <unclear/> oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna fall out eh here it come out come</u>
<u n="798" who="S0278" trans="overlap"><unclear/> to ask it's always embarrassing when I go cos he's now got the nurse that I sent the valentine card to all those years ago</u>
<u n="799" who="S0013">is she still there?</u>
<u n="800" who="S0278">she's still there yeah but she's worked her way up now she's his nurse they're a brilliant team</u>
<u n="801" who="S0370">I've got a wisdom tooth coming through</u>
<u n="802" who="S0278">but it's kind of embarrassing cos it's</u>
<u n="803" who="S0012" trans="overlap">now you will be wise</u>
<u n="804" who="S0370">it's a bit sideways no all the others I've had this is my last one</u>
<u n="805" who="S0278">oh right</u>
<u n="806" who="S0370">cos you either get them early or you get them late don't you?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0278" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="808" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="809" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="810" who="S0278">that's why they give them <unclear/></u>
<u n="811" who="S0370" trans="overlap">and it's it's a bit tight behind this molar at the back and it's coming out a bit sideways</u>
<u n="812" who="S0278">oh they might have to pull it</u>
<u n="813" who="S0013">that's how mine was and they decided to move it remove it</u>
<u n="814" who="S0012">oh you had to go to hospital didn't you?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="816" who="S0278">you do for something like that</u>
<u n="817" who="S0013" trans="overlap">they wanted to save the <trunc>ba</trunc>back tooth and they had to remove the thing from inside it</u>
<u n="818" who="S0278" trans="overlap">oh that's unless they're a surgeon is is if they're if he's <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> a surgeon if they're a surgeon they can do it in the practice</u>
<u n="819" who="S0370" trans="overlap">yeah mine mine do surgical yeah but he er he he he thinks it's alright at the moment</u>
<u n="820" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah but it's free free in hospital</u>
<u n="821" who="S0370">oh right</u>
<u n="822" who="S0012">there you go see</u>
<u n="823" who="S0013">he said I had to go to hospital he said</u>
<u n="824" who="S0012">he said you had to go to hospital so he did</u>
<u n="825" who="S0278" trans="overlap">well he so he might not have been a surgeon he might have been a dental practitioner</u>
<u n="826" who="S0370" trans="overlap">I'll tell you what he said on mine</u>
<u n="827" who="S0013">they did put me out though</u>
<u n="828" who="S0278">yeah they can do that</u>
<u n="829" who="S0370">he gave me a prescription for erm this Colgate toothpaste that's higher in fluoride you can't buy it over the counter</u>
<u n="830" who="S0278">oh right</u>
<u n="831" who="S0370">you oh sorry no you can't buy it from a an ordinary chemist you have you can buy it from the dentist or you can get a prescription you get it from the chemist</u>
<u n="832" who="S0278">yeah</u>
<u n="833" who="S0370">er so because I'm over sixty he gave me the prescription and erm what it does it people with softer teeth even when you're older it reduces the amount of work you have to have done cos you've got the fluoride</u>
<u n="834" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="835" who="S0278">oh I'll ask him <unclear/> ask him about</u>
<u n="836" who="S0013" trans="overlap">I don't want to touch any to touch any fluoride</u>
<u n="837" who="S0370">I can tell you the name of the stuff if you want? you brush them at the end of <pause dur="short"/> when you go to bed and you don't rinse after your brush</u>
<u n="838" who="S0278" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="839" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="840" who="S0370">you just spit</u>
<u n="841" who="S0013">oh don't like that</u>
<u n="842" who="S0370" trans="overlap">because then it leaves well it leaves some of the fluoride there what it says is ideally you you don't want to <trunc>rin</trunc>rinse or wash your mouth out afterwards for thirty minutes that's why he said to me look just once a day before you go to bed when you brush your teeth and if you want you can brush it with the other toothpaste first and rinse out and then brush it with this and then spit but the fluoride remains in the gaps you see where it's likely to be affected</u>
<u n="843" who="S0013" trans="overlap">you should <unclear/> really well and</u>
<u n="844" who="S0370">and it builds up the fluoride in that but</u>
<u n="845" who="S0278">well that's good that sounds good</u>
<u n="846" who="S0013" trans="overlap">I always rinse it really well but maybe you shouldn't</u>
<u n="847" who="S0278">well if you want to find out about ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="848" who="S0370">oh yeah yes oh it's the same I'll bring the tube down yeah</u>
<u n="849" who="S0278">she'll tell you about it I didn't realise then the other day I looked at the Macleans packet that's GSK as well so Macleans Aquafresh and Sensodyne they're all GSK but I didn't know the Macleans was</u>
<u n="850" who="S0012">oh right no didn't</u>
<u n="851" who="S0278" trans="overlap">I just buy what's cheapest I mean</u>
<u n="852" who="S0012" trans="overlap">so do we yeah</u>
<u n="853" who="S0278">when it's on offer</u>
<u n="854" who="S0013">yeah you get it for fifty pence if you're</u>
<u n="855" who="S0278" trans="overlap">I got it</u>
<u n="856" who="S0012">if you're lucky yeah</u>
<u n="857" who="S0013">yeah cos we left our all our wash stuff at at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="858" who="S0278" trans="overlap">need to cover this up <unclear/> on top of it</u>
<u n="859" who="S0013">cos we we were off on holiday so we had to stop off and get something and we said <unclear/> cheap so we got two er two toothbrushes for fifty P</u>
<u n="860" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah we did yeah</u>
<u n="861" who="S0013">pack of two and erm fifty pence</u>
<u n="862" who="S0012">toothpaste yeah</u>
<u n="863" who="S0013">paste and it's brilliant toothpaste</u>
<u n="864" who="S0012">yeah it was</u>
<u n="865" who="S0013">nice <unclear/> one</u>
<u n="866" who="S0278" trans="overlap">at at at our show two years ago there was Colgate took a stand right in a prominent position</u>
<u n="867" who="S0013"><unclear/></u>
<u n="868" who="S0278">oh yeah that's not <unclear/></u>
<u n="869" who="S0370">this is five thousand you see <pause dur="short"/> parts per minute</u>
<u n="870" who="S0278" trans="overlap">yeah yeah and you can see that's not a retail pack cos no one would be encouraged to buy that the way it is</u>
<u n="871" who="S0370">well the box is quite nice to <unclear>look at</unclear> isn't it?</u>
<u n="872" who="S0278">well</u>
<u n="873" who="S0013">one gram contains five milligrams of fluoride</u>
<u n="874" who="S0278" trans="overlap">Duraphat <vocal desc="laugh"/> Duraphat</u>
<u n="875" who="S0013">corresponding to five thousand</u>
<u n="876" who="S0278">parts per parts per millilitre</u>
<u n="877" who="S0013">is it?</u>
<u n="878" who="S0278">probably PPM</u>
<u n="879" who="S0370">I think it's normally about a thousand in the normal toothpaste so it's five times but <unclear>you're</unclear> not little kids aren't meant to use it</u>
<u n="880" who="S0278">no</u>
<u n="881" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="882" who="S0370">erm</u>
<u n="883" who="S0012">they won't <unclear/></u>
<u n="884" who="S0278" trans="overlap">in the water it's in the water now?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0012">that's in the water yeah</u>
<u n="886" who="S0370">I think if we'd had fluoride tablets when we were kids our teeth probably would have been much better</u>
<u n="887" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="888" who="S0278">that's right we had awful teeth haven't we?</u>
<u n="889" who="S0370">yeah</u>
<u n="890" who="S0013">well there's fluoride water in when we came to Norwich so</u>
<u n="891" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="892" who="S0013"><unclear/> week</u>
<u n="893" who="S0278">well anyway</u>
<u n="894" who="S0013" trans="overlap">and buy tablets</u>
<u n="895" who="S0278">when when Colgate took a stand at the <anon type="place"/> show they were all handing out Colgate bags you know cloth bags with Colgate written on it</u>
<u n="896" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="897" who="S0278">with free Colgate free toothbrush and all sorts of bits and pieces in the bag to everybody at the show and I got one I thought ah I could <unclear/> and I forgot about it long enough and then I took it down to her I said <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> oh I had it as a Christmas present I said and she opened it up and said <unclear/> wow <pause dur="short"/> this has given me an idea she says so they'd never thought of going to erm you know agricultural shows or these sort of shows and putting a stand up with</u>
<u n="898" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="899" who="S0278">she said I I can use this idea and she'd probably feed the idea as as coming from her but Colgate they were really clever cos the guy theyhad a photographer they had a photographer that was there <pause dur="short"/> er I I know what he was trying to do he said I'm trying to get some pictures of this I'm I'm from the Colgate so I'm trying to get some picture nice pictures of this the the guys jumping over their <pause dur="short"/> erm they they have a articulated lorry they they jump over it with their bikes and spin they let go of the bikes completely over the top</u>
<u n="900" who="S0012" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="901" who="S0278">and come down the ramp the other end they were doing that and he said can I go? can I nip through? and he must <unclear/> yeah go on and he nipped around and took pictures and the way he was taking the picture was to get the guy flying and in the background was the Colgate sign and</u>
<u n="902" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="903" who="S0012">oh right</u>
<u n="904" who="S0278">and so that was I don't know if he could use it without their permission but</u>
<u n="905" who="S0370">no</u>
<u n="906" who="S0278">but but if if you wanted if they wanted to <pause dur="short"/> set up a photoshoot with that going on you know it was the two of them flying were out together and both let go and they grabbed the bike and landed it</u>
<u n="907" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="908" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="909" who="S0278">erm it it would cost a fortune wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="910" who="S0370">oh yeah</u>
<u n="911" who="S0278">so maybe he'd take the pictures and then say well can we use it and we'll pay you so and so probably probably that way round might work <vocal desc="cough"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> so anyway <pause dur="short"/> are we are we are we are you doing woodwork now or? have you <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="912" who="S0012" trans="overlap">we were gonna go and play weren't we?</u>
<u n="913" who="S0370">yeah yeah can we just check to see if we can get that sleeve finish that order</u>
<u n="914" who="S0012">yeah we can finish the order yeah</u>
<u n="915" who="S0370" trans="overlap">and then we'll do it okay?</u>
<u n="916" who="S0278">well I'm going to try I'm going to try and make</u>
<u n="917" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><unclear/> have you found what you want now?</u>
<u n="918" who="S0370">no we haven't we haven't found the right <trunc>a</trunc>adapter to change the size have we?</u>
<u n="919" who="S0012" trans="overlap">no we haven't have we? no</u>
<u n="920" who="S0370">yeah</u>
<u n="921" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="922" who="S0370">er but it can't be difficult <pause dur="short"/> there must be a sleeve that just is threaded and has some flaps at the back and you just wind on to that thread which makes the thread bigger</u>
<u n="923" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="924" who="S0370"><unclear/> that's all it needs</u>
<u n="925" who="S0012">that's all it needs yeah <pause dur="short"/> there must be some</u>
<u n="926" who="S0370" trans="overlap">my lathe is a different size thread it's a smaller thread there are two basic sizes</u>
<u n="927" who="S0012" trans="overlap">it's <pause dur="short"/> this is three quarter <pause dur="short"/> six</u>
<u n="928" who="S0370" trans="overlap">mine is three quarter and his is <unclear/> and sixteen <pause dur="short"/> and sixteen threads per inch and mine is one inch eight threads per inch</u>
<u n="929" who="S0278">so you can't swap and change bits and pieces without this this</u>
<u n="930" who="S0012" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="931" who="S0370">well there's an adapter for the other one</u>
<u n="932" who="S0278">I I'll go another one it's not going to <unclear/></u>
<u n="933" who="S0370">yeah</u>
<u n="934" who="S0278">well can you go bigger or?</u>
<u n="935" who="S0370">you can put the little one of the big one</u>
<u n="936" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="937" who="S0370">but we can't</u>
<u n="938" who="S0012">but we can't put the big one on the little one</u>
<u n="939" who="S0278" trans="overlap">it must it must exist then</u>
<u n="940" who="S0370">there must be yeah</u>
<u n="941" who="S0012" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="942" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="943" who="S0278">there there the Chinese will have one</u>
<u n="944" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="945" who="S0278">the Chinese will have one</u>
<event desc="0012 leaves"/>
<event desc="0370 leaves"/>
<u n="946" who="S0013">mm sound exhausted</u>
<u n="947" who="S0278">well that it it where's when Maysie's walking Maysie's she's like this now she's thirteen</u>
<u n="948" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="949" who="S0278">and this this leg her back leg if if she overdoes it that leg it she had it it starts trailing and she scoops her you know it could like that her toes you can hear her nails scratching on the ground she can't lift the leg but she wants to walk</u>
<u n="950" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="951" who="S0370">but she did come round but she gets slower and slower and slower but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is good <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> realises Maysie's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s being slow and doesn't pull but Toby wants to keep going so I'm I'm having to stop Toby and it it's actually quite tiring walking slowly if you're not striding out</u>
<u n="952" who="S0013" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> it is I prefer walking faster</u>
<u n="953" who="S0278" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s saying that her back was really bad</u>
<u n="954" who="S0013" trans="overlap">her back yeah</u>
<u n="955" who="S0278" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="956" who="S0013">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="957" who="S0278" trans="overlap"><unclear/> oh she gave me a little card this morning it was nice she gave me a little card</u>
<u n="958" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="959" who="S0278">she says I've been looking for I've been looking for a valentine card she said you <pause dur="short"/> they are sloppy aren't they? and I said yeah they are really sloppy and and and I gave her one that I made I made one and put some pictures I'd taken and put it you know how I make my cards</u>
<u n="960" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="961" who="S0278">so I put I put them on and erm but mine wasn't sloppy either you know neither of us did a sloppy one it was a nice little one she'd hand written the inside it was nice</u>
<u n="962" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="963" who="S0278">it was good <pause dur="short"/> hers said thank you for you know for being a friend and</u>
<u n="964" who="S0013" trans="overlap">so she gave you a sloppy one</u>
<u n="965" who="S0278">no it wasn't no no no mine says erm I'm so pleased we've been put on the same path so happy <trunc>bri</trunc> happy bright path was a picture of snowdrops</u>
<u n="966" who="S0013">oh yeah</u>
<u n="967" who="S0278">erm that this was all when we went to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="968" who="S0013" trans="overlap">you drew it did you?</u>
<u n="969" who="S0278">no no the photographs I'd taken when she was with me</u>
<u n="970" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh I see oh yeah</u>
<u n="971" who="S0278">and then erm and it's an adventurous path and there's she's on the beach with three dogs</u>
<u n="972" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="973" who="S0278">stood all round her you see?</u>
<u n="974" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="975" who="S0278">and then adventurous one and a beautiful and peaceful one and that was oh erm there weren't so pleased we'd been put on the same path was just a path going through the snowdrops</u>
<u n="976" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh lovely</u>
<u n="977" who="S0278">at <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="978" who="S0013">worked well then</u>
<u n="979" who="S0278">there and on the back there was a picture of oh there was a picture of just one or just a clump of snowdrops erm yeah it er and and she looked at it and thought how did you since I was <unclear/> where did you find this nice one?</u>
<u n="980" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="981" who="S0278">have you got it at from <anon type="place"/> she was thinking?</u>
<u n="982" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="983" who="S0278">that's what she thought then when she opened it up and saw her picture in it</u>
<u n="984" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="985" who="S0278">realised it wasn't but if I hadn't have put her in it</u>
<u n="986" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="987" who="S0278">actually I couldn't do cards for <anon type="place"/> I could</u>
<u n="988" who="S0013">yeah course you could</u>
<u n="989" who="S0278">because they they're nice little Christian cards erm and and people would understand the way I've written it that it's a Christian card</u>
<u n="990" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="991" who="S0278">so I don't know I'm there's so many there's so many things I can do</u>
<u n="992" who="S0013">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well you know we were planning</u>
<u n="993" who="S0278" trans="overlap">but I seem to get snowed under with these ridiculous</u>
<u n="994" who="S0013" trans="overlap">we're planning an open studio</u>
<u n="995" who="S0278">are you? okay</u>
<u n="996" who="S0013">erm <pause dur="short"/> summertime I don't know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s coming up as well</u>
<u n="997" who="S0278">right</u>
<u n="998" who="S0013">and and bringing her stuff</u>
<u n="999" who="S0278">yes I know <unclear/></u>
<u n="1000" who="S0013">you're gonna say something now</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0278">I'd have an <trunc>i</trunc> yes I've been having an idea</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0278">who? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s coming up as well okay I can do that but also we <trunc>er</trunc>erm because of something they found in the church at <anon type="place"/> I'm not supposed to say too much about it but it it's it's of great importance apparently erm when we open the church we've got to man it now it's got to be manned we can't open it and just leave it open</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0013" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0278">erm so erm what one one of my thoughts were that when the heritage lottery goes through and we get the tower done it's now gonna help getting the tower done if we've got something really important in there can't let it fall down around that</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0278">so erm is that when it's open we if we remove some of pews at the back we can have an area where people local crafts could be sold</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0278">if we're gonna get more people coming</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0278" trans="overlap">I know you'll say that they're not gonna come but it they may well do when they know about this so</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0013" trans="overlap">they might do but</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0278">but then we've got to have extra car parking and everything down there as well</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0013">isn't it one of the little churches that should be left as as it is? <pause dur="short"/> without removing pews and changing things</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0278">no what I'm thinking is at the back if if say that's that's the <pause dur="short"/> we we never well these you can put them in if that's the church and there's the alter up there</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0013" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0278">now if when you come in the door where we stand when we have you know it's a good place for social as well</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0278">we never used to have pews in its people would stand</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0278">the font's there</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0278">all these old folk are stood around you know propping themselves up here there and everywhere round that</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0278">if one of the part of the plan is that <pause dur="short"/> the pew that's there you move that forward and that's got a high back and that'll give a little kitchenette area</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0278">there the loo's got to go in the tower <pause dur="short"/> that's important loos got to go in the tower</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0013" trans="overlap">are there loos there now?</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0278">no you go round the back of the church</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0013">yeah well I don't think there should be loos</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0278">you just wanna go and piddle round the back of the church do you?</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0278">you can't invite people to come expect people to come and visit the church if there's no loos in the area</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0013" trans="overlap">but there is in the in the hall isn't there?</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0278">yeah but yes but in the winter <pause dur="short"/> there's the <trunc>an</trunc> the another thing is</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah but it's so <trunc>ty</trunc> historical type especially if they found something really unusual there</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0278">mm that's that's</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0013">they should they should keep the church as a historical building</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0278">cos then you take out all the pews cos the everyone used to just stand in it and the vicar used to park his horse in it and</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0278">and it had a and it had a</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0013">yeah you're going to extremes now</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0278" trans="overlap">no I'm not he used to park his horse and it had a it had a <trunc>or</trunc>originally as it was it just had soil on the floor and people weren't buried in in in any caskets and the smell was awful that's the history</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0013">that's the history</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0278">so you keep improving it everyone that's been there has improved every church evolves with the people church is for people</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0013">yes</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0278">we don't own the church the church belongs to the village we just happen to be using it</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0013">well I know that yeah</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0278" trans="overlap">and looking after it erm but if that had erm that little kitchenette there so you can make cups of tea that's basically what it's for then there was a little area in front of that where you remove say two pews and you and put a table in the middle and people sit looking at each other</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0278">erm the <unclear/> area where people could sit and have their teas and coffees as well</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0278">but you could also and then I've seen it done in my old church at <anon type="place"/> where you've got the pews you just put a plank a wood across the end <pause dur="short"/> nice piece of wood and you put you sell the stuff across the ends of the pews you see?</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0013" trans="overlap">no one uses the hall and it's right next door</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0278">yes</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0013">no one uses the hall do they? on a Sunday</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0278">no</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0013">so why can't they just move across to there and have a lovely get together with all the little tables and they got the kitchen there?</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0278" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0013">and the loos</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0278">I'll tell you why it can't happen</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0013">why?</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0278">why it can't happen is because heritage lottery will not fund just to repair something they will only fund <pause dur="short"/> erm if it's going to benefit if what you do is going to benefit the community and people who visit</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0013">well</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0278">they won't repair the tower if we don't make an effort to make it better when people visit</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0278">it's got to be free</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0013">okay</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0278">and one of the things that they suggest is to put in a loo and to have a little tea making corner</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0013">really?</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0278">for people that visit so it's it makes it <trunc>friend</trunc> so people will want to visit no one is gonna and improve the heating system people won't want to visit in the week</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0013">yeah it just it just seems a bit silly when right next door they've got all the cups and saucers and everything there</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0278" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah well imagine right you're you're there you've just come you've parked your car in the snow you've gone into the church which is warmer we've had the service</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0278">and you want a cup of tea at the end of the service do you want to then</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0013" trans="overlap">you've still got to leave haven't you?</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0278">lock the church up walk walk through the snow to get to</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0013">no I don't think that's a problem</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0278" trans="overlap">to the hall? it's <trunc>pa</trunc></u>
<u n="1080" who="S0013">the distance is not a problem</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0278">but if we didn't ask to do things like that they wouldn't repair the tower</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0278">that's the part that's the point</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0013" trans="overlap">seems that seems rotten to me</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0278">well they won't repair the tower unless you make it accessible to everybody that building</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0278">so that's what</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0013">there must be a cos it's an it's a protected building isn't it?</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0278">yeah they're all they're all</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0013">they're all erm</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0278">they're all graded yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0278">that's a grade two listed</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0013" trans="overlap">so you've got to be very careful how what you do</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0278" trans="overlap">I know I know yeah so we don't can't can't spoil the fabric at all we won't be spoiling the fabric</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0013">oh oh</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0278">look what we do at <anon type="place"/> now when we haven't got the pews</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0013">I know</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0278">look what we can do there it's wonderful <pause dur="short"/> it's amazing</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0278">so many things and you just move the chairs around</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0278">the only pew the pews were the best that people could do</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah I</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0278">after people were standing</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0013">I kind of agree that</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0278" trans="overlap">you see?</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0013">pews aren't the best</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0278" trans="overlap">but there's twelve of us go every Sunday and the all these pews are all empty <pause dur="short"/> about twelve</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0013">twelve at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1111" who="S0278">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's all and the twelve of us have got to sort out and get the tower repaired</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0013">yeah right</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0278">so there's only about twelve of us going but if you can encourage people to come more people to come to the place they you they won't fund it unless you're improving it for people to come to it and part of it will be having erm a new path so you can get wheelchairs up there</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah a new path that makes sense yeah</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0278">chairs up there a path possibly going across cutting across which may be difficult cos it'll go across some graves but easier to get to the hall</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0278">erm <pause dur="short"/> er I mean at the moment we have to get the water out the tap</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0278">the dog tap in in bottles and leave it in bottles in the tower</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0278">and we've got tea making stuff in the tower which is just a urn that warms up you see but there's nowhere to sit cos you can't sit all facing</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0013">but that's why I think why go to all that trouble when you have a purpose built building right next door?</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0278">but it's no good in the winter if you've got the people going would you how would you like it? alright you're living in here and your kitchen is over there outside</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0013">yeah yeah but it's a church service</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0278" trans="overlap">if you</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0012">what's that? what are you talking about?</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0278">well well</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0013" trans="overlap">when we're going to have erm</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0278" trans="overlap">well when we had when we had the the folk group when we had the folk group we had the folk group</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0278">played</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0278">erm everyone had to go across and get their drinks from the hall and carry it back now that was fine unless it's bunging it with rain <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1134" who="S0012">yeah</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0278">erm you see it it it it you it's as if erm right you're inviting people to one place and all the facilities are in the house next door <pause dur="short"/> that's what</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0013">I just don't think that's</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0278" trans="overlap">it's like you wouldn't have a village here you had to go to the house next door to use the facilities would you?</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0370" trans="overlap">unless <unclear/></u>
<u n="1139" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0278">that's what it is but they won't cos the main thing is they will not fund repairs unless it improves the accessibility for everybody</u>
<event desc="background talk"/>
<event desc="0012 leaves"/>
<event desc="0370 leaves"/>
<u n="1141" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0278">and that's disabled access a loo is imperative erm you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> poor old <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he has trouble in the cold</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0278">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> he's told there and he's having his coffee after a service and and he starts going like this and like this and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are you alright? no I need I need the toilet</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0278">and so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was doing something else <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can you take take <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> round the back please? and I had to go slowly with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> right the way round the tower round to the back and he stands in the corner and widdles in the corner and I wait for him and then I fetch him back</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0278">cos he couldn't get he couldn't get to the hall</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0013">yeah mm</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0278">so I think it is important</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0278">it's not and it's not nice I mean I don't mind that I mean like I don't mind helping <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> out but see that sort of thing happens and ladies find it even more difficult</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0278">I think erm well it and the other thing is that the church actually suits some events better than the hall <pause dur="short"/> you can get more people in it looking in one direction</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0278">in the church than than the hall so it would be good if if there was anything and then they can work together that's not it's not there's not two separate things they can work together but the only way we can get the tower repaired is to make it all work <pause dur="short"/> together <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's got to be done really well though</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0278" trans="overlap">and they're even thinking about they're even thinking about trying to sort out somewhere a field somewhere for a car park because there's always a problem when there's an event there</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0278">in the hall whether it be in the hall or the church</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0278">so there needs to be a car park somewhere you know just erm gently just so it's not doesn't upset erm but I'm sure it we will get it sorted</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0013">well they they have to don't they?</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0278">yeah they have to</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0013">they have to do it</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0278">well I mean it doesn't matter to us because</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0013" trans="overlap">it's a listed building</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0278">yeah but we don't have to do it we can say go well okay I suppose ultimately if we can't get it repaired we just go and worship in we could hire the hall for six pounds an hour on a Sunday morning no worries worship in the hall and let the tower fall down but that's not not really an option but that's you could say well okay well we'll worship in the hall</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0278">because we can't go in there cos the tower's falling down <pause dur="short"/> erm it doesn't matter where we are but it's it would be nice I mean if we can really get the whole thing all working together it would be brilliant</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0278">it's a lovely spot that have you seen what they've done right round the work they've put in?</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0013" trans="overlap">they thought it was going to be up for sale when we first came here</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0278" trans="overlap">mm? what the hall?</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0013">the church</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0278">the church did they?</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0278">oh cos there was nobody using it</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0278">ah</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0013">they thought it might go up for sale</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0278">mm mm</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0013">like lots of churches need lots of people <pause dur="short"/> lots of churches being sold aren't there? chapels and things</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0278" trans="overlap">yeah but what? I don't know what you could do that I'm sure I mean it would cost you <trunc>fort</trunc> that tower just repairing the top bit of the tower is a is a hundred and twenty thousand pounds</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0278">and that's without anything else</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0278">without doing the the path to it and</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><unclear>building</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0278">the road needs doing outside as well that maybe we could include that you see? improve the road</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0013">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0278" trans="overlap">erm but it's a chance this is a chance</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0013">it does need doing that's right</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0278">we've got a chance to improve that whole area down there</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0278">look how it it's churned up in the winter <unclear/></u>
<u n="1197" who="S0013" trans="overlap">so how much will they give?</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0278">mm?</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0013">how much will they give then?</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0278">you can ask for what you want</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0013">oh I see</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0278">providing they think it's a good thing</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0278">erm but it's got to involve the community</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0278">and improving it and improving all the access</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0013">which means they've got to pay more than just for the tower anyway</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0278" trans="overlap">and interest <pause dur="short"/> yes they will</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0013" trans="overlap">got a lot more a lot more</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0278">they they they won't if you just said we just want the tower doing they wouldn't do it cos you're not improving the place for <trunc>exa</trunc> accessibility it it's it's</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0278">it's not just the building they are interested in attracting more people to see the beauty of the building</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0013">yeah mm mm</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0278">that's that's what they're trying to get <unclear/> if it we couldn't have school visits if we didn't have a loo</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0278">things like that but erm</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0278">it <trunc>re</trunc> it's very interesting and there's an awful lot but the other thing is that we're trying to find I I don't can't take it on they want somebody to head it all up all this</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0013">to what?</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0278">to head it up they want one person one person needs to be in charge of <pause dur="short"/> all of this</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0013">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0278">one person but we're all got jobs every every one of us that goes to that church does something</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0278">whether it be cleaning or or doing the catering for it or cleaning the outside area and maintaining it or doing <trunc>pre</trunc> we all do something</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0278">and <pause dur="short"/> it's a full going to be a full when it starts it'll be a full time job of somebody</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0278">and we haven't found that person yet I I you know keep looking</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0013" trans="overlap">could be you couldn't it?</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0278">well it could be if I didn't have anything else to do</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0013" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> shortly you never know do you?</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0278">well I don't know but at the minute I'm still</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0278">I'm still committed</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0013">mm mm</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0278">and if I stop signwriting then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> know he doesn't get any signs for his church cos I'm the one that I put in the bid for I put in the all the stuff that's gone in for permission to do it and about about a year down the line they might get the permission to do it</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0278">and if I'm not there then they got to start again</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0013">well you are still here though</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0278">no point is if I stop signwriting to take on this job</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0278">mm</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0013">well it wouldn't be full full time you can still do a couple of signs in the evening couldn't you?</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0278">well I probably could yeah I probably could I <unclear/></u>
<u n="1245" who="S0013" trans="overlap">just the odd odd one or two</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0278"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1247" who="S0013">mm?</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0278">I probably could yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it it's <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well you never know mm</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0278">I think I mean and we need a team as well you see? and no one's volunteered for the team either we all do our bits and keeping things as it is but it and erm</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0278">I thought see a lot of them they are retired a lot of them are retired but they they feel it's gonna be one <pause dur="short"/> I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I think for me at the minute that would be one bit of straw too too much to take to take that on and I I'm not going to do it</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah you can't take too much on</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0278">I don't think I could take on another one of something <pause dur="short"/> erm at the minute</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0278">but we'll see but the point is well I I'm <unclear/> thinking about this</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0278">is that when the church is it's gonna be open Wednesdays <pause dur="short"/> wednesday afternoon from ten till starting in April</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0013">yeah it was open we went we walked down that way last Wednesday</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0278">it's always open one <trunc>Wed</trunc> on a Wednesday cos that's when the boys are there playing they're they're doing all the clearing round lovely <unclear/> looks right across the fields it's lovely</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0278">erm and so there they are on a Wednesday that's not a problem they're normally there on a Wednesday just <unclear/></u>
<u n="1263" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0278">Saturdays it's open ten till four as well now when it's open ten till four on Saturdays possibly <pause dur="short"/> I have to say once a month bottom</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0278">erm why don't we have local crafts</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0278">for sale in there?</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0278">I mean they don't all have to be there if they came down and just set it up and you can do on the ends of the pews you can put they do it at at <anon type="place"/> they have a nice piece of timber with blocks underneath and it just locks in to the end of the pews so it can't fall</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0013">right okay</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0278">and you could put things on and if they're all priced up then whoever is manning you need two people manning as well for safety apparently to man the place so that we would that would <pause dur="short"/> maybe</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0013">more crafts yeah</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0278">if it did become famous I dunno we'll see I don't know maybe of no significant importance but I think it is</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1276" who="S0278">it is I think so</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0013">well they made enough er on their Christmas crafts didn't they? in down the down the Christmas fair thing</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0278">did they do alright?</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0013" trans="overlap">there were local crafts weren't there? they made a thousand pound well they took a thousand pound and it was seven hundred and fifty I think profit</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0278">oh wow really? over all the what people took?</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0278">that's good isn't it?</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0013">that's good isn't it?</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0278">it is yeah</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0013">cos it's very small</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0278">that was small yeah that's brilliant I did I wouldn't have thought that you would they would have sold that much some of the things were</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0013" trans="overlap">well apparently they did over a thousand pound worth</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0278">well that's good oh and they did teas and things like that as well didn't they? and that's a good one</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0013">yeah they did mm</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0278">oh</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0013">then obviously you've got to take out some</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0278">mm</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0013">I mean some of the plants I think <pause dur="short"/> they're not all donated well only some of them were theirs cos they they've got to take the some money out</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0278">mm so you could do that <unclear/></u>
<u n="1295" who="S0013" trans="overlap">seven hundred and fifty quid</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0278" trans="overlap">I could go down I could sit there could sit there and play the organ and I'd learn the organ at the same time</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0278">but the fact that's the other thing is I'm was if if if for instance down the back right where the font is just that's that's an <trunc>a</trunc> no one ever sits at the back it's cold in that corner anyway so a little tea making bit just just it just needs <pause dur="short"/> washing up bit and and and</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0278">doesn't even need a hole we just need electricity there just so that you can yeah?</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0278">that's all it needs a little washing up area everything has to be parted away from there they can all take someone takes it home in a box and fetches it back</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0013">oh right</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0278">erm and then a little square area there so the two pews are left turn one round so it's facing that way and with the timber you could make a big long table just to go in between</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0013">mm mm</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0278">so they could sit there and have their cups of tea there yeah? <pause dur="short"/> or erm you could just remove that bit and move that table I don't know the way you could probably find a way to collapse it probably and it would stand up in the tower out the way erm</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0278">erm <pause dur="short"/> I was going to say something else about that having an area <unclear/> that what was I thinking? <pause dur="short"/> erm oh yes yeah what I was thinking is that if we're keeping it open and there's someone's got work to do they could bring their work down with them and do it there in the church</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0013">they can what?</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0278">bring their work down and do it in the church I could</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0278">you see? if I've got some work to do I could fetch it down and sit there at the table there doing the work while I'm waiting to looking after the place for people to visit</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh I see yeah</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0278">you see what I mean? you <trunc>ca</trunc> at the minute there's nowhere to sit and do anything</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0013">no no</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0278">so that little area could be if you wanted to get on with something</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0013">mm mm</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0278">well actually I could do one of the things I want to do is glass painting <pause dur="short"/> I want to get away from the chemical I want to paint it hand hand painted glass</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0278">erm I could do that there</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0278">you could do all that and just let it dry and take it back stick it in the oven</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0278">erm or calligraphy I I could do hand painted signs</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0013" trans="overlap">well you can do lots of things can't you? you're very you're very artistic</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0278" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I or I can sit and play the organ or I could play music and play my <unclear/> which I've done before <pause dur="short"/> erm so I I'm happy</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0013" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1328" who="S0278">I'm happy to spend Saturdays there but not every Saturday looking after the place but I could see can you can you see imagine a long <trunc>as</trunc> each each pew has a put the board along</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0278">with a nice drape over and cards for whoever <pause dur="short"/> would work wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the cards are always good a good seller anyway aren't they?</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0278">well is it no cards cos you say you're you're your friend down here she does pottery doesn't she?</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0278">pottery and stuff like that you know just a small selection there and price it you don't <unclear/> but if you if you just trust the people that are there to take the money and make a note if you're not gonna be there</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0278">there's all sorts of possibilities you we need</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0013">mm</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0278">we we <pause dur="short"/> the next thing is to try and encourage people to come</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0278">you see</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0013">mm <pause dur="short"/> well we've got loads of cards to sell if you want them so</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0278">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah loads we've got drawers full of them</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0278" trans="overlap">well there we are you see we could put just plonk those there and erm</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0013">they're all cellophaned up <pause dur="short"/> they're all</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0278" trans="overlap">yeah that's right it make it makes them look posh doesn't it when you cellophane them?</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0013">yeah you <trunc>to</trunc> you got to present them</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0278">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0013">and they've got they've got to be clean you know? so that's the only way to keep them clean isn't it?</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0278">it is yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0013">but we did</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0278" trans="overlap">so and I've got lots of fridge magnets fridge magnets there as well</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0013" trans="overlap">we did we did ours what? how many years ago? two thousand and seven was it? <pause dur="short"/> our open studio <pause dur="short"/> first time</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0278" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0013">how long ago <unclear/></u>
<u n="1356" who="S0278" trans="overlap">it's trying to get it's trying to get people there isn't it? that's the trouble</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0278">so you're doing one this year anyway an open studio?</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0013">just us</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0278">okay</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0013">just us not open studios</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0278">oh right oh just an open studio</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0013">just an open</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0278">but it's advertising it that's the thing isn't it?</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0013" trans="overlap">just a <pause dur="short"/> yeah we thought we'd come to you on that</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0278" trans="overlap">put a big one up put a big one up one the church</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0013">just a few adverts around</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0278" trans="overlap">on that on that junction with a big arrow</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1370" who="S0278">open studio</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0013">but that was what do you think about bringing the dolls' houses down?</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0278">yeah</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0013">that type of thing</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0278">yeah</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0013">yeah well I'm going to get busy with some of my work</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0278" trans="overlap">yeah okay that's that would be fun</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0013">I haven't done any for a long time</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0278" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0013">I can't I can't get into anything at the moment</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0278">can't you?</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0013">no <pause dur="short"/> I haven't got that</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0278">buzz</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0013">you could have</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0278" trans="overlap">I keep thinking of all the sorts of things I want to do</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0013" trans="overlap">you got to you got to be in that mode haven't you?</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0278">mm</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0013">and then keep experimenting and stuff like that and just go for it but I can't <pause dur="short"/> I haven't got it at the moment</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0278">well if you can magically put a car park there all people flooding in flooding in round that area</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0013" trans="overlap">who? <pause dur="short"/> what here?</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0278">no no out up the road there in the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1391" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1392" who="S0278">might do it I don't know think we're going to do it I had a chat with when I was I phoned <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on another thing oh about the beer glasses <pause dur="short"/> the beer glasses they want for the bell ringer</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0013" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0278">erm phoned <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and er</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0013">mm mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1396" who="S0278">I hope I've I've got the information he sent to me</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0013">I've forgotten what the beer glasses were for now? for <anon type="place"/> church?</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0278">oh they forgot to pass pass the information on to</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0013">mm?</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0278">no they're not they're for the erm <pause dur="short"/> er I can pass that on to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1401" who="S0013">who are they for then?</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0278">for for the bell ringers at <anon type="place"/> they want to them great pint glasses</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0013">oh</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0278">I can pass this to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> see this is I can't say <unclear/></u>
<u n="1405" who="S0013" trans="overlap">what they all gonna buy glasses?</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0278">see this is I can't say a <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> well I don't know how he wants to do it but he wants to well they could possibly buy their own glass and that would keep the washing down to up to a minimum they buy that's why they work it here you buy your own glass and you use it and drink out of it and you keep the glass</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0013">right</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0278">that's what happens at the beer festival</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0278">you buy your glass that's part of your entry and then you pay for the beer that goes in it but you that way they don't have to keep washing the glasses up</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0013" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> that's right yeah</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0278">so that keeps it simple</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0013">so the bell ringers are gonna have like a beer festival?</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0278">not a beer festival they have a bar at <anon type="place"/> college they're running a bar at <anon type="place"/> college as part of the</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0370">that's a joke isn't it?</u>
<event desc="background talk"/>
<u n="1416" who="S0013">right <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>looks like</unclear> they've done it</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0278">I've got that logged on the computer</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0013">have you done it? have you done it?</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0278">I've got those locked on the computer</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0370" trans="overlap">we can't find the thing no the sleeve</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0370">no but they must they must do one I can't believe they don't cos they talk about adapters and <unclear/> the other</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0013">getting late look at the time <pause dur="short"/> dum dum dum</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0278" trans="overlap">I'll have to <trunc>ke</trunc> I'll have to go soon feed the dog <unclear/> are gonna have a go at a the <unclear/> I'll tell you how to do a halving joint halving joint you could teach me one of those?</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0013" trans="overlap">yeah you're <unclear/> aren't you? <pause dur="short"/> you're going to have to paint that aren't you?</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0278">well I was going <unclear/></u>
<u n="1427" who="S0370" trans="overlap">a halving joint?</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0278">make across</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0370">what?</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0278">I've come to make a cross</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0370">oh right halving joints are dead easy</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0278">well that <pause dur="short"/> okay are you going out there now or are you?</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0370">no yes we're going out there now I'll put my shoes on I'm going to put the heater on</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0278">pardon?</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0370">I'm going to put the heater on</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0278">I'm not worried about heat I've got my hat as long as I've got my</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0370" trans="overlap">yeah well some of us you know us Londoners <trunc>se</trunc> sensitive to low temperatures</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0013">which is what <unclear/></u>
<u n="1439" who="S0278">oh wow</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0013">does it work?</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0370">yeah yeah yeah so yeah it was there was just a bit of dust in the the pilot light and you had to have the pilot light</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0278" trans="overlap">oh we still have <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1443" who="S0013">it's not on at the moment</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0370" trans="overlap">no no no no no it's the one mum and dad used to have in the hall <pause dur="short"/> do you remember?</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1446" who="S0370">I persuaded him to have it instead of the instead of the paraffin heater</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0278">no I can't remember that <pause dur="short"/> I'll probably remember</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0370" trans="overlap">you'll recognise it when you see it</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0278">yeah alright</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0013">no</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0278">I haven't had a biscuit I've been ever so good <pause dur="short"/> thank you</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0013">ah <pause dur="short"/> but you had cheesecake</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0278">I know <unclear/> I haven't had any lunch <pause dur="short"/> I I</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0013" trans="overlap">it's tea soon</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0278">and I only had some muesli for breakfast</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0370"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1457" who="S0013"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1458" who="S0278">I'm gonna get my shoes on in the</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0013">yeah you get your shoes</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0278">mm but it is interesting you see the thing is we've got an opportunity for the whole village here</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0278">we'll take it but the thing is that they but they won't pay just for the tower you have to improve the</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0013">okay</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0278">you have to improve everything else that that's what that's what it's about</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0013">yeah</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0278">but really want the whole village involved in it cos the more people involved the more likely you are to get the <unclear>grant</unclear></u>
<u n="1467" who="S0013" trans="overlap">well well they are a good village aren't they?</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0278">yeah they're brilliant they're absolutely brilliant <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1469" who="S0013">one <unclear/> no did you get one?</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0278">no</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0013">didn't you? that was from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> Christmas present didn't you get one?</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0278">no</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0013">ha</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0278">no no</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0013">well I never</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
