<text id="SFET">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:22:06</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-29</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0058 S0179</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's car</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>A&amp;E, injuries</topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, inquiring, complaining, advising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T03</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0058">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Corpus Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0179">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harpenden, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years, 7 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Consultant engineer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0058">well it was interesting anyway <pause dur="short"/> ha ha</u>
<u n="2" who="S0179">well it's interesting being in an A and E department</u>
<u n="3" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> talk about all human life is here</u>
<u n="4" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="5" who="S0058">you've gotta know how much time and effort they spend giving people treatment <pause dur="short"/> who kind of yeah are too drunk to know what's going on</u>
<u n="6" who="S0179">well the erm I don't think that weirdo was er <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>f</trunc> sorry that guy was drunk <pause dur="short"/> I think he was mentally ill</u>
<u n="7" who="S0058">do you think so? Right</u>
<u n="8" who="S0179">it wasn't didn't sound drunk</u>
<u n="9" who="S0058">mm maybe yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe he was just yeah <pause dur="short"/> they put a lot of effort into him</u>
<u n="10" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0058">A lot of security guys went after him <pause dur="short"/> which I mean it just sort of I suppose it's sort of a contrast you know really really trying to help people for free</u>
<u n="12" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0058">as opposed to a system which doesn't you can't afford it <pause dur="short"/> you and you don't you know and you don't get <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> chin up chuck <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0058">I think that's it's like I said it's the same advice anyway <pause dur="short"/> after two weeks you can go and get another one done <pause dur="short"/> anyway <pause dur="short"/> through Newnham Walk</u>
<u n="16" who="S0179"><unclear/> Oh I'll put that on the calendar</u>
<u n="17" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="18" who="S0179">ay</u>
<u n="19" who="S0058">so I know <pause dur="short"/> you can go for one anyway <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> unless it's completely fine</u>
<u n="20" who="S0179" trans="overlap">could do <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0058">but you know as in after two weeks you could go for another X-ray and you might just</u>
<u n="22" who="S0179">well you don't wanna X-ray sort of</u>
<u n="23" who="S0058">true <pause dur="short"/> just because <pause dur="short"/> okay well yeah see how it is after two weeks <pause dur="short"/> like I said you're not doing anything differently <pause dur="short"/> in order to be how you behave after that two weeks is different</u>
<u n="24" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0058">yeah? Fingers crossed it is shin splints cos then it'll only be a couple of weeks <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it is <pause dur="short"/> as the symptoms are literally textbook</u>
<u n="27" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0179">er but</u>
<u n="29" who="S0058">yep <pause dur="short"/> go with it</u>
<u n="30" who="S0179">ah <pause dur="short"/> but it should be alright</u>
<u n="31" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0179">erm but yeah the treatment's the same anyway <pause dur="short"/> for two weeks nothing but swimming and weights</u>
<u n="33" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> have you got a PT session in that time?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0179">yeah next Monday</u>
<u n="35" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean that in some ways is quite good because you can well you can you know you can say exactly what the problem is and do <trunc>s</trunc> you know do <trunc>so</trunc> it'll be different <pause dur="short"/> but without it needing to be impact if you like</u>
<u n="36" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> alright</u>
<u n="37" who="S0058">it can give you some ideas for varying it <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0179">two weeks of swimming <pause dur="short"/> I can probably do that</u>
<u n="39" who="S0058">hmm mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah you can do that</u>
<u n="40" who="S0179">I don't want to know what's going on in the back of that car</u>
<u n="41" who="S0058">I didn't even see what that was <pause dur="short"/> was it bouncing?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0179">no it was trying to fit a lot of people into it</u>
<u n="43" who="S0058">oh <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="44" who="S0179">A small space</u>
<u n="45" who="S0058">ha ha <pause dur="short"/> party in a car <pause dur="short"/> okay well what'll what'll cheer you up when we get in? What would you like to do?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0179">possibly a whiskey</u>
<u n="47" who="S0058">whiskey? There's a bit of TV?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0179">yeah maybe</u>
<u n="49" who="S0058">bit of ice? Or not?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0179">yeah I probably should actually</u>
<u n="51" who="S0058">put a little bit of ice yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0179">I could use a shower actually</u>
<u n="53" who="S0058">yeah I should probably shower <pause dur="short"/> oh well</u>
<u n="54" who="S0179">well it's not going to be an early night</u>
<u n="55" who="S0058">well it's not too bad <pause dur="short"/> I had sort of well when we got in there and was sitting there I had visions of three in the morning</u>
<u n="56" who="S0179">the thing that annoyed me a little bit is it wasn't exactly rammed in there</u>
<u n="57" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0179">I did get the impression that you know just resource allocation I don't I'm not sure it's entirely necessary for us to have had to wait for it</u>
<u n="59" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="60" who="S0179">what was it? An hour and a half two hours?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0058">X-ray yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah X-ray was empty <pause dur="short"/> it just seems like they could <trunc>sl</trunc> slightly speedily get people through based on what they need but</u>
<u n="62" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Pretty much well I was pretty much the lowest priority</u>
<u n="63" who="S0058">yeah yeah I mean</u>
<u n="64" who="S0179">which as it is agonisingly painful <pause dur="short"/> but not really true to be fair</u>
<u n="65" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no but I know what you mean</u>
<u n="66" who="S0179">but it is hurting now</u>
<u n="67" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> being poked and prodded</u>
<u n="68" who="S0179">no er <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty much just hurting</u>
<u n="69" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he did it sometimes just hurts <pause dur="short"/> yeah we'll go back get some ice on it for a bit yeah?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0058">hmm <pause dur="short"/> whiskey <pause dur="short"/> nature's painkiller <pause dur="short"/> that's what I recommend</u>
<u n="72" who="S0179">can we put some American Anthems on?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0058">yeah sure <pause dur="short"/> erm any?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0179">disc three <pause dur="short"/> I pretty sure it's on disc three</u>
<u n="75" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="76" who="S0179">bizarrely driving probably isn't doing it a horrendous amount of good</u>
<u n="77" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> well maybe stay off the long journeys</u>
<u n="78" who="S0179">well that'll be fine cos it's not a lot of clutch action</u>
<u n="79" who="S0058">mm that's true yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0179">I need an automatic</u>
<u n="81" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="82" who="S0179">dad can I borrow the V seventy?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0058">oh nice <pause dur="short"/> for medical reasons</u>
<u n="84" who="S0179">I actually need it to get to work</u>
<u n="85" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh do you think he'd go for that?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0179">er <pause dur="short"/> I think I might just find out what a cunt he is <pause dur="short"/> it's a I dunno</u>
<u n="87" who="S0058">yeah maybe er best not to but</u>
<u n="88" who="S0179" trans="overlap">I don't wanna <pause dur="short"/> I prefer you know not to have that definite knowledge</u>
<u n="89" who="S0058">ha ha <pause dur="short"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="90" who="S0179">erm <pause dur="short"/> it's interesting cos I have been taking Ibuprofen as an anti inflammatory but</u>
<u n="91" who="S0058">but maybe yeah <pause dur="short"/> so she said it's better for bone pain <pause dur="short"/> paracetamol?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay well we can go with that</u>
<u n="94" who="S0179">okay well either way</u>
<u n="95" who="S0058">I think we've got a full pack in <pause dur="short"/> or nearly full</u>
<u n="96" who="S0179">just get both</u>
<u n="97" who="S0058">ha ha <pause dur="short"/> pretty much</u>
<u n="98" who="S0179">they're very effective together</u>
<u n="99" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure they are</u>
<u n="100" who="S0179">well cos you can take both at the same time</u>
<u n="101" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0179">it's a trick <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> I do take particular pride in situations like that where we're being model patient</u>
<u n="103" who="S0058">ha ha <pause dur="short"/> sitting quietly and doing what you're told</u>
<u n="104" who="S0179">well no just making sure that say thank you and</u>
<u n="105" who="S0058">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah definitely <pause dur="short"/> what a miserable world to have to go back to every night</u>
<u n="106" who="S0179">exactly <pause dur="short"/> so if you can brighten it up you should</u>
<u n="107" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> absolutely <pause dur="short"/> nah I wouldn't fancy that job</u>
<u n="108" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0058">and I mean that was a fairly quiet Thursday night <pause dur="short"/> going down tomorrow night this time I imagine it's a completely different picture</u>
<u n="110" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="111" who="S0058">which is yeah <pause dur="short"/> ha ha can't be much fun <pause dur="short"/> there looked like there was a fair few who had fight injuries</u>
<u n="112" who="S0179">the guy opposite us?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0179">I'm not sure what <pause dur="short"/> that was an odd injury</u>
<u n="115" who="S0058">yeah it was wasn't it</u>
<u n="116" who="S0179">so any others?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0058">um there was um one of the the guy who was with the guy who ran off seemed to have some kind of facial injury</u>
<u n="118" who="S0179" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="119" who="S0058">um</u>
<u n="120" who="S0179">that guy he really did have a swollen face didn't he</u>
<u n="121" who="S0058">oh my goodness <pause dur="short"/> it was awful <pause dur="short"/> ha ha <pause dur="short"/> I only saw one side of him when we came in and he turned around I was like oh my God <pause dur="short"/> your other eye's even worse <pause dur="short"/> Yeah poor soul <pause dur="short"/> and that little lad as well I did when his mother described what happened I did sort of wonder if he was just if his just wrist was a bit hurty <pause dur="short"/> but yeah then he came out with a cast and I though oh fair enough</u>
<u n="122" who="S0179">oh although casts you don't necessarily just cast from a break you can cast for</u>
<u n="123" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> but it was signalling something actually wrong <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="124" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0058">do you know what I mean? Like just when they described it she didn't</u>
<u n="126" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> incidentally we did er sort of er de facto skip ahead of us but er <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't going to object too much</u>
<u n="127" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="128" who="S0179">I'm actually going to suggest would you like to go first?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I was yeah exactly I knew you would <pause dur="short"/> but if she's you know she just sort of they were going there anyway <pause dur="short"/> didn't ask what was wrong with you or me <pause dur="short"/> ha ha</u>
<u n="130" who="S0179" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> just look at her</u>
<u n="131" who="S0058">huh <pause dur="short"/> exactly yeah I mean God <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was interesting you can get all the little stories sitting there <pause dur="short"/> the couple opposite were quite funny ha</u>
<u n="132" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0058">so the couple opposite</u>
<u n="134" who="S0179">oh yes</u>
<u n="135" who="S0058">the guy with all the tattoos messing about with the</u>
<u n="136" who="S0179">I've learnt a lot about world geography</u>
<u n="137" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> you've <trunc>ti</trunc> you've taken time to improve your mind which I really think is admirable</u>
<u n="138" who="S0179">nah I keep I just keep taken time to keep my mind occupied and not bored</u>
<u n="139" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a very good book actually <pause dur="short"/> I'm pleased I brought it</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="140" who="S0179">this is a really inappropriate song <pause dur="short"/> it's about get over it and exercise</u>
<u n="141" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0179">sort of</u>
<u n="143" who="S0058">the next one's more appropriate for the for tonight</u>
<u n="144" who="S0179">what's that?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0058">oh this is on it's on triple oh one one <pause dur="short"/> maniac <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> ha ha <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was bad enough for my dad who was just did night shifts but he was in a lab by himself <pause dur="short"/> you know he didn't have to deal with any patients <pause dur="short"/> and that was bad enough so</u>
<u n="146" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I'd think I'd quite enjoy trying shift work</u>
<u n="147" who="S0058">I think well my dad's main problem was he didn't used to sleep <pause dur="short"/> ha <pause dur="short"/> erm he used to get a couple of hours sleep while on the night shift <pause dur="short"/> but then it was changed so that you really couldn't have any sleep during the night shift</u>
<u n="148" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0058">it was on call rather than necessarily night shifts initially <pause dur="short"/> then it was turned into just being on a night shift <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> and then he's still trying not to sleep the next day <pause dur="short"/> that was a bit stupid</u>
<u n="150" who="S0179">well just sleep the next day</u>
<u n="151" who="S0058">exactly yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0179">well to be fair though that's his</u>
<u n="153" who="S0058" trans="overlap">he did <pause dur="short"/> he did but it's still</u>
<u n="154" who="S0179">I think that's sort of the problem with him not a problem with the system</u>
<u n="155" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh no I mean he did kind of learn to do that but it still made him feel rotten I think</u>
<u n="156" who="S0179">is that?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0058" trans="overlap">but it didn't suit my dad at all basically <pause dur="short"/> some some people love it <pause dur="short"/> alan loved it you know</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="158" who="S0179">I wonder if we've got a slight wheel imbalance <pause dur="short"/> it's tracking left when it's left to its own devices</u>
<u n="159" who="S0058">oh</u>
<u n="160" who="S0179">slightly <pause dur="short"/> maybe it's just the camber</u>
<u n="161" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0179"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> Challenge of our rival</u>
<u n="163" who="S0058" trans="overlap"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> rival</u>
<u n="164" who="S0058">hmm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0179">actually that's pretty good because we had some break until after <pause dur="short"/> oh God way after bank holiday <pause dur="short"/> damn it <pause dur="short"/> that's only half way through <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="166" who="S0058">you what sorry?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0179">I don't fucking believe it</u>
<u n="168" who="S0058">what the bank holiday? I know chuck</u>
<u n="169" who="S0179">hmm?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0058">hmm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0179">oh I can swim anyway</u>
<u n="172" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I would throw yourself into that because I think you've got a lot of excess energy</u>
<u n="173" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="174" who="S0058">yeah? So throw yourself into your swimming and your weights <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> upper body weights</u>
<u n="176" who="S0058">yeah <trunc>up</trunc> though</u>
<u n="177" who="S0179">actually I could do some upper body isolation <pause dur="short"/> so I mean press ups are fine <pause dur="short"/> chin ups are fine</u>
<u n="178" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0179">core's probably fine <pause dur="short"/> if I just watch what I do</u>
<u n="180" who="S0058" trans="overlap">depending on what it is but <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0179">well I could do one legged core</u>
<u n="182" who="S0058">I was just about to say one legged plank is excellent <pause dur="short"/> ha</u>
<u n="183" who="S0179">buttock exercises</u>
<u n="184" who="S0058">oh definitely <pause dur="short"/> ha</u>
<u n="185" who="S0179">some</u>
<u n="186" who="S0058"><unclear/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0179" trans="overlap">could even do some tricep isolation</u>
<u n="188" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think that's all that all sounds good <pause dur="short"/> and it's a real chance I guess to focus on that</u>
<u n="189" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0058">which you don't normally particularly do <pause dur="short"/> so you know a couple of weeks of that would be good <pause dur="short"/> nice change</u>
<u n="191" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0179">bit of body building</u>
<u n="194" who="S0058">absolutely <pause dur="short"/> I never object to a bit of body building <pause dur="short"/> ha <pause dur="short"/> in you specifically but you know generally <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0179">oh I dunno</u>
<u n="196" who="S0058">poor soul</u>
<u n="197" who="S0179">I felt the doctor person was nice</u>
<u n="198" who="S0058">she was very nice <pause dur="short"/> very helpful <pause dur="short"/> very succinct <pause dur="short"/> you don't wanna be sort of faffing about</u>
<u n="199" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="200" who="S0058">you wanna go home so yeah <pause dur="short"/> but like</u>
<u n="201" who="S0179">I'm not sure she realised I just wanted an X-ray</u>
<u n="202" who="S0058">I think she probably didn't</u>
<u n="203" who="S0179" trans="overlap">I just didn't look at the results</u>
<u n="204" who="S0058">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0179">I thought she would have actually X-ray me <pause dur="short"/> I thought she'd say just send him in there</u>
<u n="206" who="S0058">roll him over a few times</u>
<u n="207" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0058">get his leg waving about for the cameras <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Ah <pause dur="short"/> did you have to have?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0179" trans="overlap">you'd think you'd at least get a copy of the X-ray</u>
<u n="210" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that was</u>
<u n="211" who="S0179">damn it</u>
<u n="212" who="S0058">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> it <trunc>d</trunc> it was impressive it was so quick <pause dur="short"/> they just wanna get you through the system I guess at that point so that's good</u>
<u n="213" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="214" who="S0058">but erm did you <trunc>m</trunc> were you made to wear a little lead thing over you</u>
<u n="215" who="S0179">over my what?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0058">over you</u>
<u n="217" who="S0179">no no</u>
<u n="218" who="S0058">no?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0179">it's only localised <pause dur="short"/> I suspect is the reason for that</u>
<u n="220" who="S0058" trans="overlap">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0179">so they put a plate underneath my leg</u>
<u n="222" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0179">and it was closer to that</u>
<u n="224" who="S0058">my grandpa always goes in with my gran <pause dur="short"/> he just goes behind the little screen</u>
<u n="225" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0058">and er last time they were there <pause dur="short"/> erm with my gran erm they were sort of you know they'd always get chatting to everybody they ever meet ever</u>
<u n="227" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0058">and they were chatting to the girl and it transpired that they er something <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember they mentioned the grandkids <pause dur="short"/> and er who's your grandkids? Or erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know it's <pause dur="short"/> oh and she'd seen the name that was it <pause dur="short"/> and she said oh are are you relations of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? Oh yeah yeah oh yeah so I went to school with them <pause dur="short"/> I was at primary school and sixth form with her <pause dur="short"/> ha <pause dur="short"/> a really nice girl</u>
<u n="229" who="S0179">hang on this is the girl who <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0058">who erm no no no</u>
<u n="231" who="S0179">it was someone else who <unclear/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0058">erm was it? It was yeah it happened a fair bit <pause dur="short"/> erm cos <anon type="place"/> was a nice area</u>
<u n="233" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Oh my God it's a smart car</u>
<u n="234" who="S0058">that's nice <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0179">are you having trouble now?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0058">ha <pause dur="short"/> oh my God</u>
<u n="237" who="S0179">I do not believe that</u>
<u n="238" who="S0058">ha <pause dur="short"/> a speeding <trunc>s</trunc> smart car <pause dur="short"/> ha <pause dur="short"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="239" who="S0179">it's really bruising to the ego</u>
<u n="240" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0179">it shouldn't be but it is</u>
<u n="242" who="S0058" trans="overlap">I could sense you being like oh put the foot down a little bit maybe <pause dur="short"/> ha ha</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="243" who="S0058">ha <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I know I've had an X-ray but I can't for the life of me think what it was for <pause dur="short"/> oh it was my ankle that was it yeah <pause dur="short"/> when I had my dickey ankle</u>
<u n="244" who="S0179">popular apparently</u>
<u n="245" who="S0058">X-rays?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0179">no the ankle</u>
<u n="247" who="S0058">oh the ankle</u>
<u n="248" who="S0179">that's what I just had X-rayed</u>
<u n="249" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> ha what about that guy in the flip-flop? He had some speed going on in that hopping <pause dur="short"/> did you see?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0179">impressive</u>
<u n="251" who="S0058">it was very impressive <pause dur="short"/> I think I'd have worn something more substantial that a flip-flop as well <pause dur="short"/> cos if you fall over on that foot <pause dur="short"/> you know that's it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="252" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="253" who="S0058">ah <pause dur="short"/> nice and quiet this time of night</u>
<u n="254" who="S0179">I'm just watching as she's waiting for a vehicle without her lights on</u>
<u n="255" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="256" who="S0179">which would be incredibly stupid</u>
<u n="257" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="258" who="S0179">but possible</u>
<u n="259" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="260" who="S0179">oh there's the smart car</u>
<u n="261" who="S0058">oh is it?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0179">yeah it is</u>
<u n="263" who="S0058">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> ha ha</u>
<u n="264" who="S0179">it's it's sub speed limit as well</u>
<u n="265" who="S0058">interesting</u>
<u n="266" who="S0179">well maybe</u>
<u n="267" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0179">I'm sorry I'm getting past him</u>
<u n="269" who="S0058">ha ha <pause dur="short"/> just because</u>
<u n="270" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="271" who="S0058">ha</u>
<u n="272" who="S0179">he sped up by miles away actually</u>
<u n="273" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you think he's noticed ya?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0179">possibly</u>
<u n="275" who="S0058">ha ha <pause dur="short"/> oh my God <pause dur="short"/> it's an angry looking sports smart car <pause dur="short"/> do you think he's got little man syndrome?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0179">possibly</u>
<u n="277" who="S0058">which seems you'd say cos then you can change your car <pause dur="short"/> unlike your height <pause dur="short"/> there really isn't anything you can do about height is the thing <pause dur="short"/> ha</u>
<u n="278" who="S0179">unless you're Tom Cruise <pause dur="short"/> he does try very hard</u>
<u n="279" who="S0058">he does try very hard but he still can't disguise the fact he's teeny tiny</u>
<u n="280" who="S0179">who was driving?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0058">I couldn't see <pause dur="short"/> you're kind of right in the back of it and there's a big pillar in the way <pause dur="long"/> I often wonder what it's like to be a truck driver <pause dur="short"/> and to have your little cabin in your in the front of your truck and</u>
<u n="282" who="S0179">I'd love it</u>
<u n="283" who="S0058">I think in some ways it would be quite feel quite cosy <pause dur="short"/> but in some ways it would be quite depressing</u>
<u n="284" who="S0179">lovely and cosy</u>
<u n="285" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0179">imagine that <pause dur="short"/> pack of sweets <pause dur="short"/> a laptop</u>
<u n="287" who="S0058">sounds like in some ways it's quite fun <pause dur="short"/> nice book you know <pause dur="short"/> I guess you'd get sick of it after a while <pause dur="short"/> but you know because of the  it'd be quite cool</u>
<u n="288" who="S0179">A nice warm sleeping bag</u>
<u n="289" who="S0058">exactly yeah <pause dur="short"/> and a bunk <pause dur="short"/> like I said you know imagine it's fun for a bit <pause dur="short"/> ha</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="290" who="S0058">oh <pause dur="short"/> it'd be a pretty cool job <pause dur="short"/> I guess you can take pride in that</u>
<u n="291" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0058">delivering stuff <pause dur="short"/> keeps Britain going all these drivers <pause dur="short"/> lorry drivers</u>
<u n="293" who="S0179">oh that's why you thought of it because you saw the barge on the side of the road</u>
<u n="294" who="S0058">oh right yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> did you wonder what the link was? Ha <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> quite a few parked up on this road</u>
<u n="295" who="S0179">wow</u>
<u n="296" who="S0058">ha nice</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="297" who="S0058">oh <pause dur="short"/> is that the X five? I think it might be <pause dur="short"/> oh no it's the the Stagecoach</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="298" who="S0058">I wonder where that little smart car is going</u>
<u n="299" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="300" who="S0058">probably <anon type="place"/> or somewhere not very cool <pause dur="short"/> ha</u>
<u n="301" who="S0179">I'd say that's probably fairly astute</u>
<u n="302" who="S0058">ah <pause dur="short"/> the lights are still on in the pool <pause dur="short"/> bizarre</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="303" who="S0058">hang on wasn't it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who did our very first who's kind of signed us up for the hotel?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0179">yep</u>
<u n="305" who="S0058">yeah it was wasn't it <pause dur="short"/> that's weird <pause dur="short"/> thinking back to then</u>
<u n="306" who="S0179">Cos actually that was when we came to look round before we bought the house</u>
<u n="307" who="S0058">yes it was wasn't it <pause dur="short"/> he yeah he was the one who told us about the discounts</u>
<u n="308" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0058">and we wrote his name down <pause dur="short"/> cos then we spoke to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="310" who="S0179">now friends on Facebook</u>
<u n="311" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh what a trajectory</u>
<u n="312" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0058">what a trajectory <pause dur="short"/> that's nice</u>
<u n="314" who="S0179">that's very nice <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> the moon and New York city</u>
<u n="315" who="S0058">look at that full tank of fuel <pause dur="short"/> all X-rayed up back in by before midnight <pause dur="short"/> so what was I gonna do when I get back? Erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said she's emptied she emptied the bin <pause dur="short"/> or took the bin bag out but then realised she didn't know where to put it <pause dur="short"/> so er she just sort of put it beside the bin <pause dur="short"/> so I'll do that straight away when we get in</u>
<u n="316" who="S0179">before the rats get in</u>
<u n="317" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no no not outside the door <pause dur="short"/> er next to the bin inside the house so I'll erm I'll move that straight away</u>
<u n="318" who="S0179">I might possibly jump in the shower while you do that</u>
<u n="319" who="S0058">that's okay <pause dur="short"/> you won't be long <pause dur="short"/> I assume <pause dur="short"/> that was a statement not an order ha</u>
<u n="320" who="S0179">it's quite convenient having <anon type="place"/> there</u>
<u n="321" who="S0058">what do you mean such a big hospital?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0058">yes this is handy <pause dur="short"/> I just sort of actively appreciate the fact that this road is here now</u>
<u n="324" who="S0179">yep so do I <pause dur="short"/> I think we always will</u>
<u n="325" who="S0058">ha probably yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="326" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0058">that's novel <pause dur="short"/> what the hell?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0179">who's twenty-four?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0058">that's really strange</u>
</body>
</text>
