<text id="SFJ2">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:54</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-02-02</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0275 S0276</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>University canteen</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Music, the internet, TV shows, men, celebrities, weekend activities, friends, Disney movies, cafes, football, Instagram, going out, university, family, sleep, cartoons, tattoos, pizza.</topics>
		<activity>Friendly discussions over lunch break</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, complaining, advising, requesting, inviting, anecdote telling, making arrangements, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0275">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>West London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0276">
				<exactage>19</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Phillipines</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lincolnshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>e_midlands</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0276">I I don't speak Korean</u>
<u n="2" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0275"><unclear/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0276" trans="overlap">do you just want me to go on a Korean website and</u>
<u n="5" who="S0275" trans="overlap"><unclear/> just Google them there's a whole website where you like subscribe</u>
<u n="6" who="S0276">there's two websites I've already been on the first one this morning when I was brushing my teeth</u>
<u n="7" who="S0275"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh my god</u>
<u n="8" who="S0276">this one I didn't get the chance to do because <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> was yelling mum I can't I'm not going not be ready so I and I realised oh shit it's nearly time to leave</u>
<u n="9" who="S0275" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0276">I need to change <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0275">and he was there looking at <unclear/> that is so funny what's going on then?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0276">oh nothing's <trunc>go</trunc> interesting is happening <pause dur="short"/> literally it's all just boring shit oh she's gonna be on Running Man I might watch that sorry</u>
<u n="13" who="S0275">what is? what is Running Man?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0276">it's like a variety show where celebrities come on and they do all like these chat up really funny challenges</u>
<u n="15" who="S0275">oh</u>
<u n="16" who="S0276">like one of my husband's my</u>
<u n="17" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0276">like he appeared on it and they were just like a challenge where it was like really rainy and it was in the mud and he got completely covered in mud</u>
<u n="19" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="20" who="S0276">and he was just like I don't care cos like he's really <trunc>fa</trunc> <unclear/> this really big fashion icon like he works with <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> like he's got all these photos with <unclear/> fashion shows and everything like that</u>
<u n="21" who="S0275" trans="overlap">who is it? <pause dur="short"/> oh okay</u>
<u n="22" who="S0276">it was just like okay I don't care about my image I just want to lick the mud</u>
<u n="23" who="S0275" trans="overlap">mm that's your husband</u>
<u n="24" who="S0276">yeah well no no he's not my husband he I want to have an affair with him</u>
<u n="25" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0276">cos like cos he has a girlfriend</u>
<u n="27" who="S0275">oh my god <pause dur="short"/> you're so funny</u>
<u n="28" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like you want to see my husband?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0275">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0276">like he's in the army right now really sad</u>
<u n="31" who="S0275">he's in the army?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0276">yeah like he's Korean like you <trunc>ha</trunc> like they have to go to the army for like two years</u>
<u n="33" who="S0275">oh my god</u>
<u n="34" who="S0276">look at my baby</u>
<u n="35" who="S0275"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0276">like he's my husband isn't he adorable?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0275">he's very cute</u>
<u n="38" who="S0276">he's just so cute look at him</u>
<u n="39" who="S0275" trans="overlap">he looks like a marshmallow</u>
<u n="40" who="S0276">he is a marshmallow that's why do you want to see him dressed as a panda? <unclear/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0275" trans="overlap">I want to see him dressed up as a panda</u>
<u n="42" who="S0276">because for his drama like to cheer his neighbour up cos like she was a social recluse</u>
<u n="43" who="S0275">oh I thought you were going to say she was a sociopath</u>
<u n="44" who="S0276">like she was a social recluse so he dressed up as a panda and he danced around like trying to cheer her up</u>
<u n="45" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh how lovely</u>
<u n="46" who="S0276">isn't he adorabable? oh <vocal desc="nonsense"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0275"><unclear/> no top on <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0276" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh isn't he adorable?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0275">he is cute you know?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0276">okay and do you want to see who I'm going to have an affair with? like he's really like strange but he's just so <pause dur="short"/> he's really weird but if you like when he looks nice like</u>
<u n="51" who="S0275">he looks sweet I like his hair</u>
<u n="52" who="S0276">yeah and but then like some things that he does like <unclear>yeah look</unclear> such a poser he is</u>
<u n="53" who="S0275">oh definitely</u>
<u n="54" who="S0276">but when he like when he looks when he dresses normally he looks really nice</u>
<u n="55" who="S0275" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> when he <unclear/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0276">but like sometimes he just <trunc>dr</trunc><trunc>dres</trunc><trunc>dres</trunc>dresses like a fucking weirdo look look at that</u>
<u n="57" who="S0275">well at least he don't judge</u>
<u n="58" who="S0276">no and then do you want to see my babies?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0275">oh my god you sound like me you know different husbands</u>
<u n="60" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> like these are my boys like I have them on my wall they're so adorable</u>
<u n="61" who="S0275" trans="overlap">are they a band?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0276">yeah they're a band they're B one A four look they're just so adorabable</u>
<u n="63" who="S0275">adorabable?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0276">look at them they're so cute</u>
<u n="65" who="S0275">which one's your favourite?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0276">okay okay erm <pause dur="short"/> those two are my favourite I can't zoom in look that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0275" trans="overlap">are they twins?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0276">no that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like he's the visual he's really handsome he acts really mature and he <trunc>a</trunc> even though he's the youngest he acts <trunc>mo</trunc></u>
<u n="69" who="S0275" trans="overlap">I like handsome <pause dur="short"/> he's the youngest is he?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0276">yeah he's like twenty something like early really early twenties like twenty-one</u>
<u n="71" who="S0275" trans="overlap">sorry how old is the others then? they only could be twenty-two</u>
<u n="72" who="S0276">yeah like they're around that age I think like they're like twenty-four so like twenty-two twenty-three</u>
<u n="73" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh my gosh they look like babies</u>
<u n="74" who="S0276">he's my favourite even though he's not the best looking he's such a dork he just sits and he just eats all the time like in one of their in one of their TV shows like they were supposed to be looking he was supposed to go out and buy groceries but he went he spent all the money on food cos he was hungry</u>
<u n="75" who="S0275" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's like you</u>
<u n="76" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0275">he could've still got the groceries and made something</u>
<u n="78" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he wanted to eat so he was just at a children's playground like sitting on those one of those <trunc>squish</trunc> not squishy</u>
<u n="79" who="S0275" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> squidgy erm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0276" trans="overlap">you know those rocking things? yeah not</u>
<u n="81" who="S0275" trans="overlap">like the see seesaw <pause dur="short"/> ah mini seesaw</u>
<u n="82" who="S0276" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but one that you can sit on on your own or it's like <unclear/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0275" trans="overlap"><unclear/> just so lonely</u>
<u n="84" who="S0276">I was just like on that just eating all these ice creams and chocolates I relate to him so much</u>
<u n="85" who="S0275">yeah you do you do</u>
<u n="86" who="S0276">but he's he's such a good singer as well like I saw his solo performance and I cried</u>
<u n="87" who="S0275">oh my goodness getting emotional</u>
<u n="88" who="S0276" trans="overlap">I put <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0275">I want to go see the babies today haven't seen them in ages</u>
<u n="90" who="S0276">what? the one with the really V-neck guy?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0275" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> v-neck?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0276">doesn't he wear like a really low V-neck?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0275"><vocal desc="misc"/> who the hell wears a low V-neck?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0276">this is like the guy that you like watch <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh my god the V-neck</u>
<u n="96" who="S0276">yeah he wears a V-neck doesn't he? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0275">V-neck</u>
<u n="98" who="S0276">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0275"><unclear/> you know remember when he always comes and sits by himself and eats? <pause dur="short"/> you <unclear/></u>
<u n="100" who="S0276" trans="overlap">yeah that's him he wears like a really it's not a V-neck but it's like a really low-cut shirt so <unclear/> like here</u>
<u n="101" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh is it?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0276">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0275">I never notice I only see his face</u>
<u n="104" who="S0276">oh okay he wears he has like a beard right?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0275">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0276">yeah that's him</u>
<u n="107" who="S0275">oh no he has V-necks</u>
<u n="108" who="S0276">not really I mean it was like okay it's a U-neck it's really low</u>
<u n="109" who="S0275" trans="overlap">er</u>
<u n="110" who="S0276"><unclear/> I can remember seeing thinking why's that like? <vocal desc="laugh"/> like</u>
<u n="111" who="S0275">no that's not cute</u>
<u n="112" who="S0276" trans="overlap">like yeah like I also I remember seeing him thinking why? it's winter it's cold</u>
<u n="113" who="S0275">it is cold <pause dur="short"/> this is so messy I can't deal with it</u>
<u n="114" who="S0276">no</u>
<u n="115" who="S0275">how was your weekend?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0276">my weekend what did I do? oh I went ice skating</u>
<u n="117" who="S0275">how was it? I can't believe you went ice skating and you didn't tell <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0276">erm oh oh yeah I could tell her it's like a student is like eleven pounds something it's at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0275" trans="overlap">that's the same bloody price as in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0276">yeah it was at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0275">how was that? that's so far</u>
<u n="122" who="S0276">hey it was really pretty well not really</u>
<u n="123" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah but it was far</u>
<u n="124" who="S0276">it was alright cos I haven't been ice skating since like primary school so at first I was a bit okay I like hold onto the side and then I I could do it</u>
<u n="125" who="S0275"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0276">I only fell over once</u>
<u n="127" who="S0275">oh</u>
<u n="128" who="S0276">and that's cos I was trying to <trunc>s</trunc><trunc>s</trunc>stop</u>
<u n="129" who="S0275">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0276">and like obviously I put like my feet <trunc>t</trunc>towards each other <unclear/> where like that cos I wanted to slow down but obviously they kept moving so I went like that and so I fell</u>
<u n="131" who="S0275" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh mm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0276" trans="overlap">well no I went with my best <trunc>fr</trunc> I remember my two best friends and like her one of my best friends boyfriends came and obviously when he was younger he got professional training didn't he?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh that's so cute yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>rea</trunc> mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0276">so he was just like proper showing off just like going really fast</u>
<u n="135" who="S0275">and you guys <unclear>were just there</unclear></u>
<u n="136" who="S0276" trans="overlap">yeah we were just like and my other best friend like she fell over six times</u>
<u n="137" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="138" who="S0276">and in the end she got one of those polar bear things that kids have</u>
<u n="139" who="S0275">straight up <unclear>you have to</unclear></u>
<u n="140" who="S0276">but erm he was like my friend's boyfriend was so good that he even like the people who were like running it who were like going around like making sure everyone was okay</u>
<u n="141" who="S0275">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0276">they were just there teaching him tricks</u>
<u n="143" who="S0275"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0276">like how to stop using like the side of your blade</u>
<u n="145" who="S0275">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0276" trans="overlap">and how to <trunc>s</trunc> how to spin</u>
<u n="147" who="S0275"><unclear>oh my god</unclear></u>
<u n="148" who="S0276" trans="overlap">and me and me and my best friend were just like for god's sake</u>
<u n="149" who="S0275">that's so awesome though</u>
<u n="150" who="S0276">I know</u>
<u n="151" who="S0275">was he good?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0276">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah so like <trunc>t</trunc> you know it was so it was just like so <unclear/> the two of them were just going around holding hands and I was like alright then I'll just go on my own</u>
<u n="153" who="S0275">oh no</u>
<u n="154" who="S0276">and then like I made then this other couple like the guy was skating she was just holding on to the back of him cos she couldn't skate</u>
<u n="155" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh no <pause dur="short"/> that's really sad</u>
<u n="156" who="S0276" trans="overlap">get <unclear/> man but it's okay me and my friend we were just like we can be ice princesses</u>
<u n="157" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0276">you know like that Disney film?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0275">which Disney film?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0276">you know the Disney film that physics girl</u>
<u n="161" who="S0275">physics?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0276">yeah did you ever watch Buffy the Vampire Slayer? <pause dur="short"/> judging you</u>
<u n="163" who="S0275" trans="overlap">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0276">but like it's this girl that she do she does physics it's a Disney film look I'll show you</u>
<u n="165" who="S0275">yeah show me</u>
<u n="166" who="S0276">how have you not seen the Ice Princess?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0275" trans="overlap">it's called physics?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0276">no she does physics and then she does ice skating</u>
<u n="169" who="S0275" trans="overlap">what does that mean she does physics? like literal <pause dur="short"/> science?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0276">yeah like she was going to study that at uni or high school</u>
<u n="171" who="S0275" trans="overlap">a movie</u>
<u n="172" who="S0276">yeah there's a movie</u>
<u n="173" who="S0275">wait is it a real movie?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0276">yeah it's a real movie and it's called the Ice Princess this one</u>
<u n="175" who="S0275" trans="overlap">I mean like is it a real people</u>
<u n="176" who="S0276">yes this one</u>
<u n="177" who="S0275">oh</u>
<u n="178" who="S0276" trans="overlap">look at the pretty dress</u>
<u n="179" who="S0275">no I never seen it</u>
<u n="180" who="S0276">what the fuck is wrong with you?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0275"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0276">like and she does all like these tricks like cos she figures out how to do it with physics</u>
<u n="183" who="S0275">oh is it?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0276">yeah look no that's not her that's not her I don't even know what the fuck that is but look</u>
<u n="185" who="S0275">no I no I've definitely not watched that but that erm <pause dur="short"/> her dress is pretty</u>
<u n="186" who="S0276">it is I want to be that</u>
<u n="187" who="S0275">you wanna be an ice princess?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0276">I wanna be an ice princess</u>
<u n="189" who="S0275">er just <unclear/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0276"><vocal desc="gasp"/> I wanna see Disney Princesses on Ice look</u>
<u n="191" who="S0275">do you actually wanna see Disney Princesses on Ice?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0276">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0275"><vocal desc="sigh"/> oh</u>
<u n="194" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0275" trans="overlap">first of all Ariel can't do it cos Ariel hasn't got legs</u>
<u n="196" who="S0276">they could do it when she does have legs</u>
<u n="197" who="S0275">they're going to have to bring Ursula out and do the whole scene to give her some legs cos really she's a little mermaid</u>
<u n="198" who="S0276">oh why is she here? <pause dur="short"/> oh that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> from <anon type="place"/> she's called the ice princess <unclear/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh why? is she a</u>
<u n="200" who="S0276" trans="overlap">cos she has like a really cool personality</u>
<u n="201" who="S0275">I was going to say if she's is she evil?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0276">like but she's not really she's really quite sweet</u>
<u n="203" who="S0275">she's the ice princess</u>
<u n="204" who="S0276">oh who are they? <pause dur="short"/> they're Japanese I know that wait she's not Japanese that's <unclear>Gio</unclear> tiara</u>
<u n="205" who="S0275" trans="overlap">that is <unclear>Gio</unclear></u>
<u n="206" who="S0276"><unclear>that's Gian</unclear></u>
<u n="207" who="S0275">ah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0276"><unclear>Gian</unclear></u>
<u n="209" who="S0275"><unclear>Gian</unclear></u>
<u n="210" who="S0276"><unclear>Gian</unclear></u>
<u n="211" who="S0275">can we? I'm hungry</u>
<u n="212" who="S0276">you just ate</u>
<u n="213" who="S0275">I know <pause dur="short"/> where are we going to eat? I don't think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s coming</u>
<u n="214" who="S0276">okay do you wanna just go to one of those café places?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0275">yeah to on <anon type="place"/> the one that you showed me</u>
<u n="216" who="S0276">what? on <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0275">yeah you said oh do you want to go on the inside? that little inside thing?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0276">what inside thing?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0275">where we was last week</u>
<u n="220" who="S0276">oh we could do</u>
<u n="221" who="S0275">no not the actual place but you said what? <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what I'm talking about anymore</u>
<u n="222" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0275">it's cold did you watch the football yesterday?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0276">no what the fuck is this?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0275"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0276">why would I watch the football?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0275">why wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0276">because I have a life</u>
<u n="229" who="S0275">no football is life</u>
<u n="230" who="S0276" trans="overlap">and I don't have TV</u>
<u n="231" who="S0275">oh shit you don't have TV</u>
<u n="232" who="S0276">yeah I don't have TV <pause dur="short"/> I watched a Japanese film instead</u>
<u n="233" who="S0275"><vocal desc="misc"/> hiccup listen <pause dur="short"/> the game was so good yesterday</u>
<u n="234" who="S0276">was it now?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0275">it was you know because we won</u>
<u n="236" who="S0276">did you now?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0275">erm five nil</u>
<u n="238" who="S0276">oh well well done yay</u>
<u n="239" who="S0275">I know and my babes scored</u>
<u n="240" who="S0276">good for you</u>
<u n="241" who="S0275">I know <pause dur="short"/> it was amazing it was absolutely amazing</u>
<u n="242" who="S0276">okay</u>
<u n="243" who="S0275">when was the last time you went clubbing?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0276">me?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0275">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0276">give me a sec <pause dur="short"/> two weeks ago</u>
<u n="247" who="S0275">really?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0276">yeah but I know</u>
<u n="249" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0276">I know I'm going to have to go twice this month</u>
<u n="251" who="S0275"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you know you're gonna have to what do you mean you know?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0276" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like one's for going out for my friend's birthday</u>
<u n="253" who="S0275">oh right</u>
<u n="254" who="S0276">and then we're going to go to what's it called <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0275"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0276"><anon type="place"/> is that what it's called?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0276">it's a bar</u>
<u n="259" who="S0275">oh a <trunc>b</trunc> not the place</u>
<u n="260" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <unclear/> try and find it on my friends Instagram <pause dur="short"/> at least I think it's on her Instagram</u>
<u n="261" who="S0275">I'm falling asleep so</u>
<u n="262" who="S0276" trans="overlap">like cause she invited us so</u>
<u n="263" who="S0275">you kind of have to go</u>
<u n="264" who="S0276">yeah cos I haven't seen her in a while yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0275">oh <anon type="place"/> that's not the area</u>
<u n="266" who="S0276">I don't know but <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah <anon type="place"/> that's the area's name</u>
<u n="268" who="S0276" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know but that's what they're saying</u>
<u n="269" who="S0275"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="271" who="S0275">oh okay that's fun I haven't been out in ages</u>
<u n="272" who="S0276">well you're out of the house now</u>
<u n="273" who="S0275" trans="overlap">like I don't I'm at uni don't mock it I'm at uni man <pause dur="short"/> I wanna get drunk</u>
<u n="274" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0275">but I can't go out this Wednesday because I'm going to come to the seminar on Thursday</u>
<u n="276" who="S0276">yay</u>
<u n="277" who="S0275">cos you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said he's doing the erm</u>
<u n="278" who="S0276">oh shit we have to do a plan this week</u>
<u n="279" who="S0275">yeah we have to do a plan so I have to come <pause dur="short"/> and then on the weekend I always want to sleep that's all I want to do is sleep</u>
<u n="280" who="S0276">hey there's nothing wrong with sleep sleep sleep</u>
<u n="281" who="S0275" trans="overlap">sleep is so important I when I baby I babysat my nephew on Saturday night oh my goodness he was a little devil he didn't sleep he woke up every two hours from eight o'clock in the evening till till eight the next morning</u>
<u n="282" who="S0276">okay</u>
<u n="283" who="S0275">what do you mean okay? you're reading that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're not even listening to me are you?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0276">I'm sorry you were saying how you were tired</u>
<u n="285" who="S0275" trans="overlap">I told you <unclear>auntie</unclear> famous become <unclear>auntie</unclear></u>
<u n="286" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay you were talking about how like you were babysitting your nephew and that you were tired</u>
<u n="287" who="S0275" trans="overlap">what did I say after that? what time? gimme the timeframe that I gave you</u>
<u n="288" who="S0276">last week</u>
<u n="289" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0276">strawberry lace?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0275">you're trying to give me erm <pause dur="short"/> sugar</u>
<u n="292" who="S0276" trans="overlap">do you not want do you want a strawberry lace or not? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah I do <pause dur="short"/> going to give me diabetes</u>
<u n="294" who="S0276">hey there's nothing wrong with that</u>
<u n="295" who="S0275">er</u>
<u n="296" who="S0276">come on</u>
<u n="297" who="S0275"><unclear/> sweets in the morning is it nine AM?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0276">I had Wotsits on the bus to uni</u>
<u n="299" who="S0275">eight AM you had them look there's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0276">oh there she is hey she's not here she can't hear <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0275">she can't see us really <pause dur="short"/> look she can't <unclear/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0276">oh okay</u>
<u n="303" who="S0275"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> text me later anyhoos <pause dur="short"/> erm <unclear>what</unclear> was I saying?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0276">I don't even know</u>
<u n="305" who="S0275">exactly that's not good enough you should know I told you eight till eight</u>
<u n="306" who="S0276">oh that's nice</u>
<u n="307" who="S0275">no it's not are you reading again?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0276">you said it's eight to eight</u>
<u n="309" who="S0275">yeah he woke up every two hours</u>
<u n="310" who="S0276">yeah well he's a baby right?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0275">he's one years old</u>
<u n="312" who="S0276">yeah that's still a baby</u>
<u n="313" who="S0275" trans="overlap">he <trunc>sle</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said he sleeps the whole night he won't wake up is what she told me <pause dur="short"/> she lied</u>
<u n="314" who="S0276" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0275">so I realised I can't be erm I can't have no babies</u>
<u n="316" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0275" trans="overlap">because I need <unclear>sleep</unclear> like I was so furious with him <pause dur="short"/> I wanna sleep all day every day</u>
<u n="318" who="S0276">well <pause dur="short"/> maybe he does sleep</u>
<u n="319" who="S0275">yeah I think it was just cos he was in my house</u>
<u n="320" who="S0276">yeah I think it's just you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0275">and I kept on screaming <pause dur="short"/> I was trying to watch my show</u>
<u n="322" who="S0276">your what show?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0275">erm <pause dur="short"/> what is it called? it's on Netflix <pause dur="short"/> I love Netflix Netflix is literally my life <pause dur="short"/> all I do is watch Netflix</u>
<u n="324" who="S0276" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/> she's my girl crush look at her</u>
<u n="325" who="S0275">oh she's so pretty</u>
<u n="326" who="S0276">I know she's so adorable she's my girl crush</u>
<u n="327" who="S0275">is this still the news?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0276">oh no this is just like a website I go on</u>
<u n="329" who="S0275">oh</u>
<u n="330" who="S0276">do you watch how to get away with murder?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0275">no</u>
<u n="332" who="S0276">yeah like it's so good you should</u>
<u n="333" who="S0275">what does that mean?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0276"><unclear>bliss</unclear></u>
<u n="335" who="S0275">erm it's called Fringe anyways</u>
<u n="336" who="S0276">okay is it about someone murdering someone with their fringe?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0275"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh my god <unclear>you joker</unclear> no it's erm basically this crazy scientist who before he went mad he used to do experiments on humans and then now all those experiments are coming to life basically <pause dur="short"/> it's so good though I love it I love it anyways what did you say just now?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0276">you should watch How to Get Away with Murder</u>
<u n="339" who="S0275">How to Get Away with Murder How to Get er oh I mean that's not really a good show because what if someone murders someone</u>
<u n="340" who="S0276">spoiler yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0275">but I mean like if in real like what if I used that?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0276">well <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's only just started so there's not gonna be a lot of <trunc>es</trunc> episodes to catch up on</u>
<u n="343" who="S0275">where do you watch it? on the internet?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0276">yeah illegally</u>
<u n="345" who="S0275">illegally</u>
<u n="346" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> have you found it?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0275">there's been ten apple <unclear/> er oh</u>
<u n="348" who="S0276" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0275">erm <pause dur="short"/> aBC?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0276">ABC family</u>
<u n="351" who="S0275">mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0276" trans="overlap">it's American</u>
<u n="353" who="S0275">it's always American</u>
<u n="354" who="S0276">of course</u>
<u n="355" who="S0275">er oh oh I love criminals well I mean I don't love criminals I mean I love criminal shows</u>
<u n="356" who="S0276" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> exactly that's why I thought you might like it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0275">oh no <pause dur="short"/> oh no her husband's having an affair</u>
<u n="358" who="S0276">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0275">oh no</u>
<u n="360" who="S0276">you're spoiling it for yourself aren't you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0275" trans="overlap">no <unclear/> I'm not it's just the plot <pause dur="short"/> do you guys watch or do you do you watch Scandal?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0276">no but my friend does</u>
<u n="363" who="S0275">I don't wanna get into it I'm not going to watch it but my friend watches and she's always like oh my goodness</u>
<u n="364" who="S0276">yeah?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0275" trans="overlap">what's her <trunc>na</trunc> I don't know what that woman's name is</u>
<u n="366" who="S0276">eh <unclear/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0275">and then she's like oh the president the president Fitzgerald oh oh my gosh I don't know these characters</u>
<u n="368" who="S0276">yeah but erm I don't want to watch Scandal cos it's on it's like fourth season and that's too many <unclear>to watch</unclear></u>
<u n="369" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah it's too much innit? it's too late</u>
<u n="370" who="S0276">like I'm <trunc>wa</trunc> I'm watching Sex and the City right now</u>
<u n="371" who="S0275">what? from the beginning?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0276">yeah from the beginning I'm on season four now</u>
<u n="373" who="S0275" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh my goodness <pause dur="short"/> how many seasons are there? like twenty now?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0276" trans="overlap">six</u>
<u n="375" who="S0275">twenty-six?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0276">no there's six <pause dur="short"/> six</u>
<u n="377" who="S0275" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> there was only six are you serious?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0276">yeah it's like</u>
<u n="379" who="S0275" trans="overlap">how many episodes in each? there were about twenty-five?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0276" trans="overlap">they're like eighteen</u>
<u n="381" who="S0275">are you serious?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0276">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0275">that show was on for years</u>
<u n="384" who="S0276">only six years dude</u>
<u n="385" who="S0275">like about ten fifteen years man</u>
<u n="386" who="S0276">are you counting the films?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0275"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0276">are you counting the prequel series?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0275">no <pause dur="short"/> I swear it was on forever like I thought it was never gonna end</u>
<u n="390" who="S0276">were you watching it when it was on air?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0275">yeah I used to <trunc>wa</trunc> yeah by accident like you know cos it was on Channel Four and in my old flat they only had one to five so I had I used to have to watch that at night <pause dur="short"/> don't judge me I was like ten</u>
<u n="392" who="S0276" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> naughty</u>
<u n="393" who="S0275">I know there was bloody ninety-four episodes <pause dur="short"/> that's not much</u>
<u n="394" who="S0276" trans="overlap">was not <pause dur="short"/> okay there was yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0275">and only six seasons that's nothing</u>
<u n="396" who="S0276">exactly like there was a hundred episodes in the <trunc>thir</trunc> in the after four and a bit seasons of Friends</u>
<u n="397" who="S0275">I thought it was as it was on for as long as friends</u>
<u n="398" who="S0276">no friends was ten years</u>
<u n="399" who="S0275">yeah I literally thought it was ten fifteen years</u>
<u n="400" who="S0276">oh</u>
<u n="401" who="S0275">that Sex and the City was on</u>
<u n="402" who="S0276">or did you <trunc>conf</trunc> or did you confuse it with Buffy? cos Buffy was seven <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="403" who="S0275" trans="overlap"><trunc>Buff</trunc> what's with you and Buffy no</u>
<u n="404" who="S0276" trans="overlap">Buffy <trunc>wa</trunc> is amazing I could watch that over and over <trunc>ag</trunc></u>
<u n="405" who="S0275" trans="overlap">I watched Buffy once</u>
<u n="406" who="S0276">oh</u>
<u n="407" who="S0275">I <trunc>wo</trunc> literally watched one episode because it was like in my head it was like Bewitched did you used to watch Bewitched?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0276">are you talking about Bewitched or Charmed?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0275">oh Charmed</u>
<u n="410" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0276">I tried getting into to Charmed but then when I wanted to watch it</u>
<u n="412" who="S0275"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what the hell's Bewitched?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0276">I don't know I think that's some other show</u>
<u n="414" who="S0275">oh shame anyway Charmed Buffy was like Charmed my my sister my mum was against that</u>
<u n="415" who="S0276" trans="overlap">yeah but Buffy was <pause dur="short"/> but Buffy had hot guys</u>
<u n="416" who="S0275">yeah but how old was we?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0276">it was released the year like when I was like two or three</u>
<u n="418" who="S0275" trans="overlap">that was in ninety <trunc>nin</trunc> exactly ninety-ninety-five</u>
<u n="419" who="S0276" trans="overlap">but it was really good it was so like funny</u>
<u n="420" who="S0275">funny? do you know I'd I like the girl</u>
<u n="421" who="S0276">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0275">but only cos she was in Scooby Doo</u>
<u n="423" who="S0276">I know right</u>
<u n="424" who="S0275">yeah so I didn't like her as Buffy</u>
<u n="425" who="S0276">did you know that that in Scooby Doo the actor who played Fred she's married to him</u>
<u n="426" who="S0275"><vocal desc="gasp"/> really?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0276" trans="overlap">yeah they're actually married that's why they got the role cos the director wanted like a real life couple</u>
<u n="428" who="S0275" trans="overlap">no bloody way</u>
<u n="429" who="S0276">yeah</u>
<u n="430" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="431" who="S0276">the director it was so like when I found out I was like ah <vocal desc="nonsense"/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0275">I love that movie I love Fred and Velma and Louise and</u>
<u n="433" who="S0276">no</u>
<u n="434" who="S0275">Shaggy and</u>
<u n="435" who="S0276">there's no Louise</u>
<u n="436" who="S0275">oh what's her name?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0276">Velma is Daphne</u>
<u n="438" who="S0275">Daphne Daphne who's Louise?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0276" trans="overlap">did you <trunc>con</trunc> did you <trunc>confu</trunc>fu Thelma and Louise not Velma</u>
<u n="440" who="S0275">Thelma and Louise is that a different show?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0276">that's a film</u>
<u n="442" who="S0275">shit</u>
<u n="443" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0276">you're really just confusing things now</u>
<u n="445" who="S0275">oh shame so it was Velma and Daphne</u>
<u n="446" who="S0276" trans="overlap">Daphne Daphne Daphne</u>
<u n="447" who="S0275">Daphne <pause dur="short"/> shame</u>
<u n="448" who="S0276">and Scooby obviously</u>
<u n="449" who="S0275">and Scoobs yeah I liked Shaggy I always thought he was he could've been my uncle <vocal desc="laugh"/> innit? innit?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0276">well we all got to admit he was a little high</u>
<u n="451" who="S0275">he was always high</u>
<u n="452" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0275">he's eating bloody dog food</u>
<u n="454" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0275">I'm like that's high that is high I do love him though <pause dur="short"/> and the erm Mystery Machine</u>
<u n="456" who="S0276">oh like did you ever watch like the new versions of the live films? like the one where they were all teenagers</u>
<u n="457" who="S0275">oh no</u>
<u n="458" who="S0276" trans="overlap">cos like that was all bullshit</u>
<u n="459" who="S0275">no I didn't actually</u>
<u n="460" who="S0276" trans="overlap">cos apparently like Shaggy was supposed to be older than them and it was Daphne's van there was just like a whole bunch of bullshit and they completely cancelled out like the Scooby Doo kids show which was much funnier</u>
<u n="461" who="S0275" trans="overlap">what the hell <pause dur="short"/> why do they do that? they always have to ruin shit</u>
<u n="462" who="S0276" trans="overlap">and like and I don't like the way the new one like mystery incorporated Velma and Shaggy? no</u>
<u n="463" who="S0275">oh my gosh yeah I know what happened there?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0276" trans="overlap">that was just like that was just shit</u>
<u n="465" who="S0275">they chucked up the system</u>
<u n="466" who="S0276">yeah like the only couple in that friendship group was Fred and Daphne and that was just implied</u>
<u n="467" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah that was yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0276" trans="overlap">It wasn't even supposed to be full it was not supposed to be full on romance it's just implied like when they dance together</u>
<u n="469" who="S0275" trans="overlap">it was implied yeah oh well they was gorgeous they was gorgeous</u>
<u n="470" who="S0276" trans="overlap">god why's it all got to be about romance now?</u>
<u n="471" who="S0275">I know it's Valentine's Day soon</u>
<u n="472" who="S0276">oh just ignore that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="gasp"/> did you watch that other show do you know by Hanna-Barbera the like The Flintstones <pause dur="short"/> hanna-<trunc>Barbe</trunc></u>
<u n="473" who="S0275" trans="overlap">listen I never watched The Flintstones I'm not going to lie</u>
<u n="474" who="S0276" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0275">I watched one episode once it was so irritating because they was walking their car</u>
<u n="476" who="S0276">I know right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0275">that was so stupid</u>
<u n="478" who="S0276">I know</u>
<u n="479" who="S0275" trans="overlap">they should've just walked <pause dur="short"/> why was they walking their car?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0276" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc>you're thinking too much</u>
<u n="481" who="S0275">no it well I was a child and I thought that so I thought</u>
<u n="482" who="S0276">you're not supposed to think</u>
<u n="483" who="S0275">I know exactly so I thought no</u>
<u n="484" who="S0276" trans="overlap">so did you? what about the? did you watch Top Cat? <shift new="singing"/> Top Cat <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0275">no</u>
<u n="486" who="S0276">oh okay</u>
<u n="487" who="S0275">I didn't actually that's so <trunc>f</trunc> I mean I <trunc>wa</trunc> I watched like once</u>
<u n="488" who="S0276" trans="overlap">what about Wacky Racers? Wacky Racers or Races</u>
<u n="489" who="S0275" trans="overlap">no no I never actually as well that's the one where all the different animals are always having a race and no and it had the purple the purple yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0276" trans="overlap">one <pause dur="short"/> and it had the dog that went <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah I did I watched that but not like erm</u>
<u n="492" who="S0276" trans="overlap">I <trunc>collec</trunc> I got all the little toys</u>
<u n="493" who="S0275">and I used to watch the Teletubbies</u>
<u n="494" who="S0276">oh yeah we all watched the Teletubbies but no they're all all those shows were by the same like company</u>
<u n="495" who="S0275">really?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0276">yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0275">you see that <pause dur="short"/> bellerín scored his first goal yesterday oh sugar that's our new <trunc>de</trunc> our defender I can't get out <pause dur="short"/> he's a sweety <unclear>and</unclear> my babes my babe where my babes?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0276">er er I don't know</u>
<u n="499" who="S0275" trans="overlap">Theo Walcott man oh there he is oh my gosh my gorgeous</u>
<u n="500" who="S0276">ah ha</u>
<u n="501" who="S0275">oh one of the few coloured people I like <pause dur="short"/> look at his tattoos his tattoos are gorgeous</u>
<u n="502" who="S0276">oh right</u>
<u n="503" who="S0275">I want some do you know what I want a erm Mandela tattoo now when I <trunc>sa</trunc> did I already say this to you?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0276">I think you may have <pause dur="short"/> yes it was like it was like a like a fancy it looks like er</u>
<u n="505" who="S0275" trans="overlap">a <trunc>N</trunc>Nelson Mandela <pause dur="short"/> henna</u>
<u n="506" who="S0276">yeah it looks like henna</u>
<u n="507" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="508" who="S0276">yeah I remember you telling me<unclear/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0275" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> I'm going to sneeze <pause dur="short"/> bless you me</u>
<u n="510" who="S0276">what was that?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0275">that was a sneeze</u>
<u n="512" who="S0276">that was not a sneeze</u>
<u n="513" who="S0275">what the hell? what do you mean?</u>
<u n="514" who="S0276">that was not a sneeze</u>
<u n="515" who="S0275">are you serious?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0276">that wasn't a sneeze</u>
<u n="517" who="S0275">are you disrespecting my sneeze?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0276">yes that wasn't a sneeze</u>
<u n="519" who="S0275">that's dread it do you want me to sneeze like spray everywhere? <unclear>achoo</unclear></u>
<u n="520" who="S0276" trans="overlap">it was like <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's how you sneeze <unclear>achoo</unclear></u>
<u n="521" who="S0275" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that is so ugly</u>
<u n="522" who="S0276">oh I want food look at their food</u>
<u n="523" who="S0275">I don't like pizza</u>
<u n="524" who="S0276">what the fuck is wrong with you?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0275">I know I'm just like the only person the only young person in the world that doesn't like pizza</u>
<u n="526" who="S0276"><unclear/> pizza on Thursday</u>
<u n="527" who="S0275">I can eat pizza though but I just don't like it</u>
<u n="528" who="S0276" trans="overlap">am I getting pizza on Thursday? I might be</u>
<u n="529" who="S0275">yum from oh I knew you were going to say</u>
<u n="530" who="S0276" trans="overlap">could be getting Pizza Express</u>
<u n="531" who="S0275">yeah that's your gaff you know?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0276">no my pizza place is Topps</u>
<u n="533" who="S0275">don't that is just like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> her pizza place is Topps but she loves to go Pizza Express that's all that's all she does</u>
<u n="534" who="S0276" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I we first discovered Topps cos it was like me and my friend last year we was just wandering around and it was like gone midnight and we were hungry</u>
<u n="535" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0276">and all the chicken places were shut for some reason</u>
<u n="537" who="S0275" trans="overlap">obviously they're always bloody shut</u>
<u n="538" who="S0276">and we wandered all the way to Topps Pizza and we went in and he we only had like five just like about five pounds between us</u>
<u n="539" who="S0275">yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0276">and he so we could only get small which was like four slices</u>
<u n="541" who="S0275">yeah</u>
<u n="542" who="S0276">but he was so nice he bumped it up to the next size for us</u>
<u n="543" who="S0275" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0276">they are so nice like they are amazing people and you get such good deals</u>
<u n="545" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh my god I love erm cheap food</u>
<u n="546" who="S0276">it's really good</u>
<u n="547" who="S0275"><unclear/> make things easier <vocal desc="gasp"/> what did happen with that game?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0276">what game?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0275">the Chelsea and Man City?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0276">I don't care</u>
<u n="551" who="S0275"><vocal desc="laugh"/> how can you not care? <pause dur="short"/> aren't you British?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0276" trans="overlap">see this? me not caring</u>
<u n="553" who="S0275">I don't get it <pause dur="short"/> sugar oh it was one all in the end</u>
<u n="554" who="S0276">mm</u>
<u n="555" who="S0275">stayed the same I told my mum it was going to stay the same <pause dur="short"/> I told her look at that look at that you see that?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0276">do I give a shit?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0275">yeah you do</u>
<u n="558" who="S0276">do you have Twitter?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0275" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah I don't use it I don't tweet I I try it's just like I don't use Instagram I try I really do but what am I meant to do?</u>
<u n="560" who="S0276">I know</u>
<u n="561" who="S0275" trans="overlap">I say this to my work colleagues everyday what am I taking photos of and putting up? because most of the people on my Instagram they take photos of their face and put it up</u>
<u n="562" who="S0276" trans="overlap">I know I don't like doing that</u>
<u n="563" who="S0275" trans="overlap">but I can't like I don't know how to say <vocal desc="laugh"/> what am I doing? what am I doing? <unclear/> the same photo every time or</u>
<u n="564" who="S0276">I know <unclear/> what's your angle?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0275" trans="overlap"><unclear/> see <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>d</trunc> I that's what I was saying to them as well I don't know what my angle is</u>
<u n="566" who="S0276">okay but how do you do it?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0275">usually I just</u>
<u n="568" who="S0276">oh you do it from there okay I do it from up here</u>
<u n="569" who="S0275">let me see let me see</u>
<u n="570" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0275">I think I do it from up</u>
<u n="572" who="S0276">I do it from really high up cos like like it's supposed to do your V-neck feature supposed to do your chin so then like my chin or neck and like <unclear/> taught me</u>
<u n="573" who="S0275" trans="overlap">really high <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="574" who="S0276">is you always do it from above</u>
<u n="575" who="S0275">that's a good angle for you actually yeah</u>
<u n="576" who="S0276">yeah see <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0275">shit that was your good lighting for me</u>
<u n="578" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="579" who="S0275">and disappears look look you can't see <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0276" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="581" who="S0275">your phone's rude I'm so bright on my phone your phone's dread no I can't erm I don't do photos</u>
<u n="582" who="S0276">no I <trunc>do</trunc> do you want to see my Instagram? there's hardly any selfies</u>
<u n="583" who="S0275">oh I have none I</u>
<u n="584" who="S0276" trans="overlap">you have tons of selfies what are you talking?</u>
<u n="585" who="S0275" trans="overlap">no not of them just me I have always with somebody oh look that's the only</u>
<u n="586" who="S0276">ah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0275">that one <unclear/> like yeah I don't usually take it by myself look one</u>
<u n="588" who="S0276" trans="overlap">look mine's <trunc>mo</trunc> my one's a lot food for a while</u>
<u n="589" who="S0275">for a while? for the whole time</u>
<u n="590" who="S0276">yeah but then I was like okay I need to add stuff so I <trunc>cha</trunc> switched it up</u>
<u n="591" who="S0275">you see I used to have bare food on here I had other shit but then I just deleted it all</u>
<u n="592" who="S0276" trans="overlap">wait wait what what's in your bio? <pause dur="short"/> oh okay</u>
<u n="593" who="S0275"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> twenty <anon type="place"/> equals</u>
<u n="594" who="S0276" trans="overlap">I've just got <trunc>m</trunc> I've got my name and then a quote about chocolate</u>
<u n="595" who="S0275">you joker</u>
<u n="596" who="S0276">hey I should change that quote</u>
<u n="597" who="S0275">I need to have my age because sometimes erm you know them old men like to er try try it well I mean had it when I was young but now I'm not young so it doesn't really <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="598" who="S0276">do you find it weird when strangers follow you on Twitter?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah like where they <trunc>co</trunc> look at this guy look at this <pause dur="short"/> oh sugar I've another one why do you need to like this many photos? <unclear/></u>
<u n="600" who="S0276" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> that that's so fucking creepy</u>
<u n="601" who="S0275" trans="overlap">flipping creep isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> who is this? <pause dur="short"/> I don't know this person <pause dur="short"/> I don't know them</u>
<u n="602" who="S0276" trans="overlap">do you have a public one?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0275">no it used to be public but then I thought no why am I allowing people to stare at me if you want to see you got to <trunc>li</trunc> you've got to follow me mate</u>
<u n="604" who="S0276">I got super offended the other day cos someone tagged me in like an Instagram video <unclear>saying</unclear> oh this is how you can buy followers</u>
<u n="605" who="S0275" trans="overlap">why? <pause dur="short"/> buy followers?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0276">yeah it was like don't you wanna be Instagram famous? I was like are you saying I I don't have enough followers I like</u>
<u n="607" who="S0275" trans="overlap">that is oh those people yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="608" who="S0276" trans="overlap">and I was like I don't care</u>
<u n="609" who="S0275">yeah I get that sometimes I'm like I don't give a shit I don't want followers and I don't want likes go away</u>
<u n="610" who="S0276" trans="overlap">no exactly</u>
<u n="611" who="S0275">why does <trunc>e</trunc> why does it even happen?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0276">I know</u>
<u n="613" who="S0275">like is it <trunc>gonn</trunc></u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
