<text id="SFLB">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:04:17</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-02-24</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0167 S0375</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Food, domestic chores, pets, future plans, work, finances, parents, family, relationships, past activities, nostalgic stories, health </topics>
		<activity>Friends reuniting</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0167">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Ashford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South East/Kent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Romney Marsh, Kent</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Copywriter</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0375">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>White British</nat>
				<birthplace>Ashford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>(Southern British English) SSBE</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Speech and Language therapy (Adult acute)</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0167">yay I love biscuits <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="gasp"/> <pause dur="short"/> you've even got Christmas chocolates</u>
<u n="2" who="S0375">I know</u>
<u n="3" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="4" who="S0375">we've still got <trunc>ch</trunc> Christmas chocolates left upstairs</u>
<u n="5" who="S0167">how many Christmas chocolates did you have?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0375">my mum goes because like</u>
<u n="7" who="S0167" trans="overlap">I know my dad does as well</u>
<u n="8" who="S0375" trans="overlap">like all I've got on my wardrobe are these erm <pause dur="long"/> Terry's Chocolate Orange in there there's these these snowmen</u>
<u n="9" who="S0167"><vocal desc="gasp"/> I love the snowmen</u>
<u n="10" who="S0375">oh and my dad nicks them <vocal desc="laugh"/> he came kind of <trunc>f</trunc> oh he's looking for <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0375">I just went around all the places he has cups of tea like his study you know like today</u>
<u n="13" who="S0167" trans="overlap">and there's these snowmen</u>
<u n="14" who="S0375">no just empty packets of malt biscuits and Fox's biscuits I was gonna get you the nice Fox's ones but they've all gone <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0375">it's bad</u>
<u n="17" who="S0167">well I guess they are his biscuits</u>
<u n="18" who="S0375">so carry on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thinks what about everything? what's he kind of said?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0167">no he's just like being really supportive he's like <pause dur="short"/> you know well done every time I get an interview or I dunno</u>
<u n="20" who="S0375">well he's a laugh isn't he <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0167">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's away at the moment on a bit at a beer festival with a load of his erm workers for business <pause dur="short"/> and he's sent me all these pictures of them all in a club dancing with the beers <pause dur="short"/> he's in Hamburg <pause dur="short"/> like what a cool job you just get to go to beer festivals and do your research</u>
<u n="22" who="S0375">that's really informative <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like</u>
<u n="23" who="S0167">well if you have to try all the beers and stuff</u>
<u n="24" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> bet he can't remember half of what they taste like after he's finished</u>
<u n="25" who="S0167" trans="overlap">probably not <pause dur="long"/> he's staying in this really nice hotel as well and he sent me a picture of his breakfast this morning and I was like oh</u>
<u n="26" who="S0375">there's no bread</u>
<u n="27" who="S0167">I wouldn't mind being one of their workers cos <trunc>th</trunc>they get taken away and they get it all for free</u>
<u n="28" who="S0375">his <pause dur="short"/> his mum and dad own the</u>
<u n="29" who="S0167">own the restaurant and hotel yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0375">and they own a hotel as well?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0167">well it's a hotel restaurant it's all one thing</u>
<u n="32" who="S0375">how big is it then?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0167" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> mm it's quite big actually I think there's nineteen rooms or something <pause dur="short"/> and there's a <pause dur="short"/> a pub bar slash restaurant at <pause dur="short"/> one end</u>
<u n="34" who="S0375">is it quite busy?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0167" trans="overlap">it's a bit like <anon type="place"/> kind of style and that kind of size at the bottom but then there's an upstairs with loads of rooms yeah it always seems quite busy <pause dur="short"/> you should come to a dancing we can visit</u>
<u n="36" who="S0375">I want to</u>
<u n="37" who="S0167">we can go <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0375">I nearly said to you actually I'd meet you out there for a couple of days but <pause dur="short"/> you don't see each other for that that <trunc>ma</trunc> for that long do you?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0167">it's alright</u>
<u n="40" who="S0375" trans="overlap">like imagine having a gatecrasher there these are a bit stale aren't they?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0167">yeah but I I can still eat them <pause dur="short"/> don't waste good chocolate <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> come on</u>
<u n="42" who="S0375">good?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0167">come on <pause dur="short"/> these little snowmen <pause dur="short"/> will be sad if we don't eat them</u>
<u n="44" who="S0375">oh there's <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0167">hello <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0375">look at him <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0167">yeah but he is fluffy so maybe that's making him look a bit fatter</u>
<u n="48" who="S0375">oh he's huge come on didn't you come home and think oh my god he's grown twice the size?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0167">yeah I did kind of think oh he's fat <vocal desc="laugh"/> but then <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> gets fat sometimes she's like sometimes I'm like oh and sometimes she gets thin</u>
<u n="50" who="S0375" trans="overlap">in fact she's weird she seems to fluctuate every time I see her</u>
<u n="51" who="S0167" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0375">she's either really big or she's tiny</u>
<u n="53" who="S0167" trans="overlap">she's got flabby skin <pause dur="short"/> she either has a really big or she gets flabby skin where cos she's lost weight <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she obviously decides when she <trunc>wan</trunc> oh sorry when she wants to go on a erm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0167">on a diet</u>
<u n="56" who="S0375" trans="overlap">workout and when she doesn't</u>
<u n="57" who="S0167">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0375"><unclear/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0167"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s starting eating in this really weird way <pause dur="short"/> she gets the food out of the thing with her paw <pause dur="short"/> eases it off her paw <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/> because she's learning from the humans</u>
<u n="61" who="S0167">that's what I thought it does look quite cute when she's eating but the problem is she kind of drops it and it goes all over the floor and then you get all this dry food all over the floor <vocal desc="laugh"/> and it's really gross</u>
<u n="62" who="S0375">are you gonna take her to the vet at all? does that mean she can't eat in her mouth?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0167" trans="overlap">well she she's eating <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I mean she's still eating so I guess that's the most important thing</u>
<u n="64" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0167">maybe she got bored with getting her nose all dirty <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0375">maybe <vocal desc="laugh"/> dunno see I always think what do animals think?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0167">but I never clean the the floor and her cat bowl and today it was just so disgusting I thought right I've got to and it was all dried on where it's been there for like days</u>
<u n="68" who="S0375">don't</u>
<u n="69" who="S0167">all up the wall it was splashed <vocal desc="laugh"/> and so I just got like the cleaner and just sprayed loads and loads and just left it for like half an hour and then it just wiped off really easily</u>
<u n="70" who="S0375">oh yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0167">disgusting</u>
<u n="72" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I do love the cats but I think my mum does loads of that <vocal desc="laugh"/> my mum does the majority of the cleaning and stuff like that</u>
<u n="73" who="S0167">yeah I mean fortunately cats are quite easy to clean I mean it's just their food bowl that you really need to worry about isn't it?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0375">could you imagine a dog?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0167">oh my god <pause dur="long"/> I couldn't bear a dog</u>
<u n="76" who="S0375">what? what's wrong? what was that little squeal for? <pause dur="long"/> come on then</u>
<u n="77" who="S0167">come on</u>
<u n="78" who="S0375">say hello to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0167">hello <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> hello <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0375"><unclear/> cute</u>
<u n="81" who="S0167">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and he's all fluffy</u>
<u n="82" who="S0375">did I tell you about when we got him? <pause dur="short"/> his mum died like two days after we got him</u>
<u n="83" who="S0167">no</u>
<u n="84" who="S0375">she got hit by a car</u>
<u n="85" who="S0167">oh no</u>
<u n="86" who="S0375" trans="overlap">cos that was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum's work no her boss that was selling kittens</u>
<u n="87" who="S0167">right</u>
<u n="88" who="S0375">and her he the mum was really fluffy and really pretty as well erm and then yeah she got hit by a car and they were gonna keep him if we hadn't taken him so they were he would have been the one to keep</u>
<u n="89" who="S0167">oh</u>
<u n="90" who="S0375">cos he was the only ginger one in there</u>
<u n="91" who="S0167">you didn't tell us that we had <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> at the time</u>
<u n="92" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0167">we didn't tell us</u>
<u n="94" who="S0375" trans="overlap">oh I think we did I think we did</u>
<u n="95" who="S0167">maybe you did</u>
<u n="96" who="S0375">oh well <pause dur="short"/> come on <pause dur="short"/> looking at me have you spoken to the girls then recently since you've been back?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0167">which girls?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0375">this your home girls <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> how's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doing? I see pictures of her on Facebook and she</u>
<u n="99" who="S0167" trans="overlap">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s okay she's <pause dur="short"/> at uni and enjoying like uni life <pause dur="short"/> she's got loads of new friends and stuff and she's joined like the outside adventure society or something she does like rock climbing and stuff</u>
<u n="100" who="S0375">I wanna do stuff like that</u>
<u n="101" who="S0167" trans="overlap">mm I said to her can I come and visit you for a week and like do some of your activities in your club? and she was like yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0375">oh <trunc>g</trunc> let me know cos I wouldn't mind going down there and doing that</u>
<u n="103" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0375">cos rock climbing and stuff like you can do it in <anon type="place"/> but it's pretty expensive isn't it?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah cos it's all indoor isn't it?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0375">it's not cheap yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0167">and it would be much more fun to do it like where there's actual like rocks rather than <pause dur="short"/> like an indoor <pause dur="short"/> thing</u>
<u n="108" who="S0375">mm yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0167">erm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0375" trans="overlap">remember remember doing it at Guides and things do you remember doing it?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0167">yeah vaguely and I <trunc>di</trunc> I went to Snowdonia with the school for a week to do it as well</u>
<u n="112" who="S0375">yeah I didn't go to that</u>
<u n="113" who="S0167">that was really fun actually</u>
<u n="114" who="S0375">yeah I know I'd definitely like to do that</u>
<u n="115" who="S0167">yeah well we can <pause dur="short"/> look her up and stuff</u>
<u n="116" who="S0375">it's like I said</u>
<u n="117" who="S0167" trans="overlap">we still need to do skydiving</u>
<u n="118" who="S0375">yeah we never did that did we? did you sort it out?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0167">no <pause dur="short"/> I was in Peru I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can you do something? and she was like no I'll just do it when you get back I'm sure it'll be alright <pause dur="short"/> it's like okay I can't do anything from here</u>
<u n="120" who="S0375" trans="overlap">probably will</u>
<u n="121" who="S0167">erm <pause dur="short"/> but yeah if we ring up maybe we could do it like soon</u>
<u n="122" who="S0375">what?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0167">the skydiving if we ring up</u>
<u n="124" who="S0375">oh yes yeah cos you might not be here you seem to have <trunc>s</trunc> the west</u>
<u n="125" who="S0167" trans="overlap">no I'm I'm not applying for anymore abroad</u>
<u n="126" who="S0375" trans="overlap">west Yorkshire Peru</u>
<u n="127" who="S0167">oh yeah Yorkshire <vocal desc="laugh"/> I forgot about that</u>
<u n="128" who="S0375">bloody hell <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you crack me up you do</u>
<u n="129" who="S0167">I kind of regret applying to that now</u>
<u n="130" who="S0375">you don't lose anything going on the interview though do you?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0167">no <pause dur="short"/> the taxpayer does though <pause dur="long"/> you do actually you've paid for me to <trunc>g</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0375">yes right <pause dur="short"/> I erm I I I don't resent you an interview <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> though</u>
<u n="133" who="S0167">thank you</u>
<u n="134" who="S0375">that's okay</u>
<u n="135" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0375">I erm I've got the I've got to do it soon <pause dur="short"/> I'm not really I I've looked at NHS jobs and there haven't been any sort of that have come up yet or anything <pause dur="short"/> cos usually I'm I'm set to get <unclear/> notifications and they send through all cos you have a set like band five <anon type="place"/> and they</u>
<u n="137" who="S0167" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="138" who="S0375" trans="overlap">send through all the jobs <pause dur="short"/> and er</u>
<u n="139" who="S0167" trans="overlap">and they haven't got anything?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0375">no what the last sort of few months I've been getting loads and I remember thinking oh you know I can't apply yet they're like looking for someone immediately I still have two months left to go <pause dur="short"/> now I've got a month left and they're really</u>
<u n="141" who="S0167" trans="overlap">and there's nothing coming through</u>
<u n="142" who="S0375" trans="overlap">and there's nothing coming up and I'm like oh god</u>
<u n="143" who="S0167" trans="overlap">there will be there will be</u>
<u n="144" who="S0375">you know I hope so cos I always think it's coming into now</u>
<u n="145" who="S0167">have you thought about like other things that aren't NHS <pause dur="short"/> things? I don't know</u>
<u n="146" who="S0375">well yeah but I said to mum well you know I I like working for the NHS I get my I get my pension paid into</u>
<u n="147" who="S0167" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0375">they're just they're just the things that I</u>
<u n="149" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I get you know I I enjoy it I enjoy working in hospitals and <pause dur="short"/> I didn't want to look elsewhere because private is good but a again if you if you're off sick</u>
<u n="151" who="S0167">you don't get paid?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0375">you don't get paid it's self employed</u>
<u n="153" who="S0167">I used to get paid at Staples for being sick actually that was quite good for a part time job</u>
<u n="154" who="S0375">but that yeah that's a contract yeah everyone does</u>
<u n="155" who="S0167" trans="overlap">mm my mum doesn't</u>
<u n="156" who="S0375">does she not?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0167">no <pause dur="short"/> if she's off sick she doesn't get paid <vocal desc="laugh"/> my dad does obviously cos he's salaried so it doesn't matter when he's off sick but</u>
<u n="158" who="S0375">I didn't realise your mum wasn't salaried actually</u>
<u n="159" who="S0167">no she's hourly paid <pause dur="short"/> but I don't there I mean she doesn't work for the NHS she works for a</u>
<u n="160" who="S0375">she's private yeah I'm sure</u>
<u n="161" who="S0167">yeah private company so</u>
<u n="162" who="S0375">I mean er mum said that she's like you know if you get to the point where you need to then you need to <pause dur="short"/> and she was like you're in the sort of time of your life where you don't have to be there forever you just do it for you know a little <trunc>long</trunc> you know you like you've done now and then move on</u>
<u n="163" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0375">and I said that's all well and good but you get settled <pause dur="short"/> it's like I really like the staff there at the moment and I really like</u>
<u n="165" who="S0167" trans="overlap">at least <anon type="place"/> there's a lot of opportunities in <anon type="place"/> it's not like you live out in the sticks</u>
<u n="166" who="S0375" trans="overlap">yeah I know I know I I should be more <pause dur="short"/> and like I'm gonna have to be like there's no way I want to get to the end of March cos they're both</u>
<u n="167" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0375"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to me in my</u>
<u n="169" who="S0167" trans="overlap">you'll be in my position then <vocal desc="laugh"/> you'll have to apply for Jobseeker's</u>
<u n="170" who="S0375">I know like well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to me in my one to one with her on Friday cos we had a meeting at this job</u>
<u n="171" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0375">and then</u>
<u n="173" who="S0167" trans="overlap">I love these coasters</u>
<u n="174" who="S0375" trans="overlap">realised er?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0167">I love these coasters</u>
<u n="176" who="S0375">I know I do as well</u>
<u n="177" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah carry on</u>
<u n="178" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I like this bit here <pause dur="long"/> borrow your <unclear/> aren't I?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0167">mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0375">erm yeah she said to me in this one to one oh we we're we've put an extension for you for April</u>
<u n="181" who="S0167">well I think you <trunc>yo</trunc> it sounds like you might just stay on</u>
<u n="182" who="S0375">I'm just</u>
<u n="183" who="S0167" trans="overlap">to be honest</u>
<u n="184" who="S0375" trans="overlap">like cos it's the funding cos obviously with the NHS in general</u>
<u n="185" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0375" trans="overlap">like the funding is so poor at the moment I'm worried that they won't won't cos it has they have to apply for the funding to keep me</u>
<u n="187" who="S0167">oh okay <pause dur="long"/> well <pause dur="short"/> you never know at least they want to keep you that's the first step</u>
<u n="188" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0167">that's a good sign</u>
<u n="190" who="S0375">so that their their</u>
<u n="191" who="S0167" trans="overlap">and</u>
<u n="192" who="S0375">their funding allows me to stay I suppose</u>
<u n="193" who="S0167">if they don't then just see it as an opportunity to try something new</u>
<u n="194" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0167">while you're young and carefree</u>
<u n="196" who="S0375">I mean I don't even know if it's it's like I I love I don't keep up <pause dur="short"/> and sometimes you're forgetting things oh and then am I making a massive difference am I making?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0167">well everyone does everyone makes a difference every step of the journey makes a difference</u>
<u n="198" who="S0375">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I just you know they bounce back in sometimes you know we put them on this <event desc="sound of rustling"/> so they don't want anything else you know</u>
<u n="199" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0375" trans="overlap">they're old <pause dur="short"/> and erm they bounce back in and that's a few times and you think oh <pause dur="short"/> they're back in again</u>
<u n="201" who="S0167">that's the nature of this job though you're gonna have to learn to deal with that</u>
<u n="202" who="S0375" trans="overlap">yeah exactly and like I said that I said to my mum yesterday I was like that is just totally something I'm gonna have to get used to</u>
<u n="203" who="S0167">mm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0375">and <pause dur="short"/> you know switch off from <pause dur="short"/> which is why I wanted to tarts erm start all this <pause dur="short"/> yoga and</u>
<u n="205" who="S0167">mm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0375">tai chi sorry I've forgotten the words there</u>
<u n="207" who="S0167">well</u>
<u n="208" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I think I was gonna say toga <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0167">oh no you're going back this er evening I was gonna say you can come to tai chi with me this evening</u>
<u n="210" who="S0375">no I <trunc>w</trunc> yeah I'm going back this evening</u>
<u n="211" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah that's a shame</u>
<u n="212" who="S0375">oh well I'm off till tomorrow but I have so much to do in <anon type="place"/> now</u>
<u n="213" who="S0167">mm</u>
<u n="214" who="S0375">and I need to go to the bank as well</u>
<u n="215" who="S0167">yeah fair enough <pause dur="long"/> yeah it's only four pounds</u>
<u n="216" who="S0375">do my washing <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0167">it's four pounds in erm <pause dur="short"/> it's at the Tesco community centre above the shop</u>
<u n="218" who="S0375">Tesco community centre?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0167">you know where the café used to be <pause dur="short"/> at the top?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0375">they've got a community centre there in Tesco's?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0167">it's like a room that you can book out for <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whatever you wanna do <vocal desc="laugh"/> and there</u>
<u n="222" who="S0375">no</u>
<u n="223" who="S0167" trans="overlap">there's a new café the other side where the tills are <pause dur="short"/> so you <trunc>kno</trunc> the opposite side to where the old café used to be</u>
<u n="224" who="S0375">what and Tesco equips it?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0167">mm they've got a new café downstairs and right at the front and then upstairs is a community room so they do like yoga sessions you can do knitting sessions you can book it out for like toddler and baby sessions <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0375">I never knew that</u>
<u n="227" who="S0167">yeah I know it's crazy my dad <pause dur="short"/> took me up there to show me and I was like oh they do tai chi here so I started going to tai chi</u>
<u n="228" who="S0375">do you like it? is it very</u>
<u n="229" who="S0167" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0375">calming?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0167">I'm the youngest one there by about thirty years but <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0167">it's quite good <pause dur="short"/> and it gets me out the house cos at the moment I just need any excuse to get out of the house and I'm just</u>
<u n="234" who="S0375" trans="overlap">how are you finding the house? like are you like living with your mum and dad or is it kind of?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0167">no I don't mind living with my mum and dad it's just like because they're all they're <trunc>awa</trunc>away a lot of the time in the daytime cos they work or or sleep <pause dur="short"/> a lot of the time I'm just on my own and it gets a bit kind of I've I drive myself a bit crazy just looking applying for jobs and then applying for another job and then applying for another job <pause dur="short"/> and it's just like I go a bit like ah I need to get out of the house so on Friday I went to <anon type="place"/> with erm cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was down visiting her friends who go to <anon type="place"/> university and so she was going out with them and she invited me along cos obviously I don't live far <pause dur="short"/> and so I went to erm out with her and her friends in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0375">oh</u>
<u n="237" who="S0167">on Friday which was nice so that was nice cos it's the first time I've been out in ages</u>
<u n="238" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0167">I'm going <trunc>t</trunc> out for dinner with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> next week on Sunday</u>
<u n="240" who="S0375">how are they both doing?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0167" trans="overlap">at the <anon type="place"/> carvery I dunno cos I haven't <trunc>sp</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> spoken to them so that's when we're gonna catch up next week</u>
<u n="242" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0167">or this week now <pause dur="short"/> and erm yeah cos I'm trying to get everything in like the weekend I get paid because <vocal desc="laugh"/> gonna get paid this week</u>
<u n="244" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0167">it's like I may as well just get it in now and then I don't think oh I haven't got any money <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0375">yeah I know I know exactly what you mean I always put my rent and stuff in I always put all my bills</u>
<u n="247" who="S0167">I know and then it's</u>
<u n="248" who="S0375" trans="overlap">just all in and it's</u>
<u n="249" who="S0167" trans="overlap">all disappears doesn't it?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0375" trans="overlap">all just er goes and I <trunc>thi</trunc> I've still got my phone bill to come out and</u>
<u n="251" who="S0167">I like that though just getting it all out of the way</u>
<u n="252" who="S0375">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I might do that now actually <pause dur="short"/> keep a handle</u>
<u n="253" who="S0167">oh you just sprayed coffee all over me</u>
<u n="254" who="S0375" trans="overlap">sorry sorry I'm gonna do it now before I forget erm</u>
<u n="255" who="S0167">good idea <pause dur="short"/> don't you love the internet it's so easy <vocal desc="laugh"/> imagine the days when you would have had to have gone down to the post office and put the</u>
<u n="256" who="S0375">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm erm I was thinking the other day like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who live with?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0167">mm</u>
<u n="258" who="S0375">she's never had internet banking</u>
<u n="259" who="S0167">never had internet banking? how do you live without internet banking?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I I thank you and I was like do you not have the app like do you not any of of these things on your phone? and she was like no she's been ringing up the their phone line and still paying her banking and stuff</u>
<u n="261" who="S0167">oh</u>
<u n="262" who="S0375">and the other day er I mean I don't have as much money in my account but she erm she rang up and did it and she paid it didn't work so she kept doing it again she paid rent three times so we had like this</u>
<u n="263" who="S0167"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0375">loads of money in this account I mean like she's obviously got a lot of savings that she's <trunc>allow</trunc> she could do that</u>
<u n="265" who="S0167">oh okay so did she <trunc>ge</trunc> did you give it back to her?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0375">oh yeah we transferred it all back to her we were like you're an idiot why are you not internet banking? and then was it last month? yeah last month we paid rent and we went to the overdraft and sorry the erm account <pause dur="short"/> and it had gone to the overdraft by two hundred and something pounds because she hadn't paid rent</u>
<u n="267" who="S0167">oh</u>
<u n="268" who="S0375" trans="overlap">so the month before she paid it three times and then she hadn't paid it at all</u>
<u n="269" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0375">it was like well it's</u>
<u n="271" who="S0167" trans="overlap">maybe you should have just kept it in there</u>
<u n="272" who="S0375" trans="overlap">sorry</u>
<u n="273" who="S0167" trans="overlap">and then she wouldn't have had to have paid for three months</u>
<u n="274" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0167">why didn't you just do it that way or did she not have enough money to do it that way?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0375">well no I think she wanted kind of money in her</u>
<u n="277" who="S0167">her account</u>
<u n="278" who="S0375">her account yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0375">she owes me money actually</u>
<u n="281" who="S0167"><vocal desc="gasp"/> bitch <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0375">yeah she owes me forty quid I just forgot about that <pause dur="long"/> oh it's mother's day soon <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0167">I know <pause dur="short"/> gonna have to get my mum a <trunc>car</trunc> well actually it's on the seventeenth of March or something it's not that soon</u>
<u n="284" who="S0375">right pay bill <pause dur="short"/> I'm glad you made me do this <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> off oh right seven how much am I paying? I'm gonna pay seven thirty pounds</u>
<u n="285" who="S0167">is it seven thirty a month you pay?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0375">no I pay six ninety but I owe twenty-five pounds into it for erm <pause dur="short"/> the Tesco shop we did</u>
<u n="287" who="S0167">oh right</u>
<u n="288" who="S0375">and I think I owe a few more pounds here and there</u>
<u n="289" who="S0167">do you all share food then and eat together?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0375">no we did a Tesco shop between us but we do buy house food but</u>
<u n="291" who="S0167">oh right</u>
<u n="292" who="S0375">and we do sometimes</u>
<u n="293" who="S0167" trans="overlap">what like bread and milk and stuff and that sort of</u>
<u n="294" who="S0375" trans="overlap">yeah the sort of basics and then</u>
<u n="295" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0375">the rest of the time we usually just eat you know eat our own</u>
<u n="297" who="S0167">although you can't eat bread and milk so</u>
<u n="298" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0167" trans="overlap">so you've paid for that</u>
<u n="300" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I've no I have <trunc>t</trunc> I sometimes pay for my own and sometimes don't</u>
<u n="301" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0375">it clearly I don't eat bread but it's also normal bread is like one pound or ninety-nine P and mine's is three pounds seventy or whatever it is so that's three pounds</u>
<u n="303" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh right so you just buy it separately</u>
<u n="304" who="S0375">so I think sometimes I really should buy it <pause dur="long"/> right</u>
<u n="305" who="S0167">why don't you get a bread maker and then you could make gluten free bread? you can make gluten bread</u>
<u n="306" who="S0375" trans="overlap">you really like these bread makers at the moment don't you?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0167">love it</u>
<u n="308" who="S0375">right I have something else to <trunc>p</trunc> I'm going to erm do you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s getting married by the way?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0167">no</u>
<u n="310" who="S0375">she got engaged in August last year</u>
<u n="311" who="S0167" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0375" trans="overlap">and she's our we're we're going to the hen do in Budapest which you've been to haven't you?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0167">no I've never been to Hungary</u>
<u n="314" who="S0375">yeah apparently it's lovely</u>
<u n="315" who="S0167">I'd love to go to Hungary yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> lived there for six months recently doing a job</u>
<u n="316" who="S0375">who did?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0167">and <trunc>sh</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0375">did she?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0167">yeah she was doing some job out there and</u>
<u n="320" who="S0375" trans="overlap">what does she do? I don't know what she does</u>
<u n="321" who="S0167" trans="overlap">she works in theatre like a production manager or something so she works on shows and there was a show going on in Budapest that she was working on <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="322" who="S0375">I thought <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did erm <trunc>thea</trunc> like music as well</u>
<u n="323" who="S0167">no just theatre <pause dur="short"/> I mean he's worked on musicals but <pause dur="short"/> he yeah he lost his job at the National Theatre</u>
<u n="324" who="S0375">why?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0167" trans="overlap">and erm oh he got made redundant <pause dur="short"/> I guess it's just the market isn't it? and erm <trunc>th</trunc> he's got a new job at the Royal Shakespeare Company now</u>
<u n="326" who="S0375">oh wow <pause dur="short"/> but what why? was there just not enough?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0167">erm yeah I guess it's just funding and stuff they don't have as much as they did have did they? so they just had to let people go and <pause dur="short"/> reorganise</u>
<u n="328" who="S0375">oh it's hell at the moment isn't it? it's genuinely hell</u>
<u n="329" who="S0167">but yeah fortunately he's got a new job pretty quickly <pause dur="short"/> sorry the microphone <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0375">sorry</u>
<u n="331" who="S0167">that's the microphone <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0375">oh <unclear/> I forgot actually <pause dur="short"/> is he liking it still?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0167">who <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0375">mm</u>
<u n="335" who="S0167">well he's quite new there so I guess he is at the moment whether it'll stay that way I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I was gonna apply for a job there actually</u>
<u n="336" who="S0375">why didn't you?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0167">no I am going to it's a cos I I just put tabs up on my computer of jobs I see and then gradually I apply for them but I haven't applied for that one yet it's a digital marketing assistant <pause dur="short"/> at the</u>
<u n="338" who="S0375" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="339" who="S0167" trans="overlap">Royal Shakespeare Company that could sounds quite fun</u>
<u n="340" who="S0375">that would be really fun but what do you do at digital marketing what would you do?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0167" trans="overlap">it's just like it means marketing but you do it online so I guess it's just like the modern marketing</u>
<u n="342" who="S0375">is marketing something you wanna do then? is marketing cos I thought you wanted to do more sort of publishing and writing</u>
<u n="343" who="S0167">I do but then it all kind of <unclear>melger</unclear> merges into one kind of thing so I'm kind of qualified to do all those kind of things I've had the experience and the <pause dur="short"/> whatever to do all those kind of things <pause dur="short"/> like publishing writing marketing</u>
<u n="344" who="S0375" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="345" who="S0167">they're all kind of under the same umbrella <pause dur="short"/> so I've just been applying for all those type of jobs</u>
<u n="346" who="S0375">that's brill <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0167">I mean marketing is mostly writing anyway cos you have to write emails and you you have to write press releases and you have to write erm I don't know posters or leaflets or whatever <pause dur="short"/> so it's basically publishing but</u>
<u n="348" who="S0375">what about a erm you have to write people's speeches? is it ghost writing?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I guess I could apply to be a ghost writer but then you don't get the credit</u>
<u n="350" who="S0375">I know oh I think that's the worst job ever I don't know who would do it</u>
<u n="351" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> although I didn't get credit when I worked in Peru actually <pause dur="short"/> we didn't get erm bylines on our articles</u>
<u n="352" who="S0375">oh</u>
<u n="353" who="S0167">they just went onto the website with no name <pause dur="short"/> there you go <pause dur="short"/> that doesn't go in my portfolio</u>
<u n="354" who="S0375">no this is the nature of the job so anything you do <pause dur="short"/> if it doesn't have your name to it you can't put it in your portfolio?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0167">no I could say this is the website I wrote for this is my article but there's no proof it's my article they would just have to take my word for it so it's not really the same as having it in my portfolio but I've got quite a big portfolio anyway</u>
<u n="356" who="S0375">cos imagine if you had a really erm I dunno English spy type name like John Smith</u>
<u n="357" who="S0167">yeah oh and it could be anyone</u>
<u n="358" who="S0375">yeah how do they know it's definitely you?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0167">I dunno I guess they just kind of</u>
<u n="360" who="S0375">you'd have to you'd have to ask wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0167" trans="overlap">that kind of thing that is kind of just trust isn't it?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0375">cos there must a zillion John Smiths in the country imagine searching for articles by John Smith you'd be you'd be everywhere</u>
<u n="363" who="S0167" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> well like I've got all my cuttings from uni that I did like when I wrote for the paper I've got my like and I've got the book I did in in Berlin and they've got my picture in I think so that proves it's me and then my online ones have usually got my picture with them like my blogs and my Edinburgh portfolio</u>
<u n="364" who="S0375">you know you read books like Fifty Shades</u>
<u n="365" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0375" trans="overlap">it's a really good example but she got into publishing there and then got in straight into a job it's obviously not like that <pause dur="short"/> it sounds like it's pretty competitive</u>
<u n="367" who="S0167">yeah it is really competitive cos everyone wants to do it and then you've got to do like work experience to prove that you want to do it and to have work experience you need money to do the work experience in the first place and it's like you have to do all this free work before you actually get paid</u>
<u n="368" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like I've done</u>
<u n="370" who="S0375" trans="overlap">it sucks</u>
<u n="371" who="S0167" trans="overlap">I've done so much free work <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0375">yeah do you feel angry? do you feel like angry and?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah I just wanna be paid now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0167">but such is life I mean <pause dur="short"/> the more I do the better chances I've got I suppose and <pause dur="short"/> it's all <pause dur="short"/> it all adds up</u>
<u n="376" who="S0375">it does</u>
<u n="377" who="S0167">and it's all stuff I've enjoyed I guess like</u>
<u n="378" who="S0375" trans="overlap">and at least you've carried on like in a way that you haven't wanted a job that's like full time a full time wage and you've got the money there and then you don't have it anymore and you have some more experience</u>
<u n="379" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0375">at least you're on a continual kind of you you know what internships is like and you know it's gonna be for something in the long run</u>
<u n="381" who="S0167">yeah like that's the thing</u>
<u n="382" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I always think that about people that do their masters cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s just finished her masters and she pretty much <pause dur="short"/> she works alongside it in this erm well she works on <anon type="place"/> she's got a really good erm good job there but she</u>
<u n="383" who="S0167" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="384" who="S0375">to pay for a masters on the side <pause dur="short"/> er but she got paid a pittance like as a nurse clinical psychologies assistant she got twelve thousand I think</u>
<u n="385" who="S0167">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0375">and it was just pittance money and although it was ridiculous but with the training she said you know I've I've <trunc>d</trunc> all I've done is work so far <pause dur="short"/> for a good goal at the end I know I'm gonna get a good job at the end</u>
<u n="387" who="S0167">mm</u>
<u n="388" who="S0375">but she was like I've just got no money ever well she has because she's still got quite a lot of inheritance from her</u>
<u n="389" who="S0167">whereas me I've never got money <pause dur="short"/> frigging</u>
<u n="390" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0167">I've just got offered a <trunc>wor</trunc> a work experience placement <pause dur="short"/> and I couldn't take it</u>
<u n="392" who="S0375">where? what what was this from then another one?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0167">yeah this is the</u>
<u n="394" who="S0375" trans="overlap">where was this one?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> this is a publishing company in erm <pause dur="short"/> a publishing company in <anon type="place"/> which is a tiny village in the middle of nowhere <pause dur="short"/> so it's not really very easy to get to and I'd have to stay it's quite far away so I'd have to</u>
<u n="396" who="S0375" trans="overlap">where's <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0167"><anon type="place"/> it's like kind of towards <anon type="place"/> kind of way like so it's south</u>
<u n="398" who="S0375" trans="overlap">what at <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0167">no it's south but it's west er westerly it's more westerly it's quite far like it's not somewhere I could commute to every day and I'd have to go into London and then out to get to it</u>
<u n="400" who="S0375">what <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0167">yeah it's like that kind of way it's not in <anon type="place"/> it used to be in <anon type="place"/> but they moved</u>
<u n="402" who="S0375">oh okay</u>
<u n="403" who="S0167" trans="overlap">so like <anon type="place"/> which is like a tiny place in the middle of nowhere and erm they offered me a work experience placement they said you know come whenever you</u>
<u n="404" who="S0375" trans="overlap">for how long?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0167">they said when however long you want to do it for so I probably would do it for two weeks but erm I would have to stay somewhere because and I'd have to get there and I didn't I just didn't have the money and I had to be like sorry can't come <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0375">oh but you've been to Peru</u>
<u n="407" who="S0167">I know it just would have been really cos it was like a children's book publisher as well so that would have been really cool</u>
<u n="408" who="S0375">oh</u>
<u n="409" who="S0167">and she was like you can work in all the different departments and see what you like best and then</u>
<u n="410" who="S0375">oh that would be good</u>
<u n="411" who="S0167">maybe if I get enough from my these two jobs and my Jobseeker's I might see if I can make it work</u>
<u n="412" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0167">if I can find a cheap a really cheap bed and breakfast and just pay for a train ticket there and a train ticket back hopefully I might be able to make it work but we'll see I have to wait till my money's in first <pause dur="short"/> if they still want me now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0375">and what are your mum and dad saying about it all? are they like</u>
<u n="415" who="S0167">they don't know</u>
<u n="416" who="S0375">okay are they are they like really supportive of all or are they?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0375">they are aren't they? but they're like the <trunc>in</trunc> you can imagine their heads are like</u>
<u n="419" who="S0167">yeah they want me to get a job cos they keep paying for everything for me <pause dur="short"/> although mum said last night cos I cooked them a a <trunc>bee</trunc> a beef roast dinner well not a whole like a <unclear/> roast dinner but like roast beef and potatoes and</u>
<u n="420" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0167">vegetables she was like oh I don't want you to get a job cos I want to come home to lovely dinners</u>
<u n="422" who="S0375">ah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="424" who="S0375">that's cute makes you little little comments like that make you feel</u>
<u n="425" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0375" trans="overlap">a bit better don't they? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0167">I won't come home and the dishwater will be done and the washing will all be done I'm oh yes I'm miss labour am I? well yes you are</u>
<u n="428" who="S0375">see you can't win though cos I've been how long have I? I've obviously been in <anon type="place"/> six years but I've been out of my mum and dad's pocket say for about a year now I've finished uni I'm starting to pay things back and <pause dur="short"/> yeah but mum made that comment yesterday like we have a bit more money now and I'm like</u>
<u n="429" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0375">is that cos I've gone? and she said yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0375">and I <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was in that sort of like sheepishly like yeah it is a bit</u>
<u n="433" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0375">I said I'm sorry for <unclear/></u>
<u n="435" who="S0167" trans="overlap">now she's just got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s blooming</u>
<u n="436" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0167">here there and everywhere to pay for</u>
<u n="438" who="S0375">well and then I what else did I erm? <pause dur="long"/> I forgot what I was gonna say now I forgotten the point of my <pause dur="short"/> my story</u>
<u n="439" who="S0167">money parents</u>
<u n="440" who="S0375">parents</u>
<u n="441" who="S0167" trans="overlap">living away</u>
<u n="442" who="S0375">yeah sorry so that yeah that's what I was gonna say so yeah she says <trunc>th</trunc>things like that but then equally they're like oh you know you're <unclear/> now we don't see you anymore</u>
<u n="443" who="S0167">ah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0375" trans="overlap">are you gonna come home? and you can come home <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0167">well at least you live in <anon type="place"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> lives in <anon type="place"/> and never comes home <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0375">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't <trunc>belie</trunc> are they gonna get married soon do you think?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0167">I know I'm waiting I'm waiting for a niece or nephew I'm waiting for a wedding</u>
<u n="448" who="S0375">he's he's making her a salon</u>
<u n="449" who="S0167">I know</u>
<u n="450" who="S0375">who does that? I said to I said to mum and I was like</u>
<u n="451" who="S0167" trans="overlap">she's so jammy</u>
<u n="452" who="S0375">I can't get my head round this I cannot get my head round it <pause dur="short"/> I mean er are they like in the long haul are they? I mean he's</u>
<u n="453" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah I think they are</u>
<u n="454" who="S0375" trans="overlap">building her a salon it's a business he's built her a business</u>
<u n="455" who="S0167">I think they intend to be</u>
<u n="456" who="S0375">they've just gone fifteen thousand pounds over their bloody extension budget and I said so they're <pause dur="short"/> they're like a a full time like long term couple <pause dur="short"/> mum was like well I suppose you never know what's gonna happen do you? and I'm like <pause dur="short"/> no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="458" who="S0375">but you can't you can't leave someone that's built you a salon</u>
<u n="459" who="S0167">er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would <pause dur="short"/> go right <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> my salon's here so you can get out <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0375">she would yeah <pause dur="short"/> but she seems like she really likes him</u>
<u n="461" who="S0167">yeah I think they are intending to stay together <pause dur="short"/> it's funny <pause dur="short"/> at least I get free haircuts well I don't I always pay her a bit</u>
<u n="462" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0167" trans="overlap">but sometimes she doesn't charge me when she knows I haven't got any money</u>
<u n="464" who="S0375" trans="overlap">that's not bad</u>
<u n="465" who="S0167">which is nice</u>
<u n="466" who="S0375"><vocal desc="sneeze"/> I think I forgot <vocal desc="sneeze"/> I think I forgot last time though</u>
<u n="467" who="S0167">to pay her?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0375">yeah I usually put about twenty twenty-five pounds and I said I'd transfer it and I think I just forgot I never</u>
<u n="469" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh never mind</u>
<u n="470" who="S0375">and cos I went back to <anon type="place"/> that night and <pause dur="short"/> never did it <pause dur="short"/> I felt bad actually cos I obviously I rang her about doing it it was well one day this week or the weekend and erm <pause dur="short"/> she was oh you know I'm I'm going to <unclear/> and I said obviously worry <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I've been really cheeky thank you so much and then she went erm oh I could do it tonight I'm going to Pilates but I can put your foils in and erm like then had a run back and I was like oh you sweetheart it was like no don't worry I was like go tone yourself</u>
<u n="471" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0375">not jealous at all that you're toning when you see her</u>
<u n="473" who="S0167">well it's like clinical Pilates it she pays like sixty pounds a month for it</u>
<u n="474" who="S0375" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0167">or something and she pays an extortionate amount of money it's like a clinical one for people with back problems</u>
<u n="476" who="S0375">oh wow</u>
<u n="477" who="S0167" trans="overlap">it's like a special one yeah so she pays like extortionate amounts to go to this Pilates class <pause dur="short"/> she makes loads of money like</u>
<u n="478" who="S0375" trans="overlap">how how often is it? is it once once a week?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0167">I think it's once a week yeah <pause dur="short"/> or twice a week I can't remember</u>
<u n="480" who="S0375">does it help?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0167">she says it does</u>
<u n="482" who="S0375">does she get back trouble now a little bit?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0167">well she doesn't anymore cos she does Pilates but</u>
<u n="484" who="S0375">cos she sort of she's got that curvature hasn't she?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0167">yeah and I think she's just got to keep an eye on it for the rest of her life just to make sure she doesn't overexert herself maybe <pause dur="short"/> I can't be bothered to go to the jobcentre</u>
<u n="486" who="S0375">I know</u>
<u n="487" who="S0167">I'm really dreading this journey tomorrow <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0167">why did I apply for this stupid job? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="490" who="S0375">you don't yeah you don't seem that keen on it</u>
<u n="491" who="S0167">no I am it's</u>
<u n="492" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I just love the fact you send your CV to here there and everywhere and you're like mm no</u>
<u n="493" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yesterday and I said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I've got a job in <anon type="place"/> she went <anon type="place"/>? oh my god I don't know anyone who just applies like anywhere <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she but we know what you're like</u>
<u n="495" who="S0167">I just don't think <pause dur="short"/> and then I get myself in these sticky situations <pause dur="long"/> problem is always feel bad if someone's taken the effort to offer me an interview I feel bad not taking it cos I'm like oh you know they've taken the effort to read my application and</u>
<u n="496" who="S0375" trans="overlap">yeah cos they must get quite a few and it's nice to know that you've got shortlisted like</u>
<u n="497" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0375" trans="overlap">out of probably hundreds of applications and you've got a job interview</u>
<u n="499" who="S0167">yeah it is nice to know I just hope I get offered another one so l don't feel compelled to take that one <pause dur="short"/> I mean I do er it it does sound cool</u>
<u n="500" who="S0375" trans="overlap">what are you gonna do then if they then before the third of March get</u>
<u n="501" who="S0167"><trunc>off</trunc></u>
<u n="502" who="S0375">get hold of you and ask you about it? are you just gonna decline it anyway cos it's a last resort option what about if they get through to you?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0167">first?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0375"><trunc>fir</trunc> before anything <trunc>el</trunc> that's the only thing I'm worried about cos it's</u>
<u n="505" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="506" who="S0375">it's tomorrow</u>
<u n="507" who="S0167">I know</u>
<u n="508" who="S0375" trans="overlap">that's <trunc>an</trunc> a whole other week before the third of March and then what happens if you then get offered this one for some you know some bizarre reason cos it's in <anon type="place"/>? and you know you're probably gonna get it cos it's <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0375">erm</u>
<u n="511" who="S0167">I don't know</u>
<u n="512" who="S0375">that's like that job down here I applied for it didn't think I'd ever get it and I got the job <pause dur="short"/> and I was like oh I'm in <anon type="place"/> that was just</u>
<u n="513" who="S0167" trans="overlap">you're in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah I know that's what I mean you did it as well that's what I mean but</u>
<u n="516" who="S0375">slightly different <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's like <vocal desc="laugh"/> that was only an hour commute</u>
<u n="517" who="S0167">no it's just hard cos it does look like a really cool job I think to be honest when I applied for it I didn't even look where it was <vocal desc="laugh"/> I just thought oh marketing assistant for a erm music festival that sounds cool <pause dur="short"/> and then I just sent in my application cos I had to send in with my application I had to send in two marketing ideas to expand their brand and and the public's awareness or something and I just wrote like a load of crap about</u>
<u n="518" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="519" who="S0167">doing mini tours around erm <pause dur="short"/> the country in in the main towns like <anon type="place"/> or wherever <pause dur="short"/> and erm do having like mini gigs in the middle of the street and having <trunc>balloo</trunc> giving out balloons and erm doing dancing competitions <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="520" who="S0375">you didn't get interviewed for that? you <trunc>di</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so that was like I wrote this and then I said oh and also you could put erm pianos and guitars in the middle of shopping centres with the</u>
<u n="522" who="S0375" trans="overlap">oh yeah that's amazing</u>
<u n="523" who="S0167" trans="overlap">logo on and erm people can just play them and sometimes you could send down a representative to do like music competitions with the public and then <vocal desc="laugh"/> that was like I sent this in <vocal desc="laugh"/> and they erm they got back to me <vocal desc="laugh"/> and at the interview I've got to expand on my marketing ideas</u>
<u n="524" who="S0375">well when's this?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0167">tomorrow</u>
<u n="526" who="S0375">oh this is the one tomorrow?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="528" who="S0375" trans="overlap">you didn't say this is the one tomorrow</u>
<u n="529" who="S0167">yeah this is the one for tomorrow</u>
<u n="530" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="531" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so they must have liked my ideas <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0375">so what are you gonna say? do you wanna expand on it now? do you wanna go through it now? do you er want me to?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0167">yeah they just said expand so I'm just between us <pause dur="short"/> I'm just gonna go and see what they say and then I'm just gonna be like well <pause dur="short"/> you could like get a band and they could play and then you blow up some balloons <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="534" who="S0375">like I said all this in my interview like</u>
<u n="535" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0375">I thought it was about <unclear/></u>
<u n="537" who="S0167" trans="overlap">I'm not sure how I can expand on it to be honest</u>
<u n="538" who="S0375" trans="overlap">yeah it's like I can't really expand anymore really</u>
<u n="539" who="S0167" trans="overlap">I mean I'm not like a logistics manager I don't know where you're gonna get all these things from or the money that's your job <vocal desc="laugh"/> my job is to come up with the ideas <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="540" who="S0375" trans="overlap">yeah is is it is there someone to think of all these ideas and some poor sods got to do the logistics?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah the marketing the marketing is the marketing company has to think of the ideas and then the logistics</u>
<u n="542" who="S0375" trans="overlap">the poor old logistics the</u>
<u n="543" who="S0167" trans="overlap">and finance have to make it happen <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0375" trans="overlap">oh I feel sorry for them really they get major pooed on don't they?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0167">I know <pause dur="short"/> and erm my dad oh yeah I didn't tell you about this as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="546" who="S0375">oh my it's another one?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0167">he hasn't got to me actually but</u>
<u n="548" who="S0375">if anything you have them out of your ears which is really good <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s ex boyfriend?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0375">doesn't she go out with him anymore?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0167">oh no they broke up in like August</u>
<u n="552" who="S0375">why?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0167">she's living back in <anon type="place"/> now</u>
<u n="554" who="S0375">what happened?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0167">basically what happened was apparently it was going downhill for a while and they kept talking and he kept saying well I'll change I'll change and then he never did and</u>
<u n="556" who="S0375">well what was wrong with him?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0167">oh no that's sad he's got is she having a stroke? <pause dur="long"/> he just became really obsessed with football apparently <pause dur="short"/> and it was like overtaking his whole life and her whole life as well basically cos they lived together</u>
<u n="558" who="S0375">yeah it's all over Facebook</u>
<u n="559" who="S0167">mm <pause dur="short"/> and erm she just got fed up with it and he wasn't spending enough time with her and he was always either playing football or talking about football or just everything was revolved around football and they never had any time to spend together and stuff <pause dur="short"/> and erm yeah and then one day <pause dur="short"/> he was at work she packed up all her stuff and went back to her mum's <vocal desc="laugh"/> he got back and said <pause dur="short"/> where's all your stuff? she went oh yeah I don't want to be with you anymore he phoned her up she said oh I'm so sorry I don't wanna be with you anymore</u>
<u n="560" who="S0375" trans="overlap">she's <unclear>minx</unclear> isn't she? I mean she could have faced him why didn't she face him?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0167">well <trunc>d</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> asked <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she said well it's because we've already had like a million conversations and every time he's like oh I'll change</u>
<u n="562" who="S0375" trans="overlap">that's right</u>
<u n="563" who="S0167" trans="overlap">and she said I just needed to get out cos I knew if I spoke to him it would just be the same all over again <pause dur="short"/> so erm yeah he's moved out of that house obviously now and he's living with some friends <pause dur="short"/> and he's got this job in in <anon type="place"/> in central <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="564" who="S0375">football?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0167">no <pause dur="short"/> he works in the marketing department of this new start up company <pause dur="short"/> a tech company <pause dur="short"/> and they're doing like big PR campaigns and everything at the moment</u>
<u n="566" who="S0375">what's it called do you know?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0167">it's called <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/></u>
<u n="568" who="S0375">oh my word I know it</u>
<u n="569" who="S0167">do you?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0375">I went to erm erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> works at <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> which is a technology company er well they're they're like a big one and they set up a er marketing like a marketing er networking event</u>
<u n="571" who="S0167">okay and <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> was there?</u>
<u n="572" who="S0375">and <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> someone from <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> was there I don't remember seeing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> there</u>
<u n="573" who="S0167">no maybe <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wasn't there erm</u>
<u n="574" who="S0375">I mean I I I gatecrashed I was one of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friends <pause dur="short"/> I gatecrashed there got absolutely smashed</u>
<u n="575" who="S0167">oh nice</u>
<u n="576" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I met loads of lovely people</u>
<u n="577" who="S0167">yeah cool</u>
<u n="578" who="S0375" trans="overlap">all these <trunc>busines</trunc> it was really fun <pause dur="short"/> I was really honest I was like yeah <pause dur="short"/> I said I have nothing to do with technology</u>
<u n="579" who="S0167">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> put on Facebook erm</u>
<u n="580" who="S0375" trans="overlap">just <unclear/></u>
<u n="581" who="S0167" trans="overlap">we're looking we're looking for a new marketing <trunc>inter</trunc> a marketing and PR intern for our new start up company erm you'll be involved with loads of projects we're doing like a big PR campaign at the moment you'll be like trained in <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> making promotional videos and all of this kind of thing I was like mm that sounds like kind of what I'm kind of looking for</u>
<u n="582" who="S0375"><unclear/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0167">he said it's paid well <pause dur="short"/> well I emailed him and said hey <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm really interested in this job that I saw you put on Facebook and he was like oh cool okay erm just email me your CV over and I'll erm speak to the boss and so you know I emailed my CV yesterday so I don't know if anything's gonna happen with that but <pause dur="short"/> but that that's another</u>
<u n="584" who="S0375" trans="overlap">does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> mind you're working with her ex?</u>
<u n="585" who="S0167">I don't know I haven't spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="586" who="S0375">oh well <unclear/> can it?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0167">no it's kind of like it's a job and he just happens to work there and you know <pause dur="long"/> it's you know I can't really not take a job because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would might be upset</u>
<u n="588" who="S0375">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I completely agree</u>
<u n="589" who="S0167">and erm I mean the likelihood of me getting it anyway is slim but <pause dur="short"/> yeah so I've sent off my application to <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> so <pause dur="short"/> you know it's</u>
<u n="590" who="S0375">legend you're an absolute legend</u>
<u n="591" who="S0167">who bloody knows mate? it's on <anon type="place"/> as well so it's quite well placed and</u>
<u n="592" who="S0375"><anon type="place"/> is amazing</u>
<u n="593" who="S0167">mm he sent me pictures of the office and he was like yeah we've got like a bar and we just drink beer all day and you've got all these comfy seats it looks like a really cool office like there's there's like seats shaped like circles in like all different colours and I was like wow that looks like a good office <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="594" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="595" who="S0167">he said honestly we have so much fun in this office <vocal desc="laugh"/> so cool <pause dur="short"/> I'll apply then</u>
<u n="596" who="S0375">not <trunc>rea</trunc> and you're not and you're not selling it to me</u>
<u n="597" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="598" who="S0375">wow god I didn't know they'd split up</u>
<u n="599" who="S0167">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="600" who="S0375">that's crazy <pause dur="short"/> what is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> still with her boyfriend?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0167">yes they've been having some problem areas but erm <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure what's</u>
<u n="602" who="S0375" trans="overlap">what cos she's up there and he's</u>
<u n="603" who="S0167">well apparently he they they've just started arguing a lot and not really connecting in an emotional way and erm</u>
<u n="604" who="S0375">in an emotional capacity</u>
<u n="605" who="S0167">in an emotional capacity and yeah and she was <trunc>s</trunc> she was what was happening a few weeks ago just saying about how the things he was doing that really that were really annoying her and upsetting her and stuff and she was going oh I don't know how long it's gonna last but you know I'll give it another go but</u>
<u n="606" who="S0375">isn't it funny that everything <pause dur="short"/> everything you used to love about them when it just grinds on you?</u>
<u n="607" who="S0167">yeah <pause dur="long"/> I'm finding out the other way with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> though like things that used to really grind on my I'm now thinking ah that's cute</u>
<u n="608" who="S0375">that's erm that's how long term relationships start that is</u>
<u n="609" who="S0167">oh oh</u>
<u n="610" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="611" who="S0167">well that's what I want</u>
<u n="612" who="S0375">honestly I read I read a er I'm always reading studies these days and that's why I'm not in a relationship cos I read all about them so much</u>
<u n="613" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so every time someone speaks to you you go I read a study</u>
<u n="614" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="616" who="S0375">I know about this erm they were saying yeah like if you start off kind of it it grows into something rather than it being an initial kind of</u>
<u n="617" who="S0167">yes</u>
<u n="618" who="S0375">passion and it fizzles out</u>
<u n="619" who="S0167">because I didn't fancy him <pause dur="short"/> at first I didn't fancy him till he asked me out on a date</u>
<u n="620" who="S0375"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> either</u>
<u n="621" who="S0167">yeah <pause dur="long"/> and that's probably the best thing isn't it? cos you don't you don't carry on with the expectations the expectations grow as the experience grows</u>
<u n="622" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0167">so they're always in tandem they're not like there's not a big gap</u>
<u n="624" who="S0375">which is potentially where I'm going wrong <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="625" who="S0167">potentially</u>
<u n="626" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="627" who="S0167">you need to find yourself someone you don't fancy and try and find ways and things to like about them</u>
<u n="628" who="S0375">apparently though mum erm cos obviously we did everything yesterday didn't we went to so we went to <anon type="place"/> and went to Primark and went to</u>
<u n="629" who="S0167" trans="overlap">nice</u>
<u n="630" who="S0375" trans="overlap">you know went down</u>
<u n="631" who="S0167" trans="overlap">you just went everywhere</u>
<u n="632" who="S0375" trans="overlap">into <anon type="place"/> well yeah then we went to <anon type="place"/> if they had any bargains and mum texted this to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like she got the girls group from school</u>
<u n="633" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0375">they had everything like <pause dur="short"/> and erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wrote back and then we went obviously went to <unclear/> erm and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wrote back how do you expect <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to find anyone like you know really amazing to marry if you keep dragging her to all these places? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="635" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="636" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and I was like yeah mum</u>
<u n="637" who="S0167" trans="overlap">that's true <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="638" who="S0375">like why aren't we going to <pause dur="short"/> harrods and? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0167">Harrods <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="640" who="S0375">but like where do you meet people really?</u>
<u n="641" who="S0167">you work in a restaurant</u>
<u n="642" who="S0375">well yeah need to do obviously what you do <pause dur="short"/> but it is through work so I might meet someone</u>
<u n="643" who="S0167" trans="overlap">well you might meet someone through work yeah are there no nice speech therapist there or nice doctors? you went out with a doctor didn't you?</u>
<u n="644" who="S0375">yeah yeah no that was <trunc>fi</trunc> it was a good day it was a very good day I think we're gonna meet soon <pause dur="short"/> erm though no there's there's on there's one doctor at work again he's completely not my type and I didn't like him at first he's really geeky and goony obviously I'm a bit of a goon</u>
<u n="645" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="646" who="S0375">but he's quite geeky and goony but he's a doctor and erm he cracks me up and I do get a little bit of a</u>
<u n="647" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0375" trans="overlap">a buzz but he's got a girlfriend</u>
<u n="649" who="S0167">oh</u>
<u n="650" who="S0375" trans="overlap">so he's spoken for though</u>
<u n="651" who="S0167" trans="overlap">right you need to think of a plan</u>
<u n="652" who="S0375">well mum yeah mum said that she was like</u>
<u n="653" who="S0167" trans="overlap">to break them up</u>
<u n="654" who="S0375" trans="overlap">she's like right what can we do? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="655" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="656" who="S0375">and then I I don't know whether to drop it into the conversation cos I think being a being a girl asking a guy you know have you got a girlfriend? <pause dur="short"/> it's very difficult to kind of be blasé about it</u>
<u n="657" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0375">so she was like I I mean had perfect</u>
<u n="659" who="S0167" trans="overlap">why don't you invite him round for dinner and say oh bring your girlfriend you know come and come and you and your girlfriend come round for dinner</u>
<u n="660" who="S0375">oh yeah that's not creepy in any way oh my god</u>
<u n="661" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="662" who="S0375">erm we were walking to the train and we yeah we get along really well really good banter and erm I I was running I was really late for a train cos I had to get I was usually going one way to <anon type="place"/> but I needed to go the other way into town cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was gonna pick me up she works kind of near me</u>
<u n="663" who="S0167">okay</u>
<u n="664" who="S0375">but a few tube stops up anyway and I was like oh my god I said and er we we were talking about Valentine's day and he knew I was going on a date and I was talking about it and then I had the perfect opportunity for like oh how was your <trunc>va</trunc>Valentine's day with your girlfriend? to kind of drop it in</u>
<u n="665" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="666" who="S0375">and I was literally like and I'm going to the wrong train station I'm at the wrong platform you know so I ran</u>
<u n="667" who="S0167" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you might have just thrown away your whole future</u>
<u n="668" who="S0375">thank you very much <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="669" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you might have just destroyed everything and now you're gonna just grow into an old fat lady</u>
<u n="670" who="S0375" trans="overlap">and I said to mum it was like I've just realised I've just ballsed up you know the perfect opportunity to really drop in there and mum was saying like well just you know get the walking along with him and be like oh erm <pause dur="short"/> I meant to ask you like how did you have a nice Valentine's day? I haven't spoken to you since erm</u>
<u n="671" who="S0167">mm</u>
<u n="672" who="S0375">what did you get up to?</u>
<u n="673" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0375">did you treat the girlfriend?</u>
<u n="675" who="S0167">and then he's like yeah you know I think we're gonna break up soon and then you're in there</u>
<u n="676" who="S0375">you'll be like yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="677" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> why don't you just why don't you just subtly put your MP3 player on so he can hear it and it could be like <shift new="singing"/> hey hey you you I don't like your girlfriend <shift new="normal"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/>?</u>
<u n="678" who="S0375" trans="overlap"><shift new="singing"/> I don't like your girl <shift new="normal"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> do you remember we used to play that song all the time?</u>
<u n="679" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="680" who="S0375">I used did that with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="681" who="S0167">oh yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I forgot you fancied <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="682" who="S0375">I was thinking about why?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0167" trans="overlap">why did you fancy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0375" trans="overlap">why did I why? why?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0167">I swear he had loads of girls fancy him at one point</u>
<u n="686" who="S0375">I think he did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> fancied him I fancied him</u>
<u n="687" who="S0167">and it's it's when he took his glasses off I think cos he was a bit like</u>
<u n="688" who="S0375">no I liked him with his glasses I did like</u>
<u n="689" who="S0167" trans="overlap">did you?</u>
<u n="690" who="S0375">I I was the most I was the most erm consistent</u>
<u n="691" who="S0167">cos I remember he was fifteen I met him in Germany he was spotty and had glasses and was really quiet and didn't speak to anyone <pause dur="short"/> and he was he always stayed quiet he never was a loud one was he? but <pause dur="short"/> he's lost his spots and he lost his glasses he did look for it I must say</u>
<u n="692" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's like <unclear/></u>
<u n="693" who="S0167">but I never fancied him <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="694" who="S0375">I nearly went out with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well</u>
<u n="695" who="S0167">oh yeah I forgot about that I mean I remember you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> going out with him and the I forgot about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="696" who="S0375">cos you don't remember when we got really it was like and were like sixteen and we got really drunk at the village hall cos you couldn't come oh you didn't want to come why why?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0167" trans="overlap">no I I did go <pause dur="short"/> I did go wasn't it wasn't it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday?</u>
<u n="698" who="S0375" trans="overlap">no it was my mum's friend we went to the thing up in the village hall and got really drunk do you remember? and we were like sixteen and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came and whacked we were so drunk I passed out and mum and dad had to</u>
<u n="699" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh yeah I wasn't that drunk was I?</u>
<u n="700" who="S0375">no I don't think you were</u>
<u n="701" who="S0167" trans="overlap">did I did I not come? maybe I was busy that day or something <pause dur="short"/> I must have <trunc>d</trunc> been doing something</u>
<u n="702" who="S0375">no I think you were I think you were busy <pause dur="short"/> yes it was supposed to be the three of well my mum perhaps wondering if you were in France or something cos it was in the summer</u>
<u n="703" who="S0167">possibly yeah</u>
<u n="704" who="S0375">erm <pause dur="short"/> er yeah we came home and I <trunc>remem</trunc> never forget she like she <trunc>ac</trunc> fell into my <unclear/> and she was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> my fucking boyfriend had just dumped me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> don't ever go out with a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because he's not a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="705" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="706" who="S0375">we were like we literally we were like sixteen it was just life was over</u>
<u n="707" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="708" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="709" who="S0167">when you weren't here the other day we we all came round for a curry and we were talking about</u>
<u n="710" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I heard about this</u>
<u n="711" who="S0167">what the weeing? oh</u>
<u n="712" who="S0375">oh what about the weeing?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0167">anyway we were talking about</u>
<u n="714" who="S0375" trans="overlap">don't know about that</u>
<u n="715" who="S0167" trans="overlap">drunk people <vocal desc="laugh"/> I didn't say anything by the way <vocal desc="laugh"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> started going who the hell wees themselves when they're drunk? who the hell does that? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="716" who="S0375"><vocal desc="gasp"/> I've done it once and once when I was sixteen</u>
<u n="717" who="S0167" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and I wanted to say mm</u>
<u n="718" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="719" who="S0167">I kept quiet though</u>
<u n="720" who="S0375">you shouldn't have done <vocal desc="laugh"/> you should have said something</u>
<u n="721" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="722" who="S0375">I have never lived that down even now it's like never have I ever actually we've all done it in our house <pause dur="short"/> we've all done it at least once</u>
<u n="723" who="S0167" trans="overlap">and and just got a wet bum like like it hit me it was just</u>
<u n="724" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="725" who="S0167">just there was this wet bum like it was like what <vocal desc="laugh"/> what's this wet bum? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="726" who="S0375">cos we were we had to share a bed didn't we? there wasn't enough space</u>
<u n="727" who="S0167">yeah you for some yeah you were sleeping with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and you weed on your side of the <trunc>be</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then you came and jumped into bed with me and I was in your single like bunk at the top <pause dur="short"/> you were on the floor with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the double <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was on your camp bed thing and I was sleeping on your top bunk and you climbed up and climbed into bed with you you'd taken off your bottom half of everything cos it was all wet and then you just jumped into bed with me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="728" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="729" who="S0167">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> woke up in the morning she was like oh thanks <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so I've been sleeping all night with that</u>
<u n="730" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="731" who="S0167">like a puddle of wee <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="732" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I yeah what did I we'd drunk I drunk a bottle of Baileys that night didn't I?</u>
<u n="733" who="S0167">yeah I remember we were <trunc>waste</trunc> was it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? one it was one of those two was here but they were irrelevant I can't remember which one it was</u>
<u n="734" who="S0375" trans="overlap">they it was it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they threw</u>
<u n="735" who="S0167" trans="overlap">it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="736" who="S0375" trans="overlap">she threw up didn't she?</u>
<u n="737" who="S0167">oh yeah yeah I knew it was someone else was here</u>
<u n="738" who="S0375">I can't throw up I don't do the normal thing I</u>
<u n="739" who="S0167">you you wee</u>
<u n="740" who="S0375">I wee</u>
<u n="741" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="742" who="S0375">I have never done that since can I just say that again?</u>
<u n="743" who="S0167" trans="overlap">that's funny <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="744" who="S0375">I</u>
<u n="745" who="S0167" trans="overlap">it was just funny the way <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was so disgusted and I was like</u>
<u n="746" who="S0375" trans="overlap">do you know what? I have never drunk Baileys from that night when we were fifteen</u>
<u n="747" who="S0167">really? I like Baileys but erm erm in small doses I wouldn't get drunk on it</u>
<u n="748" who="S0375">I have never touched it since</u>
<u n="749" who="S0167" trans="overlap">I would have like one Baileys</u>
<u n="750" who="S0375">since I've done that I have never touched it</u>
<u n="751" who="S0167">no I like I like a bit of Baileys</u>
<u n="752" who="S0375">even at Christmas I look at it and think no you're wrong</u>
<u n="753" who="S0167">but I've decided I'm never gonna get completely smashed again no I'm gonna get drunk I did get drunk on Friday but like nice drunk it wasn't like paralytic</u>
<u n="754" who="S0375">what did you do on Friday?</u>
<u n="755" who="S0167">to <anon type="place"/> with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her friends</u>
<u n="756" who="S0375">oh you went out for drinks? I thought you went out sort of shopping I don't know I thought it was shopping</u>
<u n="757" who="S0167">no we went out out we went to <anon type="place"/> club <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="758" who="S0375" trans="overlap">oh what's it like?</u>
<u n="759" who="S0167">it was good it was right next to the <anon type="place"/> shelter where I volunteer</u>
<u n="760" who="S0375">have a look now you've got I'll see how long</u>
<u n="761" who="S0167">oh you just press that on the side</u>
<u n="762" who="S0375">oh what's <anon type="place"/> like? cos I've I've seen that</u>
<u n="763" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="764" who="S0375">I thought</u>
<u n="765" who="S0167" trans="overlap">quite good it's got like three storeys or something</u>
<u n="766" who="S0375">I don't know <anon type="place"/> very well anymore</u>
<u n="767" who="S0167">no <pause dur="short"/> but yeah</u>
<u n="768" who="S0375" trans="overlap">was it busy?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0167">yeah it was really busy and erm</u>
<u n="770" who="S0375">ah can I have a bit of that philly?</u>
<u n="771" who="S0167">yeah alright</u>
<u n="772" who="S0375">do you want?</u>
<u n="773" who="S0167" trans="overlap">I've just licked it with my spit</u>
<u n="774" who="S0375">oh that really put me off I don't I hate spit and I'm like oh I live well I don't want the biscuit part obviously but <pause dur="short"/> I just want the filling if I eat the filling can you have a biscuit?</u>
<u n="775" who="S0167">alright <pause dur="short"/> erm so yeah that was erm we did that on Friday but I did get drunk <pause dur="short"/> but I wasn't like out of control drunk I just like oh let's have a dance</u>
<u n="776" who="S0375">out of our house I don't I'm always erm the one that gets least <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> always says that <pause dur="short"/> he says you make me laugh he was like I I look on Facebook and he was like you you're always behind the camera <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="777" who="S0167">yeah it is nice that way I think cos like</u>
<u n="778" who="S0375">well it happened a few times lately</u>
<u n="779" who="S0167" trans="overlap">well once you get to once you get a point to a certain point it stops being enjoyable doesn't it? cos you don't remember anything and you do stupid stuff and <pause dur="short"/> you're kind of like I dunno</u>
<u n="780" who="S0375">when I went out with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and</u>
<u n="781" who="S0167">who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="782" who="S0375">he was my he was the doctor</u>
<u n="783" who="S0167">oh right</u>
<u n="784" who="S0375">he was the the date I went on</u>
<u n="785" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh very sophisticated <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="786" who="S0375">and erm <pause dur="short"/> we got absolutely slaughtered</u>
<u n="787" who="S0167">mm</u>
<u n="788" who="S0375">both of us did <pause dur="long"/> I'll eat that bit there</u>
<u n="789" who="S0167">mm</u>
<u n="790" who="S0375" trans="overlap">erm yeah we ended up getting absolutely slaughtered and I <vocal desc="laugh"/> came home</u>
<u n="791" who="S0167">cool</u>
<u n="792" who="S0375">erm</u>
<u n="793" who="S0167" trans="overlap">mm nice</u>
<u n="794" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="795" who="S0167" trans="overlap">how old is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="796" who="S0375">he's twenty-six</u>
<u n="797" who="S0167">mm <pause dur="short"/> nice age</u>
<u n="798" who="S0375">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know what I want <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at the moment <pause dur="short"/> to keep erm</u>
<u n="799" who="S0167">the thing is <pause dur="short"/> the right person will come along if you can enjoy your life live your life <pause dur="short"/> do what you want to do and the right person will appear <pause dur="short"/> that is what happens that's what happens in life</u>
<u n="800" who="S0375">what if I'm if I'm like thirty and <pause dur="short"/> life's passing by?</u>
<u n="801" who="S0167">life doesn't pass you by cos you'll have been doing what you enjoy if you if you stop your life to wait for someone then that's wasting your life if you do what you enjoy do what you love <pause dur="short"/> then</u>
<u n="802" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I feel like I'm having a midlife crisis at the moment where I'm like oh my god</u>
<u n="803" who="S0167">you're only twenty-four <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="804" who="S0375">I'm twenty-five this year</u>
<u n="805" who="S0167">twenty-five <pause dur="short"/> just revel in the fact that you don't have to worry about anyone else <pause dur="short"/> you you don't have to worry about <pause dur="short"/> anything about but yourself all your money can go on yourself</u>
<u n="806" who="S0375">that's very true I like this thought yeah</u>
<u n="807" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah oh I've got a coil now</u>
<u n="808" who="S0375">did you get the coil?</u>
<u n="809" who="S0167">mm</u>
<u n="810" who="S0375">what's it like?</u>
<u n="811" who="S0167">I don't feel it it was quite painful having it inserted but</u>
<u n="812" who="S0375">I really really want it but everyone's <trunc>kee</trunc>keep putting me off how long have you had it?</u>
<u n="813" who="S0167" trans="overlap">mm well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> both said it was good <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has got it and she said it was good <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got it and she said it was good <pause dur="short"/> they've all got copper coils though and I wanted a copper one and the the woman tried to put me off she was like erm this was doctor <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I don't know know her but</u>
<u n="814" who="S0375" trans="overlap">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0167">she was like well</u>
<u n="816" who="S0375" trans="overlap">she's nutty</u>
<u n="817" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah but she's quite nice though isn't she? she was like well you know it does make your periods more heavy and it does make them quite painful and there is a there is a higher rate of failure and stuff but you know it still it still works and it's not it doesn't fail all the time</u>
<u n="818" who="S0375" trans="overlap">is that the one without the hormone?</u>
<u n="819" who="S0167">yeah the one without the hormone which is what I wanted</u>
<u n="820" who="S0375" trans="overlap">cos that that's what I want I don't want anything with hormone in it</u>
<u n="821" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="822" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I don't want to mess around with</u>
<u n="823" who="S0167">no that's that's my that was my thing as well</u>
<u n="824" who="S0375" trans="overlap">mess around</u>
<u n="825" who="S0167">erm so she really tried to talk me into the the hormonal one and I was like no I'd rather to be honest just avoid hormones cos you know I've been on the pill before and you know it didn't react well with me and I'd rather not risk that again she was like well it's only a tiny bit of hormone really it's a tiny bit of hormone like the pill is a lot of hormone</u>
<u n="826" who="S0375" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="827" who="S0167">and I was like no I think I'll stick with the copper one she was like okay so she went and got the copper one and she said ah there's a problem <pause dur="short"/> she said because you haven't had a baby you're going to have a little coil cos they do them two sizes women who have had children and women who haven't and you're gonna have to have a small one we've only got the copper ones in the big size so you can either come back another time and we'll order in an a smaller coil or we do have the hormonal one in now we've got both sizes in now so it's up to you and I just thought oh I'm here</u>
<u n="828" who="S0375">get the hormonal one in</u>
<u n="829" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh yeah she was like it's only a tiny bit of hormone anyway and I was like yeah okay just do the small one that you've got so I've got the hormone one <pause dur="short"/> in</u>
<u n="830" who="S0375">and do you feel any different?</u>
<u n="831" who="S0167" trans="overlap">no I don't feel any different really <pause dur="short"/> she said the pill is like twenty milligrams of the hormone every day and this is like twenty milligrams of three years <pause dur="short"/> so she said it's like</u>
<u n="832" who="S0375" trans="overlap">oh wow</u>
<u n="833" who="S0167">minimal the amount of hormone you're getting and it's much you're much less likely to get pregnant on it than you would on the copper coil although she said the copper coil is still good for contraception but there's just a slightly higher <trunc>ra</trunc>rate of failure with the copper one <pause dur="short"/> erm so yeah so I've got that in now it does <trunc>hur</trunc> oh it was like my period when when she inserted it <vocal desc="laugh"/> I turned up</u>
<u n="834" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I <trunc>th</trunc> I thought that's one you need that you need to be I think</u>
<u n="835" who="S0167">well I don't think it matters</u>
<u n="836" who="S0375">cos I I <trunc>wen</trunc> I I asked about it erm</u>
<u n="837" who="S0167">mm</u>
<u n="838" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I've asked about it so many times and never had it done erm and she said that you need to be on your period they prefer it if you're on your period to get it inserted</u>
<u n="839" who="S0167">ah cos no one ever like <pause dur="short"/> said either way to me and then I went there and I said oh sorry I've just started my period yesterday and she was like oh no it's no problem we can still do it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="840" who="S0375"><unclear/></u>
<u n="841" who="S0167">maybe <pause dur="short"/> maybe you you just had a really on the ball doctor <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="842" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="843" who="S0167">I dunno but anyway</u>
<u n="844" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I went to a clinic</u>
<u n="845" who="S0167">I was on my</u>
<u n="846" who="S0375" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="847" who="S0167">period anyway and it was a bit gross but</u>
<u n="848" who="S0375">so erm <trunc>ha</trunc> did it how long have you had it in again sorry?</u>
<u n="849" who="S0167">since last week</u>
<u n="850" who="S0375">oh you've only had it for a week?</u>
<u n="851" who="S0167">mm</u>
<u n="852" who="S0375">oh I <trunc>rea</trunc> and have you have you had sex with it yet?</u>
<u n="853" who="S0167">no well I haven't had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> here have I?</u>
<u n="854" who="S0375">oh yeah that's true</u>
<u n="855" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="856" who="S0375">yeah sorry <pause dur="short"/> momentary momentary blank</u>
<u n="857" who="S0167">erm yeah so that's that and and I said to them I went to Peru <pause dur="short"/> erm last year and I had my injections done and I had hepatitis A and B done here in June and she said if I have another shot done when I get back that will protect me for longer and she said yes if you have a hepatitis A shot now that will finish your course that that will protect you for twenty-five years <pause dur="short"/> so okay that will that sounds good I said so do I book at appointment at the reception then to come back in for that? she said well we've got them in the fridge now if you if you're feeling brave you know you can have it done now if you want <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="858" who="S0375">bung it in</u>
<u n="859" who="S0167">and I said yeah go on then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="860" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="861" who="S0167">so I had like my I had pains from there while my coil was in and then she just jabbed a needle in and I was like ah</u>
<u n="862" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="863" who="S0167">but no it was good I just got that all out of the way at one in one fell swoop so now I'm protected for hepatitis A for twenty-five years</u>
<u n="864" who="S0375">I have done the hepatitis B one three times now</u>
<u n="865" who="S0167">do you never finish the course?</u>
<u n="866" who="S0375">no I finish it just never takes it doesn't take on dad either he's like <trunc>ha</trunc> he yeah</u>
<u n="867" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="868" who="S0375">he's had it done twice with <unclear/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> he said that he didn't ever take to it</u>
<u n="869" who="S0167" trans="overlap">so maybe it's just a genetic thing then you</u>
<u n="870" who="S0375" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="871" who="S0167">you and your dad</u>
<u n="872" who="S0375">but you have</u>
<u n="873" who="S0167" trans="overlap">so you just need to make sure you have it done every time you go away</u>
<u n="874" who="S0375" trans="overlap">you have to be like over a thousand or something</u>
<u n="875" who="S0167">mm</u>
<u n="876" who="S0375">and erm</u>
<u n="877" who="S0167" trans="overlap">it could be your weird blood</u>
<u n="878" who="S0375">I've got it done and then yeah maybe and then I've got it done and I was less than five</u>
<u n="879" who="S0167">oh</u>
<u n="880" who="S0375">every time less than five and I think what I don't want it done a fourth time I'm gonna be hepatitis Bd out with this</u>
<u n="881" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="882" who="S0375">and the first one the first one doesn't make me feel great</u>
<u n="883" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="884" who="S0375">and the rest of them are fine like er you know suppose if you're rejecting something and it makes you feel a bit sick?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0167">yeah I know yeah yeah just make sure if you ever go somewhere just to have it done every time you go away <pause dur="short"/> and erm</u>
<u n="886" who="S0375">but no I work in hospitals</u>
<u n="887" who="S0167">oh yeah</u>
<u n="888" who="S0375" trans="overlap">so I'm supposed to <trunc>hep</trunc>hepatitis B protected</u>
<u n="889" who="S0167">oh right if it doesn't take it doesn't take does it?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0375" trans="overlap">exactly <unclear/> just I've kind of said I don't want it done again I think I might just get one more course to make them happy and then you know</u>
<u n="891" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/> yeah no that's a good idea that's weird I just thought if you had it done you had it done</u>
<u n="892" who="S0375">yeah I did as well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="893" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="894" who="S0375">they so I was like na ah and the second time no</u>
<u n="895" who="S0167">you've got a weird body</u>
<u n="896" who="S0375">I know</u>
<u n="897" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="898" who="S0375">the system of an eight eighty year old it's a little oldie and they've never gone to the doctor's never gone to the dentist in their life <pause dur="short"/> you know like</u>
<u n="899" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh no go to the dentist you've got to go to the dentist</u>
<u n="900" who="S0375">oh it was so funny this guy he came in and he <pause dur="short"/> he yeah he'd never been to the doctor's in his whole entire life he was like ninety-six he'd had a stroke wasn't even a a bad stroke he had actually he had a had a had a erm he was a bit cognitively impaired but it's he was quite he'd be able to walk and and erm he'd never been to the dentist either and he just had no teeth just this one rotten stump of a tooth</u>
<u n="901" who="S0167">er</u>
<u n="902" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they were like you know when it pokes out of their lip and they're like hello love and it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="903" who="S0167">that's horrible</u>
<u n="904" who="S0375">it was one stump and I thought well you've definitely never been to the dentist that's for sure <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="905" who="S0167">cor why do people not go to the dentist? that's</u>
<u n="906" who="S0375" trans="overlap">well he's done his whole life in</u>
<u n="907" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah but then you have rotten teeth</u>
<u n="908" who="S0375">well I think <pause dur="short"/> he pulled out this he pulled out his bag and erm obviously this bag with his clothes and wanted to find his glasses and it was to do his assessment thing and in this bag were his jogging bottoms and they were just like they</u>
<u n="909" who="S0167" trans="overlap">they stink</u>
<u n="910" who="S0375" trans="overlap">stink stunk of urine and there was a bit of poo in there as well and</u>
<u n="911" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="912" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I think he just I think</u>
<u n="913" who="S0167" trans="overlap">is he is he a bit?</u>
<u n="914" who="S0375">I think so yeah</u>
<u n="915" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="916" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I mean I think there was a bit of an air of maybe a small stroke before that he just got on with</u>
<u n="917" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="918" who="S0375">and then erm he is kind of declined then and when he did come to the hospital with the second stroke I mean at ninety-six he doesn't really give a damn</u>
<u n="919" who="S0167">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so what happened?</u>
<u n="920" who="S0375" trans="overlap">and one old lady</u>
<u n="921" who="S0167" trans="overlap">was he alright after that?</u>
<u n="922" who="S0375">yeah we put put him on some anticoagulants and you know we did say he he might need to go into a nursing home or something now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="923" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="924" who="S0375">or go home with carers because</u>
<u n="925" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="926" who="S0375">because you know he needs helpers and stuff but I don't know I never know what happens to them you don't ever know do you when they leave hospital?</u>
<u n="927" who="S0167">that's weird <pause dur="short"/> why don't you set up your own erm <pause dur="short"/> speech and language therapy business where you <pause dur="short"/> you go to people's homes?</u>
<u n="928" who="S0375">you can do I think</u>
<u n="929" who="S0167" trans="overlap">why don't you do that? and then you've got your own business then and then you don't have to worry about being sacked</u>
<u n="930" who="S0375">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm a bit young I think</u>
<u n="931" who="S0167" trans="overlap">no no one's too young to start a business</u>
<u n="932" who="S0375">no but I think my generally in my job you need a bit of experience in like</u>
<u n="933" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="934" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I I do <trunc>n</trunc> actually need to get experience in how to</u>
<u n="935" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="936" who="S0375" trans="overlap">to assess and</u>
<u n="937" who="S0167">that's worth thinking about for the future</u>
<u n="938" who="S0375">yeah it is yeah and I wouldn't mind doing it privately like my <trunc>bus</trunc> but you do always I always think you need cash in hand at first to start a business</u>
<u n="939" who="S0167">mm that's where you need to save save a bit for a couple of years and then you've got a bit of money</u>
<u n="940" who="S0375">and then I think I want to live in the next couple of years like I've missed I've been at uni four years I haven't done anything</u>
<u n="941" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="942" who="S0375" trans="overlap">you know I've been in <anon type="place"/> but it's too expensive I haven't gone skiing I haven't done any of that sort of stuff that everyone always seems to do <pause dur="short"/> sod having a business I'll do that when I'm older on er <pause dur="short"/> I want to ski</u>
<u n="943" who="S0167">live</u>
<u n="944" who="S0375">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know? I really you've been skiing you've been skiing haven't you?</u>
<u n="945" who="S0167">yeah I went I've been for one weekend skiing <pause dur="short"/> I mean I think it takes a bit of practice I wasn't very good but I only did it for two days</u>
<u n="946" who="S0375">yeah do you wish you'd done it for longer?</u>
<u n="947" who="S0167">I think a weekend was enough for me just because it it I was a beginner and like</u>
<u n="948" who="S0375" trans="overlap">you you didn't really</u>
<u n="949" who="S0167">yeah I think if I went on a week's skiing holiday that would be good <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="950" who="S0375">I mean even on a <unclear/> now I can't walk in a straight line can you imagine me on skis?</u>
<u n="951" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="952" who="S0375">I can imagine rocking up in to the bar</u>
<u n="953" who="S0167" trans="overlap">it was fun it's just it is really cold I have to say <pause dur="short"/> obviously cos of the mountains <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="954" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="955" who="S0167">erm but yeah no it was fun but I'd recommend just to like I would go for a couple more ski weekends first and then to go on a</u>
<u n="956" who="S0375">well you didn't do anything like the dry ski slopes or anything did you?</u>
<u n="957" who="S0167">no</u>
<u n="958" who="S0375">like people here <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did it when she went recently they went on like a few sessions of ski sloping</u>
<u n="959" who="S0167">no I just went to the mountains</u>
<u n="960" who="S0375" trans="overlap">you just went all out and went straight to skiing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="961" who="S0167">I went to the mountains I was on the baby slope though which is like that steep <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="962" who="S0375">that would be enough for me</u>
<u n="963" who="S0167" trans="overlap">I was with with the two year olds <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="964" who="S0375">used to probably oh you snow ploughed into these er</u>
<u n="965" who="S0167">oh yeah that was on the slightly that was the that was the <trunc>st</trunc> erm</u>
<u n="966" who="S0375">because they go blue don't they?</u>
<u n="967" who="S0167">yeah the well green is lower than blue there's green blue</u>
<u n="968" who="S0375">and then black</u>
<u n="969" who="S0167" trans="overlap">red and black</u>
<u n="970" who="S0375">that's it yeah</u>
<u n="971" who="S0167" trans="overlap">green blue red black</u>
<u n="972" who="S0375">they all seem to be very much the same don't they?</u>
<u n="973" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="974" who="S0375">cos I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had the same colours she went to Andorra</u>
<u n="975" who="S0167">oh well I went on the red one accidentally and it was really steep and then when I went on a green one and I was like god this is more my</u>
<u n="976" who="S0375">did you go down the red one?</u>
<u n="977" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="978" who="S0375">did you manage it?</u>
<u n="979" who="S0167">not really I couldn't really control myself <vocal desc="laugh"/> no it's because okay so we went this girl organised it who's like she's been doing skiing since she was like three <pause dur="short"/> she didn't notice the colour of the slope she just took us on this slope and we like none of us could get it and after about an hour she was like <pause dur="short"/> oh we're on the red slope no wonder none of you are getting it cos we all just couldn't control ourselves we were all just whizzing off and like falling off cos it was so steep <vocal desc="laugh"/> and we didn't know how to control ourselves</u>
<u n="980" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="981" who="S0167">and that's the one below black</u>
<u n="982" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="983" who="S0167">it's the <vocal desc="laugh"/> so that was a really hard one to like begin with <pause dur="short"/> so we went on the baby ones and then we were much better</u>
<u n="984" who="S0375">oh bless you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="985" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="986" who="S0375">bless you little ducklings <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="987" who="S0167">yeah that's what we were like <pause dur="short"/> cos she kept saying right go off and then stop yourself and I couldn't stop myself so I was just whizzing off like and I didn't know how to stop myself</u>
<u n="988" who="S0375">she's <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="989" who="S0167">so <vocal desc="laugh"/> I just had and erm so I just used to <trunc>s</trunc> she said if you really can't stop just sit down on your bum and that will slow you down so <trunc>tha</trunc> I would just do that every time I wanted to stop I'd just sit on my bum and then you'd just come to a slow half stop</u>
<u n="990" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="991" who="S0167">well</u>
<u n="992" who="S0375">what even on the green slope?</u>
<u n="993" who="S0167">yeah even on the green one</u>
<u n="994" who="S0375" trans="overlap">you didn't master <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="995" who="S0167">didn't even master it I kept trying I didn't master it <pause dur="short"/> I needed a bit more practice I think</u>
<u n="996" who="S0375" trans="overlap">were you on your own then on the green slope in the end or were you with other people?</u>
<u n="997" who="S0167">with other people <pause dur="long"/> people that yeah I think with a bit more practice I'd be alright I think with anything</u>
<u n="998" who="S0375" trans="overlap">did you have to rent skiing stuff and everything like that?</u>
<u n="999" who="S0167">yeah you have to rent the skis</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0375">was it expensive?</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0167">I can't remember how much it was really <pause dur="short"/> I remember I just went and erm <pause dur="short"/> I got the ski jacket no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> lent me a ski jacket the helmet the skis and the poles I got and I <trunc>w</trunc> I went on the cable car at to the top of the mountain and then it was cool</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0375">cos erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s a good skier isn't she?</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0167">yeah she's like black slope <unclear/></u>
<u n="1004" who="S0375">does she?</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0167">she got off she's er she's even <trunc>mor</trunc> erm above that she's er off piste she does it off piste which is over the which is more than the black slope</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0375">does she? what</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0167" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0375">she just goes anywhere sort of thing?</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0167">yeah <pause dur="short"/> which is quite dangerous actually</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0167">but she I guess she's quite experienced so she knows <pause dur="short"/> where to go and where not to go and stuff <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1012" who="S0375">she I didn't know that is she still doing PT work by the way?</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0167">yeah I think so <pause dur="short"/> you're very got the lingo there <pause dur="short"/> pT work</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0375">sorry</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1016" who="S0375">yeah I've got the PT physiotherapist cos we work with PTs don't we? like mostly</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0167" trans="overlap">I guess you do yeah</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0375"><unclear/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I always think I always think where's she gonna go? is she gonna be a like a hospital PT or <pause dur="short"/> is she gonna work in sports? what's she gonna do?</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0167">I dunno I guess she could probably work on a ski slope shouldn't shouldn't she?</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1022" who="S0375">yeah</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0167" trans="overlap">on a ski slope hospital <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1024" who="S0375">oh could you imagine?</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0167">that would be cool</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0375">wonder if they do speech and <trunc>lang</trunc> no that wouldn't happen</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0167" trans="overlap">let's yeah cos I don't think people generally</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0375">stay there no</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0167">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1030" who="S0375">they're just on <trunc>hol</trunc></u>
<u n="1031" who="S0167">you could help Michael Schumacher couldn't you? you could go and help Michael Schumacher</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0375">oh yes and by the sounds of it I can just imagine him being I I can sort of imagine the sort of patient he'd be cos I've worked with lots of them <pause dur="short"/> I can imagine him being very much <pause dur="short"/> you know we work with nonverbal eye gaze that sort of thing</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0167">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1034" who="S0375">not to say he doesn't make progress you know we've got this guy at the moment and he's been in hospital eight months? erm maybe longer than that he got beaten up in a pub</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0167"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1036" who="S0375">erm</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0167">why do people beat <trunc>peo</trunc>?</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0375" trans="overlap">it was like in a fight and</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0375">I think it was over someone tried to hit his wife? I don't I don't know what happened</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0167">oh for god's sake</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0375">erm there was like a fight yeah and he got really bad TBI and</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0167">what's TBI?</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0375">traumatic brain injury erm he's been tracheostomied he's got a trachy in</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0167">oh god</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0375">erm he's off that and everything now</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0167">was the man arrested who beat him up?</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0375" trans="overlap">he's stimulated yeah he got life <pause dur="short"/> erm he's been decannulated now and everything so he's got a voice now and he got really down and we were like you know we need to give him antidepressants he had this big thing cos <trunc>ha</trunc> he's got no verbal communication so <trunc>unab</trunc> he was unable to communicate at the time</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0167">oh how did you know he was depressed then?</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0375">well he had some sort of <pause dur="short"/> he was able cos we were we had we'd got him within quite a lot of time just to take <unclear/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> he at one time he was like fuck off it was like automatic language so we were like he's obviously got some sort of verbal the ability to verby up but he just needs to relearn it all</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0375">so we started you know working with him doing the erm <trunc>communic</trunc> the mood charts and it was very much he was very angry at everyone</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0167">oh</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0375">especially because we was bung the suction tube down his throat</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0375">but erm</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0167">does his wife come in and?</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0375">the wife's really on the ball but we've got to put we were trying to get him to self suction and he got that and everything and then he like when he was self suctioning you get a you then get to realise that you've got feeling and you're very <trunc>indepen</trunc> you know it just stimulates your own sensory input rather than someone else doing it for you <pause dur="short"/> and then from there he then started to manage his own secretions and you know onwards and upwards and we got to tick off down there</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0167">oh that's good</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0375">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and erm</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0167">so will he like make a full <trunc>recov</trunc>? oh my god <pause dur="short"/> look at this</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0375">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0167">shit <pause dur="short"/> hope he didn't die</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0375">are they okay?</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0167">oh my god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1066" who="S0375">where is that is that London?</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0167">I guess</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0375">it looked like a</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0167" trans="overlap">well no it's world news so it could be anywhere</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0375">oh so like a so like a platform but yeah no he's er so we've got him on these antidepressants you know everything he's done is very angry and erm <pause dur="short"/> he's now making an incredible recovery <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like he's really happy</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0167">oh that's good</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0375" trans="overlap">to the point there <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> left her hoodie there we got an email from her Monday actually it was on a Friday er</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0167">who's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0375">she's the band seven erm <pause dur="short"/> speech and analyst therapist</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0167">okay</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0375">and she's like a few bands above me she's like a good really high band and erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah she'd left her hoodie there on Friday and on Tuesday we got this email about it and I didn't know any of this but about our uniform we need to wear black cardigans only you know it's so you see them come in they're a health organisation and <unclear/> it needed to be washed ironed very white erm it came on the back of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she'd left her hoodie there and it was obviously in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s room and she'd taken it off to then do stuff with him came in and he was wearing her hoodie on the Monday <vocal desc="laugh"/> and apparently he was giggling away he obviously knew that he was wearing her hoodie</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1078" who="S0375">and er he told the nursing staff cos they all change that it was his hoodie and they'd put it on him and he was going <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1079" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1080" who="S0375"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came in and then they then had to wrestle him out of it cos he wouldn't let go he was giggling away and wouldn't let <trunc>g</trunc> and wouldn't get himself out of this hoodie</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0375">and erm yeah so and then they got this massive email about the uniform <pause dur="short"/> cos <unclear/> at the time we're like you shouldn't be wearing it anyway it's stupid <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah he's doing really well he's now</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh that's so cool</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0375">he's now going to rehab cos he's got loads of rehab to do</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0167">so he'll be able to speak and everything normally like</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0375">I don't think so</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0167">never be normal again?</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0375" trans="overlap">it'll be quite a it'll be quite a low level</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0167">oh <pause dur="short"/> it's why do men beat each other up?</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0375">well women do as well</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0167">yeah but it's mostly men <pause dur="short"/> but whoever whether you're a man or a woman why would you beat someone up? I just</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I don't know</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0167">just go to the pub and enjoy yourself don't have to beat someone up it used to really annoy me when we'd go out in <anon type="place"/> and like every night there'd be someone like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or <trunc>s</trunc> they'd all be in some kind of fight and they'd all go out like and they'd look for a fight as well they wouldn't just like be picked on they'd be like yeah I'm gonna go and</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0375">but they were a bit druggy though weren't they?</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0167">yeah oh they were just <pause dur="short"/> oh see I just don't get it it's like <trunc>h</trunc> oh I just don't get it understand it I need to just <unclear/></u>
<u n="1096" who="S0375" trans="overlap">I don't either I don't either <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1097" who="S0167">oh do you want to stop?</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0375">yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
