<text id="SFLQ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:12:00</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-28</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0448 S0449</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Theatre, Disney films, websites, post, Christmas, jobs</topics>
		<activity>Mother and daughter talking about theatre</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, announcing, making arrangement</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0448">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>High Wycombe</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South East England/ Standard English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>High Wycombe</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Currently seeking graduate job</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0449">
				<exactage>44</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Northampton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South East England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>High Wycombe</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>Since birth</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Team Leader</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0448">hello</u>
<u n="2" who="S0449">yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0448">you you said to ring when you got in</u>
<u n="4" who="S0449">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0449" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0448">what?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0449" trans="overlap">when are you when are you planning to go?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0448">erm I don't know whenever's cheap presumably one of the holidays when I'm back cos otherwise I'm at uni and it's in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0449">oh how come you're going to that one?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0448">huh?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0449">well what made you want to go to that one?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0448">because The Lion King's amazing</u>
<u n="14" who="S0449">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> are you dragging <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> along? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0448">it's not dragging it's inviting him to experience the wonder that was The Lion King in musical</u>
<u n="16" who="S0449">yeah does he like Disney?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0448">yes</u>
<u n="18" who="S0449">are you sure?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0448">he watched Frozen and Tangled without complaining so yes</u>
<u n="20" who="S0449">yeah but you hadn't known him <unclear/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0448">yes because who doesn't love The Lion King?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0449">pardon?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0448">who doesn't love The Lion King?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0449">well yeah <unclear/> say anything but you're <unclear/> thought you might be</u>
<u n="25" who="S0448">hm?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0449">I finally watched it yesterday with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0448">what Frozen?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0449">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0448">and what did you think?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0449">well it's okay I don't think it's one of their better ones though</u>
<u n="31" who="S0448">okay? it was more than okay</u>
<u n="32" who="S0449">no it's not one of their better ones</u>
<u n="33" who="S0448">no it wasn't their best but it was not just okay</u>
<u n="34" who="S0449">mm are there any more DVDs you want to get if <unclear/> comes <unclear>send me a text</unclear></u>
<u n="35" who="S0448">okay I don't know</u>
<u n="36" who="S0449" trans="overlap"><unclear/> so I usually when I went the last time I kept looking around for different offers I mean if you can well no you probably won't well maybe you'll have opened if you're really lucky <unclear/> you know they have that <unclear>Get Into</unclear> London Theatre <unclear>dock</unclear> thing remember <unclear/> London theatre?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0448">Get Into London Theatre?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0449">yeah but it only I think opens it's on in January time</u>
<u n="39" who="S0448">right</u>
<u n="40" who="S0449"><vocal desc="cough"/> they always <unclear/> some bits for The Lion King I've never managed to get them but I never always actually get on as soon as they open you know the bookings for it</u>
<u n="41" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0449"><vocal desc="cough"/> you know the one I mean? the one I try I think I booked Wicked on it that time we went to Wicked</u>
<u n="43" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0449">so it depends whether you're in a hurry to go or not <unclear/> say quite often <unclear/> look when I just look <unclear/> I off <unclear/> there's a website called Theatre Monkey</u>
<u n="45" who="S0448">yep</u>
<u n="46" who="S0449">then go on there <vocal desc="cough"/> you can like search by either venue or show title <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0448">okay</u>
<u n="48" who="S0449">and it sort of gives you a list not always of all of the different things but it does give you a list of special offers that have put on <unclear/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0448">okay</u>
<u n="50" who="S0449">remember when I got the ticket I really had to keep looking around for different special offers</u>
<u n="51" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0449">so there's not like one good if you if you go there now can you see it?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0448">er hang on</u>
<u n="54" who="S0449">what?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0448">what?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0449">so go onto Theatre Monkey dot com</u>
<u n="57" who="S0448">I'm going onto Theatre Monkey dot com</u>
<u n="58" who="S0449">and what I mean if you're not in a hurry to book I can look cos obviously I get where I've bought different tickets I still get various various different <trunc>off</trunc> special offers</u>
<u n="59" who="S0448">no I'm not in a hurry it's just he said to me cos you know when we go to <anon type="place"/> for our meal</u>
<u n="60" who="S0449">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0448">and he said do you wanna go and see a show? and then it just reminded me Lion King is amazing even though I think he meant something a bit cheaper I thought if I looked then I could suggest it to him that we do it like in the new year sometime</u>
<u n="62" who="S0449">yeah <unclear/> for The Lion King <unclear/> tell you what you have to do you have to just keep looking out and I'll tell you when <anon type="place"/> Get Into London Theatre thing opens it it might I can't remember when booking starts <unclear>though</unclear> I think it's it's booking in January but they usually start reminding you in December it's like about a six week period when you can use it but you yeah oh for The Lion King obviously you have to book it pretty much as soon as they open for bookings cos they always go <pause dur="short"/> have have you gone to Theatre Monkey?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0449">or have you put in Disney's The Lion King?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0449">and then if you scroll down a bit</u>
<u n="67" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0449">you'll see what is offers maybe available click here</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="69" who="S0448">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0449">yes or no?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0448">no it go it goes to reviews</u>
<u n="72" who="S0449">no alright let me see so did you search by show title?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0448">yes</u>
<u n="74" who="S0449">right let me do it again so you should be underneath Lion King now <unclear>first</unclear> you scroll down then you've got a picture of Disney's The Lion King and then it says kimba <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0448">what?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0449" trans="overlap"><unclear/> you've got three pictures at the top yeah?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0448">no</u>
<u n="78" who="S0449">are you on Theatre Monkey dot com?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0448">yes</u>
<u n="80" who="S0449">then it should say forward slash Lyceum booking dot ATM</u>
<u n="81" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0449">right start scrolling down</u>
<u n="83" who="S0448">scrolling</u>
<u n="84" who="S0449">have you passed the pictures?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0449">scrolling now you've got the reviews</u>
<u n="87" who="S0448">scrolling yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0449">scrolling stop at the end of the reviews</u>
<u n="89" who="S0448">yep</u>
<u n="90" who="S0449">and it starts to say performance schedule</u>
<u n="91" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0449">and then you see on the right offers may be available click here</u>
<u n="93" who="S0448">yes</u>
<u n="94" who="S0449">so then what happens is it gives you a list of different types of offers on and these aren't every cos I notice that more and more they are linked to <unclear>their</unclear> Theatre Monkey so they're not always until I normally if I have a little look down to see if and that what I did was I just looked to see if there's anything you know when I was booking for us?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0449">I looked and eventually I found something and I was like oh that's a good one can you see a lot of these are only for performances until November</u>
<u n="97" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0449">which is why like I said it depends when you want to go and obviously December is gonna be a busy period over the Christmas holidays which is that's when a lot you know if you think when people go like half term would be bad and the Christmas holidays</u>
<u n="99" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0449" trans="overlap"><unclear/> you don't go back until a bit later you might get something you see what I mean? it just depends how much of a rush you're in</u>
<u n="101" who="S0448">mm mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0449">and that's quite a good one to use like I said I rarely would book through Last Minute dot com because you can't pick your seats</u>
<u n="103" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0449">so I have these <unclear/> have these <anon type="place"/> theatre before definitely is one of the <unclear/> I can't remember which other one I've used I sort of have a few that I'll have a little look around as well</u>
<u n="105" who="S0448">okay</u>
<u n="106" who="S0449">so does that help a bit?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0448">yes</u>
<u n="108" who="S0449">okay then I'll obviously I'll let you know when that other one's but I'm sure <trunc>it</trunc>it's either it's definitely in January I just don't know whether it's also in in December as well <pause dur="short"/> I mean you could have a look otherwise and see if there's any cheaper shows for your trip your other trip</u>
<u n="109" who="S0448">okay</u>
<u n="110" who="S0449">again you can look on here for different ideas and also it's quite good it gives you a few like oh these are good seats and these are bad seats</u>
<u n="111" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="112" who="S0449">did your charger turn up?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0448">yes and no they tried to deliver it today but I was on campus so I've rebooked delivery for Wednesday cos I can't be bothered to walk to town and pick it up because it's like right at the other end of town up a hill and I don't wanna go there so I rebooked it</u>
<u n="114" who="S0449">oh okay fine erm <pause dur="short"/> we're going to see another free show tomorrow</u>
<u n="115" who="S0448">ah what are you seeing now?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0449">oh I don't know it's called Stones In His Pockets or something?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0448">stone village pockets?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0449">Stones In His Pockets or something it's had quite good reviews from different places</u>
<u n="119" who="S0448">and what's it about?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0449">I dunno set in Ireland something to do with some people being extras</u>
<u n="121" who="S0448">oh okay</u>
<u n="122" who="S0449">but it was free so I <unclear/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0448" trans="overlap">are you going with nan?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0449">no nan <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0448">oh</u>
<u n="126" who="S0449">well yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0448">what do I want for Christmas?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0449">I dunno why? who's asking?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0448">dad</u>
<u n="130" who="S0449">he's got no money</u>
<u n="131" who="S0448" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="132" who="S0449">or is he asking for nan and grandad?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0448">I don't know he er just</u>
<u n="134" who="S0449" trans="overlap">have you got makeup on your list still?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0449">oh Love Theatre that's another one I've used they were quite good</u>
<u n="137" who="S0448">okay I need makeup and I need <trunc>t</trunc>two bags now I need a big one and a small one cos my little one for going out broke</u>
<u n="138" who="S0449">yeah but bags you can only do if you can find the bag you know that</u>
<u n="139" who="S0448">yeah I know but that's my point is that that's what I need</u>
<u n="140" who="S0449">yeah but if there's makeup cos you can give them exactly what you want and that way you and they like shopping in Boots</u>
<u n="141" who="S0448">fine</u>
<u n="142" who="S0449">so give them the makeup and just but you need to write down exactly what you want and that means you won't get Gok Wan <unclear/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay</u>
<u n="144" who="S0449">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0449">then see if there's anything else like even if it's another <unclear>tangle tube</unclear> I don't know some <unclear/> think what was left then was is is there anything outstanding on your list? or anything you think might come up that you know that you can just go yep this is it this is the product code and that you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0448">okay</u>
<u n="148" who="S0449">and don't forget to check on your DVDs</u>
<u n="149" who="S0448">okay</u>
<u n="150" who="S0449">if there's anything else you need</u>
<u n="151" who="S0448">okay</u>
<u n="152" who="S0449" trans="overlap">on the <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0448">huh?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0449">did he make you watch any of his films?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0448">what? did you what?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0449">to torture poor <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> with</u>
<u n="157" who="S0448">oh it's not torturing he loved it</u>
<u n="158" who="S0449">yeah I bet he did he didn't know you for very long I didn't realise you'd made him watch Frozen as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0448">I didn't make him I gave him the choice of which one he wanted to watch and he picked Frozen</u>
<u n="160" who="S0449">oh right</u>
<u n="161" who="S0448">but then I made him watch Tangled after anyway</u>
<u n="162" who="S0449">oh right</u>
<u n="163" who="S0448"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0449">which one did he prefer?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0448">huh?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0449">which one did he prefer?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0448">I don't know he said they were both alright <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0449">they're alright <vocal desc="laugh"/> see I think Tangled is infinitely superior</u>
<u n="169" who="S0448"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0449">alright okay anything else?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0448">no</u>
<u n="172" who="S0449">so alright then</u>
<u n="173" who="S0448">okay</u>
<u n="174" who="S0449">have you spoken to nanna? I haven't seen her yet I haven't told her yet</u>
<u n="175" who="S0448">no I'm not gonna do it</u>
<u n="176" who="S0449">alright I didn't know if you were fostering at all</u>
<u n="177" who="S0448">what do you mean by fostering?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0449">you know you said you foster a little bit? have you actually contacted nan since you've been back?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0448">yeah I spoke to her literally like on the Wednesday when I was at the doctors but I just didn't tell her because I didn't wanna tell her because she'll she'll be caring too much and I didn't wanna tell her that's why you were meant to tell her</u>
<u n="180" who="S0449">oh fine</u>
<u n="181" who="S0448">and you're supposed to tell her that I know the rough graduation dates now</u>
<u n="182" who="S0449">oh I forgot well I'll try and remember I'd better tell dad while I'm there have you told dad? not that he'll remember</u>
<u n="183" who="S0448">no I just presumed you'd actually be not useless enough to not tell everyone</u>
<u n="184" who="S0449">I haven't seen anyone I've been so bad I haven't seen anyone lately</u>
<u n="185" who="S0448">you saw dad er like half an hour ago I was on the phone to him before you trying to find you and he said you'd been there</u>
<u n="186" who="S0449">oh yeah but you know I didn't think <unclear/> didn't I'll tell him tomorrow when we go to the theatre I'll give <unclear/> now I've got them now oh bugger oh what about looking at being a classroom assistant rather than going and working in the in the shop?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0448">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0449">just giving you you know just trying to sort of think a bit more I don't know I don't know if you're going to work somewhere like John Lewis or Waitrose don't have a degree and then bloody well go and waste it working in a shop</u>
<u n="189" who="S0448">I'm not</u>
<u n="190" who="S0449"><unclear/> just checking</u>
<u n="191" who="S0448">chicken?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0449">checking you're sort of <unclear/> and don't forget that thing twenty-ninth</u>
<u n="193" who="S0448">what thing? oh god what oh yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0449">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="195" who="S0448">okay</u>
<u n="196" who="S0449">gotta go I need the toilet</u>
<u n="197" who="S0448">okay</u>
<u n="198" who="S0449"><trunc>by</trunc></u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
