<text id="SFM7">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:26:39</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-02-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A pub, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Alphabets, drinking and alcohol, drugs, boxing, racism in football</topics>
		<activity>Alphabets, drinking and alcohol, drugs, boxing, racism in football</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0037">what's it like then that beer?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> well yeah it's like a sort of a strongish lager <pause dur="short"/> five point five</u>
<u n="3" who="S0037">it's pretty cheap though</u>
<u n="4" who="S0115">percent and it's <pause dur="short"/> quite a strong taste <pause dur="short"/> quite rich <pause dur="short"/> uh quite quite malty I suppose</u>
<u n="5" who="S0037">malty</u>
<u n="6" who="S0115">bit malty yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0037">ah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0115">got that sort of richness</u>
<u n="9" who="S0037" trans="overlap">hey what's that badge?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0115">sorry? Is that good or bad?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0037">oh Russia <pause dur="short"/> it's a Russian one <pause dur="short"/> no I said What's that badge?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah it's it's written in Russian script isn't it if you look there you've got the Russian B</u>
<u n="13" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so what's that  what's that  letter there?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0115">that's L</u>
<u n="15" who="S0037">that J? Is it attached to there?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0115">it <pause dur="short"/> yeah the it looks like J I but it's actually L <pause dur="short"/> like a lambda</u>
<u n="17" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="18" who="S0115">looks a bit like a lambda</u>
<u n="19" who="S0037">and then that H is an I?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0115">yeah that's right yeah that's a capital E sound yeah yeah so E</u>
<u n="21" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's really confusing like</u>
<u n="22" who="S0115" trans="overlap">K A the same <pause dur="short"/> b uh</u>
<u n="23" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that looks like a B</u>
<u n="24" who="S0115">it's confusing because there's another B in Russian</u>
<u n="25" who="S0037">is there?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0115">yeah which is which looks the same as our B but it's pronounced V</u>
<u n="27" who="S0037">like a capital B?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's pronounced V</u>
<u n="29" who="S0037">oh right</u>
<u n="30" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> t's the same obviously but some of the small letters are confusing as well</u>
<u n="31" who="S0037">I know there's the like some backwards don't they like? The backwards N?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah like</u>
<u n="33" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is it N it's N?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah like like a T is  T is  like a M when it's small I think</u>
<u n="35" who="S0037">mm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0115">the their their small T isn't like our small T</u>
<u n="37" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh so you mean the? Oh right</u>
<u n="38" who="S0115">lower case yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>e</trunc> yeah one that looks like a upside down M or W or something is is like Sh</u>
<u n="39" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0115">which looks like a W</u>
<u n="41" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0115">and then there's um Shch which has a sort of um</u>
<u n="43" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it looks good <pause dur="short"/> I think I like sort of my favourite one is like um Thai <pause dur="short"/> is it Thai with all the circles?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0115">oh um</u>
<u n="45" who="S0037">is it Thai or is it?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0115">Thai has uh circles and they look sort of like they're attached to they look like little tadpoles I suppose like sort of got strings attached to them</u>
<u n="47" who="S0037" trans="overlap">little what? Right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0115">so it looks somehow similar to tadpoles <pause dur="short"/> uh not exactly</u>
<u n="49" who="S0037">oh tadpoles? I thought you said something  I thought you said something  else <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="50" who="S0115">ah no um <pause dur="short"/> what you thought I said um</u>
<u n="51" who="S0037">yeah anyway so</u>
<u n="52" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no no no no <vocal desc="laugh"/> no <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> uh there is there's a lot of interesting <trunc>s</trunc> uh if you're a graphophile or whatever and you like <trunc>le</trunc> letters then there's a lot of systems out there like uh</u>
<u n="53" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0115">Thai's quite hard I think because it has letters that that don't have a sound like</u>
<u n="55" who="S0037">and Arabic as well like <pause dur="short"/> I think you know from that book that I bought you it's really hard like <pause dur="short"/> when like a tiny little  a tiny little  mark changes the whole thing?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0115">ah yeah well the <trunc>pr</trunc> the main problem with uh Arabic is that</u>
<u n="57" who="S0037" trans="overlap">dunno how you could get used to that</u>
<u n="58" who="S0115">one of the main problems with Arabic is that a lot of the vowels aren't written down</u>
<u n="59" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0115">uh and sometimes the vowels are symbolized with a tiny little uh underscore like</u>
<u n="61" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what I mean <pause dur="short"/> like a diacritic thing</u>
<u n="62" who="S0115"><trunc>Sub</trunc> superscript and subscript</u>
<u n="63" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0115">um and also Arabic has some confusion because the the start of the word and the end of the word and the middle of the word</u>
<u n="65" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0115">and <trunc>u</trunc> a separate on its own</u>
<u n="67" who="S0037">what d'you mean?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0115">all have different forms of the letter</u>
<u n="69" who="S0037">oh right right <pause dur="short"/> I see <pause dur="short"/> sign</u>
<u n="70" who="S0115" trans="overlap">A letter has <pause dur="short"/> a letter at the start of a word has a different shape from when it's at the end of a word</u>
<u n="71" who="S0037">I think it looks really nice <pause dur="short"/> I like the look of it</u>
<u n="72" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um and that also happens a bit in Hebrew as well <pause dur="short"/> which is</u>
<u n="73" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I do like the look of it but I dunno if I would ever be able to like understand it or anything</u>
<u n="74" who="S0115">arabic? No I don't think it's that it's not that bad it's not as hard as like um</u>
<u n="75" who="S0037">no I had a friend who went to uni</u>
<u n="76" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh it's not as hard as Thai I would've thought</u>
<u n="77" who="S0037">I had a friend who went to uni who'd done like <trunc>i</trunc> um French French A level and that was all and she went to uni to do Arabic</u>
<u n="78" who="S0115">yeah to become she ended up becoming working in the in diplomacy or something</u>
<u n="79" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like she's from <pause dur="short"/> she works in the <pause dur="short"/> she works in she's doing a PhD but I think she's worked in Congress and she's worked at the UN</u>
<u n="80" who="S0115">what American Congress?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she did an internship thing</u>
<u n="82" who="S0115">that's really <pause dur="short"/> that's quite good isn't it? Actually Liz has got a friend who uh <trunc>els</trunc> is uh works in diplomacy international relations doesn't she?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0037" trans="overlap">she's a bit of a high flyer <pause dur="short"/> oh has she?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="85" who="S0037">and also um <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? Her um friend she went travelling with works for the Foreign Office in <pause dur="short"/> can't remember where she is now but she was in Kazakhstan</u>
<u n="86" who="S0115">oh excellent <pause dur="short"/> um they got their script over there</u>
<u n="87" who="S0037">oh the Russian?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0115">cyrillic script</u>
<u n="89" who="S0037">so what do?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0115">but they don't speak a language related to Russian they speak their own <pause dur="short"/> kazakh</u>
<u n="91" who="S0037">ah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0115">the uh the drunk man's leaving <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what are them old fellas doing?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0115" trans="overlap">ay?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0037">what are you?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0115">well no I I just assumed he was drunk cos he's normally drunk when I see him <pause dur="short"/> he might actually not be drunk he may just a disease which causes the person to behave as if they're drunk</u>
<u n="97" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh that guy <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and that <pause dur="short"/> that would be so bad like if you had that</u>
<u n="98" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> cos like there are a few of them sorts of diseases uh like that affect the nervous system aren't there so</u>
<u n="99" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I know that like when me me Granda had a stroke and he sounded pissed all the time <pause dur="short"/> obviously he wasn't <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I'm sure he much would have much rather have been <pause dur="short"/> but he was like really slurring and sort of</u>
<u n="100" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah well no it's it's horrible to  it's horrible to  have your nervous system go isn't it it's the?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0037">I think it was because I think it wasn't like</u>
<u n="102" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0037">he didn't think any different he said like obviously once he was better he was saying like he still felt the same but he was it couldn't come out of his mouth like</u>
<u n="104" who="S0115">yeah it's horrible to feel like you're sort of trapped like that like um</u>
<u n="105" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> must be really scary</u>
<u n="106" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you can't uh</u>
<u n="107" who="S0037">like our neighbour <pause dur="short"/> me dad's next-door neighbour knocked on the door and me dad answered and she was like slurring and like just acting weird and <pause dur="short"/> like me dad thought at first that she was drunk but it turned out that she'd had a stroke</u>
<u n="108" who="S0115">was that in the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0037">it's in <anon type="place"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0115">ah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0037">must be really scary</u>
<u n="114" who="S0115">actually yeah cos I sometimes see them through the  see them through the  kitchen window sometimes</u>
<u n="115" who="S0037">oh yeah what's his <trunc>ca</trunc> what's he called? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the guy next door <pause dur="short"/> and he's like Well I've got a million pounds all the time <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Is he coming across as a bit sort of like</u>
<u n="117" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh he's quite annoying</u>
<u n="118" who="S0115">Boastful</u>
<u n="119" who="S0037">he really does like a burst sausage face</u>
<u n="120" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh no boastful and the face of a sausage <pause dur="short"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="121" who="S0037">sausage face yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that's not a good combo combination uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah and some of them diseases are pretty bad but <trunc>n</trunc> no I think that guy is actually drunk and that's why he's he's always in the pub <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="123" who="S0037">is he the one who like paints his nails?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0115">no that's a different one <pause dur="short"/> actually he's left his coat so I think he's coming back</u>
<u n="125" who="S0037">oh right</u>
<u n="126" who="S0115"><unclear/> coat <pause dur="short"/> but uh</u>
<u n="127" who="S0037">maybe we come here too often if we're like that guy</u>
<u n="128" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he <pause dur="short"/> oh well I know  I know  a few of the I mean I don't really <pause dur="short"/> I don't don't <trunc>nor</trunc> I don't speak to the people <pause dur="short"/> apart from sometimes the bar <trunc>s</trunc> staff</u>
<u n="129" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0115">uh but uh yeah I do there are a few regulars that I know that come here obviously</u>
<u n="131" who="S0037">well you just see people don't you like it's the same anywhere you live you sort of get to see people</u>
<u n="132" who="S0115">yeah I mean <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="133" who="S0037">there was a few people I recognized in the shop this morning</u>
<u n="134" who="S0115">yeah from round the area I mean <pause dur="short"/> this sort of community is like it's a funny community cos you get the students don't you?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's a really weird mix though like <pause dur="short"/> so when I was  I was  in the shop this morning like buying some bread to have with me boiled egg <pause dur="short"/> and then like so in there at the same time there was like people buying croissants and like the Guardian and stuff and fresh <trunc>j</trunc> orange juice</u>
<u n="136" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and like people buying cans of <trunc>Stro</trunc> like Special Brew <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's like such a weird mix</u>
<u n="138" who="S0115">yeah um</u>
<u n="139" who="S0037">like tramps it's cos of that tramp shelter thing</u>
<u n="140" who="S0115">there's a  there's a  couple of uh them sorts of halfway houses or whatever local shelters</u>
<u n="141" who="S0037" trans="overlap">must be really weird like</u>
<u n="142" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="143" who="S0037">I just don't know how you could I mean I like beer and everything but I don't know how you could face like a a Special Brew at like what time was in there? Like ten AM or something</u>
<u n="144" who="S0115">well it's the sort of need for it isn't it the the uh dependency</u>
<u n="145" who="S0037">but I was reading somewhere that like that cheap</u>
<u n="146" who="S0115" trans="overlap">dependence on it</u>
<u n="147" who="S0037">I I don't mean like cheap booze like a in like you know deals on drinks or whatever I mean like serious like cheap really hard like that hard cider and like Frosty Joe's or whatever it's called and</u>
<u n="148" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Jack Jack Frost uh</u>
<u n="149" who="S0037" trans="overlap">D'you know what I mean White Lightening <trunc>Light</trunc> <trunc>Nigh</trunc> Lightening and that</u>
<u n="150" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh Frosty Jacks um</u>
<u n="151" who="S0037">frosty Jacks</u>
<u n="152" who="S0115">White Lightening and then obviously the like <trunc>T</trunc> Tenant's uh Super <trunc>ne</trunc> step past a can of that uh</u>
<u n="153" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and the Special Brews and the super all the super ones yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's true <pause dur="short"/> outside</u>
<u n="154" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so so I mean it's it's what is it like a pound a can or it's like nine percent or so?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0037">but I watched a it's awful like I watched a programme saying that like that's the biggest threat it's not like <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously if you're a tramp you're not gonna be like</u>
<u n="156" who="S0115">it's a terrible strain on the NHS isn't it?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0037">it well it is but I mean you're not <trunc>g</trunc> if you're a tramp you're not gonna be like Oh please can I have?</u>
<event desc="sound of drinkers in background"/>
<u n="158" who="S0037">what they doing?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0115">I'd like a Campari and soda <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0037">exactly <pause dur="short"/> you're not gonna be like A bottle of <trunc>c</trunc> bottle of your finest wine it's like What've you got? Like that Tudor Rose that's really strong <pause dur="short"/> it's like port <pause dur="short"/> like horrible</u>
<u n="161" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="162" who="S0037">but I watched a programme where they were like it was like a wet hostel so they were allowed to drink but they were basically these old fellas all basically dying</u>
<u n="163" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0037">like with alcohol poisoning and um just sitting there like <pause dur="short"/> just drinking and shaking and <pause dur="short"/> just so</u>
<u n="165" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yes cos they're locked in a cycle aren't they because they're</u>
<u n="166" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's like worse</u>
<u n="167" who="S0115" trans="overlap">if you if you're dependent on it and you've got <trunc>u</trunc> you've got um the shakes then</u>
<u n="168" who="S0037">people were saying it's it's worse than</u>
<u n="169" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh <trunc>y</trunc> you would need some alcohol but you obviously have to step don't you? You have to um <pause dur="short"/> you have to have some alcohol and gradually reduce it and you come off it like that</u>
<u n="170" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well the same <trunc>wi</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> well it's the same with coming off anything I suppose like</u>
<u n="171" who="S0115">it's it's difficult because then they would have the decision of whether to be teetotal or not</u>
<u n="172" who="S0037">but they that's the thing they can't some of them like</u>
<u n="173" who="S0115" trans="overlap">if they go back on it then</u>
<u n="174" who="S0037">it it knacks them like</u>
<u n="175" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah it can be a bit dangerous can't it yeah like <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0037" trans="overlap">if you've drank <trunc>f</trunc> if you've drank that much for that long</u>
<u n="177" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> if you've um been dependent on it like you would probably have to have some alcohol sometimes which runs the risk of you getting back addicted to it</u>
<u n="178" who="S0037">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0115">uh part of it is you've got to</u>
<u n="180" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think if you're that bad</u>
<u n="181" who="S0115">you've got to sort of be able to sober up for a bit</u>
<u n="182" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think if you're that bad you've you've gotta be like managed off it like <pause dur="short"/> you can't just stop</u>
<u n="183" who="S0115">yeah I mean it's just that discipline isn't it? And it's to do with self-control isn't it?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0037">Cos is that not what happened to Amy Winehouse like <pause dur="short"/> she stopped and then when she went back on it her body was just like And that's that like <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0115">I'm not exactly sure what happened with her but uh <pause dur="short"/> I think she was just a very big drinker and then</u>
<u n="186" who="S0037">it's such a shame though</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115">she probably got that died of alcohol poisoning but she <trunc>w</trunc> she had come off it hadn't she?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well but <pause dur="short"/> but what I was saying about</u>
<u n="189" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you can die of  you can die of  being off it as well cos the body  the body  uh is used to it and um</u>
<u n="190" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the shock? What's it called again? Thingybob tremens</u>
<u n="191" who="S0115">so it gets all and delirium tremens is the  is the  shakes</u>
<u n="192" who="S0037">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but but you get um</u>
<u n="194" who="S0037">but I was reading</u>
<u n="195" who="S0115">but because alcohol goes in goes into I think every cell in the body</u>
<u n="196" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0115">it goes it enters every single cell so every single cell all types of cells and obviously the nervous system the muscles</u>
<u n="198" who="S0037" trans="overlap">damaged</u>
<u n="199" who="S0115">all the cells are gonna be slightly altered in their uh behaviour by having alcohol in them so</u>
<u n="200" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I was reading a thing about <pause dur="short"/> the thing that I was um saying the it was an article I think <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what paper it was in but <pause dur="short"/> it was like saying that it's it's worse because it's more socially acceptable <pause dur="short"/> like if you saw like somebody on the street just like buying crack or what some drugs you would be like oh like that's really that's illegal isn't it?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You would go like oh wouldn't you? You'd be like oh dear <pause dur="short"/> I saw a man taking crack today it was very disappointing <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well no but <pause dur="short"/> no but you know what I mean? You <trunc>w</trunc> you would like would feel like you had to do something about it like you would tell the police or I dunno what you would do but <pause dur="short"/> d'you know what I mean but obviously if you saw someone just buying like cans of Special Brew or something then you would think like Aw poor him sort of thing but you wouldn't <pause dur="short"/> it hasn't got the same stigma has it that like taking drugs has</u>
<u n="203" who="S0115">no it's funny well it is a drug isn't it? It's a hard  it's a hard  drug it's it's a psychoactive drug isn't it so uh</u>
<u n="204" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think they should put the prices up of those like of well all in fact all beer really as much as I like it</u>
<u n="205" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah well <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's there's a lot of difficult ethical political issues aren't there because there's a rather large number of people in Britain who are addicted to alcohol or other drugs perhaps</u>
<u n="206" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115">and these people are in some sense being kept alive by by the state um and yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't they should I don't think it should be cheap  I don't think it should be cheap  and freely available like I don't think you should be able to buy those horrible bottles of like the really strong alcohol with <trunc>u</trunc> like pennies <pause dur="short"/> I think that's wrong</u>
<u n="209" who="S0115">well <pause dur="short"/> I think it's the there's also a problem in terms of the economy is actually there's a lot of money goes back into the economy from um sales of this stuff <pause dur="short"/> if you raise taxes I mean <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I know that <pause dur="short"/> but that's that's part of like a tension isn't it like if they put up the price of beer then</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115">well some of the other would've actually said that a better policy might be to legalize certain drugs because um it brings them in  it brings them in  to you can get tax revenue so it shrinks your black market and it possibly shrinks gang activity as well</u>
<u n="212" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no but does does it not like just move those people like who are vulnerable onto something else like?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115">I don't know if you change I they would change it because of that I mean <pause dur="short"/> well the the obviously <unclear/> marijuana if you  if you  legalize that in some <trunc>w</trunc> in some ways marijuana's softer than alcohol isn't it so?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037">well I <trunc>do</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115">I think if they legalized it more people would take it but that would mean that less people would take alcohol which would take alcohol money away from the uh</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly less <pause dur="short"/> pubs and clubs</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115">take alcohol money <pause dur="short"/> but you'd have to look at places where this has been implemented like</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115">Holland and uh and I think they've they've done it in uh they've done stuff in Portugal <unclear/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know but it's been <pause dur="short"/> but it's been like that in for a long time in Holland like <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>I</trunc> there hasn't been like a change has there?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115">no I think it is technically illegal but they just tolerate it <unclear/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0037">well actually when we were there were were they not changing it? I know they were changing it like I remember seeing signs in the shops saying that you couldn't buy magic mushrooms there <pause dur="short"/> but you previously could have or something <pause dur="short"/> in Holland</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh yeah I mean I don't really see why you would wanna ban magic mushrooms um</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="225" who="S0115">personally but that's <pause dur="short"/> they're kind of natural so it's it's not illegal to grow them cos they grow naturally <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> um yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but marijuana grows naturally and it's so they could grow that</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115" trans="overlap">not in  not in  England it doesn't</u>
<u n="228" who="S0037">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115">it requires uh like</u>
<u n="230" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah cultivation</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115">you know they have to</u>
<u n="232" who="S0037">get them UV lamps</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you see the programmes don't you? You see them with the whole house with like uh full plants a <trunc>ma</trunc> cannabis plants and like uh</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's crazy isn't it when they strip the everything out of the house</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115">they've gotta the the radiators then</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah yeah the UV lights</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115">uV lights and well also well infrared you know heat</u>
<u n="238" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> heat lamps yeah yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0115" trans="overlap">energy is needed um and you need to buy <trunc>f</trunc> the compost</u>
<u n="240" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0115">got to uh water them so I mean and they put like proper farmers you know proper like sprinklers and that</u>
<u n="242" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the irrigation systems yeah yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0115"><unclear/> It's all very well  very well  done you see</u>
<u n="244" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know I've seen them on those like police police things</u>
<u n="245" who="S0115" trans="overlap">legalization would bring a lot of it would shrink the black market for that cos there's a lot of money in uh cannabis as you know there's uh often often smell whiffs of it as I walk down round here in this uh student area like</u>
<u n="246" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's quite studenty</u>
<u n="247" who="S0115">um well I think it's uh I think it's it's not <trunc>da</trunc> really dangerous but like there is a problem if you smoke it obviously the like the health risk of smoking it</u>
<u n="248" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> but eating it I don't uh I don't personally see that's that dangerous</u>
<u n="250" who="S0037">well I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if I've made me mind up about it</u>
<u n="251" who="S0115">well compared to for example alcohol which is just notoriously uh dangerous and</u>
<u n="252" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0115">causes numerous accidents and massive strain on the NHS</u>
<u n="254" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's funny isn't it how like <pause dur="short"/> I suppose it's just evolved over time that one thing's acceptable and another isn't</u>
<u n="255" who="S0115">well it's funny I think think we've been drinking <trunc>alc</trunc> we've been drinking alcohol in this country I would imagine you know like from you know like since like Stonehenge</u>
<u n="256" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Cos people always drank beer haven't they? From the word go</u>
<u n="257" who="S0115">from the year dot <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> I imagine that the the ancient stone age people would probably</u>
<u n="258" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah small beer <pause dur="short"/> what was it called?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0115">well the <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>p</trunc> part of it is what we were saying before about about mushrooms is that they're that it's natural <pause dur="short"/> like uh</u>
<u n="260" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0115">alcohol <pause dur="short"/> like <trunc>f</trunc> rotten fruit naturally ferment cos the because the yeast yeasts live in the  yeasts live in the  air don't they naturally?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but all those other ones <pause dur="short"/> all those chemical ones though like MDMA and all them they are like they're manufactured aren't they?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0115">MDMA what is that uh?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0037">and like acid and E</u>
<u n="265" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><trunc>Me</trunc> <trunc>meth</trunc> methamphetamine like ecstasy and stuff</u>
<u n="266" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no MDM <pause dur="short"/> mDMA is is that not ecstasy?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0115">yeah <trunc>m</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> something uh something uh methyl amphetamine isn't it or methamphetamine which is a <trunc>sim</trunc> that's that's a similar one isn't it um crystal meth?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> crystal meth saw a horrible programme about that</u>
<u n="269" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> loads of addicts and that round American aren't there?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0115">I don't know about ecstasy I mean there was that thing wasn't there when there was uh a guy called Mr Nutt</u>
<u n="272" who="S0037">mr what?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0115"><trunc>Mis</trunc> <trunc>Mis</trunc> Mr Nutt <pause dur="short"/> I think he was a doctor actually so Dr Nutt</u>
<u n="274" who="S0037" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="275" who="S0115">and he uh and he said that ecstasy was less dangerous than horse riding</u>
<u n="276" who="S0037">oh</u>
<u n="277" who="S0115">and and um there was a massive  there was a massive  media storm about that and uh</u>
<u n="278" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know who that was <pause dur="short"/> he was on the <pause dur="short"/> he was on like the the the uh government panel for drug drug</u>
<u n="279" who="S0115" trans="overlap">government government <unclear/> and he got  he got  reprimanded for saying and uh <pause dur="short"/> but he's raised an uh interesting if that is true the fact that he you know the statement he made has raised more interesting ethical questions hasn't it</u>
<u n="280" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know but it doesn't do any good saying things like that <trunc>do</trunc> does it like?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0115">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> if it's more dangerous to ride a horse than take ecstasy then I'd think well what's the sort of?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but that not just mean that more people have died riding a horse than have done? That doesn't mean it's necessarily more dangerous</u>
<u n="283" who="S0115">I think it  I think it  does like</u>
<u n="284" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Cos you can't equate the number of people with <pause dur="short"/> can you?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh</u>
<u n="286" who="S0037">the amount of people that ride horses versus the amount of people who do drugs or whatever</u>
<u n="287" who="S0115">why not?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0037">I mean did he do that?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0115">it's like it's more dangerous to go like on a parachute it's more dangerous to go like um Formula 1 racing than it is for example to play uh to play chess</u>
<u n="290" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know I get his point he was saying <pause dur="short"/> oh I'd love to go on one of them rally things</u>
<u n="291" who="S0115">I think more people have died <trunc>f</trunc> Formula One racing got injured Formula One racing than than uh than playing chess</u>
<u n="292" who="S0037">well that's probably</u>
<u n="293" who="S0115">so therefore Formula One racing's more dangerous than than chess</u>
<u n="294" who="S0037" trans="overlap">dunno you could have some wild chess games <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0115">although you could  you could  have some like</u>
<u n="296" who="S0037" trans="overlap">extreme chess have you seen extreme ironing</u>
<u n="297" who="S0115">I've seen  I've seen  chess and boxing played together</u>
<u n="298" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh yeah when what was that on?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0115" trans="overlap">where which where you you use your brain and then you bash your brain</u>
<u n="300" who="S0037">what was that on?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0115">it was in Germany and I don't know what it was on but</u>
<u n="302" who="S0037">I saw something</u>
<u n="303" who="S0115">it was on  it was on  uh on the box and uh</u>
<u n="304" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I saw a similar thing actually yesterday I was watching a programme about the US Coast Guard in the Caribbean and like they're doing their training where they make them do all kinds of physical exertions <pause dur="short"/> and like fire these questions at them while they're like in these stress positions you know like holding things out like that or <pause dur="short"/> and like make them answer questions</u>
<u n="305" who="S0115" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="306" who="S0037">similar to like boxing chess</u>
<u n="307" who="S0115">that's um <trunc>s</trunc> just strange isn't it?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0037" trans="overlap">just crazy</u>
<u n="309" who="S0115">I watched a bit of boxing yesterday actually <pause dur="short"/> it was Chris Eubank's son um</u>
<u n="310" who="S0037">he's got such a funny lisp</u>
<u n="311" who="S0115">Chris Eubank Junior uh who looks quite similar to Chris Eubank <pause dur="short"/> and he narrowly defeated by like a fifty-six fifty-two something very close <pause dur="short"/> no fifty-eight fifty-six I think</u>
<u n="312" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0115">there was like two points in it <pause dur="short"/> narrowly defeated Chris Eubank</u>
<u n="314" who="S0037">Chris Eubank's funny isn't he? Did you see all that stuff on the news? Did you see it there? It was just on the TV</u>
<u n="315" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he's a strange  he's a strange  guy</u>
<u n="316" who="S0037">about what happened after that the other fight that was on? The that Russian fella</u>
<u n="317" who="S0115">oh yeah that was in the news wasn't it today um? Russian the the sort of <pause dur="short"/> you said like the English ones were being really behaved really in an uncivilized way <pause dur="short"/> and then like the Russian one had behaved much better and then the English one had then like the English one had you know got all  got all  boastful and <trunc>s</trunc> then he'd got beaten by the Russian one <unclear/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think I I sort of knew he was gonna get beat</u>
<u n="319" who="S0115">but then the used to be the two English ones actually started scrapping afterwards or something</u>
<u n="320" who="S0037" trans="overlap">David <pause dur="short"/> yeah so David Haye <pause dur="short"/> who's like <pause dur="short"/> he was the the one who um <pause dur="short"/> so he was <trunc>figh</trunc> the these two Russian fellas <pause dur="short"/> uh I can't remember what their names are they begin with a K they're brothers <pause dur="short"/> they're massive like absolutely men mountains you know what I mean like? Six foot five type you know total</u>
<u n="321" who="S0115">is it super heavyweight or?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0037">uh <pause dur="short"/> well just really big guys heavyweight I think <pause dur="short"/> and these two um and he one of  one of  them ones <trunc>Vladim</trunc> Vladimir well he was fighting David Haye and he was on um I saw him on the telly the Russian guy and he was just so nice like he was like Well you know it'll be a good fight and I'm looking forward to it and <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's funny isn't it? Mind you you can be  you can be  polite but evil can't you?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0037">well I think he was I mean he's obviously like a fighter so he's obviously used to like git punching people in the face and that but um</u>
<u n="325" who="S0115" trans="overlap">cold cold blooded <unclear/> person</u>
<u n="326" who="S0037">but but then the other guy <trunc>u</trunc> David Haye was like I'm gonna take him down I'm gonna beat the crap out of him <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna do this I'm gonna do that and like <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well it reminds me of uh</u>
<u n="328" who="S0037">and he just got totally sat down like in the fight</u>
<u n="329" who="S0115" trans="overlap">reminds me uh <trunc>Rick</trunc> Ricky Hatton yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0037"><trunc>E</trunc> exactly the same it lasted like</u>
<u n="331" who="S0115">although he was apparently <trunc>punch</trunc> fighting above his weight when he was like <unclear/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> but apparently it lasted like about one round and he'd just got totally like put on his arse by this</u>
<u n="333" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well I think that's just a cultural thing uh I think in Britain and maybe America too they expect</u>
<u n="334" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but anyway</u>
<u n="335" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they expect the boxers to to have this kind of like bravado sort of thing</u>
<u n="336" who="S0037">but anyway this other guy this other um</u>
<u n="337" who="S0115">like wrestling I suppose isn't it where wrestlers sort of insult each other and it seems to be rather choreographed doesn't it?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but it's not like <pause dur="short"/> but it's really I think it's bad for the sport like <pause dur="short"/> people are trying to just you know if you can call it a sport <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's debatable as to whether punching people in the face is truly something that we wanna be encouraging but um I think it's bad like it's really <pause dur="short"/> You know it's like when you see in a football match there's people scrapping in the tunnel and stuff like <pause dur="short"/> they shouldn't be doing that <pause dur="short"/> You know</u>
<u n="339" who="S0115">they shouldn't uh it it it's well it is it's making them like cos they say that boxing is supposed to provide discipline isn't it to to sort of people on the street uh who might otherwise be getting dragged down into crime and general general ridiculous behaviour</u>
<u n="340" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well he bottled him <pause dur="short"/> anyway this is what I was coming up to <pause dur="short"/> so David Haye like punched this other guy in the face while he had a bottle in his hand like that's just I mean he's a boxer why does he need to do that?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0115"><unclear/> the <trunc>bo</trunc> the the puncher had a bottle? David Haye had a bottle in his hand?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0037">so there's two two separate  two separate  English guys fought these two brothers on two separate occasions</u>
<u n="343" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0037">one of the occasions was last night when <pause dur="short"/> this other guy who's not <trunc>Dav</trunc> I I should learn the names cos obviously this is a really complicated story <pause dur="short"/> the other guy who's not David Haye fought him and lost on points <pause dur="short"/> but David Haye was there <pause dur="short"/> david Haye took exception to this British guy <pause dur="short"/> so nothing to do with these two Russians any more</u>
<u n="345" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0037">and went for him and punched him in the face <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="347" who="S0115">bit strange innit? It's like you don't think it's choreographed?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0037">and then this other British guy said he's gonna shoot him <pause dur="short"/> like who says those sort of things? Then two Russians were like We've we don't wanna have any more fights with British guys like we've had enough <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0115">so what happened to the discipline? I mean cos some of them like Amir Khan um</u>
<u n="350" who="S0037">I mean I don't know that much about boxing except for Tony Jeffries obviously</u>
<u n="351" who="S0115">Amir Kahn seems to be reasonably reasonably well behaved doesn't he?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> but uh no it's a bit it is a bit bad when sports people behave like that isn't it the sort of behave in a really sort of uncivilized way?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think it's bad like <pause dur="short"/> it <pause dur="short"/> like that thing as well on um the at the Man U match like when like he wouldn't shake Everett's hand <pause dur="short"/> everett wouldn't shake thingybob's hand</u>
<u n="355" who="S0115">who wouldn't shake whose hand?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0037">so um <pause dur="short"/> I'm terrible at remembering details so like there was a Man Man U</u>
<u n="357" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no you're not you're really good at remembering foods and uh parts of the body <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="358" who="S0037">that's me specialist subject</u>
<u n="359" who="S0115">anatomy and anatomy and food terms</u>
<u n="360" who="S0037">but that's that's cos I like eating <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like pancetta <pause dur="short"/> I always forget what pancetta is <pause dur="short"/> I think it's bacon isn't it?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's like a</u>
<u n="363" who="S0115">I've remembered that but <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0037">no no <pause dur="short"/> so um <pause dur="short"/> man U's got this um player who's black and then um a few months ago I can't remember who they were playing <pause dur="short"/> anyway this one guy um racially abused him <pause dur="short"/> was reported and he was fined and he was banned</u>
<u n="365" who="S0115">there's a lot of that in like <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0037">he was banned for however many months <pause dur="short"/> anyway last week was the the first match that he had back after his ban and they were playing Man U again <pause dur="short"/> and they went down the line you know when they shake hands <pause dur="short"/> and the black  the black  guy had his hand out like that to shake his and he just went like that and wouldn't shake his hand <pause dur="short"/> and then the guy grabbed him as if to say What are you doing? Like Shake my hand and then he wouldn't <pause dur="short"/> so like</u>
<u n="367" who="S0115">what was that one's name again the one who wouldn't shake his hand?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> one of them's called Everett and I can't remember which one which one's which <pause dur="short"/> I think Everett's the</u>
<u n="369" who="S0115" trans="overlap">isn't Everett? Isn't that one? Isn't um one of them like notoriously bad like thugs or something or is that someone else?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0037">I don't know but</u>
<u n="371" who="S0115">like two brothers like</u>
<u n="372" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="373" who="S0115">the brother was like in prison and</u>
<u n="374" who="S0037">I don't know</u>
<u n="375" who="S0115">did he use to play for Newcastle? <trunc>Bat</trunc> Batty</u>
<u n="376" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><trunc>Bar</trunc> Barton</u>
<u n="377" who="S0115"><trunc>Bar</trunc> Barton</u>
<u n="378" who="S0037">yeah he's horrible</u>
<u n="379" who="S0115">they're their family's like they've got a just a</u>
<u n="380" who="S0037">they're chavs</u>
<u n="381" who="S0115">just a bad family haven't they? Wrong 'uns</u>
<u n="382" who="S0037">ah <pause dur="short"/> no but <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> they are wrong 'uns but uh</u>
<u n="383" who="S0115">wrong 'uns</u>
<u n="384" who="S0037">no but this was really bad cos like it's a really bad message</u>
<u n="385" who="S0115">it's it's it's a <trunc>pr</trunc> there has been a bit of that hasn't there like with the <trunc>f</trunc> the racial abuse so the like the John Terry one's quite quite well known here uh</u>
<u n="386" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0115">bit of uh</u>
<u n="388" who="S0037">bit of singing</u>
<u n="389" who="S0115">action over there</u>
<u n="390" who="S0037">I was reading something in in the uh paper this morning where they were saying like on the subject of like racism and football <pause dur="short"/> under some like committee you know Association For Not Being Racist And Homophobic In Football that's not its name obviously</u>
<u n="391" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> and they'd like sent out loads of information to all the Premier all the clubs in the top three divisions in the UK like saying um This is what you can do <pause dur="short"/> here are some ideas about how to prevent racism and homophobia and only six clubs had replied to them saying like Yeah we'll do it <pause dur="short"/> Like</u>
<u n="393" who="S0115">right</u>
<u n="394" who="S0037">I mean people just aren't <pause dur="short"/> like they're not really tackling it so</u>
<u n="395" who="S0115">yeah the I mean there are some the football's always been an area some of the unpleasant parts of society sometimes uh you know</u>
<u n="396" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="397" who="S0115">rear their head like in the the crowd <pause dur="short"/> obviously hooliganism and violence <pause dur="short"/> organized fights uh</u>
<u n="398" who="S0037">just so stupid</u>
<u n="399" who="S0115">obviously various uh extreme uh opinions such as dislike of gays or dislike of women or dislike of uh people with different skin colour and stuff like that in football</u>
<u n="400" who="S0037">it's just stupid isn't it? I can't understand it at all</u>
<u n="401" who="S0115">but uh at least I think it's improving though <pause dur="short"/> but I think it's worse in other countries isn't it like uh?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0115">I think think we <trunc>Bri</trunc> Britain's better than I think perhaps some of the ones where I dunno if there's many players with darker skin</u>
<u n="404" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0115">and <trunc>there</trunc> therefore if they see someone with dark skin they would shout various abuse at that person like sort of happened in one of the games we watched last week actually in <pause dur="short"/> was it the Spain one? With <trunc>Portu</trunc> Porto</u>
<u n="406" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> they were shouting abuse at like um the uh in uh players from uh <pause dur="short"/> who was it who played Porto last week?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0037">I dunno I'm terrible</u>
<u n="409" who="S0115">hold on <pause dur="short"/> was it Man City? Did they beat them?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0037">oh yeah that's right</u>
<u n="411" who="S0115">they beat them Uh we watched obviously we watched Arsenal and Inter Milan which was <pause dur="short"/> a C Milan which was uh</u>
<u n="412" who="S0037">that was a good match</u>
<u n="413" who="S0115">which was a really great match uh <pause dur="short"/> milan was like the performance was really really good</u>
<u n="414" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I knew Sunderland would win you know <pause dur="short"/> I knew they would</u>
<u n="415" who="S0115">I mean um</u>
<u n="416" who="S0037">I really thought that they would win</u>
<u n="417" who="S0115">but yeah that game was between Sunderland and Arsenal was a result but I mean <trunc>v</trunc> but very bad if you're an Arsenal because of the the sort of lacklustre that that Arsenal did they often advanced by passing backwards</u>
<u n="418" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0115">uh which is like something that um</u>
<u n="420" who="S0037">I I really thought they would win</u>
<u n="421" who="S0115">but often the passing you know right back to the defenders and the goalkeeper um</u>
<u n="422" who="S0037">maybe they can win the whole cup that'd be good</u>
<u n="423" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah course they said there's a statistic wasn't there um <pause dur="short"/> might go to the</u>
<u n="424" who="S0037">okay I'm alright I don't want one but <pause dur="short"/> shall we press pause?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0115">bar if you want one uh <pause dur="short"/> oh good idea</u>
</body>
</text>
