<text id="SFP5">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:35</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-11</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0024 S0144</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>The countryside, Norfolk</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Countryside, economics, wildlife, graveyards</topics>
		<activity>Couple take a walk and have a chat in the countryside.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T20</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0024">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>28</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0144">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Norwich, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0144">what? So that one there used to be the post office?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0024">this one <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's erm <pause dur="short"/> oh I think it's this one <pause dur="short"/> hang on</u>
<u n="3" who="S0144">yeah well it's called The Old Post Office <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0144">yeah it looks like an old</u>
<u n="6" who="S0024" trans="overlap">right in the middle of this little tiny village there used to be an old post office there</u>
<u n="7" who="S0144">what? That used to be there when you lived here?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0024">yeah I think so <pause dur="short"/> well now you <pause dur="short"/> only when I was little I don't really remember</u>
<u n="9" who="S0144">but that must have been servicing only</u>
<u n="10" who="S0024">only these house <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> thirty</u>
<u n="11" who="S0144">wow <pause dur="short"/> thirty odd houses</u>
<u n="12" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I don't know how many <unclear/> But that's how it was wasn't it before <pause dur="short"/> like you used to have all of the</u>
<u n="13" who="S0144">well you did there used to be a police station as well?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0024" trans="overlap">they've still a telephone box look</u>
<u n="15" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0024">that's surprising because like do you remember when we went to <anon type="place"/> and we were looking are we had no no batteries on our telephones</u>
<u n="17" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah and all the phones have gone now haven't they</u>
<u n="18" who="S0024" trans="overlap">erm and we couldn't find a telephone box anywhere and we ended up walking all that way in the rain <pause dur="short"/> and we couldn't hire a taxi could we <pause dur="short"/> couldn't flag down a taxi</u>
<u n="19" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> cos you can't flag them down anymore you have to book them over the phone</u>
<u n="20" who="S0024" trans="overlap">and we didn't know <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> we didn't realise that did we</u>
<u n="21" who="S0144">hmm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> yeah I wonder if it will go round again that these places start opening</u>
<u n="22" who="S0024">well they can't they're residential now <pause dur="short"/> I think it is</u>
<u n="23" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but where was it we were a couple of months ago when we first got back and I think it was in London somewhere in the suburbs <pause dur="short"/> remember? In near Kingston somewhere around there</u>
<u n="24" who="S0024">what?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0144">and we went into town looking for a post office <pause dur="short"/> it was quite a big town but they didn't have a single post office and it was in</u>
<u n="26" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> look at that yellow bird <pause dur="short"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> yeah no they they only had it in er WH Smiths</u>
<u n="27" who="S0144">in WH Smiths <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what was that?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0144">what colour was it?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0024">it was bright yellow</u>
<u n="31" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="32" who="S0024" trans="overlap">what's a bright yellow bird?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0144">erm it could've been a greenfinch <pause dur="short"/> maybe a yellowhammer</u>
<u n="34" who="S0024">it was really pretty I've never seen that one before</u>
<u n="35" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0024">well I probably have seen it</u>
<u n="37" who="S0144">yeah there's lots of beautiful birds down here</u>
<u n="38" who="S0024">but yeah it's really sad about the post office <unclear/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0144">hmm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0024">they keep trying all those different ideas don't they but it's not <pause dur="short"/> like all those different weighting of the packages and things like that but it doesn't really</u>
<u n="41" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's sad <pause dur="short"/> I hope <pause dur="short"/> I'd love <pause dur="short"/> who was saying the other day like you know like we always talked about the era of Pisces and like how this <pause dur="short"/> I know  not like  not like er astronomy astrology type stuff that that other other big massive era like from Jesus' Jesus' <unclear/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well the age <pause dur="short"/> it was the age of Pisces yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0024" trans="overlap">Jesus started the the Pisces and that's why there's so many fish in the bible and stuff like that</u>
<u n="45" who="S0144">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0024">and because of the the way that the earth is twisted or something and now it's kind of going into the era or age of Aquarius</u>
<u n="47" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0024">and that's when <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="49" who="S0144">this is the dawning of the age of Aquarius</u>
<u n="50" who="S0024">but they said that's when people start to realise going back to their roots and living off the land again</u>
<u n="51" who="S0144">yeah I don't believe any of that</u>
<u n="52" who="S0024">no but mm it's difficult isn't it? You can see that it's happening but people kind of fit the story  to the  to the happenings not <unclear/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> well it's happening  it's happening  here <pause dur="short"/> it's not happening in the rest of the world</u>
<u n="54" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's happening here because people are getting fed up</u>
<u n="55" who="S0144" trans="overlap">but that's  but that's  also why people are saying it's going to be like the end of the word in two thousand and twelve because of the end of the Mayan calendar <pause dur="short"/> they weren't saying it's going to be the end of the astrological age where we're going to be moving into Pisces into Aquarius</u>
<u n="56" who="S0024" trans="overlap">end of the age <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I still think it's going to be a weird year <pause dur="short"/> mind you we're a third of the way through the year now and we thought it was going to be such a weird year</u>
<u n="57" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I still think it will be <pause dur="short"/> it's the economy has gone really quiet for a few months hasn't it <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="58" who="S0024" trans="overlap">it's the end <pause dur="short"/> and  they keep  they keep doing all this on the in the government like erm I don't know <pause dur="short"/> say trying to get all these companies to pay out money and stuff like that</u>
<u n="59" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0024">and like you said it's it could just be almost like a trap for the public to go ah great they're doing something <pause dur="short"/> oh great you know they're getting some money back for the poor people</u>
<u n="61" who="S0144">yeah yeah we said that</u>
<u n="62" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but in the whole big picture hmm I don't know <pause dur="short"/> is that what you were saying the other day?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0144">hmm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's just gone quiet <pause dur="short"/> there must be a lot of stuff going on behind the scenes</u>
<u n="64" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty round here isn't it</u>
<u n="65" who="S0144">it's lovely <pause dur="short"/> there's not many animals around here though is there?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0024">no it's cos there's not much</u>
<u n="67" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I mean that's just a big field <pause dur="short"/> what are they doing with it? It's very</u>
<u n="68" who="S0024">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it looks like <pause dur="short"/> I mean is that meadow land? Is that what they classify as meadow land?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0144">I don't know it looks like a</u>
<u n="70" who="S0024">it's just a nothing</u>
<u n="71" who="S0144">but it's so flat</u>
<u n="72" who="S0024">it can't be meadow land because there would be flowers starting to grow <pause dur="short"/> it's just grass</u>
<u n="73" who="S0144">no they've cut the grass</u>
<u n="74" who="S0024">that's not part of the golf course is it?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="76" who="S0024">maybe it is</u>
<u n="77" who="S0144">or maybe they bought it</u>
<u n="78" who="S0024">it could be part of the golf course cos <unclear/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it doesn't link up though <pause dur="short"/> where is the golf course?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0024">over there <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I'm confused</u>
<u n="81" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what that it but they're keeping it though aren't they <pause dur="short"/> haven't just let it go</u>
<u n="82" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><unclear/> looks like they've treated the land and only let the grass grow and stuff</u>
<u n="83" who="S0144">yeah there's no weeds on it is there</u>
<u n="84" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> I mean look look at that edge line and then it goes down into the ditch and all sorts grows</u>
<u n="85" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0024">I wonder</u>
<u n="87" who="S0144">hmm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0024">that would be nice land for a house</u>
<u n="89" who="S0144">huh</u>
<u n="90" who="S0024">but it's just so flat around here <pause dur="short"/> that's why there's no animals you know <pause dur="short"/> well there is lots of animals obviously but</u>
<u n="91" who="S0144">right <pause dur="short"/> what? Animals don't like?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> no but you know <pause dur="short"/> it's so flat you can't even see an animal <unclear/> there</u>
<u n="93" who="S0144" trans="overlap">right okay</u>
<u n="94" who="S0024">it's only when you get to the trees that you get the birds and a few bunnies hopping about</u>
<u n="95" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah but <anon type="place"/>'s about the sky though isn't it <pause dur="short"/> I mean look at the sky man</u>
<u n="96" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I know it's beautiful</u>
<u n="97" who="S0144">it's got such a big sky <pause dur="short"/> it's beautiful</u>
<u n="98" who="S0024" trans="overlap">look at that blue over there</u>
<u n="99" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0024">it's really pretty</u>
<u n="101" who="S0144">huh <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's what I like about <anon type="place"/> the most is the sky</u>
<u n="102" who="S0024" trans="overlap">sky yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0144">apart from when all the American jets are flying around it</u>
<u n="104" who="S0024">well it is a problem now <pause dur="short"/> I can't believe that <pause dur="short"/> see</u>
<u n="105" who="S0144">so many isn't there</u>
<u n="106" who="S0024">I still don't remember that from when I was growing up</u>
<u n="107" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="108" who="S0024">I don't remember it <pause dur="short"/> and dad said to me that they've always been flying about</u>
<u n="109" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0024">I mean there's periods of time when they up their training</u>
<u n="111" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0024">and especially now they've upped all their training haven't they?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0024">they're just all over the place</u>
<u n="115" who="S0144">huh</u>
<u n="116" who="S0024">but still I don't remember all those jets especially how low they go over my house <pause dur="short"/> I don't remember that at all</u>
<u n="117" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well a <trunc>heli</trunc> was it last week a helicopter crashed into a pylon or something?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0024">yeah I think they covered that up quite a lot because I never saw it on that should have been national news</u>
<u n="119" who="S0144" trans="overlap">huh <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0024">I don't remember <trunc>see</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I think I missed the news that particular day but you would've thought they'd have said the story again</u>
<u n="121" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well I don't think it crashed crashed <pause dur="short"/> it hit a pylon and then had to land <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't</u>
<u n="122" who="S0024">oh really?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0144">yeah it didn't like burst into flames or anything like that <pause dur="short"/> do you think there's any farms around here that sell erm straw bales that we could use in the party as seats and stuff</u>
<u n="124" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> no because erm <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>he knows all of the farmers around here and they don't do them any more <pause dur="short"/> they only do the big big ones</u>
<u n="125" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> it's a shame isn't it</u>
<u n="126" who="S0024">so we'll be lucky <pause dur="short"/> I went passed some farms <pause dur="short"/> when was? Where were we? Oh we were in the car yesterday think it was <pause dur="short"/> I was looking in all the farms and they only had those big massive straw circular bales</u>
<u n="127" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0024">that's the way they're going cos it's easier for them</u>
<u n="129" who="S0144" trans="overlap">huh <pause dur="short"/> what have they got in there? Are they pheasant? Oh it's chickens</u>
<u n="130" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><unclear/> no it's chickens <pause dur="short"/> sounds er ah it's pretty <pause dur="short"/> have we ever walked down there</u>
<u n="131" who="S0144">no it says no through road there</u>
<u n="132" who="S0024">there might be a footpath though at the other end or something</u>
<u n="133" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0024">somewhere around here there's that secret church in the middle of the of erm some land and there is <unclear/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0144" trans="overlap">wow look at that peacock</u>
<u n="136" who="S0024">where?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0144">that's <trunc>b</trunc> wow that's beautiful</u>
<u n="138" who="S0024" trans="overlap">wow <pause dur="short"/> look at that <pause dur="short"/> hello <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know they had peacocks here <pause dur="short"/> who lives here?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> don't know <pause dur="short"/> have they just got one or is there?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0024">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> don't go away</u>
<u n="141" who="S0144">God he's beautiful isn't he</u>
<u n="142" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> he's got a nice bit of land there</u>
<u n="143" who="S0144">mm <pause dur="short"/> remember in erm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0024"><unclear/> picnic table look <pause dur="short"/> go and sit with the peacock</u>
<u n="145" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's nice isn't it</u>
<u n="146" who="S0024"><unclear/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0144">do you remember in where were we in Nepal? We went to that national park and there was that big peacock doing the display</u>
<u n="148" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that was fantastic <pause dur="short"/> that was in the middle of the road wasn't it?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0024">well not road <pause dur="short"/> track or whatever</u>
<u n="151" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0024">yeah that was fantastic to see that <pause dur="short"/> cos those types of things you only usually see on the TV don't you?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0024">I should think well you've got a peacock</u>
<u n="155" who="S0144">they've got quite a lot of land haven't they?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0024">yeah who lives there?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0144">huh</u>
<u n="158" who="S0024">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> they've got quite a lot of bird boxes and stuff <pause dur="short"/> I wonder if they're making an aviary or something?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> did erm did your dad get an owl?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I'm starting to feel a bit nosey</u>
<u n="161" who="S0144">you are nosey</u>
<u n="162" who="S0024">no I'm not I'm not I'm just looking</u>
<u n="163" who="S0144">did your dad get an owl in that owl box he made?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> he got some other animals <pause dur="short"/> but you do hear the erm is it the tawny owl?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0024">sometimes I hear the tawny owl at night</u>
<u n="167" who="S0144">well which one is it that goes twit-twoo?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0024">yeah that's I think that's the <pause dur="short"/> ah I've got to get it right</u>
<u n="169" who="S0144">Cos it's only one owl that does that <pause dur="short"/> all the others go <event desc="sound of screeching"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0024">yeah but it's two owls</u>
<u n="171" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0024">the male goes twit and the female replies twoo</u>
<u n="173" who="S0144">oh really?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so they're actually talking to each other <pause dur="short"/> it's not one owl going twit-twoo twit-twoo <pause dur="short"/> it's like one going twit and the other one goes twoo <pause dur="short"/> and if you listen really carefully sometimes the male calls and the female doesn't reply <pause dur="short"/> at the beginning of the it if in the evening when they first start it <pause dur="short"/> it's like a mating thing?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0144" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> what he goes twit <pause dur="short"/> who? Me? That's why she doesn't reply</u>
<u n="176" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0144">that's why she doesn't reply</u>
<u n="178" who="S0024">I'm not a twit</u>
<u n="179" who="S0144">he needs to work on his chat up lines</u>
<u n="180" who="S0024">I'm not a twit <pause dur="short"/> who's calling me a twit</u>
<u n="181" who="S0144">look at those daffodils coming up</u>
<u n="182" who="S0024">mm lovely</u>
<u n="183" who="S0144">there's hundreds of them</u>
<u n="184" who="S0024">beautiful <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> that's a lovely house actually they've got little port holes on the sides and everything</u>
<u n="185" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="186" who="S0024">hmm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0144">so that must have been there originally because the planning permission <pause dur="short"/> oh no look they haven't been allowed a window in that that wall either</u>
<u n="188" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="189" who="S0144">they've got those tiny little round ones <pause dur="short"/> hmm <pause dur="short"/> hiya <pause dur="short"/> yeah beautiful day</u>
<u n="190" who="S0024" trans="overlap">you know even though you know we were walking around and we kept doing that boring walk I think <pause dur="short"/> that was our problem</u>
<u n="191" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0024">kept doing that boring walk and we we're like I don't want to live around here</u>
<u n="193" who="S0144" trans="overlap">watch out there's a car coming</u>
<u n="194" who="S0024">I don't want to live around here cos it's so flat and every corner looks the same <pause dur="short"/> and even when your dad was driving us home I almost got lost because every road did basically look the same <pause dur="short"/> it's a field</u>
<u n="195" who="S0144">it does <pause dur="short"/> they all look <pause dur="short"/> and cos it's all flat and it's all the same trees <pause dur="short"/> you've you've got no landmarks or anything</u>
<u n="196" who="S0024">well that's the thing but like dad driving around he would recognize every single tree</u>
<u n="197" who="S0144">oh yeah well he's been here for donkey's years</u>
<u n="198" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah but I grew <pause dur="short"/> I've lived here <pause dur="short"/> I grew up here <pause dur="short"/> I should recognize the trees but I don't</u>
<u n="199" who="S0144">yeah well you've been away for what fifteen years though pretty much <pause dur="short"/> god it's like the M25 here <pause dur="short"/> bloody hell</u>
<u n="200" who="S0024"><unclear/> wow he was going a bit wasn't he?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0144">huh <pause dur="short"/> have they still er they have still got all the school buses around here haven't they?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0024">er yeah it only drops off in that one place <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't come through here</u>
<u n="203" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0024">it it drops off in <anon type="place"/> by the church and it drops off at the crossroads by our house</u>
<u n="205" who="S0144">hmm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0024">and then it goes on to <anon type="place"/> you see</u>
<u n="207" who="S0144">right <pause dur="short"/> see look at all these hedges how they've chopped them all back <pause dur="short"/> they look like pretty old ones</u>
<u n="208" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0144">Cos they've been erm where was that? They've been planting so many hedgerows now and they're giving them money aren't they to plant them</u>
<u n="210" who="S0024">are they?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0144">yeah they all ripped them up and now they are putting them back again because</u>
<u n="212" who="S0024">because of the wildlife <pause dur="short"/> the lost all of the wildlife</u>
<u n="213" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah because of the wildlife but they they get paid for each each piece they put in</u>
<u n="214" who="S0024" trans="overlap">whose field is that?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0144">I don't know</u>
<u n="216" who="S0024">they all look so empty but I guess that's just because the crops haven't grown yet</u>
<u n="217" who="S0144">well it's winter isn't it <pause dur="short"/> I suppose</u>
<u n="218" who="S0024">well it's spring now</u>
<u n="219" who="S0144">well nearly <pause dur="short"/> when does spring start?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0024">I think it starts Mothers' Day so it start doesn't it?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh shit it's Mothers' Day tomorrow</u>
<u n="222" who="S0024">oh no <pause dur="short"/> not tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> saturday and we're too late for the postman</u>
<u n="223" who="S0144">well it's Saturday tomorrow</u>
<u n="224" who="S0024">ah yeah I know but  we could  we could have done first class <pause dur="short"/> that was what we were supposed to do <pause dur="short"/> we promised that we would do it <pause dur="short"/> first class stamp</u>
<u n="225" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh bollocks <pause dur="short"/> yeah <trunc>sh</trunc></u>
<u n="226" who="S0024">every time</u>
<u n="227" who="S0144">erm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0024">I <trunc>re</trunc> see that's when I could do with one of those fancy phones that give me an alarm of what to do</u>
<u n="229" who="S0144">huh</u>
<u n="230" who="S0024">I can set alarms on my my phone</u>
<u n="231" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well we did remember we were talking about it the other day</u>
<u n="232" who="S0024">yesterday <pause dur="short"/> I said we have to send a letter in the morning tomorrow and we said yeah no problem</u>
<u n="233" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0024">oh your mum must be so sad</u>
<u n="235" who="S0144">well</u>
<u n="236" who="S0024">she never gets anything on time</u>
<u n="237" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah she does <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="238" who="S0024">not on time</u>
<u n="239" who="S0144">well if I phone her then at least I'll have a chat with her <pause dur="short"/> she'll keep me on the phone for about three hours</u>
<u n="240" who="S0024">yeah but it's just that some people <pause dur="short"/> they love <pause dur="short"/> even I realised when last year when we were</u>
<u n="241" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh car <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> stuck</u>
<u n="242" who="S0024" trans="overlap">ah I can't get up from the road <pause dur="short"/> last year in Tunisia <pause dur="short"/> that's Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> that's Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> who knows all the farmers</u>
<u n="243" who="S0144">oh is it?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0024">I should have stopped him really</u>
<u n="245" who="S0144">alright Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> do you you know anyone with some hay bales?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0024">huh</u>
<u n="247" who="S0144">was that a good <anon type="place"/> accent?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> it was rubbish</u>
<u n="249" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I need to work on it don't I</u>
<u n="250" who="S0024">yeah what was I saying anyway? A er no lost it</u>
<u n="251" who="S0144">er Mothers' Day <pause dur="short"/> er I don't know <pause dur="short"/> well I'll phone her in the morning anyway so</u>
<u n="252" who="S0024">I know</u>
<u n="253" who="S0144">what?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0024">we could do that erm thingy cards</u>
<u n="255" who="S0144">moon Pig</u>
<u n="256" who="S0024">yeah maybe <pause dur="short"/> if we do it straight away when we get home if it's before five o'clock it might well get there</u>
<u n="257" who="S0144">what for Mothers' Day when?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0024">tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> yeah if it's before five o'clock it might do it</u>
<u n="259" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah? Okay</u>
<u n="260" who="S0024">yeah let's do it <pause dur="short"/> I'd rather</u>
<u n="261" who="S0144">alright <pause dur="short"/> we'll do that when we get back then</u>
<u n="262" who="S0024">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what I was saying <pause dur="short"/> last year because we were away and not many people had our address and stuff</u>
<u n="263" who="S0144">do you want to go and have a look at the church?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos we were away and not not many people had our address and those that did <pause dur="short"/> well my and the Tunisian post <pause dur="short"/> ah how rubbish was the Tunisian post</u>
<u n="265" who="S0144">well it's</u>
<u n="266" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I really felt it because I didn't get a card at all</u>
<u n="267" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0024">Cos I didn't get any did I</u>
<u n="269" who="S0144">no the customs all nicked it</u>
<u n="270" who="S0024">yeah but you know I think with people <pause dur="short"/> some people love that stuff don't they <pause dur="short"/> getting just a little card</u>
<u n="271" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> how do we get in here? Are we allowed in here?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0024">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0144">must be allowed in</u>
<u n="274" who="S0024">yeah cos if you go round by the hall <unclear/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0144">oh yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0024">yeah yeah round here</u>
<u n="277" who="S0144">that's where your dad had his party isn't it?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and over there <pause dur="short"/> the last time you went over there past the gravestones that had that someone had made a big archway in the trees</u>
<u n="280" who="S0024">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0144">is that still there?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0024">yeah it should be still there <pause dur="short"/> look at these <pause dur="short"/> these are so ancient <pause dur="short"/> eighteen seventy-six</u>
<u n="283" who="S0144">see that eighteen seventy-six and he was seventy-one years old <pause dur="short"/> that's not bad is it?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0024">no that's not bad at all really <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="285" who="S0144">quite surprised by that actually <pause dur="short"/> I thought they died a lot longer younger</u>
<u n="286" who="S0024">no that's living quite long <pause dur="short"/> look how look how beautiful they used to make their stones look</u>
<u n="287" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0024">that one joined to it <pause dur="short"/> is that er?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0144">it must be husband and wife is it?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah that's the wife look</u>
<u n="291" who="S0144">huh</u>
<u n="292" who="S0024">ah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0144">and that's such a beautiful erm spire</u>
<u n="294" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh look there's another <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> family <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0144">oh we're standing on the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0024">oh and there's another one <pause dur="short"/> wow <pause dur="short"/> that's that must they must have been a prominent family here</u>
<u n="297" who="S0144">yep</u>
<u n="298" who="S0024"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0144">well people used to get buried all together didn't they but people can't do it anymore because there's no space</u>
<u n="300" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah but <unclear/> I suppose this didn't used to be a very big community did it before? <unclear/> got that big <unclear/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well exactly <pause dur="short"/> or I don't know because that's why there's so many churches around here is because so many people used to work on the land in such a small area that they needed a a church to go to</u>
<u n="302" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> look there's another <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and here's all the <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="303" who="S0144" trans="overlap">so but I guess the peasants weren't buried in places like this <pause dur="short"/> age sixty <pause dur="short"/> see they all lived to a ripe old age</u>
<u n="304" who="S0024" trans="overlap">look at this <pause dur="short"/> eighteen ninety-six aged ninety-one years</u>
<u n="305" who="S0144">bloody hell</u>
<u n="306" who="S0024">ninety-one <pause dur="short"/> now that you'd consider a good life span today</u>
<u n="307" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="308" who="S0024">I thought <trunc>we</trunc></u>
<u n="309" who="S0144" trans="overlap">so they must have been born in what? Eighteen O five and they lived</u>
<u n="310" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> nearly lived the whole century long <pause dur="short"/> that's pretty impressive</u>
<u n="311" who="S0144">that is incredible isn't it?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0024">I thought <pause dur="short"/> we were always taught in school that</u>
<u n="313" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0024">look here's a ninety-five years old <pause dur="short"/> oh no eighteen-ninety-five</u>
<u n="315" who="S0144">huh</u>
<u n="316" who="S0024">but erm</u>
<u n="317" who="S0144">but we get told so much that oh you're living longer now because of all the health advances</u>
<u n="318" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0144">I mean these people wouldn't have had anything</u>
<u n="320" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> but they they would have been <trunc>health</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I I reckon cos look at these stones they would have been quite rich</u>
<u n="321" who="S0144">yeah maybe they didn't do much work</u>
<u n="322" who="S0024">and yeah but still kept healthy <pause dur="short"/> you know ate ate lots of fruit and veg probably cos well they're farmers aren't they</u>
<u n="323" who="S0144" trans="overlap">Cos I think <pause dur="short"/> hmm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0024">now if you look at that tower <pause dur="short"/> that looks almost like a witch's tower really rather than a church doesn't it</u>
<u n="325" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0024">the round <pause dur="short"/> what style is it? Is that gothic?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0144" trans="overlap">are we allowed to go in it?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0024">you see we should have stopped <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and said</u>
<u n="329" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> it looks quite Dutch actually</u>
<u n="330" who="S0024"><trunc>D</trunc> oh yeah Dutch</u>
<u n="331" who="S0144">Cos I don't know there's lots of Dutch influence here isn't there cos you've got the windmills and</u>
<u n="332" who="S0024">we should have stopped <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and asked him for the keys <pause dur="short"/> he's like the key holder of the  of the  hall</u>
<u n="333" who="S0144">oh is he?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0024">yeah he looks after the place <pause dur="short"/> that's why that's probably why he's driving past look <pause dur="short"/> he always looks after the place</u>
<u n="335" who="S0144">look at all that wicker stuff <pause dur="short"/> that's pretty spooky</u>
<u n="336" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><unclear/> You can't tell me that doesn't look like a witch</u>
<u n="337" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0024">what is that supposed to be? It's like a erm a person bending over backwards <pause dur="short"/> a ballerina</u>
<u n="339" who="S0144">oh yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0024">is there a head the other side? You can't see the head <pause dur="short"/> ah somebody's been doing some wonderful art work <pause dur="short"/> it is <pause dur="short"/> there's the head</u>
<u n="341" who="S0144">yeah I <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="342" who="S0024">that's lovely</u>
<u n="343" who="S0144">it's quite clever <pause dur="short"/> I find it a bit freaky though</u>
<u n="344" who="S0024">yeah it is a bit freaky</u>
<u n="345" who="S0144">it looks a bit</u>
<u n="346" who="S0024">witchy <pause dur="short"/> oh we'll have to come <pause dur="short"/> we'll have to <pause dur="short"/> did you bring the camera? Have you got your camera?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0144" trans="overlap">that is pretty cool actually <pause dur="short"/> no no</u>
<u n="348" who="S0024">I'm going to come down here and take some photos <pause dur="short"/> there's some wicked photos</u>
<u n="349" who="S0144">huh that is a bit like Wicker Man or something though isn't it <pause dur="short"/> I think we have to be careful Dawn</u>
<u n="350" who="S0024" trans="overlap">that's <pause dur="short"/> well they're not going to burn it are they?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0144">they might burn us</u>
<u n="352" who="S0024">they're not going to burn the wicker though <pause dur="short"/> that's too good</u>
<u n="353" who="S0144">oh look and that one over there</u>
<u n="354" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><unclear/> They weren't here before I'm sure <pause dur="short"/> that is a Wicker Man structure</u>
<u n="355" who="S0144">it bloody is as well <vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh look <anon type="place"/> arts festival look</u>
<u n="356" who="S0024">do you live?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0144"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="358" who="S0024" trans="overlap">that must be hers then</u>
<u n="359" who="S0144">so she must have done all of this <pause dur="short"/> there's loads of them look</u>
<u n="360" who="S0024">well I don't remember mum and dad talking about it</u>
<u n="361" who="S0144">well they probably haven't been down here have they</u>
<u n="362" who="S0024">well they've they were here for the <anon type="place"/> arts festival</u>
<u n="363" who="S0144">oh okay</u>
<u n="364" who="S0024">Cos they were selling art</u>
<u n="365" who="S0144">oh <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> so that's all made from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> I want to make something like that</u>
<u n="367" who="S0144">it's huge isn't it <pause dur="short"/> that must have taken her ages <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="368" who="S0024">I think you need <pause dur="short"/> how many hazel trees? You've just got to collect <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> branches</u>
<u n="369" who="S0144">I wouldn't even be able to tell you what a hazel tree looks like <pause dur="short"/> well I know</u>
<u n="370" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I guess it's bendy like willow I suppose</u>
<u n="371" who="S0144">oh it's not bendy any more <pause dur="short"/> woops</u>
<u n="372" who="S0024" trans="overlap">that <pause dur="short"/> oh look there's some more here look <pause dur="short"/> they're like little cavities for people to stand in or hide in or something</u>
<u n="373" who="S0144">or maybe they do <pause dur="short"/> that's where people come and sleep at night</u>
<u n="374" who="S0024">look well they hide in here</u>
<u n="375" who="S0144">no it's</u>
<u n="376" who="S0024">they hide in here and jump out at at people during the festival probably <pause dur="short"/> god there's loads of them <pause dur="short"/> oh that's <trunc>prob</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> there's the ring</u>
<u n="377" who="S0144">yeah there's the ring yeah <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="378" who="S0024">I'm glad we came down here</u>
<u n="379" who="S0144">yeah it's nice isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> even though I don't really like churches there is something quite magical about graveyards I do like</u>
<u n="380" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><unclear/> so maybe that's <pause dur="short"/> no this church is quite special</u>
<u n="381" who="S0144">yeah I prefer the outside to the inside</u>
<u n="382" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><unclear/> all this wicker stuff all this wicker stuff makes it unusual</u>
<u n="383" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0024">God it's almost like a a tourist place <pause dur="short"/> people should come here to see the wicker art</u>
<u n="385" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty cool isn't it</u>
<u n="386" who="S0024" trans="overlap">the wicker church <pause dur="short"/> rename the <anon type="place"/> church like <anon type="place"/> Wicker</u>
<u n="387" who="S0144">huh</u>
<u n="388" who="S0024">or something <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> ah I'm going to definitely take the camera down here next time <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="389" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's definitely not a pagan church though <pause dur="short"/> I mean look at all those Christian symbols</u>
<u n="390" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0144">did the pagans have a church?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0024">no they didn't have churches <pause dur="short"/> they they praised the land</u>
<u n="393" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah exactly</u>
<u n="394" who="S0024">praised the land <pause dur="short"/> praised the water <pause dur="short"/> praised the sun <pause dur="short"/> praised love <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0144">well it was nature wasn't it?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0024">nature yeah <pause dur="short"/> so they didn't need buildings to praise did they <pause dur="short"/> I was thinking those erm</u>
<u n="397" who="S0144">I can't believe how old those people were living to</u>
<u n="398" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> that's amazing I know</u>
<u n="399" who="S0144">there must be something in the water around here <pause dur="short"/> oh twenty-five years</u>
<u n="400" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="401" who="S0144">not so good <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> that's nineteen-thirty though</u>
<u n="402" who="S0024">ah <pause dur="short"/> nineteen-thirty</u>
<u n="403" who="S0144">hmm</u>
<u n="404" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> when did the First World War end?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0144">first World War <pause dur="short"/> nineteen seventeen was it?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0024">end?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0024">when did it begin?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0144">erm fourteen I think <pause dur="short"/> it's getting a bit windy now</u>
<u n="410" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0144">huh <pause dur="short"/> yeah that was nice <pause dur="short"/> I'm glad we did that</u>
<u n="412" who="S0024" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> I I think erm I think tomorrow if it's a nice day I'm going to bring the camera down and have a look <pause dur="short"/> it does look really lovely</u>
<u n="413" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="414" who="S0024">and take pictures of those wicker <pause dur="short"/> and even those gates and stuff</u>
<u n="415" who="S0144">you could get some really nice pictures down here <pause dur="short"/> shall we look at the notice board?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh I don't like that</u>
<u n="417" who="S0144">hmm?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0024">peacefully awaiting us all</u>
<u n="419" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0024">waiting for you</u>
<u n="421" who="S0144">peacefully waiting</u>
<u n="422" who="S0024">I read  I read  it a bit wrong <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what I read but it kind of freaked me out and made me stop</u>
<u n="423" who="S0144">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> they're waiting for us to die</u>
<u n="424" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> I bet that was her last joke or something <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> on my gravestone</u>
<u n="425" who="S0144">that is a bit freaky</u>
<u n="426" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0144">right what's going on then? Carol service <pause dur="short"/> well they haven't changed that in a while have they <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="428" who="S0024">they need to update that don't they</u>
<u n="429" who="S0144">huh</u>
<u n="430" who="S0024">animal healing courses</u>
<u n="431" who="S0144" trans="overlap">animal healing?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0024">animal communication courses</u>
<u n="433" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0024"><unclear/> Fully certified <pause dur="short"/> animal communication and body balancing workshops</u>
<u n="435" who="S0144" trans="overlap">animal <trunc>commun</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> what you can get?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0024">I wonder what they do? Reiki master <pause dur="short"/> she's a Reiki master <pause dur="short"/> she probably does Reiki on all of the animals <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would love that <pause dur="short"/> oh my god</u>
<u n="437" who="S0144">animal healing and communication</u>
<u n="438" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0144">what do you get to learn to speak dog?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0024">no it's probably like a a mental communication like through or energy <pause dur="short"/> cos it's Reiki</u>
<u n="441" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> What you both sit there and stare at each other?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0024">no you probably like give them lots of attention and just learning to understand the animal</u>
<u n="443" who="S0144"><event desc="sound of whining dog"/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0024"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would love that <pause dur="short"/> ah UK animal healer dot co dot UK <pause dur="short"/> okay I'll try and remember that</u>
<u n="445" who="S0144">sounds like a lot of bollocks to me</u>
<u n="446" who="S0024">yeah but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would still love it <pause dur="short"/> if she could get a job doing that then she would be in her element</u>
<u n="447" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah she would love it</u>
<u n="448" who="S0024">she could do her Reiki which she loves to do but do it on animals instead of doing it on people</u>
<u n="449" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we need to go that way don't we</u>
<u n="450" who="S0024">yeah we're going straight <pause dur="short"/> unless you want to walk around a bit more?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="452" who="S0024">that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0144">go down <anon type="place"/> Road</u>
<u n="454" who="S0024">yeah but <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah look we've nearly been out for an hour now <pause dur="short"/> oh no cos we buried that <unclear/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0144">no we've been out for about half an hour</u>
<u n="456" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="457" who="S0144">better get back <pause dur="short"/> do some work <pause dur="short"/> blah de blah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0024">tomorrow might be the day Tom <pause dur="short"/> I know we keep saying that</u>
<u n="459" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it is <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> tomorrow is the day of reckoning <pause dur="short"/> look if they don't get us tomorrow we're going to have to start</u>
<u n="460" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well then we're going to have to write to the other</u>
<u n="461" who="S0144" trans="overlap">we're going to have to say look <pause dur="short"/> they've been pissing us about for what two months now? Said we had the job two months ago <pause dur="short"/> we need some kind of <pause dur="short"/> you know you just just if they wrote to us once a week saying oh sorry it's taking a long time blah blah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0144">but to hear nothing <pause dur="short"/> and this is</u>
<u n="464" who="S0024">I know <pause dur="short"/> well I can't believe after those emails that I sent and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> phoning us up going saying oh sorry</u>
<u n="465" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah and they were quite blunt as well <pause dur="short"/> they were to the point</u>
<u n="466" who="S0024">yeah and I put please contact at the top of my last email</u>
<u n="467" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="468" who="S0024">and all <pause dur="short"/> and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> phoned him up saying they are wondering what what's going on can you let them know? And then he turns round and says well I'll email them in a few days <pause dur="short"/> I'm sorry just email us <pause dur="short"/> hello</u>
<u n="469" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I I get the impression something's not right <pause dur="short"/> and I think</u>
<u n="470" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah me too <pause dur="short"/> ah can you imagine we're going to end up without a job</u>
<u n="471" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0024">oh no <pause dur="short"/> after waiting for a job</u>
<u n="473" who="S0144">huh</u>
<u n="474" who="S0024">I feel like we should have been paid for like being on standby or something</u>
<u n="475" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah well we've lost like two <trunc>month</trunc> no <trunc>th</trunc> what is it? It's March now</u>
<u n="476" who="S0024" trans="overlap">two months <pause dur="short"/> well yeah yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0144">yeah it's nearly half way through March now <pause dur="short"/> it's nearly like three months</u>
<u n="478" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I know it's like nearly half a quarter of a year</u>
<u n="479" who="S0144">fucking hell</u>
<u n="480" who="S0024">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> well it's getting a bit to the point of extremes now</u>
<u n="481" who="S0144">hello <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="482" who="S0024">where? Where's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0144">he's gone <pause dur="short"/> yeah well <pause dur="short"/> we should say to them <pause dur="short"/> write them an email <pause dur="short"/> if they don't hold of us tomorrow like Barry said they would <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to have to write an email saying look <pause dur="short"/> extremely worried <pause dur="short"/> I don't you know <pause dur="short"/> tell us what's going on <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="484" who="S0024" trans="overlap">or we'll have to find work</u>
<u n="485" who="S0144">I mean no I'll say look we're in no other position financially <pause dur="short"/> we're going to have to start looking for another job</u>
<u n="486" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0144">it could just be bad communication <pause dur="short"/> cos we know</u>
<u n="488" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>st</trunc> I think it is bad communication and that's why I think</u>
<u n="489" who="S0144">well it is bad communication</u>
<u n="490" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well yeah it definitely is but I think that's all it</u>
<u n="491" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it could just be you know Arabic communication <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="493" who="S0144">I'm hoping that's what it is <pause dur="short"/> if they turn around and say something's changed <pause dur="short"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> I'm not going to be best happy</u>
<u n="494" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="495" who="S0144">last time we came down here all that was iced over <pause dur="short"/> it had a load of ducks walking over it <pause dur="short"/> moo <pause dur="short"/> did you see all of the cows?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> where? Are they in the shed?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's loads of cows in there</u>
<u n="498" who="S0024">oh they're quite nice <unclear/></u>
<u n="499" who="S0144">they're scruffy looking buggers they are</u>
<u n="500" who="S0024">no I think their faces are nice but</u>
<u n="501" who="S0144">look he's staring at us</u>
<u n="502" who="S0024">they're stuck in they're stuck in the pen that's why because of the cold</u>
<u n="503" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0024">they'll be out and about soon</u>
<u n="505" who="S0144">hmm <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="506" who="S0024">yeah cos they used to be in the feed field opposite us and I haven't seen cows there for ages</u>
<u n="507" who="S0144">mm</u>
</body>
</text>
