<text id="SFUT">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:37:19</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-03-08</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0482 S0483</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Life, family, work</topics>
		<activity>Talking while cooking.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0482">
				<exactage>37</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Guildford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Post Doc Researcher, Health Pyschologist</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Rudimentary; French -- almost  conversational</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0483">
				<exactage>37</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Bromsgrove</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Assessment Manager (Education)</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Rudimentary; German -- Rudimentary; Spanish -- Rudimentary</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0483">so how was the teaching?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0482">er it was alright it was quite tiring <pause dur="short"/> erm I'm really pleased to have it over and done with today I sort of blagged it a bit this afternoon I hadn't really <pause dur="short"/> like properly read through my slides I mean I'd done them you know <pause dur="short"/> I've done very similar slides for a number of years bit still wasn't you know? <pause dur="short"/> wasn't quite sure what was coming up next but er you know I I think it I think it was fine <pause dur="short"/> in fact actually I I'm a bit quicker when I've not thought about it too much cos I just get to the point and move on so it probably it probably ends up being better</u>
<u n="3" who="S0483">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0482">that's alright I still have to you know sort of <pause dur="short"/> be around for guest speakers as they arrive so <pause dur="short"/> I'm doing a revision session in a few in a bit <pause dur="short"/> yeah I've written the exam questions as well so I'm kind of mostly done for that module which is good <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't quite work</u>
<u n="5" who="S0483">cool well that's something</u>
<u n="6" who="S0482">how was your day?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0483">er a bit dull didn't have a great deal to do erm <pause dur="short"/> er but yeah you know? <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0482">oh no smell that that's lovely <pause dur="short"/> just a</u>
<u n="9" who="S0483">oh god yeah that's amazing</u>
<u n="10" who="S0482">it's a really nice dish oh are these the stuffed ones? <pause dur="short"/> butterfly sea bass stuffed with tomatoes and olives <pause dur="short"/> yummy yum</u>
<u n="11" who="S0483">mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0482">oh er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has texted and said that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> er if you're looking for a birthday present for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> er</u>
<u n="13" who="S0483" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0482">whisky so we'll get him some whisky that'll be a nice pressie</u>
<u n="15" who="S0483" trans="overlap">mm job done yep that's really helpful</u>
<u n="16" who="S0482" trans="overlap">result yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> what do we do send it? we might as well send it direct to him there's no point in getting it delivered here and then sending it on</u>
<u n="17" who="S0483">well we are <pause dur="short"/> are we going to see them over Easter? could we just?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0482">er I don't know but even so we still thinking about it it's gonna get delivered somewhere we might as well have it delivered to him on his birthday rather than us</u>
<u n="19" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yep erm that one my brother got me was blinking nice why don't we just get him some of that?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0482" trans="overlap">mm yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> no complaints on that one <pause dur="short"/> absolutely <pause dur="short"/> right think I want to turn this over <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0483">excellent well <pause dur="long"/> jolly good <pause dur="long"/> erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0482">that doesn't really help <pause dur="short"/> so yeah though I forgot about this birthday she said er he doesn't really want anything <unclear>I was like come on</unclear></u>
<u n="23" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> apart from whisky</u>
<u n="24" who="S0482">yeah not not</u>
<u n="25" who="S0483" trans="overlap">that's very interesting no he doesn't want anything apart from whisky</u>
<u n="26" who="S0482">can't not get him something for his birthday</u>
<u n="27" who="S0483">no <pause dur="short"/> probably not <pause dur="long"/> erm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0482">what do you want for your birthday?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0483">er well <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="long"/> phwoar I don't know I haven't really thought about it not much I mean I've already spent my birthday money <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0482">have you? <pause dur="short"/> birthday money you haven't got yet?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0483">yep <pause dur="short"/> erm I spent it on my spa day so erm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0482">that sounds like a really good thing</u>
<u n="33" who="S0483">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the only trouble is I also spent it in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0482">mm what you spent it twice?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0483">I spent it twice <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0482">that doesn't really work does it?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0483">well you know <pause dur="short"/> well technically the spa was more than the money I'm getting as well so you know</u>
<u n="38" who="S0482">oh okay so two and a half times</u>
<u n="39" who="S0483">I've spent two and a half times my birthday money erm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0482">oh well <pause dur="short"/> what's it for if you don't if you're not going to spend it? <pause dur="long"/> yeah okay well forget that aside what would you like?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0483">erm <pause dur="long"/> erm I don't <trunc>s</trunc> I don't know I mean you know there's not really you know we've been spending a lot recently <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0482">yeah but nothing and not not <trunc>frivo</trunc>frivolous <unclear/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no so no er I would like a nice meal cooked for me at some point</u>
<u n="44" who="S0482">yeah but that's not a birthday present is it? <pause dur="short"/> that's a given</u>
<u n="45" who="S0483" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> if you can afford some time off then I would like to go for a erm walk on the <trunc>Mon</trunc> on Monday <pause dur="short"/> er weather dependent</u>
<u n="46" who="S0482" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay let me er consult my diary</u>
<u n="47" who="S0483">erm what else? what else? what else? what else? <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> phwoar erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I <trunc>do</trunc>don't know I mean there's there's nothing I want seriously I've I've bought myself everything that I want recently so erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I would simply say</u>
<u n="48" who="S0482"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="49" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I dunno you know? whatever surprise me don't spend much</u>
<u n="50" who="S0482" trans="overlap">a new phone?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0483">erm <pause dur="short"/> I do I do want a new phone but er you know</u>
<u n="52" who="S0482">requires a bit of research</u>
<u n="53" who="S0483">it it does require a bit of research and you know? I'm really quite happy with Sony as a brand erm <pause dur="short"/> but I you know? I've heard bad reports of their latest models you know they're also starting to get too big you know? like I was looking at the Experia Z it's already significantly bigger than mine which means it won't conveniently fit into any of my bags erm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0482">mm yeah it's a bit of a dilemma that big phone <pause dur="short"/> little space</u>
<u n="55" who="S0483">erm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0482">I quite liked it when I could wear a phone on my belt</u>
<u n="57" who="S0483">yeah didn't you look cool but then you know?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0482">perhaps I don't</u>
<u n="59" who="S0483">er</u>
<u n="60" who="S0482">I know I must have looked like a right Charlie</u>
<u n="61" who="S0483">yeah you did erm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0482">why didn't you say anything earlier?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0483">well you know</u>
<u n="64" who="S0482">and when I reflect back on it I can remember a few people taking the piss</u>
<u n="65" who="S0483">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0482">I <pause dur="short"/> I thought it was just banter <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I wonder why <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0482">it was such a practical place to have it though it was secure <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah looking at that I must have looked like one of those I know the bloke I look like</u>
<u n="69" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0482">there are still some there are still some people who wear them on their hip <pause dur="short"/> I think I carried it off better than most</u>
<u n="71" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you hope</u>
<u n="72" who="S0482">thing is it doesn't work with a touch screen <pause dur="short"/> so for starters that's but okay but then when now now it's in my pocket its you know? it gets in the way if I'm trying if I'm cycling it has to be at a certain angle if one of the kids sort of sits on me it usually resets the phone so you know? how else am I meant to <trunc>ca</trunc> how is a bloke meant to carry a phone?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0483">I dunno</u>
<u n="74" who="S0482">we don't have bags generally <pause dur="short"/> mostly</u>
<u n="75" who="S0483" trans="overlap">you could get yourself a little man bag couldn't you?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0482">yeah but most of us don't have them</u>
<u n="77" who="S0483">well <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="long"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah no I mean you know? surprise me little nick nack paddy whack <pause dur="short"/> give a dog a bone type things</u>
<u n="78" who="S0482">you want a bone?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0483" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah blimey that looks like a prison <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0482">okay doesn't really help but yeah alright</u>
<u n="81" who="S0483">erm okay erm er ah I mean good <pause dur="short"/> or you've you've succeeded in this region before could you do a pair of earrings for me? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0482">maybe it's quite it's actually quite a hard thing to find</u>
<u n="83" who="S0483">right erm no no no no</u>
<u n="84" who="S0482" trans="overlap">but yeah yeah no no no for you my darling <pause dur="short"/> anything</u>
<u n="85" who="S0483">no forget it I don't think I want earrings anymore erm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0482">no no no</u>
<u n="87" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no you've ruined it now I don't even want it don't even want it</u>
<u n="88" who="S0482" trans="overlap">easier easier easier you easier that you tell more a few things you want and then I can you know? get the right thing</u>
<u n="89" who="S0483">erm <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0482">we do need to</u>
<u n="91" who="S0483">sort Center Parcs</u>
<u n="92" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0483">erm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0482">it didn't tell us where we are did it? <pause dur="short"/> we're in Itchy Lot</u>
<u n="95" who="S0483">yeah I mean it sounds it sounds oh no I know I know it sounds far away</u>
<u n="96" who="S0482" trans="overlap">oh yeah it does we phoned up <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> ah that's a big number</u>
<u n="97" who="S0483">there's a big it's a big number</u>
<u n="98" who="S0482"><anon type="address"/> what have we done? <pause dur="short"/> okay I'm gonna look at the furthest area away <pause dur="short"/> oh actually <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="address"/> I've found it it's not too bad</u>
<u n="99" who="S0483">who who what?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0483">really?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0483">are you sure?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0482">I'm sure <pause dur="short"/> okay <anon type="address"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0482">Maple</u>
<u n="107" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0482"><anon type="address"/>'s there</u>
<u n="109" who="S0483">okay</u>
<u n="110" who="S0482">look it's not far is it?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0483">blimey no er <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0482" trans="overlap">you know and then walk down that way <pause dur="short"/> whereas look we could be we could've been like in the Itchy lot over here</u>
<u n="113" who="S0483">oh yeah that would've been evil</u>
<u n="114" who="S0482">well no that would have been alright</u>
<u n="115" who="S0483">no that would have been tough <pause dur="short"/> oh fantastic well that's good <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0482">woodland lodge two bed yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0483">yep</u>
<u n="118" who="S0482">one yeah or or that I mean obviously in fact no actually we in fact that's pretty good</u>
<u n="119" who="S0483">no do that's that's good that is good</u>
<u n="120" who="S0482">erm <anon type="address"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0483">well</u>
<u n="122" who="S0482">there's quite a few that it's it's like they did they don't half pack them in but yeah we're not far that's really good and and we're right near er some water as well look <pause dur="short"/> I presume that's water</u>
<u n="123" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> don't know</u>
<u n="124" who="S0482">it's quite watery this place</u>
<u n="125" who="S0483">er <vocal desc="misc"/> erm dunno we oh <pause dur="short"/> we've we've been before <unclear/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0482">shall we try and go no we went to the country club there's a oh in the country club there's a little erm kiddy area play area <pause dur="short"/> cos that's where I took <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that time when I was looking after her when you went to the spa</u>
<u n="127" who="S0483">oh yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0482">erm we could book at table oh</u>
<u n="129" who="S0483">oh we've already booked a table somewhere that wasn't that it didn't it wasn't that appealing let's take a look</u>
<u n="130" who="S0482" trans="overlap">alright alright lets book a table for lunch or something</u>
<u n="131" who="S0483">oh okay</u>
<u n="132" who="S0482">yeah we we booked a table at</u>
<u n="133" who="S0483">okay</u>
<u n="134" who="S0482">that French French place er</u>
<u n="135" who="S0483">er Café Rouge</u>
<u n="136" who="S0482"><trunc>C</trunc>Café Rouge yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0483">yeah French <vocal desc="laugh"/> and the er the er</u>
<u n="138" who="S0482" trans="overlap">yeah alright not really French <pause dur="short"/> faux French but erm</u>
<u n="139" who="S0483" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0482">I remember that place I it was alright it was a it's a pub basically but erm it's <pause dur="short"/> it's got like a play area for kids <pause dur="short"/> it's not massive but</u>
<u n="141" who="S0483">yeah oh no I remember it yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0482">it's got like erm a suspension bridge and stuff</u>
<u n="143" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I remember it well I remember it well no no I know</u>
<u n="144" who="S0482">let's face it it's not bad</u>
<u n="145" who="S0483">no</u>
<u n="146" who="S0482">erm ah that's good <pause dur="short"/> I mean nowhere's that this is quite a good place for it I suppose cos nowhere's too far away</u>
<u n="147" who="S0483">ah you know? <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna be a nice er little break</u>
<u n="148" who="S0482">aye</u>
<u n="149" who="S0483">erm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0482">aye <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0483">so yeah no that sounds good to me</u>
<u n="152" who="S0482">that's cool oh well <pause dur="short"/> some er <pause dur="short"/> positive news saved ourselves forty quid not sure where I'm not sure where's closer really <pause dur="short"/> I mean okay there there is closer but look we're in like that's probably that and there's probably the closest but we</u>
<u n="153" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no it was erm pretty jammy maybe <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> intervened for us</u>
<u n="154" who="S0482">do you think?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0482">hi I've got some friends coming to stay I just want to check they're in there <pause dur="short"/> do you think maybe he's upgraded to a</u>
<u n="157" who="S0483">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0482">one of those ones with a sauna garden <pause dur="short"/> garden? <pause dur="short"/> right okay <pause dur="short"/> this is good <pause dur="short"/> see that's what I imagine Center Parcs was like you know? it's just so not like that at all they just clearly taking the photo which excludes</u>
<u n="159" who="S0483" trans="overlap">well it's quite narrow I mean the thing is though if you think about the adverts for Center Parcs when we were kids it was literally like a cabin isolated in the woods</u>
<u n="160" who="S0482">ah I know</u>
<u n="161" who="S0483">and maybe about a mile down the track there was another cabin isolated in the woods and that's how I imagined it</u>
<u n="162" who="S0482" trans="overlap">or cycling around a lake and there's no one else there like</u>
<u n="163" who="S0483">no exactly</u>
<u n="164" who="S0482">and then you just imagine acres and acres of forest that occasionally dotted around little places</u>
<u n="165" who="S0483">yeah you might bump into someone every now and then but actually the reality is</u>
<u n="166" who="S0482" trans="overlap">rather than <pause dur="short"/> it's all roads</u>
<u n="167" who="S0483">well you know the reality is it's incredibly crowded it's like a it's a like fucking Butlins</u>
<u n="168" who="S0482">but it's for <pause dur="short"/> for well it's one up from that</u>
<u n="169" who="S0483">it's one up from Butlins</u>
<u n="170" who="S0482">the the cost of it excludes some of the</u>
<u n="171" who="S0483">some of the Butlins people but a lot of the Butlins people have in fact got into Center Parcs</u>
<u n="172" who="S0482">well they aspire</u>
<u n="173" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0482">right <pause dur="short"/> what have you got here? oh look children's activities okay? chocolate chefs' academy</u>
<u n="175" who="S0483">ah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0482">three hours</u>
<u n="177" who="S0483">fucking hell we could be in the spa</u>
<u n="178" who="S0482">three to seven years old</u>
<u n="179" who="S0483">no</u>
<u n="180" who="S0482">from twenty-four quid</u>
<u n="181" who="S0483">I bet they make you stay</u>
<u n="182" who="S0482">I bet that it's not free anymore I bet it's not available anymore <pause dur="short"/> three hours twenty-four quid but who cares?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0483">I mean twenty-four quid for three hours <trunc>ch</trunc>childcare's alright</u>
<u n="184" who="S0482" trans="overlap">nine AM on Sunday morning</u>
<u n="185" who="S0483">but they're not gonna <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit early but they're gonna make an adult stay aren't they? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0482">let's have a look it says keys so</u>
<u n="187" who="S0483">if they're three if it's from three they're going to make you stay <pause dur="short"/> but imagine if they didn't we could get to the spa</u>
<u n="188" who="S0482">well look this is weird cos there's a section here</u>
<u n="189" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0482">this is children's activities in the den yeah?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0482">Pirate and Princess adventure</u>
<u n="193" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0482">I think this place has got</u>
<u n="195" who="S0483" trans="overlap">looks bang on bring an adult eighteen years</u>
<u n="196" who="S0482">yeah yeah yeah but look that's bring an adult bring a paying adult bring an adult</u>
<u n="197" who="S0483" trans="overlap">hang on bring a paying adult bring an adult</u>
<u n="198" who="S0482">but there's nothing for this section here</u>
<u n="199" who="S0483">really?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0482">I'm not saying it means look the <unclear/> crèche</u>
<u n="201" who="S0483" trans="overlap">hang on let's have a look down here badminton you don't have to bring an adult</u>
<u n="202" who="S0482">but look crèche</u>
<u n="203" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0482">they're not gonna make you bring an adult then are they?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no no no</u>
<u n="206" who="S0482"><unclear/> it's three to seven so obviously it covers <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="207" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah but basically what we're saying is do we want to get rid of the kids for three hours? possibly</u>
<u n="208" who="S0482">no <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="209" who="S0483">but listen but maybe they don't have to stay for the full three hours but what what is going to happen is whist we're enjoying ourselves relaxing in the spa they're gonna be filling themselves with chocolate so what we're going to pick up is two children sick but probably probably probably puking maybe pooing <pause dur="short"/> you know? <pause dur="short"/> is it worth it?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0482">yep</u>
<u n="211" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they can't regulate they can't regulate</u>
<u n="212" who="S0482">well they're not gonna they're not just gonna say here's a massive amount of chocolate fill your boots are they?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0483">well they might do <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0482">they have some some duty of care for children</u>
<u n="215" who="S0483">I don't know the thing is is it's not their problem is it?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0482">thing is the thing is they</u>
<u n="217" who="S0483" trans="overlap">they can fill them up with shit and then hand them back over</u>
<u n="218" who="S0482">the things is we're we're we're erm we're you know we're late on this</u>
<u n="219" who="S0483"><vocal desc="misc"/> excuse me kids will have had the best time ever <pause dur="short"/> you know? <pause dur="short"/> mummy daddy can we do that again? meanwhile they're puking everywhere</u>
<u n="220" who="S0482">I'll tell you what we've not had any response back from this erm returning</u>
<u n="221" who="S0483">well I don't think we're necessarily going to well you know what can we do?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0482" trans="overlap">well it's under guarantee</u>
<u n="223" who="S0483">yeah exactly well you know</u>
<u n="224" who="S0482">it says you have to contact the erm you know</u>
<u n="225" who="S0483">more wine?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0482">hang on hang on hang on hang on we <trunc>a</trunc> we've accepted your return request once <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> once <anon type="place"/> receives the item we'll issue a refund <pause dur="short"/> okay we're good</u>
<u n="227" who="S0483" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> alright but I'd like another</u>
<u n="228" who="S0482">ah but we can get a <trunc>re</trunc> look</u>
<u n="229" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah I know yeah yeah yeah yeah no I know yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0482" trans="overlap">they say this is refundable get a refund buy another one</u>
<u n="231" who="S0483">birthday present sorted birthday present sorted</u>
<u n="232" who="S0482">with twenty quid to spare that'll go <vocal desc="laugh"/> that'll cover your birthday present</u>
<u n="233" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that'll cover my present that'll cover my earrings wonderful</u>
<u n="234" who="S0482">exactly oh that's a result</u>
<u n="235" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0482">I don't mean that bit about the birthday <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> self despatch I hope they <pause dur="short"/> oh hang on they're not paying for the er <trunc>deli</trunc></u>
<u n="237" who="S0483"><vocal desc="yawn"/> oh really?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0482">whatever</u>
<u n="239" who="S0483">it only cost two pound eighty to get it back to them</u>
<u n="240" who="S0482" trans="overlap">no that's fine</u>
<u n="241" who="S0483">doesn't matter</u>
<u n="242" who="S0482">now I have to work out how to forward it <pause dur="short"/> why why why is it just so impossible to do anything? <pause dur="short"/> I can respond right ah okay so click and respond is the same as forward but responding and forward are quite different things</u>
<u n="243" who="S0483">true that</u>
<u n="244" who="S0482"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> you're next Amazon er Love Film disc is on the way the Great Beauty</u>
<u n="245" who="S0483">never heard of it</u>
<u n="246" who="S0482">what's that? don't know <pause dur="short"/> a sixty-five year old journalist and once promising novelist spends his easy life among Rome's high society in a swirl of roof top parties <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> dot dot dot dot it sounds good alright</u>
<u n="247" who="S0483">yeah doesn't sound like a <unclear/> does it?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0482" trans="overlap">right okay <pause dur="short"/> so here is party hour one hour pirate and princess adventure three hours woodland adventure three hours it's a this is pretty substantial <pause dur="short"/> I think these are the <pause dur="short"/> we'll look after your kids for you kind of things</u>
<u n="249" who="S0483">well or two but I mean it doesn't seem well I dunno maybe <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> we'll erm we'll look into it definitely</u>
<u n="250" who="S0482">okay then we've got all the other things like archery and mini crossbows three to seven years old</u>
<u n="251" who="S0483"><vocal desc="misc"/> they'll be bored by that I would be bored</u>
<u n="252" who="S0482" trans="overlap">baby Bo's bike buddy</u>
<u n="253" who="S0483">ah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0482">ten months to two years</u>
<u n="255" who="S0483">can I have a wine?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0482" trans="overlap"><unclear/> imprint friend</u>
<u n="257" who="S0483"><vocal desc="misc"/> in there</u>
<u n="258" who="S0482">from six weeks cup cake decorating <pause dur="short"/> eight to eleven what?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0483">pff</u>
<u n="260" who="S0482">you don't need to be eight to decorate cup cakes</u>
<u n="261" who="S0483" trans="overlap">decorate cup cakes maybe you do <pause dur="short"/> maybe with the cup cake comes great responsibility</u>
<u n="262" who="S0482">adventure of the senses</u>
<u n="263" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0482">dome building</u>
<u n="265" who="S0483" trans="overlap">as long as it's not the erotic arts</u>
<u n="266" who="S0482">dome building and decorating that sounds quite fun</u>
<u n="267" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0482">forty-six pounds per plot <pause dur="short"/> for one hour thirty minutes <pause dur="short"/> jeez in the wrong business face painting ten minutes five seventy-five <pause dur="short"/> that's quite expensive isn't it? for face painting</u>
<u n="269" who="S0483" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> very expensive</u>
<u n="270" who="S0482">I mean they do like it fairy fun time is that what we did?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0483">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="272" who="S0482" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> forty-five minutes no it was longer than that</u>
<u n="273" who="S0483">er <pause dur="short"/> it was how whatever it was</u>
<u n="274" who="S0482">what do you mean good fun?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0483">it took forever</u>
<u n="276" who="S0482">horse crafts</u>
<u n="277" who="S0483">three hours seems I dunno three hours gives you time to walk across have a couple of hours in the spa jeez even the spa will probably be booked up by now</u>
<u n="278" who="S0482" trans="overlap">I don't I bet I think the kids I mean I dunno chocolate chefs' cabin if they if they cover three years look <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they're institutionalised</u>
<u n="279" who="S0483">yeah I mean if if if they if we didn't have to stay and if we could get a place in the spa then we'd be considering it <pause dur="short"/> we'd have to talk to them about it though <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="280" who="S0482" trans="overlap">I know I know</u>
<u n="281" who="S0483">you know what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will be like I don't like it</u>
<u n="282" who="S0482">I really don't I <trunc>real</trunc> I mean I'm not I wasn't looking for things</u>
<u n="283" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I know but</u>
<u n="284" who="S0482">I wasn't looking for things to get rid of them</u>
<u n="285" who="S0483" trans="overlap">so I was I was erm you know somebody a Zumba was sort of saying I I cos there's Zumbathon on the weekend we're going and I said oh I can't oh I'm going to Center Parcs and they said oh great that'll be lovely I went er <pause dur="short"/> she said oh you know you know just put the kids in the crèche and go and do things and I <trunc>sa</trunc> and you know I came very close to sort of saying yeah you know going on holiday with the kids cos I want to spend time with them but erm you know didn't want to er offend her but <pause dur="short"/> basically I'm going on I'm going on holiday with them cos I want to spend time with them so</u>
<u n="286" who="S0482" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh no I'm look I'm looking forward to I'm really looking forward to you know doing things with them that's why I'm looking for things that we can all you know</u>
<u n="287" who="S0483">but at the same time I don't want to enjoy some sort of holiday camp activity with them <pause dur="short"/> if the if we're going to have to suffer that I'd rather they suffered alone</u>
<u n="288" who="S0482">there's there's quite a lot of things that <pause dur="short"/> both can't do like there's like teddy bears' picnic two to five years old and</u>
<u n="289" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well they <pause dur="short"/> they can</u>
<u n="290" who="S0482">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will be fine yeah yeah that's true</u>
<u n="291" who="S0483">yeah that's fine they can do that</u>
<u n="292" who="S0482">but anyway I I didn't want that toddlers' party hour? <pause dur="short"/> I don't know it doesn't say bowling</u>
<u n="293" who="S0483">oh I want to do the erm <pause dur="short"/> er roller booting by the way B T Dubs</u>
<u n="294" who="S0482">er okay <pause dur="short"/> erm R roller disco</u>
<u n="295" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0482"><vocal desc="gasp"/> six years plus</u>
<u n="297" who="S0483">I know it doesn't matter we can lie</u>
<u n="298" who="S0482">oh man</u>
<u n="299" who="S0483">why can't we lie?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0482">we've probably already said how old they are</u>
<u n="301" who="S0483">have we?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0482">well you know what they're like</u>
<u n="303" who="S0483" trans="overlap">oh bollocks</u>
<u n="304" who="S0482">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can't do it <pause dur="short"/> she's never ridden</u>
<u n="305" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah but she be couldn't do it anyway</u>
<u n="306" who="S0482">no that's true but then we'd have ah yeah no no let's do roller disco some other time</u>
<u n="307" who="S0483" trans="overlap">maybe <pause dur="short"/> that's just bollocks</u>
<u n="308" who="S0482">ten pin bowling</u>
<u n="309" who="S0483">can I go to the roller disco by myself?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0482">six plus it doesn't say</u>
<u n="313" who="S0483" trans="overlap">what what time <pause dur="short"/> what time is it?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0482">erm <pause dur="short"/> weekend <pause dur="short"/> erm Friday Friday Saturday Sunday roller disco there's one on Friday at four thirty there's one on Saturday at seven thirty PM</u>
<u n="315" who="S0483" trans="overlap">look why the fuck can't we go to the roller disco? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s a better roller booter than most of the kids there</u>
<u n="316" who="S0482" trans="overlap">hey look <pause dur="short"/> seven thirty PM on Saturday or four thirty PM on Friday <pause dur="short"/> that's the only choice</u>
<u n="317" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> shall we? I might er <pause dur="short"/> they're not gonna know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0482">they will</u>
<u n="319" who="S0483">we'll just turn up <pause dur="short"/> and I'll just say that we put we made a mistake on the booking form that she's actually six</u>
<u n="320" who="S0482">oh she was er yeah probably her date of birth it's a year out got it wrong</u>
<u n="321" who="S0483">you know <pause dur="short"/> be fine <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0482">yeah but there's seven we can't do the Saturday evening one cos <pause dur="short"/> that's seven thirty</u>
<u n="323" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah I was only saying we can't make either of them</u>
<u n="324" who="S0482">although the four thirty-one is possible</u>
<u n="325" who="S0483" trans="overlap">we're going we're going on the <unclear/> well we're going roller booting with erm</u>
<u n="326" who="S0482">I'd say let's just do roller <trunc>boot</trunc> yeah it's one thing we can do here <pause dur="short"/> whereas there's quite a lot of things on this list we can't do with them or they can't do <pause dur="short"/> here you know locally it's either so</u>
<u n="327" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> got to find something for you to do it's your birthday <pause dur="short"/> let's see what you can do</u>
<u n="328" who="S0482">oh yeah yeah yeah do</u>
<u n="329" who="S0483">water sports baby dolphins do you want to do baby dolphins? do you want to learn to snorkel?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0482" trans="overlap">I love baby dolphins <pause dur="short"/> I bet they're really cute</u>
<u n="331" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> how about <pause dur="short"/> would you like to do <pause dur="short"/> a laser clay shootout eight years plus?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0482" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="333" who="S0483">no <pause dur="short"/> would you like to do <pause dur="short"/> walk with trees? four years plus</u>
<u n="334" who="S0482">walk with trees?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0483">pff</u>
<u n="336" who="S0482">they don't really walk</u>
<u n="337" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I imagine it's like erm <pause dur="short"/> you know something from Lord of the Rings where the trees go walking</u>
<u n="338" who="S0482">they're called Ents darling</u>
<u n="339" who="S0483">you can do spa from fourteen years I'd have thought you'd might have to be older <pause dur="short"/> would you like to do?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0482">spa yes please <pause dur="short"/> a massage</u>
<u n="341" who="S0483">seriously go for a spa and massage</u>
<u n="342" who="S0482">I know wouldn't it be wouldn't it be a coup if we <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> if we both go it would be amazing but <pause dur="short"/> erm what about hula party? twelve plus years <vocal desc="laugh"/> just turn up at a twelve-year-old's hula party</u>
<u n="344" who="S0482">I tell you what I bet they've designed these three hour things around you literally going having time to do the spa for two hours</u>
<u n="345" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0482">oh look here we go aqua sauna they've put it in here as well</u>
<u n="347" who="S0483" trans="overlap">squash <pause dur="short"/> squash court would you like to play squash by yourself?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0482" trans="overlap">yeah I'll play play on my own <pause dur="short"/> sounds great</u>
<u n="349" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'll send to you it it was <unclear/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0482">spa session three hour evening where you can escape for the day <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="351" who="S0483" trans="overlap">cheerleading three plus years you have to have an adult with you but how sweet would that be?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0482">hey that sounds like a good thing they'd love it</u>
<u n="353" who="S0483" trans="overlap">they'd frigging love that I'll do it with them</u>
<u n="354" who="S0482">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0483">seriously you can have a massage and I'll go cheerleading with then</u>
<u n="356" who="S0482">perfect but <trunc>l</trunc> seriously you've got to do <pause dur="short"/> other people will have got this pack today as well people like us who aren't that well <pause dur="short"/> organised</u>
<u n="357" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'll take the cheerleading <pause dur="short"/> it says cheerleading three plus years <pause dur="short"/> from six seventy-five ten AM on a Sunday</u>
<u n="358" who="S0482" trans="overlap">how long? <pause dur="short"/> okay that works <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> get booking</u>
<u n="359" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> tops movie moves three to five years I wonder what that is? <pause dur="short"/> it's got a yellow with it bring an adult bring a paying adult see I've got to pay to do cheerleading but I don't need to pay</u>
<u n="360" who="S0482" trans="overlap">how?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0483">listen but you don't need to be a paying adult it's cheaper for us to do tops movie moves <pause dur="short"/> at <pause dur="short"/> oh it's only available during the week can't actually do that one</u>
<u n="362" who="S0482">do you think there's any do you think it's worth considering? cos like we're not very far away I suppose there's a bit of traffic but we could you know we could stay the Sunday night</u>
<u n="363" who="S0483">oh I see what you're saying</u>
<u n="364" who="S0482">and then just leave at seven forty-five in the morning let's face it we're up at six or whatever</u>
<u n="365" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0482">erm and just drop <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> straight off at school <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0483">yeah could be a bit weird for them but yeah we can do that yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0482" trans="overlap">be quite be quite fun</u>
<u n="369" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah yeah absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0482">could we could stay for that third night</u>
<u n="371" who="S0483">yeah we certainly could</u>
<u n="372" who="S0482">and that way you know we can do all the you know lose a bit of packing or whatever</u>
<u n="373" who="S0483">oh yeah but we literally just get up you know we get up at six have breakfast be on the road for half past six even that's two early</u>
<u n="374" who="S0482" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no no no</u>
<u n="375" who="S0483">be on the road at seven</u>
<u n="376" who="S0482" trans="overlap">yeah seven forty-five or something</u>
<u n="377" who="S0483">yeah yeah no I mean that that yeah yeah yeah yeah <trunc>exac</trunc></u>
<u n="378" who="S0482">or come here if we make a good run of it cos it's only forty-five minutes</u>
<u n="379" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah yeah and that way we've had your birthday night there</u>
<u n="380" who="S0482" trans="overlap">it could be traffic so if we allow an hour and a bit</u>
<u n="381" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah we've had your birthday night there then</u>
<u n="382" who="S0482">yeah yeah exactly it could be quite fun</u>
<u n="383" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0482">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then it's a bit more relaxed for the week it's a full weekend</u>
<u n="385" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah no it's a good plan that's a good plan</u>
<u n="386" who="S0482" trans="overlap">rather than feeling like oh we're going home tonight yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0483">that's a good plan am I going cheerleading?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0482">yeah that's a good plan and I'm going for a massage</u>
<u n="389" who="S0483">yeah that's a good plan <pause dur="short"/> swim a song swimming lesson swim a song no she's they're too young for that you could take <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> though</u>
<u n="390" who="S0482">I'd like a rainbow massage</u>
<u n="391" who="S0483" trans="overlap">mini jet skis three to seven years I mean come on</u>
<u n="392" who="S0482">what?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0483">that can't be anything real</u>
<u n="394" who="S0482">it can't be a swimmer</u>
<u n="395" who="S0483">three to seven year what what? aqua what what?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0482">oh hang on jet no but jet skis though what?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0483">it says three to seven years <pause dur="short"/> fun oh hang on</u>
<u n="398" who="S0482">how would that work?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0483">fencing for tots three to five years <pause dur="short"/> what's that gonna be? roller tots two to five years</u>
<u n="400" who="S0482">do you see what I mean about the? I mean</u>
<u n="401" who="S0483" trans="overlap">this is I mean the roller tots <pause dur="short"/> the thing is like do you know what I mean? there'll be people like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on her little roller skates not being able to do it and then</u>
<u n="402" who="S0482">oh yeah right</u>
<u n="403" who="S0483">do you know what I mean you couldn't take <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to roller tots she'd just <pause dur="short"/> see what I mean? it'd be like taking a fucking <trunc>tor</trunc>Torvill and Dean with them</u>
<u n="404" who="S0482">yeah but it's probably in the same area where they do roller disco and all the rest of it so if you're good you can just do it yourself and if you're not then</u>
<u n="405" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah it's really it's really shitty that I can't take her to the roller disco I wanna go to the roller disco</u>
<u n="406" who="S0482">well you can</u>
<u n="407" who="S0483">but well we just have to lie about her date of birth</u>
<u n="408" who="S0482">yeah <pause dur="short"/> or like basically she can roller boot and she's like a month or so off or a couple of months off</u>
<u n="409" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0482">so you know I I I I doubt I doubt they'll say in the booking process warning you could not go to this</u>
<u n="411" who="S0483" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah no no no I'll I'll do it</u>
<u n="412" who="S0482">and</u>
<u n="413" who="S0483">six year plus</u>
<u n="414" who="S0482" trans="overlap">they never really check age</u>
<u n="415" who="S0483">minimum feet size junior eight junior eight</u>
<u n="416" who="S0482">well she's ten</u>
<u n="417" who="S0483">well that's the thing</u>
<u n="418" who="S0482">she's got her own boots anyway</u>
<u n="419" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="420" who="S0482">but and she does does</u>
<u n="421" who="S0483">so it's at oh yeah but we couldn't go at any of the times could we?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0482">I know well there's four thirty on the Friday</u>
<u n="423" who="S0483">no</u>
<u n="424" who="S0482">but we can't do that can we?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0483" trans="overlap">we can't make that no can't do that no</u>
<u n="426" who="S0482" trans="overlap">oh we'll go this weekend</u>
<u n="427" who="S0483">no we're not gonna be able to go <pause dur="short"/> it's really crappy though cos I really wanna go</u>
<u n="428" who="S0482">er <pause dur="short"/> unless we have a really late night Saturday</u>
<u n="429" who="S0483" trans="overlap">Sunday unless there's something on Sunday <pause dur="short"/> I know but Saturday we're going out for a meal aren't we?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0482">do you want a sweetcorn?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0483">no I wanna go roller booting roller skating six plus years</u>
<u n="434" who="S0482">yeah are you gonna do that? oh six yeah okay yeah six or over yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0483">same deal yeah <pause dur="short"/> I could go at like three PM I yeah there's no there's no point I'll take I'm taking them to a roller disco here anyway so</u>
<u n="436" who="S0482">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but book book some of the other ones</u>
<u n="437" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah no I think I think basically we'll do the erm whatever it was cheerleading</u>
<u n="438" who="S0482">yeah that's quite fun</u>
<u n="439" who="S0483">I'll do cheerleading on a Sunday you can have a a massage or whatnot</u>
<u n="440" who="S0482">does it say erm adult required for that?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0482">cool</u>
<u n="443" who="S0483">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> and and you've got to pay for the pleasure</u>
<u n="444" who="S0482">but seriously I mean some of these other things sounded quite fun <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> you know don't it'd be nice to do it'd be nice to have something else</u>
<u n="445" who="S0483" trans="overlap">forest crafts hobby horse three plus years seventeen quid each</u>
<u n="446" who="S0482">seventy?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0483">seventeen</u>
<u n="448" who="S0482">oh</u>
<u n="449" who="S0483">but I guess they're going to make a hobby horse</u>
<u n="450" who="S0482">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what's that?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0483">you know? <pause dur="short"/> a stick with a horse on the end of it put that in the bin</u>
<u n="452" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0483">erm</u>
<u n="454" who="S0482">I mean I I think like they're quite good at doing organised events aren't they? cos they're quite</u>
<u n="455" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I mean ten pin bowling should we do ten pin bowling? they liked that</u>
<u n="456" who="S0482">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think yeah I think something a family activity</u>
<u n="457" who="S0483" trans="overlap">forty-five minutes up to four people nineteen quid</u>
<u n="458" who="S0482">or whatever <unclear/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0483">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="460" who="S0482">payment the cost of it's irrelevant</u>
<u n="461" who="S0483">yeah nine thirty AM to ten fifty PM you know I think I think why why don't we do that?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0482">yeah I mean I remember <pause dur="short"/> you know you just you just find a slot basically don't you?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0483">yeah absolutely and table tennis tournament it says eight plus years two hours eight pound fifty but I mean we could pay eight pound fifty just to get a table tennis table we can sit them in the corner with some colouring or an Ipad and we can play some table tennis</u>
<u n="464" who="S0482">I remember we did</u>
<u n="465" who="S0483" trans="overlap">cos they had that big games room didn't they?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0482" trans="overlap">oh yeah we we played table tennis when we were there last time</u>
<u n="467" who="S0483">maybe well they have that big games area</u>
<u n="468" who="S0482" trans="overlap">with erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and that lot <pause dur="short"/> do you remember?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0483" trans="overlap">we had that big games area didn't we? <pause dur="short"/> I to be honest <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I had a stonking headache and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was ill as well</u>
<u n="470" who="S0482">oh know yeah</u>
<u n="471" who="S0483"><vocal desc="cough"/> but yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="long"/> basically</u>
<u n="472" who="S0482">hey look table tennis that's a great idea especially if we bought like tablets and stuff and and they'd probably wanna join in as well</u>
<u n="473" who="S0483">yeah they would but at the same time I'd like to not</u>
<u n="474" who="S0482">I'd like them not to join in</u>
<u n="475" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'd like them not to join in <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="476" who="S0482">okay so what have we got? we've got bowling table tennis cheerleading</u>
<u n="477" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0482">sounds like a great night in</u>
<u n="479" who="S0483">does doesn't it?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0482">try and book this</u>
<u n="481" who="S0483">I'll make sure we get some decent food in for the Friday night <pause dur="short"/> ra ra</u>
<u n="482" who="S0482" trans="overlap">well I suggest we do what we did last time that was perfect</u>
<u n="483" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah absolutely yeah trip to Marks and Spencer's</u>
<u n="484" who="S0482">oh I heard a beep</u>
<u n="485" who="S0483">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah no it's it's gonna be good <pause dur="long"/> what's our erm viewing pleasure gonna be tonight?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0482">madame</u>
<u n="487" who="S0483">for your viewing pleasure</u>
<u n="488" who="S0482" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> shall we? we can do er okay <pause dur="short"/> trapped is an option</u>
<u n="489" who="S0483">Trapped?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0482">yeah the</u>
<u n="491" who="S0483">what's Trapped? <pause dur="short"/> trapped</u>
<u n="492" who="S0482">Trapped</u>
<u n="493" who="S0483">I don't know what that is</u>
<u n="494" who="S0482">oh come on that's</u>
<u n="495" who="S0483" trans="overlap">oh yeah Trapped yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0482">oh yeah Trapped</u>
<u n="497" who="S0483" trans="overlap">sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="498" who="S0482">the thing we're watching called Trapped I can't remember how else to say it</u>
<u n="499" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah alright alright <pause dur="short"/> erm yep Trapped yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0482">bit more?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0483">er yeah it might help me remember Trapped yes keep it coming <pause dur="short"/> I think I remember that <pause dur="short"/> oh bloody hell how's that happened? no</u>
<u n="502" who="S0482" trans="overlap">right I'm just gonna <unclear/> do it <pause dur="short"/> well that didn't take long did it? <pause dur="short"/> I think it's the excitement of talking about a little mini break</u>
<u n="503" who="S0483">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="504" who="S0482" trans="overlap">so now have you you gone onto the website now?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0483">what? <pause dur="short"/> of I'm not</u>
<u n="506" who="S0482">CP</u>
<u n="507" who="S0483">no</u>
<u n="508" who="S0482">go on book it literally just get on the</u>
<u n="509" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="510" who="S0482">when we when we left it before it may have been even earlier than we are now <pause dur="short"/> literally like it was quite hard to find things</u>
<u n="511" who="S0483">oh no <vocal desc="yawn"/> no I'm not</u>
<u n="512" who="S0482">you're an eejit</u>
<u n="513" who="S0483">no I'm not doing that</u>
<u n="514" who="S0482">but we need to do it</u>
<u n="515" who="S0483">ah I'm not doing it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0482">ah right <pause dur="short"/> okay so I'm not going to heat the plates up <pause dur="short"/> for obvious reasons <pause dur="short"/> which are not that obvious <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> so yeah so where would you ideally go on holiday?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0483">er <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I think ideally maybe the Amalfi coast <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0482">why don't you go there? <pause dur="short"/> yeah Italy perfect</u>
<u n="519" who="S0483">erm</u>
<u n="520" who="S0482">is there a good reason not to go to Italy oh think of it it'd be lovely fantastic food lovely you know <pause dur="short"/> is it expensive?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah erm er er maybe a little bit I'm not really sure what I'm doing with Italy I must say <pause dur="short"/> I also quite fancy going to Carcassonne</u>
<u n="522" who="S0482">erm who's who's who knows Italy well?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0483">er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I've I've already spoken to him about it <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean Italian Riviera is certainly an option I just I just dunno</u>
<u n="524" who="S0482">and that would also be nice cos like you know you've not been there before so for your sister and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it would feel like you know you're all doing something new whereas I think you will have been to Spain and stuff you know?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I just don't know enough about Italy to know where's by the sea and by the beach and things like that</u>
<u n="526" who="S0482">yeah but why do you know Spain enough? you're talking about places you've not been to</u>
<u n="527" who="S0483" trans="overlap">well you know <trunc>Cos</trunc>Costa del Sol's by the sea for example</u>
<u n="528" who="S0482">yeah but <pause dur="short"/> yeah sure but you also <pause dur="short"/> can find out quite easily if somewhere else is by the sea</u>
<u n="529" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0482">it's not gonna be very difficult is it?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0483">no</u>
<u n="532" who="S0482">you know you can</u>
<u n="533" who="S0483">like you you've been to Florence haven't you?</u>
<u n="534" who="S0482">erm <pause dur="short"/> no the the town I've been</u>
<u n="535" who="S0483">well like you know I don't know</u>
<u n="536" who="S0482" trans="overlap">Florence is meant to be nice but it's not it's not by the coast</u>
<u n="537" who="S0483" trans="overlap">but is it anywhere near the sea?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0482">it's it's inland</u>
<u n="539" who="S0483">yeah this is this is the thing I just don't know any I don't I don't know anything</u>
<u n="540" who="S0482">you can just you can find out where it is on the map and go oh look it's not near the sea</u>
<u n="541" who="S0483">I know but I mean basically I don't know what I'm doing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="542" who="S0482">yeah okay but</u>
<u n="543" who="S0483">I don't know where's by the sea</u>
<u n="544" who="S0482">right how how does one find out if something's by the sea or not?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0483">well I don't know but is it you know you don't want the extra effort <pause dur="short"/> of finding places <vocal desc="yawn"/> <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="546" who="S0482">I know but you're having to look for places in Spain what's the difference if you look in Italy?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0483">I don't know</u>
<u n="548" who="S0482">you can be agnostic to countries</u>
<u n="549" who="S0483">where's Malta?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0482">Malta?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0483">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0482">in the Mediterranean <pause dur="short"/> it's very anglicised <pause dur="short"/> they they you know</u>
<u n="553" who="S0483">is it Crete?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0482">no it's not Crete it's Malta <pause dur="short"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="555" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it was it just said there for a moment it said Malta Crete</u>
<u n="556" who="S0482">they're they're not that far away so Malta Crete as in <pause dur="short"/> they're they're probably categorising it in different areas but no they're not the same place <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'd say if you're looking for culture Malta's probably not the place</u>
<u n="557" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm not looking for culture</u>
<u n="558" who="S0482" trans="overlap">I think Italy sounds lovely I bet you'd have a fantastic time</u>
<u n="559" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I know I know but you know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="560" who="S0482">I'm happy to help you with er you know sourcing some Italy <pause dur="short"/> italy locations</u>
<u n="561" who="S0483">I'm checking out Malta now <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="562" who="S0482">right <pause dur="short"/> you do that</u>
<u n="563" who="S0483">but seriously where is Malta?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0482">it's in the Mediterranean it's quite far erm east and south</u>
<u n="565" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> how long do I have to be on a plane?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0482">four hours?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0483">what?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0482">it's quite far</u>
<u n="569" who="S0483">yeah I don't fancy that <pause dur="short"/> that's too far</u>
<u n="570" who="S0482">but <pause dur="short"/> I think you're <unclear/> if I was going on this holiday which I'm not</u>
<u n="571" who="S0483" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="572" who="S0482">I'd er I'd be most interested in the Italy bit</u>
<u n="573" who="S0483">yeah I know I know but the thing is my companions are not so</u>
<u n="574" who="S0482">oh why not? have they expressed that?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0483">no well not particularly but you know I I think <pause dur="short"/> I think they're more up for <pause dur="short"/> sitting around not doing much erm <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="576" who="S0482">hang on earlier I said find somewhere near a beach and you said oh I don't think we'll be spending much time on the beach</u>
<u n="577" who="S0483">I didn't <pause dur="short"/> I</u>
<u n="578" who="S0482" trans="overlap">you did</u>
<u n="579" who="S0483">I I no</u>
<u n="580" who="S0482">well we we could go back to the <trunc>record</trunc> we could go back to the recording maybe I'm wrong but I seem to remember</u>
<u n="581" who="S0483" trans="overlap">you are wrong</u>
<u n="582" who="S0482">cos I said an island's a good place</u>
<u n="583" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="584" who="S0482">because you're never very far from a beach</u>
<u n="585" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0482">and you said I I remember you saying I thought I remember you saying something like but that's not really what we're after</u>
<u n="587" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no no no no no you you said there's lots of beaches nearby and I said we we wouldn't be really travelling around much as in like you know not planning on</u>
<u n="588" who="S0482" trans="overlap">oh sorry I <trunc>misinter</trunc></u>
<u n="589" who="S0483">yeah you did</u>
<u n="590" who="S0482">so you <trunc>wan</trunc> you want somewhere on a beach?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0483">yeah basically we don't want to have to be you know travelling here there and everywhere to get to a beach we just wanna be near the beach</u>
<u n="592" who="S0482">and you definitely don't want to be travelling for very for very long</u>
<u n="593" who="S0483">no</u>
<u n="594" who="S0482">erm cos you're only going for three nights or something</u>
<u n="595" who="S0483">exactly <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> right</u>
<u n="596" who="S0482">yeah is it time to eat?</u>
<u n="597" who="S0483">I think it's time to eat</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
