<text id="SFXF">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:25:47</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-11</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0024 S0144</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Bell pub, Norfolk</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Cars, Facebook, internet</topics>
		<activity>Couple have a drink and chat in a pub garden.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T20</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0024">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>28</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0144">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Norwich, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0144">I don't know if I've put the volume up <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's on maximum <pause dur="short"/> there you go <pause dur="short"/> well how long did that take to get here then? Forty minutes?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0024">yeah it wasn't that far really <pause dur="short"/> was it?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> on a day like this it doesn't matter does it <pause dur="short"/> it's nice walking</u>
<u n="4" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I'd like to go to that pub quiz but that really would be pushing it walking back late at night</u>
<u n="5" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh I'd love to go to a pub quiz</u>
<u n="6" who="S0024">plus like you said we haven't got a very big team at the moment</u>
<u n="7" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> it can be a bit embarrassing with two people if it goes wrong</u>
<u n="8" who="S0024" trans="overlap">why?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0144">well if it's about TV or famous people <pause dur="short"/> we wouldn't get anything</u>
<u n="10" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> we'd be <trunc>sc</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0144">you need a couple of those <pause dur="short"/> a couple of people that are into that don't you in your team</u>
<u n="12" who="S0024">yeah yeah you've got to mix it up a bit <pause dur="short"/> there you go <pause dur="short"/> I'm just telling them that we got here <pause dur="short"/> no that's me <pause dur="short"/> oops</u>
<u n="13" who="S0144">you just told yourself that you've got here</u>
<u n="14" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Look at that funny red car</u>
<u n="15" who="S0144">yeah it's pathetic isn't it?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0024">looks like a erm one of those flat pack cars that you put together yourselves</u>
<u n="17" who="S0144">A kit car?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is isn't it?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0024">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> that's what it looks like but I don't know</u>
<u n="21" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no it's a Toyota</u>
<u n="22" who="S0024">mm?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0144">well that's what the wheel says anyway</u>
<u n="24" who="S0024">well you have to buy some sort of wheels <pause dur="short"/> has to have</u>
<u n="25" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no but it looks like a Toyota</u>
<u n="26" who="S0024">does it?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0024">how old is that?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0144">eighties?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0144">I don't understand those two seaters <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm just way too practical <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="32" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> even <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s a bit gutted about her two seater cos he bought it for her to be nice and just so that she's got a little run around while he's out in the van</u>
<u n="33" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0024">you know <pause dur="short"/> se <trunc>g</trunc> cos otherwise she'd be like us and just stuck</u>
<u n="35" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0024">can't get out all on her own <pause dur="short"/> so he bought that for that <pause dur="short"/> but even she was like oh god well I <trunc>c</trunc> if it was a if it had some more seats I could come by and pick you and you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> up and then we could go out somewhere</u>
<u n="37" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0024">but she can't</u>
<u n="39" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0024">so it's a bit useless really <pause dur="short"/> if you can't pick your friends up and go somewhere then just useless</u>
<u n="41" who="S0144">well it's big enough for her and her dog isn't it?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's it</u>
<u n="43" who="S0144">it looks nice <pause dur="short"/> well it's like my brother <pause dur="short"/> remember? With <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0024" trans="overlap">what's happened?  What's happened?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0144">when she came to meet us at Heathrow at that hotel</u>
<u n="46" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh god</u>
<u n="47" who="S0144">and then they they and then we had to go to the pub</u>
<u n="48" who="S0024" trans="overlap">that was an absolute nightmare</u>
<u n="49" who="S0144">and they were like okay do you mind walking? Cos we've only got a two seater <pause dur="short"/> we had to walk <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't that far <pause dur="short"/> it was only half a mile or so</u>
<u n="50" who="S0024">and then we got stuck at the bus as well <pause dur="short"/> we we missed most of the family reunion basically</u>
<u n="51" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah we did</u>
<u n="52" who="S0024">Cos nobody could come pick us up in these two seater cars</u>
<u n="53" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0024">know what I was going to say? Is what happened about his car the other day? Cos I didn't hear all the news</u>
<u n="55" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0024">Cos he said it <trunc>wa</trunc> it got <pause dur="short"/> somebody <trunc>bro</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="57" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> someone <pause dur="short"/> it was in the car park at work and someone driving the forklift <pause dur="short"/> erm he was parked behind a palette with refrigerators on it</u>
<u n="58" who="S0024" trans="overlap">why was he parked behind a palette?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0144">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> but the forklift went through the palette and went straight through his erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> his radiator which exploded all over the place</u>
<u n="60" who="S0024">oh my god</u>
<u n="61" who="S0144">and I think it it went through half of the engine as well</u>
<u n="62" who="S0024">really?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0144">and it's destroyed it <pause dur="short"/> erm but he was saying that work said erm they have taken full responsibility for it <pause dur="short"/> they're not going to go through the insurance companies at all</u>
<u n="64" who="S0024">oh really <pause dur="short"/> why?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0144" trans="overlap">which is good <pause dur="short"/> huh?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0024">why?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0144">well cos he'd lose his no claims wouldn't he</u>
<u n="68" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0144">erm so they've</u>
<u n="70" who="S0024">so they're going to pay for it?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0144">yeah they've put it into the garage <pause dur="short"/> said it will take about a week</u>
<u n="72" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0144">they'll pay for everything <pause dur="short"/> and they've given him a van to drive around for in the meantime with all the petrol paid for</u>
<u n="74" who="S0024">yep <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> that sounds alright</u>
<u n="75" who="S0144" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0024">it just depends on how long it's going to take to fix it</u>
<u n="77" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> it depends as well how they fix it</u>
<u n="78" who="S0024">who's fixing it? Somebody at work?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> no <trunc>pro</trunc> they've given it to garage but</u>
<u n="80" who="S0024">okay</u>
<u n="81" who="S0144">I don't know with <pause dur="short"/> when the engine gets damaged that badly <pause dur="short"/> I mean it might not ever be the same again</u>
<u n="82" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0144">things might go wrong more frequently</u>
<u n="84" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="85" who="S0144">I don't know</u>
<u n="86" who="S0024">no who knows? He'll buy a new car then won't he?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> that was <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't the new one it was the old banger he bought</u>
<u n="88" who="S0024">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> I thought it was his brand new car</u>
<u n="89" who="S0144">no no god no</u>
<u n="90" who="S0024">what banger?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0144">he bought a little thing <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what it is</u>
<u n="92" who="S0024">did he? I'm getting really confused now</u>
<u n="93" who="S0144">he's got a little run around car <pause dur="short"/> it's just a rust bucket <pause dur="short"/> and he's got that one him and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> bought <pause dur="short"/> that big car</u>
<u n="94" who="S0024" trans="overlap">they picked us up in the nice car</u>
<u n="95" who="S0144">yeah that big four by four looking thing</u>
<u n="96" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> oh I do know because you've just pointed it to me</u>
<u n="97" who="S0144" trans="overlap">which they stuck on credit</u>
<u n="98" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> er I just hope everybody's alright with this credit stuff</u>
<u n="99" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> they won't be <pause dur="short"/> well it's alright if you can <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think</u>
<u n="100" who="S0024" trans="overlap">we're funny aren't we cos we're <pause dur="short"/> we haven't got anything <pause dur="short"/> we haven't even got a car to get to the pub <pause dur="short"/> we have to walk <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="101" who="S0144">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I quite like it though</u>
<u n="102" who="S0024">I do quite like it</u>
<u n="103" who="S0144">but I don't</u>
<u n="104" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but I do feel like I'm missing out sometimes on like a car or something like that <pause dur="short"/> something <trunc>p</trunc> something useful</u>
<u n="105" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but things like phones <pause dur="short"/> I mean I think I've looked at my phone once this week</u>
<u n="106" who="S0024">that's because we haven't got any friends</u>
<u n="107" who="S0144">any then I realised I haven't got any batteries <pause dur="short"/> so it's been charging for the last three days</u>
<u n="108" who="S0024">what without it being switched on?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0144">no I think it was switched on but</u>
<u n="110" who="S0024">but you haven't looked at it</u>
<u n="111" who="S0144">I haven't looked at it <pause dur="short"/> well I'm just waiting for <pause dur="short"/> because all our correspondence is coming through email at the moment <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="112" who="S0024">yeah that's true <pause dur="short"/> nobody's really got these new English numbers have they?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and and I don't know anyone who lives around here so I'm not exactly phoning anyone up saying oh do you fancy a pint? or whatever</u>
<u n="114" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I mean we should get down to London or something shouldn't we?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah I need to get out of here <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> I'm starting to pull my hair out</u>
<u n="116" who="S0024">well I think tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> I know we keep saying oh tomorrow is crunch day but tomorrow really is</u>
<u n="117" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it is it is crunch day tomorrow</u>
<u n="118" who="S0024">erm if they don't contact us tomorrow I'm going to phone them</u>
<u n="119" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0024">I nearly thought about phoning them today but I thought I'd wait for London correspondence <pause dur="short"/> so I think up early tomorrow and if they haven't phoned <pause dur="short"/> if they haven't contacted us by ten o'clock we will phone them</u>
<u n="121" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah cos ten o'clock will be what? Two o'clock there</u>
<u n="122" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> then we have to phone</u>
<u n="123" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0024">definitely</u>
<u n="125" who="S0144">yeah yeah I'll phone</u>
<u n="126" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0144">we have got his number haven't we?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0024">yep yeah we have got his number <pause dur="short"/> we should have phoned before really <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why we didn't</u>
<u n="129" who="S0144" trans="overlap">er <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="130" who="S0024">that's weird isn't it? There's that little bit of <pause dur="short"/> I'm not very good on the phone <pause dur="short"/> I always have that little bit of <pause dur="short"/> not a phobia but I am a little bit anxious of getting on the phone sometimes <pause dur="short"/> I am</u>
<u n="131" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0024">it's weird isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why</u>
<u n="133" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0024">it's cos I don't use it very often</u>
<u n="135" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's because your parents</u>
<u n="136" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I'm not really a phone person <pause dur="short"/> I I mean Skype took me ages to get used to but Skype is alright now I can get used to that</u>
<u n="137" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0024">but it made me think <pause dur="short"/> you know like when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was on Skype the other day and her friend the the chef <pause dur="short"/> I've forgotten what her <trunc>na</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> she came bounding along and sat in front Skype <pause dur="short"/> hello <pause dur="short"/> and I thought wow <pause dur="short"/> she's pretty confident because I don't know if my friends' parents or family were on Skype I don't thnk I would be bounding across the room just to say hello</u>
<u n="139" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0024">erm cos I don't like phones and things like that</u>
<u n="141" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0024">I like face to face better</u>
<u n="143" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah well me too</u>
<u n="144" who="S0024">I find there's oh there's <pause dur="short"/> people don't understand me I don't think unless I'm face to face</u>
<u n="145" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="146" who="S0024">you just always feel like I've said something weird or they've not understood me <pause dur="short"/> it's like that anyway <pause dur="short"/> face to face in my house <pause dur="short"/> mum never understands what I'm saying <pause dur="short"/> oh bless her</u>
<u n="147" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0024">oh and they just <pause dur="short"/> but you know at least you can look at somebody's face and if it if they look like they've got the wrong end of the stick you can clarify your point or something like that</u>
<u n="149" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah which happens to me constantly</u>
<u n="150" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> you can tell from their eyes <pause dur="short"/> yeah if they're looking at you like you're an idiot then it's like oh no hang on a minute you completely misunderstood what I'm talking about <pause dur="short"/> I think you can fix it</u>
<u n="151" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0024">whereas on this Facebook and stuff and on the telephone I find it really hard</u>
<u n="153" who="S0144">mm mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0024">I find it really hard to</u>
<u n="155" who="S0144">well I'm absolutely sick of Facebook <pause dur="short"/> god <pause dur="short"/> I'm ninety-five percent there to closing it</u>
<u n="156" who="S0024">no don't close it because it's good for the old correspondents <pause dur="short"/> you don't have to do all of the updates and stuff</u>
<u n="157" who="S0144">oh god</u>
<u n="158" who="S0024">why?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0144">just irritates me <pause dur="short"/> well so many reasons</u>
<u n="160" who="S0024">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> but there's</u>
<u n="161" who="S0144">just the crap people put on it</u>
<u n="162" who="S0024">well it's annoying there's so many other people and they're using it and and then</u>
<u n="163" who="S0144">and then</u>
<u n="164" who="S0024" trans="overlap">like some people if you if you they don't get a message from you or from somebody they're they're offended</u>
<u n="165" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0024">and it's like well I haven't been on it for for two weeks or <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="167" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0024" trans="overlap">why would I have sent you a message?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and then I I keep getting sent all these fucking things saying oh poor little <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dying of whatever</u>
<u n="170" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0144">pass this on otherwise you're a selfless bastard <pause dur="short"/> basically is what it says you know</u>
<u n="172" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="173" who="S0144">it's like for god sake <pause dur="short"/> go away <pause dur="short"/> get out of my space <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to read all that crap</u>
<u n="174" who="S0024">yeah it's horrible that people <pause dur="short"/> it's almost well it's like an old an old erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't mean this in a bad way but like an old gypsy woman casting a spell or something <pause dur="short"/> not bad not bad on the gypsies but but it's like a it's like people want to cast curses on you for not</u>
<u n="175" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah that's what it's like <pause dur="short"/> it's like the old gypsies going around with their lavender or whatever it was <pause dur="short"/> and I put a curse on you <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0024">but that doesn't mean like <pause dur="short"/> I mean how can they say if you don't answer something like that that you're a bad person?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0144">well</u>
<u n="178" who="S0024">it's just <trunc>stu</trunc> stupid to say that <trunc>som</trunc> if they don't post this on their wall then they're a bad person</u>
<u n="179" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it's idiotic <pause dur="short"/> but that's how most religions operate as well <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well if you don't go to church you're a bad person</u>
<u n="180" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh dear that's not very nice at all is it <pause dur="short"/> who <trunc>sa</trunc>? Well not that many people say that nowadays <pause dur="short"/> not nowadays</u>
<u n="181" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well they don't now in this country <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="182" who="S0024" trans="overlap">even even people who are religious they say it's okay if you want to pray at home <pause dur="short"/> it's alright</u>
<u n="183" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah but another thing about Facebook that I hate is how when you write your messages <pause dur="short"/> your private messages to people and then you have another chat about three years later <pause dur="short"/> your previous message is there</u>
<u n="184" who="S0024" trans="overlap">the whole history <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no but I found a way <pause dur="short"/> I found a way to delete it</u>
<u n="185" who="S0144">and if you've had <pause dur="short"/> you know you could be talking about anything</u>
<u n="186" who="S0024">yeah I know it's not good</u>
<u n="187" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and then it's right there next to your new one so you've got all this history which is directly tied to the present and you can't escape it</u>
<u n="188" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0144">I mean some people must be having nightmares with that</u>
<u n="190" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0144">I don't like at all because it it it colours the the new message</u>
<u n="192" who="S0024" trans="overlap">it just pops up <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0144">it's not a fresh message <pause dur="short"/> it's it's influenced by all this baggage of the past</u>
<u n="194" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> I emailed <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the other day and that came up <pause dur="short"/> and and the last I'd said it was just after she'd got married and like you know that we didn't go to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s wedding but erm <pause dur="short"/> it was just after she got married and she had put oh hope you're doing alright <pause dur="short"/> I'm <trunc>goin</trunc> I just got married to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I said I said on the message oh congratulations <pause dur="short"/> that's great <pause dur="short"/> right I'm going into the jungle for a bit cos I'm having a rough time <pause dur="short"/> erm I'll speak to you when I come out <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0024">and I didn't speak to her since then <pause dur="short"/> that was four <pause dur="short"/> when did we go?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0144">I'm going into the jungle cos I'm having a rough time</u>
<u n="198" who="S0024">yeah do you remember? When we were in China and we said right <pause dur="short"/> let's go to the jungle <pause dur="short"/> and we went and we went all the way down</u>
<u n="199" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0024" trans="overlap">and we went we just travelled for days <pause dur="short"/> we travelled for about a week</u>
<u n="201" who="S0144" trans="overlap">we travelled about three thousand miles <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0024">and then finally got to to Sumatra and went in the jungle and sat there</u>
<u n="203" who="S0144">yeah that was</u>
<u n="204" who="S0024">but that was because we were enjoying <unclear/> and and and I'd put I'll email you when I come out and I never emailed her back</u>
<u n="205" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That was fucked up man <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="206" who="S0024">but she was off <pause dur="short"/> obviously wasn't enquiring how I was doing <pause dur="short"/> and then I'd put on there the message now <pause dur="short"/> I mean how many years ago was that? Five? Six?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh it must have been <pause dur="short"/> don't know</u>
<u n="208" who="S0024">six <pause dur="short"/> six years ago <pause dur="short"/> something like that <pause dur="short"/> and I didn't realise because she was only like an old friend from school wasn't she?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0144" trans="overlap">five years ago <pause dur="short"/> wow <pause dur="short"/> five years ago</u>
<u n="210" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but she was an old friend from school why would I contact her all the time? And I don't really do that kind of thing</u>
<u n="211" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0024">and she doesn't either obviously <pause dur="short"/> cos otherwise there would be some more messages and erm yeah the next the next one was wow that was quite a long time <pause dur="short"/> I put <pause dur="short"/> Wow that was longer than I thought <pause dur="short"/> I haven't been in the jungle that long but how are you? God can you believe it <pause dur="short"/> But</u>
<u n="213" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0144">yeah and every time you message her she's going to go oh god yeah she never did bloody write to me in that jungle thing <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0024">no I mine was the last message so I'm pleased that mine was the last message cos <unclear/></u>
<u n="216" who="S0144" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> well that's another thing <pause dur="short"/> well make sure mine's the last message <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't want that kind of relationship with people</u>
<u n="217" who="S0024">no but but that on the plus side you've you have got these <trunc>con</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> you've got people</u>
<u n="218" who="S0144" trans="overlap">that that is the only plus side is that I've got into touch with people that I thought I'd lost</u>
<u n="219" who="S0024" trans="overlap">people that you can <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and you might not speak to them all the time but they're there and if you need them and you you know the special people <pause dur="short"/> that they email you</u>
<u n="220" who="S0144" trans="overlap">but it was only <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but now you've got their email address can't you just leave it as that?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0024">well it depends on you doesn't it?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well is there a way of getting their email address?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well if you've got their email <pause dur="short"/> have you got all their everybody's email address nowadays?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well I could ask for them couldn't I</u>
<u n="225" who="S0024">I hardly use email these days <pause dur="short"/> I just use Facebook</u>
<u n="226" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well no one does do they <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0024">apart <trunc>fr</trunc> yeah apart from the there is a few people who are just on the <unclear/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0144" trans="overlap">writing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> likes your status</u>
<u n="229" who="S0024">I don't do anything like that</u>
<u n="230" who="S0144" trans="overlap">you don't even write anything <pause dur="short"/> you just click on a button now</u>
<u n="231" who="S0024">I don't do too much of that crap</u>
<u n="232" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>likes what you've said</u>
<u n="233" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I only do that <pause dur="short"/> but this is the bad manipulative thing because I do that with the people that I know are gonna care whether I like their status or not</u>
<u n="234" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0024">you know most of my friends wouldn't give two monkeys <pause dur="short"/> they wouldn't give two monkeys whether I you know was interested in what they say</u>
<u n="236" who="S0144" trans="overlap">but there's no effort is there <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0024">oh I like their picture <pause dur="short"/> but some people <pause dur="short"/> they do give two monkeys</u>
<u n="238" who="S0144">yeah but you can't live your life if you're trying to please people who care about stuff you couldn't give two hoots about</u>
<u n="239" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no I know <pause dur="short"/> that's what makes it <trunc>har</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> well it hard when it's family because when it's friends if they if they're you know they probably wouldn't stay my friends too long if they have expectations like that from me</u>
<u n="240" who="S0144">but if you look at half of your friends on Facebook I bet you don't give a damn about half of those people</u>
<u n="241" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no no I should clean it up really <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0144" trans="overlap">but then you can't <pause dur="short"/> it's so <pause dur="short"/> I don't know it's such a weird thing innit?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0024">it is really weird <pause dur="short"/> and now that everybody has got those stupid timelines I'm not getting one <pause dur="short"/> I refuse <pause dur="short"/> unless they make me <pause dur="short"/> I'm not getting one <pause dur="short"/> I can't believe everybody's signing up to it and just clicking on the button going yeah that looks nice <pause dur="short"/> I don't</u>
<u n="244" who="S0144" trans="overlap">why don't you want it?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0024">because there's something about it <pause dur="short"/> I think erm I was I I saw something on the TV about it and it's to do with access of information again</u>
<u n="246" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I haven't even looked at it <pause dur="short"/> what does it? What is it?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0024">and erm them recording your <trunc>informa</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> what? You haven't looked at it?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="249" who="S0024">right <pause dur="short"/> well it's a timeline right from when you started all the way through <pause dur="short"/> so then you can look on a year and look at somebody's yearly posts or you can click on a month <pause dur="short"/> so say like this Christmas <pause dur="short"/> last Christmas you could look at somebody's thing and go right er two thousand and eleven</u>
<u n="250" who="S0144" trans="overlap">but who gives a shit? Who gives a shit what I was doing last September?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0024" trans="overlap">what were you doing? It's it's basically a diary of your life</u>
<u n="252" who="S0144">so you're looking in other people's diaries?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0024" trans="overlap">it's a diary with photos <pause dur="short"/> but it's it's different for you because and it's different for me because we don't put pictures up right <pause dur="short"/> but people who <trunc>t</trunc> who go round taking pictures and writing loads of comments and stuff <pause dur="short"/> it's basically a diary <pause dur="short"/> a recorded online diary that everybody can read</u>
<u n="254" who="S0144">well a diary with entries of five words at a time</u>
<u n="255" who="S0024">but it but all the photos <pause dur="short"/> it's like a photo album as well</u>
<u n="256" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0024">yeah well I hate it <pause dur="short"/> but you don't have <pause dur="short"/> yeah I hate it too</u>
<u n="258" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> so are they going to make everyone do that are they?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0024">they were talking about making everybody do it but I don't know if that's true</u>
<u n="260" who="S0144">well it will eventually won't it</u>
<u n="261" who="S0024">I don't want it though <pause dur="short"/> I just want my <pause dur="short"/> god they keep changing it and I don't understand and I <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="262" who="S0144" trans="overlap">but they have to keep changing it that's the whole purpose <pause dur="short"/> you have to</u>
<u n="263" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but I don't want it to change because once I know how to use something then I just want it to continue <pause dur="short"/> and like when they changed it last time all of the security settings changed</u>
<u n="264" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="265" who="S0024">and like and you're supposed to know that <pause dur="short"/> and you're supposed to go on that and change your security again <pause dur="short"/> I don't agree with that</u>
<u n="266" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="267" who="S0024">if you've got security settings to say they can't look at my pictures then it should be stuck <pause dur="short"/> that should be for life <pause dur="short"/> why should you have to come and do it again? Why should they be able to change it? But with Google</u>
<u n="268" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> well I was reading something the other day <pause dur="short"/> it someone was saying like oh how so what if they are taking our Facebook statuses you know what difference is that going to make to my life?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> depends what you write <pause dur="short"/> like we would write stuff about revolutions and shit wouldn't we? We'd write</u>
<u n="270" who="S0144">well</u>
<u n="271" who="S0024">we'd be arrested</u>
<u n="272" who="S0144">well we did get cut off didn't we <pause dur="short"/> but erm <pause dur="short"/> what was I saying?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0024">like why why does it matter? Why does it matter that they have the information?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0144">yeah because it basically have you heard that all of this stuff is going to these big vaults in the North Pole?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I've heard that <pause dur="short"/> I don't know about that</u>
<u n="276" who="S0144" trans="overlap">where you've got these underground storage facilities <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if that's cos it's cold and they need to keep it cold <pause dur="short"/> cos it runs at a super</u>
<u n="277" who="S0024" trans="overlap">such a big hard drive <pause dur="short"/> it's going to overheat</u>
<u n="278" who="S0144">but can you imagine the marketing possibilities <pause dur="short"/> like how to really get <pause dur="short"/> like with these computer software now with the amount of data you could really <pause dur="short"/> like the data mining possibilities would really intense</u>
<u n="279" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah but can you believe that they spend all of this <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="280" who="S0144">that's that's what it's about</u>
<u n="281" who="S0024">but can you believe that this kind of marketing can produce so much revenue and so much money that it's worth it <pause dur="short"/> it's worth it</u>
<u n="282" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well no because it's it's producing nothing <pause dur="short"/> it's a point why this society is fucked <pause dur="short"/> because it's producing <pause dur="short"/> it's not producing anything physical</u>
<u n="283" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><unclear/> No</u>
<u n="284" who="S0144">all <pause dur="short"/> half of <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> ninety percent of probably what this country produces is just abstract shit</u>
<u n="285" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well it's seeing what kind of abstract shit people like</u>
<u n="286" who="S0144">so if it's generating ideas or <pause dur="short"/> I mean ideas are good <pause dur="short"/> you've got to innovate <pause dur="short"/> you've got to progress</u>
<u n="287" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0144">but when you're generating like marketing stuff that's just generating greed</u>
<u n="289" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="290" who="S0144">I don't know and then you've got all of these financial products</u>
<u n="291" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but Tom you've got to be really careful on your Google because I was on I was on it right <pause dur="short"/> erm every time you sign in you're the whole of the Google address changes to an HTTP <pause dur="short"/> and HTTP is what it used to be didn't it <pause dur="short"/> do you remember when you used to have to type HTTP dot WWW</u>
<u n="292" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh right</u>
<u n="293" who="S0024">right <pause dur="short"/> that's all gone right</u>
<u n="294" who="S0144" trans="overlap">oh has it?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0024">now it's just WWW but if you want high security <pause dur="short"/> security <pause dur="short"/> where their access to your data</u>
<u n="296" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh I want security <pause dur="short"/> yes please</u>
<u n="297" who="S0024">it's now <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if you've noticed <pause dur="short"/> now if you want high security Hotmail are asking me to do it <pause dur="short"/> google are doing it</u>
<u n="298" who="S0144">what the phone number?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0024">as soon as you sign into Google</u>
<u n="300" who="S0144">it wants your phone number <pause dur="short"/> is that? No?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> as soon as you sign into Google it becomes a HTTP address and I don't know what they've done <pause dur="short"/> but they were talking about their security that erm then anything that you go on while you're logged into Google <pause dur="short"/> any anything you search any website you go on <pause dur="short"/> anything like that is all connected to your web <pause dur="short"/> to you</u>
<u n="302" who="S0144">hmm</u>
<u n="303" who="S0024">to them building a profile of you</u>
<u n="304" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0024">but HTTP used to be a normal thing that you used to see</u>
<u n="306" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0024">so now they're now on my Hotmail it flashes up <pause dur="short"/> high security <pause dur="short"/> would you like this high security HTTP? And it seems like such a normal thing to do because it all used to be that anyway</u>
<u n="308" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0024">it used to be that <pause dur="short"/> I mean I really don't really know much about it <pause dur="short"/> but it I know that used to be that <pause dur="short"/> now they're asking me to do that for high security and Google do that now and they've just had that erm big European legal battle haven't they <pause dur="short"/> with like the</u>
<u n="310" who="S0144" trans="overlap">hmm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0024">with all of your data <pause dur="short"/> storing all of your data</u>
<u n="312" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="313" who="S0024">and storing while you're logged into Google <pause dur="short"/> they wanted access to anything that you've searched on the internet</u>
<u n="314" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0024">and I'm stopping using Google Chrome <pause dur="short"/> I'm not going to use Google <pause dur="short"/> I'm using Mozilla</u>
<u n="316" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well I've noticed cos I was trying to do something the other day I can't remember what but I had to find out where Google Chrome was storing all of the information</u>
<u n="317" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="318" who="S0144">and it isn't it's not like Internet Explorer <pause dur="short"/> it stores it in this really weird place <pause dur="short"/> like really deep inside somewhere and it's it's a real hassle getting getting to it</u>
<u n="319" who="S0024">storing what?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0144">well storing the the cookies and all of the other stuff</u>
<u n="321" who="S0024">well cos yeah with Google Chrome you have to delete it from the computer and then you delete it from the Google Chrome site as well <pause dur="short"/> you have to delete it twice</u>
<u n="322" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it's really weird <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it's bizarre the way they do it and I don't know why they do it like that</u>
<u n="323" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0144">but I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it's annoying because you click on something and then every advert that bloody pops up is to do with that <pause dur="short"/> I'm still getting marquees popping up</u>
<u n="325" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh marquees <pause dur="short"/> we've got to book that <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0144">yeah but you know people would say oh that's convenient</u>
<u n="327" who="S0024">it's not convenient because I because they're the companies that we don't want <pause dur="short"/> they're the companies that we research and we didn't want them and now they just pop onto the screen all of the time</u>
<u n="328" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="329" who="S0024">it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="330" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0024">but that's why you've got to be really careful with Google now</u>
<u n="332" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="333" who="S0024">and now I think we should change to <pause dur="short"/> can we change to Mozilla Fox?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well it's like <pause dur="short"/> it's just <pause dur="short"/> well I don't know <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> whatever</u>
<u n="335" who="S0024">I don't like Google anymore <pause dur="short"/> I use Mozilla Fox on the other <pause dur="short"/> on dad's computer and it works fine and I'm happy with it and it's nice <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why we went on off it <pause dur="short"/> we went off Internet Explorer because we thought Microsoft taking over the world weren't we</u>
<u n="336" who="S0144" trans="overlap">internet Explorer's really clunky and it's just horrible</u>
<u n="337" who="S0024">clunky?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0024">they're all the same</u>
<u n="340" who="S0144">no they're not <pause dur="short"/> Internet Explorer's horrible</u>
<u n="341" who="S0024">really?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0144">it looks ugly <pause dur="short"/> it's slow to respond <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I just don't like it</u>
<u n="343" who="S0024">well Mozilla Fox then <pause dur="short"/> I think we should do</u>
<u n="344" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah okay</u>
<u n="345" who="S0024">and you've just got to make sure that you always sign out from your Google account</u>
<u n="346" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0024">Cos of those <pause dur="short"/> but it's so weird though that HTTP thing <pause dur="short"/> I'd like to research it <pause dur="short"/> I don't really know what it's all about <pause dur="short"/> but that's my idea of it</u>
<u n="348" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and I liked the Google one because <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> no I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I like the Google one because you've got that iGoogle stuff with which I used a lot for the currency converters</u>
<u n="349" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you did <pause dur="short"/> but now we don't so much because</u>
<u n="350" who="S0144">well only because we're here <pause dur="short"/> we'll be gone again soon</u>
<u n="351" who="S0024">well there was a glitch wasn't there <pause dur="short"/> and it didn't come up <pause dur="short"/> we lost our homepage that's why</u>
<u n="352" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and I've got direct I've got a direct link to my email as well <pause dur="short"/> my gmail</u>
<u n="353" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> no Mozilla Fox you can do that <pause dur="short"/> you've got a direct link as soon as you go on Google</u>
<u n="354" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0024">you only have to go on the Google homepage and it says gmail at the top <pause dur="short"/> it's nothing to do with the</u>
<u n="356" who="S0144">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> oh isn't it?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> not to do with Google Chrome</u>
<u n="358" who="S0144">okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah well we could do that</u>
<u n="359" who="S0024" trans="overlap">shall we? Are we going to walk back now?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0144">are we going to have another one or are we walking back?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> we'll walk back because it's getting cold and I think <pause dur="short"/> we'll have to come down again</u>
<u n="362" who="S0144">mm <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="363" who="S0024">it's nice I like it</u>
<u n="364" who="S0144">it is a nice pub</u>
<u n="365" who="S0024">if we go and speak to them in the pub and say hello and find out about the quiz and</u>
<u n="366" who="S0144">well it says Wednesday</u>
<u n="367" who="S0024">I know but we can say hello and say goodbye</u>
<u n="368" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0024">yeah?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0144">yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> oh I need to turn that off <pause dur="short"/> it's the red one</u>
</body>
</text>
