<text id="SFYX">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:45:26</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-10-07</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0486 S0491</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Marion’s home in Taunton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Aquaintences</relationships>
		<topics>Work and childhood, general life.</topics>
		<activity>Acquaintances getting to know each other better. </activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T17</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0486">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Well, Somerset</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/Wales</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>I may have a slight Somerset accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Taunton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>40 years on and off</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>retired artist and antique dealer/gallery owner</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0491">
				<exactage>69</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sydney</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Australia</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>R.P</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Taunton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired speech and Langauge Therapist</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- to A-level, no recent use</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0486">there we are good morning <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0491" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> good morning <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0486">erm and erm <pause dur="short"/> I see from your form that you were born in <anon type="place"/> in Australia</u>
<u n="4" who="S0491">mm yes</u>
<u n="5" who="S0486">so can you tell me er erm how er how old you were when you left Australia?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0491">yes well if I can go back a step just to explain both my parents er are English</u>
<u n="7" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0491">or were English and they met on a ship going out</u>
<u n="9" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right yes</u>
<u n="10" who="S0491">and erm my father was a clergyman and he'd signed on for five years of <unclear/> poverty chastity and obedience in a <trunc>b</trunc> what was called the Bush Brotherhood in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right right oh</u>
<u n="12" who="S0491">and erm so it was a bit inconvenient really that he met my mother going out but anyway they kept in touch for five years and at the end of his five years of going around the bush erm he they got married</u>
<u n="13" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="14" who="S0491">and er and then the war came and he was a chaplain in the Australian army and then erm we lived in two two parishes in <anon type="place"/> and came back to England when I was seven</u>
<u n="15" who="S0486">oh right</u>
<u n="16" who="S0491">and that was quite hard for my mother because she'd left all her family behind</u>
<u n="17" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="18" who="S0491">cos the whole family had emigrated but not together she'd gone separately erm so <pause dur="short"/> anyway that that's what happened and and we ended up in <anon type="place"/> actually because my father had to look for a parish and for us to live somewhere <pause dur="short"/> erm and so I spent most of my childhood in in <anon type="place"/> just over the border from <anon type="place"/> actually so we used to do our shopping in <anon type="place"/> so coming to live in <anon type="place"/> was a little bit like coming home</u>
<u n="19" who="S0486">yes I see it's it's it's a a bit weird because we've got similar circumstances cos my father was actually erm he he became a padre in the army erm but but he was also a vicar and we moved from <anon type="place"/> when I was seven erm and erm we went to Germany for three years</u>
<u n="20" who="S0491">really?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0486">and another thing that I can draw a parallel with is that when we came back from Germany cos he did three years that's all it was a sort of er appeal from the bishop for erm clergy to go abroad and when we came back there was no living for us and we had to look for one and that was extremely difficult we ended up living in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0491">oh goodness me</u>
<u n="23" who="S0486" trans="overlap">isn't it strange?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0491">well there's a bigger coincidence because when we came back from Australia we had to sort of stay with various people and we came to <anon type="place"/> and stayed in erm the on the edge of the park <pause dur="short"/> can't think of the name of the road</u>
<u n="25" who="S0486">erm <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0491"><anon type="place"/> yeah we caught with a former colleague of my my mother's and erm dad went to see the bishop of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="28" who="S0491">to look for a living</u>
<u n="29" who="S0486" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0491">and one of the livings that was available was <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0486">was it?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0491"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes</u>
<u n="33" who="S0486">how weird</u>
<u n="34" who="S0491">that is probably not just after your father left it because I'm I'm a lot older than you so it would've all happened before</u>
<u n="35" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right before how weird</u>
<u n="36" who="S0491">yes yes</u>
<u n="37" who="S0486">isn't the life's full of coincidences isn't it?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0491" trans="overlap">it is <pause dur="short"/> but it but I think I don't know why he decided against it it just didn't feel right presumably and we ended up actually in a lovely place on the coast near <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0486">oh oh wow yes</u>
<u n="40" who="S0491">he had two parishes <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0486">oh right course <anon type="place"/> is very I mean the war the horrible war story there and the tragedy of <anon type="place"/> yes</u>
<u n="42" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes yes yes well at the time that wasn't the facts weren't really known</u>
<u n="43" who="S0486">ah it was all secret then wasn't it?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0491" trans="overlap">it was a bit secret</u>
<u n="45" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0491">and er but while we were there erm the commemoration erm stone was put up but still people didn't really know the full details unless they'd lived there all their lives and and I don't think anybody ever told us how it really happened</u>
<u n="47" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right no no it's come out a lot recently hasn't it?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0491" trans="overlap">it has yes</u>
<u n="49" who="S0486">erm and erm you know it it was one of those things that you just couldn't they just couldn't erm they were having an exercise I believe weren't they?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="51" who="S0486">and then the <unclear>U boat</unclear> came up and and and saw them exercising and wiped a lot of them out it was just terrible</u>
<u n="52" who="S0491" trans="overlap">that's right yes yes yes</u>
<u n="53" who="S0486">erm but you must have had a a very interesting childhood what did you what do you remember of Australia then?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0491">erm well just a few impressions really erm <pause dur="short"/> er not a lot I remember going to school and it was rather sort of marshal we had to do exercises in the playground we went in <unclear/> to to <unclear/> music</u>
<u n="55" who="S0486" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0491">erm and I just remember playing and er remember doing in a vicarage which had had a tennis court but it was terribly overrun and er overgrown rather erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> my parents decided they'd have some chickens but of course the wire netting had all gone in the corners and all the chickens escaped <unclear/> so it was pretty <unclear/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0491">erm I had lots of cousins and I still do and I get a little visit from time to time</u>
<u n="59" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="60" who="S0491">in fact erm <pause dur="short"/> at a recent count I had seventeen first cousins</u>
<u n="61" who="S0486">really?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0491">yes</u>
<u n="63" who="S0486">seventeen?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0491">but they lived a long way away</u>
<u n="65" who="S0486">yes yes</u>
<u n="66" who="S0491">and and er so we didn't see them often but that <trunc>w</trunc> that was nice so I <trunc>d</trunc> I vaguely remember things but not not anything very spectacular I remember the planned visit of erm I think Princess Elizabeth as she then was</u>
<u n="67" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right oh right</u>
<u n="68" who="S0491">we were all issued with medals which I still have</u>
<u n="69" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="70" who="S0491">but she but she didn't come because her her father died</u>
<u n="71" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="72" who="S0491">erm <pause dur="short"/> I do remember that I remember being attacked by erm kookaburra</u>
<u n="73" who="S0486">oh right</u>
<u n="74" who="S0491">but it <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's put me off birds flying around for life</u>
<u n="75" who="S0486" trans="overlap">I'm sure I'm sure</u>
<u n="76" who="S0491">erm but <trunc>the</trunc>they are a little bit possessive of their nests <unclear>they get a bit aggressive</unclear></u>
<u n="77" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="78" who="S0491">erm but I can't really remember many things I remember sort of visits to other members of the family and</u>
<u n="79" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes what about erm did you ever go sort of on on a <trunc>f</trunc> sheep farm or erm one of those large sheep farms they have in in the centre of Australia?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0491">no</u>
<u n="81" who="S0486">no visits there?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0491">no we were in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="84" who="S0491"><vocal desc="cough"/> I suppose there were sheep farms but I don't remember them as being anything very special</u>
<u n="85" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes no no</u>
<u n="86" who="S0491">I do remember <trunc>f</trunc> having <trunc>t</trunc> to take a plane to get to Sydney a little tiny plane</u>
<u n="87" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right yes</u>
<u n="88" who="S0491">that was <vocal desc="cough"/> cos that was quite a long way away for us</u>
<u n="89" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right er were you are you interested at all or have you read in in the past the works of Nevil Shute?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0491">yes <unclear>a tiny bit</unclear> yes</u>
<u n="91" who="S0486" trans="overlap">and A Town Like Alice</u>
<u n="92" who="S0491">well that was I think the town or the area where my father was and so it was very interesting</u>
<u n="93" who="S0486">oh was it? yes oh I've I've been I've rediscovered Nevil Shute a while ago actually</u>
<u n="94" who="S0491">ah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0486">I read them all when I was about sixteen and I've rediscovered them all a while ago</u>
<u n="96" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="97" who="S0486">erm and I've started rereading them but I really must keep up on that because it's amazing how clear they are in my head yet still I miss so much in my memory and going back to Nevil Shute is wonderful</u>
<u n="98" who="S0491" trans="overlap">mm mm yes</u>
<u n="99" who="S0486">erm and of course it's what I'm going forty year forty years ago when I read the last book and and of it's even more <trunc>e</trunc>er of an era almost vintage stuff really</u>
<u n="100" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes yes it's a good idea to go back and reread because I think the first time you read you read for the story don't you?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes you do yes</u>
<u n="102" who="S0491">the second time you you read as much for the story as for the detail or the detail as much as the story</u>
<u n="103" who="S0486">do you find that too with watching drama on television? because some of the Morse for instance and the Lewis erm series I don't know whether you like them but erm we find and the Frost the good series a good drama series we find that we don't watch them <trunc>we</trunc> when we watch just one for the second time which we try not to do but we do I always say to my husband I'm watching them for the acting I love the acting the way they play the parts so it's so good and how they inter react with the other characters and that I find absolutely fascinating which like you say I'm not looking for the narrative because I know really what happens cos I've seen it before</u>
<u n="104" who="S0491" trans="overlap">mm mm yes ah yes yes yes</u>
<u n="105" who="S0486">erm you you see the erm the frisson between erm Lewis and er his sidekick erm and how they talk to one another and the body language and everything is just right er and and also the actors have evolved that over time they've started to work together so much that they they're actually in a relationship as the part rather than acting the part</u>
<u n="106" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="107" who="S0486">so it's very good</u>
<u n="108" who="S0491" trans="overlap">oh yeah yes that's that's an interesting aspect my my husband doesn't like <trunc>Mor</trunc> didn't like Morse he didn't like his voice for some reason but erm I enjoy <trunc>l</trunc> cos we lived erm in <anon type="place"/> before we came here and I've worked in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="110" who="S0491">and erm I look for the bits of <anon type="place"/> <unclear>that we know</unclear></u>
<u n="111" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="112" who="S0491"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and that that makes it fun</u>
<u n="113" who="S0486">yeah and that really does make it fun I mean in the same way I went to school in <anon type="place"/> eventually and they did the Eddie Shoestring series from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0491" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="115" who="S0486">and I mean that's a long time ago and that was all around <anon type="place"/> at all places I knew and there's that wonderful feeling of you're actually involved in it because you know the places so well I walked down you know <anon type="place"/> every day or whatever</u>
<u n="116" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes yes yes</u>
<u n="117" who="S0486">erm and so there is that lovely feeling</u>
<u n="118" who="S0491">yes</u>
<u n="119" who="S0486">but tell me about <anon type="place"/> then tell me about erm your work cos</u>
<u n="120" who="S0491">right well I went to <anon type="place"/> because I was I was working in <anon type="place"/> and then <vocal desc="cough"/> <trunc>intere</trunc> got interested in cleft palate</u>
<u n="121" who="S0486">oh right</u>
<u n="122" who="S0491">and there was a erm well <anon type="place"/> was a centre of excellence for that so I I applied for a job there and erm it was very interesting working in cleft palate though thing was there's well the whole job was just too huge for one person to do and we were terribly terribly underfunded erm for speech and language therapy and erm yeah I was pulled in the direction of cleft palate but also neurology neurosurgery elderly paediatrics</u>
<u n="123" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="124" who="S0491">it was it was impossible and looking back it it you know I I find it erm difficult really to see how I actually got through it all <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes yes of course yes of course</u>
<u n="126" who="S0491" trans="overlap">it was but anyway the I tried to give the cleft palate priority erm because I was working with a a surgeon who was very very eminent and did research and and erm that involved me as well to an extent but it it was it was quite hard but being in <anon type="place"/> I just loved I just loved going out at lunchtime if I had the time to just walk through the streets and and look at the architecture and everything it was it was really beautiful</u>
<u n="127" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="128" who="S0491">we lived in a village outside <anon type="place"/> er seven or eight miles out near <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="130" who="S0491">and erm so travelling in and out was was quite difficult <anon type="place"/> traffic is dreadful</u>
<u n="131" who="S0486">yes it's like <anon type="place"/> I mean we've just been to <anon type="place"/> for the weekend and oh my goodness the traffic is a problem and we decided <vocal desc="laugh"/> the hotel we usually stay in has got so expensive cos they've had a refit and so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I decided to to stay outside and then that's a problem cos you've got to keep getting in all the time</u>
<u n="132" who="S0491" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="133" who="S0486">erm but we went to some really good lectures erm the <unclear/> erm it was really really good erm so we enjoyed that but getting back to <anon type="place"/> then so the question I'd like to ask you about cleft palate erm how did you manage obviously there's so much surgery involved with cleft palate so obviously you've got to wait until the end and the surgery's be done been done so you can start working with the patient on their speech?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0491">well erm not exactly because you would attend the combined cleft clinic</u>
<u n="135" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="136" who="S0491">erm where there was a surgeon and maybe an orthodontist you know</u>
<u n="137" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="138" who="S0491">erm and others involved in the care and in fact I would see erm the moms and erm just <pause dur="short"/> on their first the baby's first admission just to say hello who who I am and as a the surgeon would have explained what was gonna happen <pause dur="short"/> erm but with this surgery the recent surgery much many of the children had normal speech</u>
<u n="139" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="140" who="S0491">it was fantastic but I my job was to monitor that</u>
<u n="141" who="S0486">right yes</u>
<u n="142" who="S0491">and if there was any sign that any more input was needed</u>
<u n="143" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="144" who="S0491">erm at a certain stage then I would I would be involved not personally necessarily because erm the <anon type="place"/> hospitals covered a wide wide area including <anon type="place"/> at that time</u>
<u n="145" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh <unclear/> yes</u>
<u n="146" who="S0491">so I would contact the local speech and language therapists and ask them to do some work with a child if necessary <pause dur="short"/> erm but the results erm were very much better in the later years I worked there for ten years in the early years there was a type of surgery which erm left a very good result as far as parents was concerned but less good speech results</u>
<u n="147" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0491">we did some some research and looked at that and it was quite clear that that was not the way to proceed</u>
<u n="149" who="S0486">no</u>
<u n="150" who="S0491">and so the surgeon erm <pause dur="short"/> worked erm very early in repairing the cleft</u>
<u n="151" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right right</u>
<u n="152" who="S0491">so the child had a normal anatomy to use as speech developed</u>
<u n="153" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes yeah yeah oh erm I suppose the the the most vital part of it all and I used to work on ENTs years ago</u>
<u n="154" who="S0491" trans="overlap">oh did you?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0486">yeah it's closing up the hole in the cleft isn't it?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="157" who="S0486">so the the the whistling and the noise isn't isn't coming down through through the opening</u>
<u n="158" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="159" who="S0486">erm and I always thought and also then obviously food gets inhaled and it it it must be a terrible thing to have</u>
<u n="160" who="S0491">yes it was and the the the feeding is a real problem for some children</u>
<u n="161" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="162" who="S0491">there are various teats as you probably know</u>
<u n="163" who="S0486">yes yes</u>
<u n="164" who="S0491" trans="overlap">various ones developed for for cleft children but erm the surgeon I worked with was closing the front of the cleft very very early</u>
<u n="165" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="166" who="S0491">so the child would have a normal hard palate to press the the tongue tip against <unclear/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right yes</u>
<u n="168" who="S0491">erm they used to make plates to put into <unclear/> sometimes didn't they to close erm the front palate?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="170" who="S0491">but I don't know I I'm now very out of date because it's so it's ten years since I retired and it's <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> oh a very long much longer time since I had any contact with cleft</u>
<u n="171" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah yes yeah and so you went on after that to do erm a more general erm <pause dur="short"/> you know stroke victims and that that type of?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes I I when I came here to <anon type="place"/> erm <vocal desc="cough"/> I came to <anon type="place"/> erm and worked here for ten years er because I wanted to do some management</u>
<u n="173" who="S0486">right yeah oh right</u>
<u n="174" who="S0491" trans="overlap">so I managed as speech therapist there in <anon type="place"/> and that limited erm my own clinical work</u>
<u n="175" who="S0486" trans="overlap">absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0491">but I was expected to do fifty percent clinical work which is I mean sheer impossibility</u>
<u n="177" who="S0486">yes I can understand that</u>
<u n="178" who="S0491">erm but anyway I did keep up a little bit of cleft work but mainly worked in community hospitals</u>
<u n="179" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="180" who="S0491">with elderly people</u>
<u n="181" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="182" who="S0491">but they're not necessarily elderly people some were people with younger people with voice problems</u>
<u n="183" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="184" who="S0491">erm and well anyhow the head injuries like that <unclear/> ongoing rehab</u>
<u n="185" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes yes yes</u>
<u n="186" who="S0491">so in in a way it was a good thing that I had to keep up my my clinical work because after ten years I'd felt I'd had enough of working as a manager because the budgets were getting tighter and we were expected to do more with less basically and of course the situation's got much much worse since I left</u>
<u n="187" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes oh yes</u>
<u n="188" who="S0491">erm <pause dur="short"/> anyway I wanted to work part time partly because I wanted to spend some time with my husband</u>
<u n="189" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0491">he had been retired <vocal desc="cough"/> oh a very long time and also my mother was ninety living in <anon type="place"/> so we decided to go back to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0486">right right ah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0491">and I got a part time job in community hospitals</u>
<u n="193" who="S0486">oh</u>
<u n="194" who="S0491">and I worked there for eight years and it was lovely I worked three days a week</u>
<u n="195" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="196" who="S0491">they gave me a day for mom <pause dur="short"/> and a long weekend so we could enjoy</u>
<u n="197" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="198" who="S0491">and I I just loved driving around and I loved <vocal desc="cough"/> meeting the people in community hospitals</u>
<u n="199" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="200" who="S0491">and after being a manager I really relished the erm clinical again</u>
<u n="201" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah I can see that you did because as soon as you started talking about it your face lit up <vocal desc="laugh"/> and it was like oh this is the best thing I've ever done was it the best thing you've ever done?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0491" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes erm I don't know I enjoyed the challenge of the management and I I think I achieved a lot well it was <trunc>im</trunc> imposed the changes were imposed</u>
<u n="203" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="204" who="S0491">but we we went along with them and did them and I think ended up with quite a good service</u>
<u n="205" who="S0486">great</u>
<u n="206" who="S0491">which then <pause dur="short"/> got cut and they'd broken up</u>
<u n="207" who="S0486">ah yes</u>
<u n="208" who="S0491">and anyway that's <unclear/> but yes I think I became a better clinical therapist in a way having been a manager</u>
<u n="209" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="210" who="S0491">it made me think differently</u>
<u n="211" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="212" who="S0491">erm I always thought value for money when <trunc>I</trunc> after being a a manager er and doing my clinical work you know <unclear/> if I'd <unclear/> would it have been worthwhile <pause dur="short"/> erm which made me in a way more objective and I was more easily able to manage a a pretty impossible caseload because of that</u>
<u n="213" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="214" who="S0491">erm and I think people also because I was then older <pause dur="short"/> erm they enjoyed relating to somebody older who had life experience because so many of them would say oh wow she was such a sweet young girl you know <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> therapist</u>
<u n="215" who="S0486"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes yes</u>
<u n="216" who="S0491">but she was so young you know I think the young therapists are remarkably mature when I compare myself eh with them when I was that age they are amazing people and erm and very academic these days</u>
<u n="217" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="218" who="S0491">but I think being older helped also in you know when you're relating to to the families as you as you do and to carers at residential nursing homes</u>
<u n="219" who="S0486" trans="overlap">mm yes</u>
<u n="220" who="S0491">they have a bit more respect for you cos you're older and you've obviously seen life</u>
<u n="221" who="S0486">absolutely</u>
<u n="222" who="S0491">and I suppose you have more confidence as well</u>
<u n="223" who="S0486">well that's right that's right I mean the confidence only comes with experience</u>
<u n="224" who="S0491">yes</u>
<u n="225" who="S0486">I mean it's it's erm it's it's like you go to a young doctor and erm he hasn't really learned the tricks of the trade yet and they're I mean <vocal desc="laugh"/> there are in in all walks of life ways of doing things</u>
<u n="226" who="S0491">yes</u>
<u n="227" who="S0486">erm and erm you know er I just changed from a very young doctor to an older doctor erm because erm ah I my erm my er care was mismanaged to such an extent that we lost our erm our private medical insurance</u>
<u n="228" who="S0491">oh</u>
<u n="229" who="S0486">erm I was given a a a drug that gave me a erm stroke and TIA erm just a small stroke you know</u>
<u n="230" who="S0491" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0486">erm but I did I did on two occasions I reported speech erm I I couldn't think of the right words and also my speech was slurred and erm I erm I reported it oh you know given <unclear/> I think it's a bit slurry my speech oh he said oh no no give it another go and I I did and then I had the stroke and then erm and then erm we were <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was in the process of retiring and we were leaving the company scheme after thirty thirty-five years the company erm medical insurance scheme and we were going on to somebody else and erm my doctor I had the stroke the the the erm the actual scheme came into effect on one day erm and it was the day erm before I had the stroke but she insisted that I'd had it earlier and he put it down and therefore that was the end of my insurance and he couldn't see that from a humanitarian purpose but an elder doctor would have said when did you have the stroke? would've taken my word for it and er but it made a huge difference and that was it so now I can't have private health insurance</u>
<u n="232" who="S0491" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="233" who="S0486">and so but but there's been lots and lots of mistakes in that regard there've been so many mistakes with that surgery that I couldn't stand it any longer and it was more stressful going to them so now I've booked in with another doctor who well unfortunately I saw him for the first time last week and he's okay he's much older I I didn't choose him they they they won't let you choose</u>
<u n="234" who="S0491" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0486">I wanted a female actually I thought it'd be much better at my age if I see a lady doctor I mean it'd be much better but they wouldn't anyway there you go</u>
<u n="236" who="S0491">mm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0486">erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> and so we go on you know</u>
<u n="238" who="S0491">yes</u>
<u n="239" who="S0486">but erm it it's just erm yes it's it's</u>
<u n="240" who="S0491" trans="overlap">that's a really awful experience you just had</u>
<u n="241" who="S0486">erm just interesting what you said about value for money and also the two aspects of that and the way your face brightened up when you were saying erm about that because in the last two years running the gallery was the best thing that I ever did</u>
<u n="242" who="S0491">oh was it?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0486">and every time anyone asks me about it I brighten up and say <unclear/> it was the best thing I ever did and value for money was key point because if people were coming in to buy art which they did erm I I made sure that the artists didn't ask unrealistic prices for them for two reasons really one that you want the artists to sell and they're not famous so they're not gonna get a huge amount for it and secondly the the member of the public can come at the shop and say great I bought a piece of original art and it didn't cost me that much and that's such a wonderful thing</u>
<u n="244" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes mm mm yes</u>
<u n="245" who="S0486">so that's what keeps people coming back keeps the artists coming back and keeps the erm buyers coming back</u>
<u n="246" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="247" who="S0486">so there you are but I mean they used to <unclear/> very interesting picture up there</u>
<u n="248" who="S0491">oh</u>
<u n="249" who="S0486">was that something that you did?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0491">no no that was my mother's actually</u>
<u n="251" who="S0486">oh</u>
<u n="252" who="S0491">erm it was always in her lounge</u>
<u n="253" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="254" who="S0491">and erm when she died I said I'd really love that and it I think it goes rather well in here with the with the dark beams and other things</u>
<u n="255" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh it does definitely</u>
<u n="256" who="S0491">erm I just I just love it I love paintings and pictures which are not too definite and cos you can keep looking at them and see different things <unclear/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes absolutely well <unclear/> the horizon and you're looking towards the horizon and I was listening to a video by erm my I I go to <anon type="place"/> on a Monday for erm an art course and there was one by someone called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's really quite good I didn't realise I saw her website last night and she was talking about horizons and how everybody likes horizons and looking towards them because everybody wants to look into the future and be elevated by what they see and imagine what's beyond that side</u>
<u n="258" who="S0491" trans="overlap">oh yes yes yes yes</u>
<u n="259" who="S0486">and it sort of it's sort of romantic version erm those do you think they were <unclear/> hanging on those?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0491" trans="overlap">I think they must have been <unclear/> but they're just just there I suppose</u>
<u n="261" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes yes <unclear/> take down <unclear/> away or something</u>
<u n="262" who="S0491">yes</u>
<u n="263" who="S0486">it's a nice isolated scene</u>
<u n="264" who="S0491">yes</u>
<u n="265" who="S0486">it's the sort of scene you get over the <unclear/> talking from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> it's that sort of thing</u>
<u n="266" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0486">in the <anon type="place"/> there is a river <unclear/> which is wonderful</u>
<u n="268" who="S0491">yes</u>
<u n="269" who="S0486">so erm so what now now you're retired then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what are your hobbies here?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0491">I don't have too many hobbies I'm afraid erm I did go to an art group well it was a class <unclear/></u>
<u n="271" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="272" who="S0491">er our teacher was lovely and he but he was a commercial artist and he got too much work which was lovely for him</u>
<u n="273" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right good for him yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0491">erm and then we continued to meet as a group but to be honest I never wanted to <vocal desc="laugh"/> to do any painting</u>
<u n="275" who="S0486">really?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0491">no it didn't a lot of them would say oh I can't wait to get going with the painting</u>
<u n="277" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="278" who="S0491">I just didn't feel like that I think perhaps although I did one or two things which I was amazed at</u>
<u n="279" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0491">erm I I'm not artistic really I don't have a gift for it and I think I'm always a little bit worried about wasting time and being dissatisfied with what I've done</u>
<u n="281" who="S0486">well yes it putting yourself in the right situation for it er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> teaches completely differently to anyone I've ever met erm what she does is she gives you exercises to do and that sounds really boring erm for me if if someone had told me that I would never have gone to the class right</u>
<u n="282" who="S0491" trans="overlap">no yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0486">it's very hard to explain she's very insidious <vocal desc="laugh"/> in her ways of getting you to do things and you don't realise that you're doing them you see</u>
<u n="284" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes right</u>
<u n="285" who="S0486">so erm she showed us a picture last week of a of erm well several erm pictures of of the New York erm skyline the Chicago skyline and they were all in silhouette so they were just black and she asked us using a rigger and a flat brush to erm gave us a demonstration she does a demonstration to everyone very very simple to just try some brushstrokes with these brushes to make this erm skyline or make a skyline up</u>
<u n="286" who="S0491" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0486">well honestly it it I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says to me you can sell that he said it's so good you could sell it nice <unclear/> it was an exercise erm and erm but <unclear/> were producing things they could sell just with these two brushes by doing things not planning just letting it happen</u>
<u n="288" who="S0491" trans="overlap">no oh</u>
<u n="289" who="S0486">and erm she paints horizon pictures but it's very much it's very similar to the atmospheric work in that painting up on the wall where you've got the sky and and so on so you might enjoy that class</u>
<u n="290" who="S0491"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes I don't think I'll go</u>
<u n="291" who="S0486"><unclear>you don't?</unclear></u>
<u n="292" who="S0491">no I I came to the conclusion that really I like being with people</u>
<u n="293" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0491">when I go to an art class I mean you have <unclear/> but basically it's not chatting I like talking</u>
<u n="295" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="296" who="S0491"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0486">oh it's lovely to talk to you it really is and I I actually approached the library long before I got interested in this I approached the library in <anon type="place"/> and asked them if erm if I could run the art of conversation classes and erm what we would do is just sit down and choose a topic or several topics depending on which one wore out the quickest and talk about it because there were an awful lot of people around who want to have a conversation but <pause dur="short"/> when you're in a a partnership for a long time you sort of almost become the other person you were actually thinking what they're thinking and you actually don't have as good a conversation as you might do with a stranger which is obvious really you don't know the stranger do you?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0491" trans="overlap">mm yes yes yes</u>
<u n="299" who="S0486">so I wanted to start it and erm they say well we we do this knitting and nattering</u>
<u n="300" who="S0491">oh</u>
<u n="301" who="S0486">and I said no it's not it's not gossip <vocal desc="laugh"/> what we're talking about is we might actually discuss erm for instance what's going on at the conservative conference or talk about women priests in the church or my goodness anything</u>
<u n="302" who="S0491">mm</u>
<u n="303" who="S0486">but they just couldn't seem to and they said would you be charging for this? and I said well obviously I'd have to ask people for the money in order us to pay for the room I can't just you know so I would do it free but so I was thinking about that but no erm they said well we we'll put it on the board with the friends of the library but when I thought they were doing origami and knitting and nattering I said no I want to raise the game a bit <vocal desc="laugh"/> and talk about something else so erm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0486">it did it fell on stony ground</u>
<u n="306" who="S0491">yes well what I do I have quite a lot of friends and I seemed to have filled <vocal desc="cough"/> the diary with you know meeting one or two the one I go for a walk with and one I and couple I meet for coffee</u>
<u n="307" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes ah yes</u>
<u n="308" who="S0491">and <unclear>I suppose</unclear> my other interest apart from gardening and stuff</u>
<u n="309" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes getting things done</u>
<u n="310" who="S0491">yes erm <pause dur="short"/> and and also I want to be free to to go out with <unclear/> say it's a lovely day or something</u>
<u n="311" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes of course that's it</u>
<u n="312" who="S0491">erm so I don't want to to tie myself down too much</u>
<u n="313" who="S0486">no</u>
<u n="314" who="S0491">erm I do go to keep fit on a Friday morning</u>
<u n="315" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="316" who="S0491">I've been away so I haven't been for a while but that is quite important I suppose</u>
<u n="317" who="S0486">when do you do that then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0491">I go to <anon type="place"/> church hall</u>
<u n="319" who="S0486">oh yes I went for a couple of weeks the dancing to music thing?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0491">well it's very dancey isn't it?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes it is yes</u>
<u n="322" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="323" who="S0486">and I kept going the wrong way so I had to stop <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="324" who="S0491">oh well I do all the time and and some of us do perennially perpetually</u>
<u n="325" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="326" who="S0491">erm but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is so nice</u>
<u n="327" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes she is she's very nice</u>
<u n="328" who="S0491" trans="overlap">I I like the fact that it's on in the morning you see because the one I went to moved to the afternoon</u>
<u n="329" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="330" who="S0491">and although it was a better workout it was somebody called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she does quite a lot of erm classes</u>
<u n="331" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="332" who="S0491">I don't I didn't like having to keep myself sort of relatively inactive in the morning to conserve my energy for the afternoon</u>
<u n="333" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="334" who="S0491">cos I do have limited energy</u>
<u n="335" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes I well we all do when we get older</u>
<u n="336" who="S0491">yes</u>
<u n="337" who="S0486">I mean we all do yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0491">so this one is fine it's at ten well you know ten o'clock on a Friday</u>
<u n="339" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah ten o'clock yes</u>
<u n="340" who="S0491">and erm yeah we all I think we all do it in our own way and have our own standard</u>
<u n="341" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes yes well I joined when I left the shop but then I but then I thought I I did try but I was going the wrong way so often and and there is a class that I really like to <unclear/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0491">uhu</u>
<u n="343" who="S0486">which is in the afternoon again I'm not <unclear/> afternoons either I mean it's in the afternoon and erm it's it's a lot of dancing it's a lot of it but I do want to do dancing you see</u>
<u n="344" who="S0491">uhu</u>
<u n="345" who="S0486">erm but erm I've never been very good at dancing as a team member I seem to go in the opposite direction a bit like my painting <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0491"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0486">I'm not a team player I don't think I'm an individual and unfortunately you know that comes with its limitations erm</u>
<u n="348" who="S0491">yes</u>
<u n="349" who="S0486">and so I I did pay for the oh I paid for a long session with her long sessions with her erm but unfortunately erm and I paid for the keep fit society or whatever it was</u>
<u n="350" who="S0491">mm</u>
<u n="351" who="S0486">but erm I had to pull out erm at the time I was I was I was ill for three or four weeks with with dizziness and then I just said oh <unclear/> anymore so that was that erm all very amicable</u>
<u n="352" who="S0491">mm</u>
<u n="353" who="S0486">but it's a nice group isn't it?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0491">it is they're very friendly and my other interest of course is is the church</u>
<u n="355" who="S0486">oh right</u>
<u n="356" who="S0491">I'm <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm very active</u>
<u n="357" who="S0486">oh tell me about <anon type="place"/> is it St <pause dur="short"/>George's <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="359" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="360" who="S0491">yes well erm I don't I I said I didn't want to belong to the <unclear/> church council I've done that elsewhere and it all seems very intensive here</u>
<u n="361" who="S0486">oh right</u>
<u n="362" who="S0491">they're very much delegated to them by by the vicar who I have a great deal of respect for <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I go to er the home group</u>
<u n="363" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="364" who="S0491">which is only monthly and I'm in prayer circle which means you get requests for prayers emailed through to pray for the people</u>
<u n="365" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right oh right oh</u>
<u n="366" who="S0491">it's very good actually</u>
<u n="367" who="S0486">I hadn't thought of doing praying by email before <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0491"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well it used to be that you've you've you were in a chain and you phoned but it was when everybody got email there's one person in the chain who doesn't have email so she has to be phoned</u>
<u n="369" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh did you? email</u>
<u n="370" who="S0491">but it does mean that everybody gets the prayer request simultaneously or you know <unclear/> they switch on</u>
<u n="371" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0491">and if if you're away it doesn't matter too cos you know the others are doing it anyway</u>
<u n="373" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0491">but that is something which is is tremendous and it actually means that I do pray every day and not just when I have a bit of time</u>
<u n="375" who="S0486">yes I know</u>
<u n="376" who="S0491">and erm <pause dur="short"/> so that is good erm for for many reasons and also on a Sunday occasionally erm I'm part of the prayer ministry team which means that if somebody wants a prayer at the service you pray with them like a standard prayer</u>
<u n="377" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes right</u>
<u n="378" who="S0491">erm <pause dur="short"/> and otherwise oh yes the other thing is that I order the bible reading fellowship booklets on behalf of the church</u>
<u n="379" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="380" who="S0491">you've heard of them I'm sure <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> parts</u>
<u n="381" who="S0486" trans="overlap">erm yes I have yes I think so yes</u>
<u n="382" who="S0491">yes and they're still going strong</u>
<u n="383" who="S0486">are they? oh right</u>
<u n="384" who="S0491">and that was that is something I do</u>
<u n="385" who="S0486">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0491">but erm <pause dur="short"/> otherwise I just turn up and I I sometimes have helped with the with the decoration of the church but I'm not very flower arranging erm expert you know</u>
<u n="387" who="S0486" trans="overlap">sort of person</u>
<u n="388" who="S0491">I like to stick them in a vase and enjoy them</u>
<u n="389" who="S0486" trans="overlap">they look lovely in that vase I'd I'd love to get er a sketchpad now not even a pad or sketch it but just blob on some different you know just blob on some different colours there very sort of <unclear/> and erm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes they are lovely aren't they?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0486" trans="overlap">they're gorgeous and of course you've got the brush strokes you can see the brush strokes can't you? <unclear/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="393" who="S0486">well I should have a go at that <unclear/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0491" trans="overlap">well I might just take a photo of them and then when I when I can I'll erm paint them</u>
<u n="395" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah and the stems are rather nice because <unclear/> a bit distorted in that vase aren't they because it's so curved?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0491" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="397" who="S0486">well it's a rose pink colour it's it's amazing it's really nice</u>
<u n="398" who="S0491">yes</u>
<u n="399" who="S0486">erm so erm we I I don't really remember it I don't know whether it's <pause dur="short"/> do you remember a fashion show being staged in <anon type="place"/> church years ago?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0491">no I don't think I was here then</u>
<u n="401" who="S0486">well there was a young <unclear/> from <anon type="place"/> hospital and erm <pause dur="short"/> it was all <trunc>trad</trunc> she was she ran a Christian group at <anon type="place"/> and and I used to go erm years ago and erm I'm sure she was involved in it and and that's how I got the invitation and they they actually put erm it was when they had the pews they actually put boards all across the top of the pews <pause dur="short"/> and the models walked all over them over the pews</u>
<u n="402" who="S0491" trans="overlap">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0486">and I remember thinking at the time <pause dur="short"/> this is a bit strange for a church and they were selling you know I'm I'm terribly mindful of I mean we're talking about <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <vocal desc="cough"/> seventy-eight erm nineteen eighty early nineteen eighty we're talking <pause dur="short"/> and I remember you know what Jesus said about the moneylenders and and transactions going on in church of course nobody takes any notice about that now we've got we've got cafes we've got erm gift shops and all <unclear/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0491">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="405" who="S0486">I can't believe it how how the church as an institution has divorced itself from Christianity and I find that very hard to to to take on board <pause dur="short"/> erm and yeah so yes I was I remember being absolutely amazed and I went to it was a very nice erm I think maybe a lot of these erm items had been made locally erm I bought a skirt which I wore for a long time a patchwork skirt which was very nice but I I often say to my husband <unclear/> he said do you really think that they would have allowed have allowed that to happen at <anon type="place"/>? erm because the other thing too about <anon type="place"/> church was er just very briefly <trunc>be</trunc> I'm sure you've had enough by now but erm just very briefly</u>
<u n="406" who="S0491" trans="overlap">it's very interesting <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0486"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well erm my husband and I met twenty-one years ago</u>
<u n="408" who="S0491">oh yes</u>
<u n="409" who="S0486">and erm we were both erm you know quite mature by then and er he and his parents had lived in this area for years and he'd been an altar boy erm for years at <anon type="place"/> church</u>
<u n="410" who="S0491">uhu</u>
<u n="411" who="S0486">and erm he erm <pause dur="short"/> we were we were living in <anon type="place"/> erm and erm we were going to get married and and he said well I'd like to get married at <anon type="place"/> church erm although I haven't been because I'm you know er well he used to go to the eight o'clock quite rightly but he hadn't been for a while</u>
<u n="412" who="S0491">mm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0486">and it was during the interregnum and we rang up and the secretary told me there was no chance we could get married at <anon type="place"/> church I thought <unclear/> when I thought think of the time after my mum died and and erm for four years I <unclear/> to my father while he was vicar of <anon type="place"/> and I had to I was nursing full time <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I was cleaning the house making all the coffee for taking all the <unclear/> over the phone letting the people out in the hospital and having the undertaker ring me up when I got home for four years I don't know how I survived</u>
<u n="414" who="S0491">goodness me</u>
<u n="415" who="S0486">and then and and you know and then they weren't even marrying me at <anon type="place"/> church and I I plus I didn't have the fortitude to explain to her a bit about my life it just made me so totally angry and I thought that is typical of bureaucracy and not only in the church but in the NHS in everywhere I mean yesterday we went to have for a meal and we could only eat so much and we could only drink coffee for this special price and in the end <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I didn't have anything any of this special price food which <unclear/> be eight pounds a head it's just bureaucracy gone mad so we sat down and ate this meal and the thing the meal which was just two small meals came to seventeen pounds and and erm it was only in a garden centre oh but you've got to have this this and this and if you deviate you've got to pay the full price</u>
<u n="416" who="S0491">oh</u>
<u n="417" who="S0486">and it was just like that and I thought where is bureaucracy it's gone completely mad in some cases</u>
<u n="418" who="S0491">well it's a good thing my husband isn't here because <vocal desc="laugh"/> I we had a similar well not as extreme erm an experience about getting married as you did</u>
<u n="419" who="S0486" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0491">but I'd lived in this village in in erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> for some time and I'd been secretary of the PCC I'd done the gift <unclear/> returns I've been a bell ringer I've cleaned the church</u>
<u n="421" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes yes you've done a lot</u>
<u n="422" who="S0491">came to getting married <pause dur="short"/> and we went to see the vicar and he said well I'm afraid cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had been divorced <unclear/> before we couldn't do it</u>
<u n="423" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right yes yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0491">and that's why I wrote to the bishop</u>
<u n="425" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="426" who="S0491">and erm I felt well well I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm not bothered how how it's done we'll go and go to a registry office and we'll have a service blessing afterwards which we did</u>
<u n="427" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="428" who="S0491">and the vicar <unclear/> everybody <unclear/> their services free and we had a <unclear/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah sounds lovely</u>
<u n="430" who="S0491">everybody did all they could to make it nice but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has never got over the fact fact</u>
<u n="431" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="432" who="S0491">with all my background</u>
<u n="433" who="S0486">exactly</u>
<u n="434" who="S0491">erm we couldn't get married in church</u>
<u n="435" who="S0486" trans="overlap">no exactly well my father when he was vicar of <anon type="place"/> he he made it his business to marry divorced people I mean he was it wasn't really then the thing to do but he had lots and lots of people who came in and he he always married them</u>
<u n="436" who="S0491" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="437" who="S0486">and erm it was just the way he felt about it</u>
<u n="438" who="S0491">well I'm sure he's right because in fact <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> first wife left him</u>
<u n="439" who="S0486">right so</u>
<u n="440" who="S0491">and okay they probably he was at fault to some extent but how on earth can clergy gauge whose fault it was?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0486" trans="overlap">exactly no exactly you can't</u>
<u n="442" who="S0491">no</u>
<u n="443" who="S0486">and it it's like people look at you in life I mean as you get older erm and you're retired and they don't know that you've been a brilliant speech therapist in your life they don't know that I actually have written three plays and been to drama school I've been a you know I've got three professional qualifications</u>
<u n="444" who="S0491" trans="overlap"><unclear/> wide ranging life haven't you?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes well it was because I was on my own for so long we didn't get married until our mid forties you see so erm it's because I've been on my own for so long and I thought well blow it I read a book once called Anybody Can Do Anything and erm it was about this girl <vocal desc="laugh"/> was quite a crazy book I can't really remember but she would take a job and then she would erm decide well that's not really interesting I'll do something else and she'd just go on and on until she got bigger and better jobs basically well I wasn't really working towards that plan but things tend to happen to me in my life good things and very bad things like everybody but erm <pause dur="short"/> it it did enable me to erm to try a few things out and erm you know I've had my you know I've had my highs and I've had my lows if you have very big highs you do get very big lows <pause dur="short"/> I was just reading Nicholas Parsons' biography</u>
<u n="446" who="S0491">oh really?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0486">and erm he started out at Clydebank as an engineer because his parents just didn't want him to go on stage at all his parents were so against it and he said he writes a bit about the basic way he was treated by the other men of course he had a very posh accent and everything</u>
<u n="448" who="S0491" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="449" who="S0486">and erm he said you know erm <pause dur="short"/> he got on well in the theatre and on the radio because he developed he felt that after Clydebank <vocal desc="laugh"/> he could do anything</u>
<u n="450" who="S0491"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0486">the way he was reared and the way he was treated and I mean and he still passed his engineering exams he still did a good job but he went on to to be an actor and all the time he was doing it he was having small parts on the radio and <unclear/> still keeping going but he said that was the basis of his</u>
<u n="452" who="S0491">mm</u>
<u n="453" who="S0486">so there you are</u>
<u n="454" who="S0491" trans="overlap">interesting</u>
<u n="455" who="S0486">so erm is there anything else you'd like to say? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0491"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we've done quite well</u>
<u n="457" who="S0486">do you think we've finished?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0491">is it fifty minutes?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0486">er hang on forty-five oh we've really done really well haven't we?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0491">well it hasn't been an effort <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0486">no how good <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> so I'll pause recording <vocal desc="misc"/> and press red button</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
