<text id="SG3P">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:14:40</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-21</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0618 S0619</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Campervan journey – a short drive to a friend’s house in Tarnow, Poland.</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Travel arrangements. </topics>
		<activity>Two friends discussing travel arrangements while driving the short distance to another friend’s house in Tarnow, Poland.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0618">
				<exactage>42</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge/Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months on and off</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>unemployed/ Some part-time private TEFL teacher/ Semi-retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0619">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury, Lancashire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Nort West: Lancs, Greater Manchester</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>nearly 4 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher of English as a foreign Language</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0619">hello oh god</u>
<u n="2" who="S0618">anyway yes right so nice to see you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0619">nice to see you</u>
<u n="4" who="S0618">er is there anything behind me?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0619">there's no</u>
<u n="6" who="S0618">good so I can put my <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> satnav on and find <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house erm now I've had second thoughts about our road trip because it's gonna involve five hours' driving four hundred and fifty kilometres two hundred and forty odd miles which isn't isn't bad you know it's fine in the summer <vocal desc="laugh"/> but I think when the road is covered in snow <pause dur="short"/> that's good <pause dur="short"/> erm I think that's I don't know it's doable but I don't think I would find it so enjoyable being the responsible driver lady</u>
<u n="7" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah for <pause dur="short"/> mm mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah sure okay <pause dur="short"/> okay so</u>
<u n="8" who="S0618">so where do we go? <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="9" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think we ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0619">for an idea</u>
<u n="12" who="S0618">I think you are right I</u>
<u n="13" who="S0619"><anon type="place"/> so I don't know how far away that is</u>
<u n="14" who="S0618">no I don't I've got erm a list here that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did the other day and I've got my big map which you've got you are holding and erm that's a tourist attractions of Poland guide thing and I thought if we go somewhere that's sort of like main roads an hour's drive or something yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0618">or an hour and a half I don't mind but I just thought a total of five hours' driving in a a day is a bit mental really</u>
<u n="17" who="S0619">uhu <pause dur="short"/> yeah sure <pause dur="short"/> turn off the <anon type="place"/> so</u>
<u n="18" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">at the end of the road turn right</u>
<u n="19" who="S0619">thanks Simon</u>
<u n="20" who="S0618">thanks Simon <pause dur="long"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> you were so virtuous going to the gym this morning well done</u>
<u n="21" who="S0619">thanks <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0619">erm I really wasn't going to go because I felt oh well you know ten thirty is still kind of early for the holidays you don't need to go but I woke up at a quarter past seven and oh I'm awake I'll go to the gym I think I woke up <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and his girlfriend and I'm really really quiet in the mornings I'm a very sort of quiet house person but I think I woke them up and I was like balls but they were getting up anyway to go they went to like <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="24" who="S0618" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="sound of satnav"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh were they? for the day?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0619">no for the night</u>
<u n="26" who="S0618">oh good</u>
<u n="27" who="S0619">yeah they are staying in a hostel that someone found online or recommended to them</u>
<u n="28" who="S0618">cool</u>
<u n="29" who="S0619">erm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0618"><anon type="place"/> ski</u>
<u n="31" who="S0619">no no they are not going skiing they are just going <pause dur="short"/> there's a new here new cafe bistro thing</u>
<u n="32" who="S0618">oh</u>
<u n="33" who="S0619">yeah look</u>
<u n="34" who="S0618">have you been in it?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0619">no</u>
<u n="36" who="S0618">we will have to try that</u>
<u n="37" who="S0619">because I don't know whether it's you know just a very nice looking erm kebab shop</u>
<u n="38" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah I know what you mean <pause dur="short"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0618">but I think it you know it looks quite nice inside so we'll see <pause dur="short"/> erm so yeah they went about nine an hour and a bit to <anon type="place"/> and then two hours I think an hour and a half to <anon type="place"/>'s place I mean it is really close I've done that journey back and it was like you know four hours I think in total and that was to get to <anon type="place"/> which is an extra sort of hour on the journey so <pause dur="short"/> it's kind of nice but I've got so many clothes on today</u>
<u n="40" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it is <pause dur="short"/> wow <pause dur="short"/> have you?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0618">I've got a fair few</u>
<u n="43" who="S0619">I'm sweating I might have to undress once I get to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house</u>
<u n="44" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm going to need to lose a fleece I've got my long johns on today and my jeans and I was <unclear/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0619">me too <pause dur="short"/> I was like bloody hell I've turned into someone else I think <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0618"><anon type="place"/> oh yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0619">is that <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0618">okay cool where's that then?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0619">it says it's like north</u>
<u n="50" who="S0618">oh hang on</u>
<u n="51" who="S0619">north somewhere</u>
<u n="52" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="53" who="S0619">I can't tell you anything more than that I can't even find it on the map so the place is <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0618">is it north?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0619">aha</u>
<u n="56" who="S0618">yeah the place that we were going to go to</u>
<u n="57" who="S0619">yeah it is in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0618">I know <pause dur="short"/>I found it on the map it's near the German border I thought oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0619">yeah I know because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said that and I thought well maybe it's just the really east bit</u>
<u n="60" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know I didn't really I mean she did say the other day and I just thought oh yeah that's a great road trip what an adventure but I don't think I really thought oh time oh distance</u>
<u n="61" who="S0619">oh shall we go to Poland's oldest salt mine in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0618">yes let's do that it's funny you should say that I was thinking about <anon type="place"/> because I love I love caves and stuff and it's fucking freezing down there anyway so it doesn't really matter and we are dressed for it</u>
<u n="63" who="S0619">because it's really close <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> forty-four page forty-four</u>
<u n="64" who="S0618">well now I don't know that is I think the erm that gives grid references to a map that I don't have which is annoying you can do pages and stuff but this one five two seventeen business not a bloody notion mate</u>
<u n="65" who="S0619">erm the mine's largest cavern the <unclear> the Wazyn Chamber</unclear> has facilities for recreation health and treatment should have brought your bikini</u>
<u n="66" who="S0618">oh <pause dur="short"/> it's not too late</u>
<u n="67" who="S0619">well or well where else is there? but yeah I just thought</u>
<u n="68" who="S0618"><anon type="place"/> is a nice distance and it's</u>
<u n="69" who="S0619">and it's not even <anon type="place"/> it's like</u>
<u n="70" who="S0618">no and it's on an A road</u>
<u n="71" who="S0619">forty-five minutes</u>
<u n="72" who="S0618">so yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe and then we've got this big here from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> oh that's a form for you to sign by the way</u>
<u n="73" who="S0619">okay great</u>
<u n="74" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0619">well we live where would you say? like I would say like one five two-ish</u>
<u n="76" who="S0618">oh where did you get that map?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0619">it was just there</u>
<u n="78" who="S0618">oh I was looking for the map I couldn't find it</u>
<u n="79" who="S0619">so one five two <pause dur="long"/> it's like the worst map <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0618">I know it hasn't actually got any roads or anything useful on it</u>
<u n="81" who="S0619">one five three that's us oh okay so the closest thing on the map is one hundred and forty-six</u>
<u n="82" who="S0618">oh there's a shitload of wooden churches around here</u>
<u n="83" who="S0619">yeah which is <anon type="place"/> national park is it your national park the <anon type="place"/>? is that where your where your hippies live?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0618">no <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0619">oh</u>
<u n="86" who="S0618">and that's erm between <anon type="place"/> and erm <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0619">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm oh er one hundred and forty-six is what? timber architecture trail of timber churches</u>
<u n="88" who="S0618">I think once you've seen one wooden church you've seen every wooden church</u>
<u n="89" who="S0619">one hundred and fifty-six is er renaissance residence perfectly preserved oh this is <anon type="place"/> I think</u>
<u n="90" who="S0618">oh yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0619">is it sumptuous late renaissance magnet magnate residence from the turn of the sixteenth century <pause dur="short"/> right or would you prefer to go to the world's oldest oil well? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0619">the choice is yours today</u>
<u n="94" who="S0618">no wonder people were invading Poland <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0619">one hundred and thirty-seven this isn't <pause dur="short"/> clearly boring I'm just trying to find oh it's more churches <pause dur="short"/> no you can shove your churches</u>
<u n="96" who="S0618">indeed <pause dur="short"/> I lived in Ireland for eight years I don't need more churches</u>
<u n="97" who="S0619">one three four is what?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0618">get in the right lane <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this is near where I went wrong the other day <pause dur="short"/> cor bumpy road</u>
<u n="99" who="S0619">yeah be ready to turn left I think is</u>
<u n="100" who="S0618">yeah it's a little bit ah pick a lane mind the pedestrians the light might be red it might be green it might be your light it might not be</u>
<u n="101" who="S0619">keep driving just pretend you are in a video game where it doesn't matter <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0618">go go go <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I know you just sort of bowl people across the bonnet I can do that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I used to play a game called Driver where the aim was to drive without getting caught by the police but it was better if you got caught by the police and then just sort of you know</u>
<u n="104" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> said I'm playing a game and I just lost no</u>
<u n="105" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no and then <pause dur="short"/> no and then just be chased by the police and try and get away from them and then just do it again just to sort of to get within touching distance of the police <unclear/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh my god <pause dur="short"/> is this a video game or is this reality?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0619">it's not reality <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay</u>
<u n="109" who="S0619">I didn't go like bumper to bumper with a police car and then waiting for them to turn around and then drive off</u>
<u n="110" who="S0618">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/> and drive off I did wonder but you know</u>
<u n="111" who="S0619">no I'm not that bad one hundred and thirty-six</u>
<u n="112" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> your childhood</u>
<u n="113" who="S0619">right we are getting <pause dur="short"/> I'm making some progress with this map one hundred and thirty-six is there</u>
<u n="114" who="S0618">I thought that was a policeman who is reading a map but of course I'm looking at the passenger <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0619">he doesn't know where he's going</u>
<u n="116" who="S0618">he doesn't he needs <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s satnav mate</u>
<u n="117" who="S0619">one hundred and thirty-six is there and that is <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> is no I've lost the <anon type="place"/> thing now</u>
<u n="118" who="S0618">yeah every time</u>
<u n="119" who="S0619" trans="overlap">that's nice one hundred and thirty-five</u>
<u n="120" who="S0618">every time I go past <anon type="place"/> I think oh I must go there I mean and I suppose another part of me thinks well while the sky is blue and the sun is out and it's just beautiful it might be nice to have a wander around outside somewhere but yeah I know what you mean</u>
<u n="121" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I could say that</u>
<u n="122" who="S0618">I just don't want to drive for five hours today</u>
<u n="123" who="S0619">no yeah <pause dur="short"/> one hundred and forty <pause dur="short"/> I just can't tell the distance on this map</u>
<u n="124" who="S0618">yeah I think it's all relative as well it depends on erm what sort of roads you've got if you've got little wiggly woggly ones then it can be really close but take forever</u>
<u n="125" who="S0619">I think <anon type="place"/> I've gone off <anon type="place"/> because we can do it anytime in <trunc>forty</trunc> in forty-five minutes and it's and it's inside yeah so <anon type="place"/> is I believe erm there we could do it in</u>
<u n="126" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh okay the car park in foothills</u>
<u n="127" who="S0619">it is in the carpark no it's not it's in a place that I can't pronounce</u>
<u n="128" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="129" who="S0619">I know that it has got a beautiful square it's like a little <anon type="place"/> er it's got a square so there will be restaurants and places to roam around and castle things all castle and things</u>
<u n="130" who="S0618"><pause dur="short"/> and when it's raining <pause dur="short"/> cool</u>
<u n="131" who="S0619">er</u>
<u n="132" who="S0618">I like the sound of that</u>
<u n="133" who="S0619">er I'm supposed to make all the decisions <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0618">it sounds like it's got everything</u>
<u n="135" who="S0619">I think it would be nice for the day</u>
<u n="136" who="S0618">and I think if it's south of here it's going to have beautiful scenery as well</u>
<u n="137" who="S0619">it's not south it's north</u>
<u n="138" who="S0618">what? is it?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0619">yeah I just don't think it's on this map because it's in <anon type="place"/> it is in the next one</u>
<u n="140" who="S0618">ah okay</u>
<u n="141" who="S0619">but if you want to stay if you want to go south then</u>
<u n="142" who="S0618">oh shit that's where I should have turned oh done it again <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0619">dammit <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0618">oh can I turn here? now which what is that no entry sign? maybe that's for me</u>
<u n="145" who="S0619">I think</u>
<u n="146" who="S0618">I'll turn around here again like we did the other day oh well at least I know I can turn around here</u>
<u n="147" who="S0619">so if we go south then the next one south is one hundred and forty-six which is one of the churches</u>
<u n="148" who="S0618">I don't mind going north alright</u>
<u n="149" who="S0619">or one five seven what's that? one five seven is <pause dur="short"/> oh that's the <unclear/> oil <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0618">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0619">you've already said no to that</u>
<u n="152" who="S0618">I know I think that just needs just striking off who is interested apart from George Bush?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0619">I need a pen and then I can edit this</u>
<u n="154" who="S0618">I've got erm I've got pens in my bag</u>
<u n="155" who="S0619">but then if we go too far south we are just you know in Slovakia one sixty what's that? palace music and oh that's <unclear>Mein Suit</unclear></u>
<u n="156" who="S0618">what's going on there? right</u>
<u n="157" who="S0619">one six two here that's churches</u>
<u n="158" who="S0618">I need to reverse out again <pause dur="short"/> oh I seem to have a bit of queue behind me <vocal desc="laugh"/> oops sorry <pause dur="long"/> so talk amongst yourself</u>
<u n="159" who="S0619">one hundred and fifty-eight</u>
<u n="160" who="S0618">castle and park complex that does look nice</u>
<u n="161" who="S0619">one five eight</u>
<u n="162" who="S0618">you see I like the sound of the place that we were going to go miles away because I like the sound of the grounds and everything <event desc="sound of car beeping"/> everybody move along we are turning round <pause dur="short"/> sorry <pause dur="long"/> here we are can you point that heater thing towards your window because I can't see in my mirror? <pause dur="short"/> ta <pause dur="short"/> so where did we decide on?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="165" who="S0619">I don't know how you say it or yeah that's as far as I've got</u>
<u n="166" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="167" who="S0619">we will have to rely on the satnav because of this map</u>
<u n="168" who="S0618">no the satnav is good</u>
<u n="169" who="S0619">because I've just run out of map <pause dur="long"/> I think unless yeah here we are</u>
<u n="170" who="S0618">that was quite simply negotiated I think we've got quite good at things like that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0619">well I don't think it was negotiated it was me just going well we are going to go here so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0618">okay fair enough no you did come up with a few options there</u>
<u n="173" who="S0619">well and yeah from a selfish perspective I've always wanted to go <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0618">what to this <anon type="place"/> place?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0619">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0618">I've never heard of it</u>
<u n="177" who="S0619">and people have recommended it to me before but to get to on public transport you've either got to go to <anon type="place"/> which is two buses away and then go from <anon type="place"/> to there or go to <anon type="place"/> and go from there</u>
<u n="178" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0619">so it's a bit of a faff</u>
<u n="180" who="S0618" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> however you look at it it's not really working</u>
<u n="181" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0618">so if I drive in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s driveway am I going to get out again? yeah I should do shouldn't I? there's enough bumpy bits</u>
<u n="183" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0618">I think this is my theory in Northern Ireland as well that you know when things freeze and stuff? if you've got like a well-maintained road that's really flat then you've got problems in snow and ice but bumpy roads grip</u>
<u n="185" who="S0619">bumpy roads are brilliant</u>
<u n="186" who="S0618">yeah you've got loads of grip and I reckon as well Northern Ireland didn't bother with speed bumps really they just didn't bother repairing their roads it worked fine <pause dur="long"/> yeah we are reversing in snow</u>
<u n="187" who="S0619">in snow with the valency tyres</u>
<u n="188" who="S0618">yeah so let's see if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s overslept today?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0619">no because she sent a text unless she would have woke up sent a text and then erm went back to sleep let me just take off many clothes</u>
<u n="190" who="S0618">yeah me too say bye</u>
<u n="191" who="S0619">bye</u>
<u n="192" who="S0618">bye</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
