<text id="SG78">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:11:11</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-28</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0336 S0337 S0341</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Kerrie Owen's house</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Food, cooking, moving house, qualifications, medical care, bins, white goods, friends, furniture, crafts, news</topics>
		<activity>Dinner at ANON's House</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, complaining, advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0336">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Wegberg</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Germany</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>none</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Peterborough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>17 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>German -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0337">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Peterborough</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>none</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Peterborough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0341">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Swansea</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Wales</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Welsh</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Peterborough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>17 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>wales</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>wales</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>wales</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Accountant</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>German -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0341">erm this is kind of a first attempt at the old erm sautéed potatoes haven't done this in a long time so</u>
<u n="2" who="S0337">how do you do sautéed potatoes?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0336" trans="overlap">I'm sure it'll taste okay</u>
<u n="4" who="S0341">are you alright in that chair?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0337">I'm okay</u>
<u n="6" who="S0341">yeah?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0337">yeah I wouldn't worry</u>
<u n="8" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0336">looks nice anyway</u>
<u n="10" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0337">what's the er chicken sauce?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0341">it's one of those Maggi ones</u>
<u n="13" who="S0337" trans="overlap">do you know what?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0341"><unclear/> <trunc>garl</trunc> erm mixed herb I think</u>
<u n="15" who="S0337">mixed herb</u>
<u n="16" who="S0336">we haven't tried any of those yet</u>
<u n="17" who="S0337">no we haven't we haven't we've cooked a lot it's weird isn't it? we've cooked a lot but what have we been having?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0336">well we went to the butchers on Saturday and got</u>
<u n="19" who="S0337" trans="overlap">oh that was so good</u>
<u n="20" who="S0336">a ridiculous amount of meat that we've not actually been able to get through this week</u>
<u n="21" who="S0337">for</u>
<u n="22" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="23" who="S0337">for twenty-two quid</u>
<u n="24" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> for twenty-two quid</u>
<u n="25" who="S0341"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0336"><unclear>but like</unclear></u>
<u n="27" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0336">I was thinking about this though I think what we should've done is taken the meat out of the packets maybe put it either in Tupperware or frozen it straightaway because when I cooked that mince last night it wasn't off by any means but it had already gone a bit brown</u>
<u n="29" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0337">mince is alright brown though beef</u>
<u n="31" who="S0336">and er well I wouldn't have cooked it if I didn't think it was okay but</u>
<u n="32" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah it's good it's good it's even better</u>
<u n="33" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> how's it even better? that's a bit of a claim</u>
<u n="34" who="S0337">no definitely is I think you're meant to make you're meant to let steak go slightly brown</u>
<u n="35" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0341">you are</u>
<u n="37" who="S0337">you <trunc>ar</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> why is that funny?</u>
<u n="38" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0337">just trust me</u>
<u n="40" who="S0336">okay famous last words</u>
<u n="41" who="S0337">mm mm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0341">er do you know there's a lot of food waste around ain't there? because people use those use by dates as erm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0337" trans="overlap">use by dates or they use best before dates as</u>
<u n="44" who="S0341">gospel you know</u>
<u n="45" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0341">and I think sometimes</u>
<u n="47" who="S0337">er I agree</u>
<u n="48" who="S0341">you can actually use products</u>
<u n="49" who="S0336">I know but we've got we leave</u>
<u n="50" who="S0337">got bacon left that's it</u>
<u n="51" who="S0336" trans="overlap">got bacon left yeah which I think we'll probably use tomorrow night</u>
<u n="52" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0336">and I'm sure it's fine but obviously it it</u>
<u n="54" who="S0337">it's not vacuum packed</u>
<u n="55" who="S0336">it isn't vacuum packed so</u>
<u n="56" who="S0337" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="57" who="S0336">you're just it's not it isn't gonna keep quite as long</u>
<u n="58" who="S0337" trans="overlap">agreed</u>
<u n="59" who="S0336">but you should've seen these chickens</u>
<u n="60" who="S0337">chickens?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0336" trans="overlap">chickens <vocal desc="laugh"/> whole chickens no erm we bought some chicken breasts they were the most expensive thing we bought I think we paid like er</u>
<u n="62" who="S0337">paid eight quid</u>
<u n="63" who="S0336">yeah eight pound for four erm but I have honestly never seen chicken breasts so big</u>
<u n="64" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0336">they were absolutely huge like</u>
<u n="66" who="S0337">you know when they're cut slightly in half and it's like flat? they all had like er</u>
<u n="67" who="S0336">basically another breast <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0337" trans="overlap">another breast yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0341">right</u>
<u n="70" who="S0337">I'd say that little flap was about the same size as a normal breast</u>
<u n="71" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0337">it was crazy they were huge absolutely huge</u>
<u n="74" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0336">so that was quite nice <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> made this little like tomato crème fraîche dish thing it was really good we've still got some this is the thing though like we've we've been cooking so much in the evenings that there's plenty to take for lunch like not normally just the next day but the day after that as well</u>
<u n="76" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0336">like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actually had a choice of leftovers this morning <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0336">when he went to work</u>
<u n="80" who="S0337">oh yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0336">so it is going a long way but like I went and did a big shop on Sunday morning cos we were having <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> over <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> over for a barbecue I spent like seventy quid but I bought so like obviously we'd already done the meat shop on the Saturday</u>
<u n="82" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0336">so that's seventy quid like without any meat which is quite a lot of money</u>
<u n="84" who="S0337">there's cleaning stuff in there as well</u>
<u n="85" who="S0336">but yeah I had bought like fabric softener and kitchen bathroom cleaner all that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="86" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0336">and there was like a couple of things that kind of topped it over the edge and actually we'll have a quiet week next week cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s going into hospital on Tuesday</u>
<u n="88" who="S0341">okay</u>
<u n="89" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and erm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0337">so I won't eat</u>
<u n="92" who="S0336">so he won't be eating much on Tuesday and then we're away from Thursday through to Monday so I imagine we'll just try to make do with what we've got in the cupboards</u>
<u n="93" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0337">got fish and stuff</u>
<u n="95" who="S0336">we've got fish we've got other stuff as well that we'll make do</u>
<u n="96" who="S0341">er are you having that procedure done at our place or at the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0337"><anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> again</u>
<u n="98" who="S0336">guess what time they've given him did I tell you? quarter past four</u>
<u n="99" who="S0341">oh for goodness sake</u>
<u n="100" who="S0337">bit harsh isn't it?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0336">we</u>
<u n="102" who="S0337"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0336">we need we need to go back through the literature cos I'm not really sure whether he he can have dinner the night before or not cos it's so late I'm I think he might have to take those sachets like first thing in the morning</u>
<u n="104" who="S0337">no one's the night before <unclear>at least</unclear></u>
<u n="105" who="S0336">do you think so? even er even</u>
<u n="106" who="S0337" trans="overlap">I think I think they're both the night before</u>
<u n="107" who="S0336">even for a four o'clock appointment?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0337" trans="overlap">I think they're both the night before</u>
<u n="109" who="S0336">mm I'm not sure</u>
<u n="110" who="S0337">still a long way</u>
<u n="111" who="S0336">I'm sure it was like if you were in the morning you take them the day before both of them one at lunch one at dinner but if you're in er an afternoon appointment you take one the night before and one first thing in the morning I'm almost certain of it</u>
<u n="112" who="S0337">okay <pause dur="short"/> not too sure about that</u>
<u n="113" who="S0336">well we'll that's what I mean we need to go back through it don't we?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0337">yep</u>
<u n="115" who="S0336">but yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0341">it would seem an extraordinarily long time between kind of eating the evening before cos I'm sure once you start taking them you're not supposed to eat again after that but</u>
<u n="117" who="S0336">no</u>
<u n="118" who="S0337">I definitely can't eat that day I know that</u>
<u n="119" who="S0336">we'll have to think of something nice you can eat afterwards</u>
<u n="120" who="S0341" trans="overlap">but I think I think you probably can have clear liquids so you might find there might be a soup a clear soup that you can buy</u>
<u n="121" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah or you can just like save yourself and like binge on Tuesday night when you get back</u>
<u n="122" who="S0337">oh yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0336">although the last <unclear>like</unclear> even if you're hungry the last thing you might feel like doing after that <vocal desc="laugh"/> is eating</u>
<u n="124" who="S0337"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0341">oh right er well personally I found that one better than the endoscopy</u>
<u n="126" who="S0337">yeah <unclear>we'll</unclear> see</u>
<u n="127" who="S0337">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0341">I think it just kind of does your dignity <unclear>in</unclear></u>
<u n="129" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0337">mm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0341">dents your dignity rather than it being painful or</u>
<u n="132" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0337">yep <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0336">be happy to start getting some answers I think er</u>
<u n="136" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0337">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0336">it'll be worth it</u>
<u n="139" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0336">I'm erm I'm gonna go in early on Tuesday so that I can come back and take him</u>
<u n="141" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0336">saves <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> coming all the way over again cos I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got the keys to his bungalow</u>
<u n="143" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0336">yesterday from what I <trunc>r</trunc> er from what I er well I think that's what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was trying to say</u>
<u n="145" who="S0341">okay</u>
<u n="146" who="S0336">so erm they were keeping it a secret cos they didn't want him to know when all of his stuff was coming down <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0337" trans="overlap">cos he he keeps waking up really early for no reason</u>
<u n="148" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0337">so like when he had his cast off he woke up at I think it was woke up at five o'clock for a ten AM appointment in <anon type="place"/> there's no need for him to be up that early</u>
<u n="150" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0337">just to get dressed</u>
<u n="152" who="S0336">so yeah so they've been keeping it from him and also because erm they wanna get the bathroom and kitchen sorted before he actually moves in</u>
<u n="153" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0336">so they didn't want him to think that oh because he's got the keys to his bungalow he's moving in</u>
<u n="155" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0336">erm but as far as I can tell the erm they went to see the bathroom people in <anon type="place"/> that we kind of accidentally found when we were looking for like a heated towel rail or something erm they were really really really nice to us so we went back and sort of said oh when it comes to doing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s bathroom like it's probably worth like talking to them and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> really likes the guy so</u>
<u n="157" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0336">erm I think they're gonna go through them to do all the bathroom stuff and he seems to think that they can act on it like straightaway</u>
<u n="159" who="S0341" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0336">so hopefully it won't be too long cos I think I mean you're not completely convinced by him living on his own anyway are you? but</u>
<u n="161" who="S0337">no I'm just worried about him I don't think he's ready <unclear>I don't think he can</unclear> again</u>
<u n="162" who="S0336">but they need to try it don't they?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0336">they need to try it they need to give him his independence and <trunc>event</trunc> er like <vocal desc="sigh"/> he's really got to be the one that says oh actually you know like I probably can't do this yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0337" trans="overlap">can't do this yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0336">mm we'll see it's all been kicking off this week erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had his final erm <unclear/> exam this week as well</u>
<u n="167" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0341" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="169" who="S0336">erm so he sat I don't know how much of it you know or remember or anything like that but he sat an exam back in May all of the penultimate exams but it's supposedly the hardest one you sit and he was basically saying that over half the people that sit it fail it</u>
<u n="170" who="S0341">right</u>
<u n="171" who="S0336">and he came out of it wasn't really sure how he'd done et cetera et cetera but when he got his results back I think he er got like fifty-six percent or something which was more than what he <trunc>m</trunc> far more than what he</u>
<u n="172" who="S0337">no there was a few of them he did he got like seventies and <unclear/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0336" trans="overlap">oh yeah he got some really really amazing results</u>
<u n="174" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0336">but he got like fifty-six percent on this exam that <trunc>ba</trunc>basically most people fail</u>
<u n="176" who="S0337">was that the one?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0336">no and then er and then a collection of like basically fairly outstanding results so he's really really chuffed he got a letter a couple of weeks telling him that he was like one of the top in the UK for <unclear/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0337">no ninth overall so that's that's in Europe isn't <unclear/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah it will still be in the it won't be Europe</u>
<u n="180" who="S0337"><unclear/> he did was for out of out of people in Europe</u>
<u n="181" who="S0336">really?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0337">yep</u>
<u n="183" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="184" who="S0337">it was out of five thousand five hundred people or something</u>
<u n="185" who="S0336">and came ninth</u>
<u n="186" who="S0341"><unclear>crikey</unclear></u>
<u n="187" who="S0337">came ninth</u>
<u n="188" who="S0341">that's impressive</u>
<u n="189" who="S0337">yeah he must be doing something right</u>
<u n="190" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0337">not bad erm he I haven't told you about the cos I spoke to him today erm his latest plan is that they're gonna build a house</u>
<u n="192" who="S0336">okay</u>
<u n="193" who="S0337">and have already applied for planning</u>
<u n="194" who="S0336">I don't think that's er I don't think</u>
<u n="195" who="S0337">I don't know but</u>
<u n="196" who="S0336">no</u>
<u n="197" who="S0337">still</u>
<u n="198" who="S0336">have they found a plot of land or anything? surely if they're applying for planning permission</u>
<u n="199" who="S0337">right so it turns out that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> obviously owns their house</u>
<u n="200" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0337">he owns the house that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are in he also owns the other bungalow there which is kind of between them so you know the track goes like that and then goes down <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah so they wanna build a house next to her parents?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0337">they're gonna build a house there in the</u>
<u n="204" who="S0336">oh</u>
<u n="205" who="S0337">at the bungalow's back garden</u>
<u n="206" who="S0336">oh</u>
<u n="207" who="S0337">er cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gonna give them the land <pause dur="short"/> and they've already applied for planning so yeah okay great er the conversation was obviously about <unclear/> about <unclear/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0336" trans="overlap">that's fairly big news and I think they'll get a lot more for their money building their house</u>
<u n="209" who="S0337">you know he said it'll cost them like a hundred and something K</u>
<u n="210" who="S0336">oh yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0337">and it'll be worth like two hundred and something</u>
<u n="212" who="S0336">and the rest</u>
<u n="213" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="214" who="S0336">given the location but they're committing themselves to living next to her parents for a considerable amount of time <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0337">yeah and the deal was would be that they can't sell it to someone else so they'd have to keep it or sell it to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because he doesn't want some randomers sat in the house between</u>
<u n="216" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0337">three of his houses yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0336">that's very very generous of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0337">what? to give them the garden?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0337">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I didn't get to the end of the conversation cos er it cut out and then never called me back</u>
<u n="222" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0336">that's that's</u>
<u n="225" who="S0341">that's huge</u>
<u n="226" who="S0336">that's yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0336">that's really big news that's exciting</u>
<u n="229" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0336">and it's scary as hell and it's gonna take them well</u>
<u n="231" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0336">having watched Grand Designs <vocal desc="laugh"/> it could take them twelve to eighteen months to actually have a house that's like inhabitable</u>
<u n="233" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah but they've got one to live in the whole time</u>
<u n="234" who="S0336">oh yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0337">and if they don't even er cos I think they'd have to do it off loans <unclear>at</unclear> the beginning cos you can't get a mortgage for a plot of land</u>
<u n="236" who="S0336" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="237" who="S0337">so buy it start it off with loans and then once they've got</u>
<u n="238" who="S0341"><unclear/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0337">part of the house</u>
<u n="240" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0337">they can mortgage it</u>
<u n="242" who="S0336">erm it's not quite part of the house the house has to actually look like a house you can't</u>
<u n="243" who="S0337" trans="overlap">just look like a house?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0336">erm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0341">it has to have four walls</u>
<u n="246" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0341">and a door</u>
<u n="248" who="S0336">so it it effectively has to be kind of inhabitable for you to be able to get a mortgage</u>
<u n="249" who="S0337" trans="overlap">er a shell a shell at least</u>
<u n="250" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="252" who="S0336">so you can't it's not like you can put the foundations down and be like okay now I'll get a mortgage on the foundations like it does have to still has to resemble a house but yeah that's that's that's how they do it on on like Grand Designs and stuff they tend to erm they tend to erm use any savings and stuff they have to like buy buy the land and then they'll take loans out on the building and then like throughout the process they'll apply for a mortgage and then kind of gradually as the house gets more and more finished as it were and the value increases they can increase the mortgage</u>
<u n="253" who="S0337">okay</u>
<u n="254" who="S0336">so effectively like if the house is just as it is obviously it'll be valued a lot less than if it's a finished house so they'll get a loan out then once it's valued at a little bit</u>
<u n="255" who="S0337" trans="overlap">er <vocal desc="cough"/> so if they get if they get the land I don't know how much money he's got I presume it's quite a lot because of his salary must be a lot I don't know any of this stuff but</u>
<u n="256" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0337">er</u>
<u n="258" who="S0341">what does he do now? where is he working?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0337">he is an accountant he's not chartered</u>
<u n="260" who="S0336" trans="overlap">er just in er independent like accountancy firm I think</u>
<u n="261" who="S0337">and I don't think <unclear/> before I don't know if I can erm yeah erm but he's been earning he must be on a decent whack</u>
<u n="262" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0337"><unclear/> erm and then</u>
<u n="264" who="S0336">and to think that he's saved enough for a deposit down there which would've been substantial</u>
<u n="265" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah he's got he's got enough for a deposit</u>
<u n="266" who="S0336">stamp duty on top of that like all the legal fees on <trunc>t</trunc></u>
<u n="267" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0336">like</u>
<u n="269" who="S0337">when they were yeah when they were looking for a house</u>
<u n="270" who="S0336" trans="overlap">they have a substantial amount</u>
<u n="271" who="S0337">the only thing that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was waiting for was that extra six months worth of salary they advise you to have</u>
<u n="272" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0337">in case you lose your job and that's the only bit he didn't have erm so yeah he must be on a decent wage so if he has that they've got er <trunc>f</trunc> land <trunc>f</trunc> given to them and they're getting a loan he's laughing</u>
<u n="274" who="S0336">mm and er they will the loan'll be fairly high interest so it</u>
<u n="275" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0336">it'll be it'll be a bit crap to start with because they'll probably be paying quite a lot of money each month to pay for the loan but as soon as they can mortgage that it'll become a lot like a lot more manageable because I'm pretty sure obviously with personal loans you you can't have them anywhere near as long as you have the mortgage which is why the repayments are so high and the interest rates will be generally be a bit higher than they are</u>
<u n="277" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="278" who="S0336">in the mortgage as well</u>
<u n="279" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0336">so I imagine it'll be one of those things they will be able to get a loan but they actually probably</u>
<u n="281" who="S0337" trans="overlap">they want to get a mortgage straightaway yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0336" trans="overlap">they're having to get it as soon as possible yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="284" who="S0337"><unclear>I dunno what er</unclear></u>
<u n="285" who="S0336">but I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is the perfect person to be doing something like that because he'll be able to like effectively like project manage it so that he knows like where where the money's going and stuff like that</u>
<u n="286" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> obviously she's in <trunc>s</trunc><trunc>sh</trunc>she's been in she's doing her chartered surveying she's got a master's in like erm <pause dur="short"/> er what what was her job before? erm estate agency or something like that erm so she's not she knows what she's doing on that side of things and he's</u>
<u n="287" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0337">knows what he's doing on the money side of things</u>
<u n="289" who="S0336">that's exciting</u>
<u n="290" who="S0341">it is isn't it?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0336">mm don't er I don't envy them tying themselves quite like that</u>
<u n="293" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0336">cos like to <trunc>s</trunc>to sort of say like oh <trunc>y</trunc>you're not just living in like her parents' like back garden as it were but then to sort of say oh you're not actually just allowed to up and sell like you either have to sell it to me or like you know we have to come to sort of some sort of arrangement that's a huge commitment</u>
<u n="295" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0341">yes cos I mean if if they can only sell it back to him</u>
<u n="297" who="S0337" trans="overlap">oh no yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0341">they've got they've gotta accept his offer</u>
<u n="299" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="300" who="S0337">well yeah I think they'd end up getting <trunc>r</trunc> leasing it out once it's completed and then getting an actual mortgage on a house or something I dunno</u>
<u n="301" who="S0336">well who knows</u>
<u n="302" who="S0337"><unclear>just</unclear> opens doors doesn't it?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0337">well you could mortgage that and use yours as a <trunc>depo</trunc> I dunno</u>
<u n="305" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="306" who="S0337">they'd <trunc>w</trunc> they'd work it out so yeah <unclear/> I never got to the end of it cos yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0336">I can't believe they've already I can't really believe they've already applied for planning permission either cos that means they've already got plans draw up like</u>
<u n="308" who="S0337">no you can get planning permission to have use the land as</u>
<u n="309" who="S0336" trans="overlap">just a dwelling</u>
<u n="310" who="S0337">a dwelling yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="312" who="S0336">I thought when you applied for planning permission you had to have like oh this er</u>
<u n="313" who="S0337">no I think</u>
<u n="314" who="S0336" trans="overlap">this is what we're applying for</u>
<u n="315" who="S0337">I think you can apply to build like a two two-storey two-bed house or something</u>
<u n="316" who="S0336" trans="overlap">oh right okay</u>
<u n="317" who="S0337">erm and then you can then you have to have all the relevant parties that it would affect like to be in on it so then you've gotta tell people but obviously the bungalow that's there is being rented out to someone er let out to someone so they'd have to tell <unclear/> I dunno</u>
<u n="318" who="S0336">I don't think as erm like if they were renting</u>
<u n="319" who="S0337" trans="overlap">tenants</u>
<u n="320" who="S0336">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0337">no but still yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0336" trans="overlap">a courtesy thing yeah that's quite exciting though now I I would love to build my own house but I'd be so scared that</u>
<u n="323" who="S0337" trans="overlap">well that looks not a dream house to build is it? that's just a</u>
<u n="324" who="S0336" trans="overlap">no it's just a oh this this is the best option we have at the moment I'm so fickle as well like one minute I'd be like yeah this is exactly this is exactly what I want this is the perfect use of this space this is gonna be like a brilliant house and then I'd build it and be like oh why did I put that wall there? or like why have I chosen to do that that way? or</u>
<u n="325" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="326" who="S0336">oh why didn't I try that? or why didn't we do this? and you can't blame anyone you can't be like oh well you know no house is perfect or well this is just the way it came because <trunc>y</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> you put it like that</u>
<u n="327" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0336">you chose to do it</u>
<u n="329" who="S0337">mm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0336">but that's exciting</u>
<u n="331" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="332" who="S0336">so when is he putting a ring on her finger? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0337">dunno <pause dur="short"/> they keep like pushing it back for like</u>
<u n="334" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0337">reasons</u>
<u n="336" who="S0336">yeah oh I'm just gonna finish my exams oh just</u>
<u n="337" who="S0337">gonna build a house</u>
<u n="338" who="S0336">gonna wait till the house is built <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh right okay</u>
<u n="339" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="340" who="S0337">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if mum and dad know even I thought it was interesting</u>
<u n="341" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0336" trans="overlap">I would I don't think your mum does know cos I almost feel like she'd been sobbing while she was telling us <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0337">why? that she's lost him?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0336">yeah like that's not just losing him that's like oh I'm gonna build a house in my mother-in-law's garden <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah but I heard not long ago that I heard not long ago that they could er always move back up here to commute to <anon type="place"/> cos there's obviously more opportunities for both of their professions in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0336">and up north I heard that they <trunc>kn</trunc>they knew like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> with his skills could go anywhere why live in one of the most expensive parts in the country?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0336">it's the same with her like both of them are transferable skills</u>
<u n="350" who="S0341" trans="overlap">they are supposed to be developing the north aren't they? where did I er? there was also erm oh I think you may've mentioned it a few months back that the east the kind of</u>
<u n="351" who="S0337">east</u>
<u n="352" who="S0341">East Anglia</u>
<u n="353" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="354" who="S0341">and that was gonna be the most developed erm area over the next five years</u>
<u n="355" who="S0336">they're putting so they're <trunc>pu</trunc><trunc>pu</trunc>putting so much money into like and even <anon type="place"/> like as a hub they've spent all that money on a train station to like increase it's capacity they're putting more and more routes though <anon type="place"/> because it's so centralised cos the routes to the north at the moment are <trunc>n</trunc>they're not strong enough it it takes like three hours on a train from here to get to <anon type="place"/> like takes you want pud? what do you want?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0337">scone</u>
<u n="357" who="S0336">scone?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0336">erm yeah so erm from <anon type="place"/> it can take anything three-and-a-half four hours to get from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> well <anon type="place"/> is one of the biggest cities in the north to say that especially <unclear>now seeing</unclear> the BBC are moving up to <anon type="place"/> and stuff to say that it <trunc>c</trunc> still take four hours to get from one to the other is just ridiculous</u>
<u n="360" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="361" who="S0336">erm</u>
<u n="362" who="S0337" trans="overlap">well there was something in the news about tourists coming here and it mapped out like tourist attractions from <anon type="place"/> and how long it took and I think <anon type="place"/> was <unclear/> one of the examples</u>
<u n="363" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="364" who="S0337">and it was a joke</u>
<u n="365" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="366" who="S0337">like the route that you have to take was so obscure</u>
<u n="367" who="S0341"><unclear>mm that's right</unclear></u>
<u n="368" who="S0337">and like hard cos er it's just such a bad country for transport</u>
<u n="369" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0337">and just</u>
<u n="371" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="372" who="S0337">getting around we're not a big country</u>
<u n="373" who="S0336">but like it's not as if rail's even cheap now so I'm concerned that if they are planning to put a load more infrastructure in that the only way they're gonna be able to pay for it is by charging the people who are using the trains so</u>
<u n="374" who="S0341"><unclear>they're</unclear> gonna wait until that HS2 is built won't they?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0337">yeah but that's still another <pause dur="short"/> three or four years <unclear>four</unclear> years</u>
<u n="376" who="S0336" trans="overlap">what's that?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0337">HS2</u>
<u n="378" who="S0341">HS2</u>
<u n="379" who="S0336">yeah it's a way off still I think</u>
<u n="380" who="S0341">do you want any forks? or <unclear/> or spoons?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0337">I won't use a fork</u>
<u n="382" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0337">I'll use my hands</u>
<u n="384" who="S0341" trans="overlap"><unclear>what do you want</unclear>?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0336">erm</u>
<u n="386" who="S0337">use a fork</u>
<u n="387" who="S0336">I probably should use a fork</u>
<u n="388" who="S0337">what for?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0336">it's just etiquette isn't it?</u>
<u n="390" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="392" who="S0336">erm <trunc>y</trunc>yeah I might have a little dessert fork please? do you have a preference to scone or turnover?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0341"><unclear/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0336">okay I think I'm gonna go scone then</u>
<u n="395" who="S0337"><unclear>can I just touch them</unclear>?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0336">does it pass the touch test? or?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0337">I dunno I might I might might <unclear>have both</unclear></u>
<u n="398" who="S0341">you didn't want one did you?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0337">er no thanks</u>
<u n="400" who="S0336">well it wouldn't be unlike you to not have both so</u>
<u n="401" who="S0337">I don't know what to do</u>
<u n="402" who="S0336">well they need eating</u>
<u n="403" who="S0337" trans="overlap">can I <unclear>have a bite of</unclear> one of those please?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="404" who="S0336">not satisfactory?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0337">it's alright actually</u>
<u n="406" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they have been there since Sunday so they've definitely like seen better days</u>
<u n="407" who="S0337">that's what they said about you</u>
<u n="408" who="S0336">that's just rude</u>
<u n="409" who="S0337"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0336">how's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0341">he's alright</u>
<u n="412" who="S0337">is he at football?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0341">yes but he he seemed he seemed happy that he'd get to speak to you tonight at some point so</u>
<u n="414" who="S0336">he's <unclear/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0337">oh <pause dur="short"/> he's been working?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0341">er he has been working yes</u>
<u n="417" who="S0337">oh good</u>
<u n="418" who="S0341">the last couple of weeks so</u>
<u n="419" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="421" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="423" who="S0336">yeah that's good news but still not <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="424" who="S0337"><unclear>permanent</unclear></u>
<u n="425" who="S0336">still not making a lot of money</u>
<u n="426" who="S0341">no</u>
<u n="427" who="S0337">yeah but I think he's always happier when he's busy</u>
<u n="428" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="429" who="S0341">he does seem to have a bit of er a bounce if you like because he likes what he's doing</u>
<u n="430" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0341">I think he enjoys the physical labour being outdoors</u>
<u n="432" who="S0336">and I think it makes a huge difference when you do something that you want to talk to people about</u>
<u n="433" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="434" who="S0336">so like he can come home and he can talk about the project he's working on</u>
<u n="435" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="436" who="S0336">talk about the things he's learning or where he's been working whereas in previous jobs it was just all so monotonous</u>
<u n="437" who="S0341">yes</u>
<u n="438" who="S0336">I don't think he could even bring himself to like <vocal desc="laugh"/> talk about it</u>
<u n="439" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="440" who="S0336">when he wasn't working</u>
<u n="441" who="S0337">yeah but that's what we're like we're like about our jobs you have an end product that's had problems along the way that you've solved</u>
<u n="442" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="443" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="444" who="S0337">projects it's always about projects you wanna you wanna finished good or product at the end</u>
<u n="445" who="S0336">you want something to measure yourself by</u>
<u n="446" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="447" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0336">well it'll be nice to see him as well he keeps saying he's gonna like pop in and never does so</u>
<u n="450" who="S0341">well I think he may he may just be reluctant to just drop in and he hasn't had any credit for his phone for months <unclear>now</unclear></u>
<u n="451" who="S0336">well if he's driving all the way over to <anon type="place"/> for football like two or three times a week he might as well like pop in on his way just to say hi or on his way back for a drink like he's more than welcome to</u>
<u n="452" who="S0341">well yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0336">dad did it like a couple of weeks ago literally just dropped in on his way back from the golf course like it's almost nicer to see people like that</u>
<u n="454" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0336">because it doesn't feel like it puts you out that much just for them to pop in and say</u>
<u n="456" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0336">hi</u>
<u n="458" who="S0341">yes and I nearly did that at the weekend but I thought mm I really wanted a really quiet</u>
<u n="459" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0341">do nothing weekend so</u>
<u n="461" who="S0337">we had a barbecue on Saturday with one of the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> used to work with</u>
<u n="462" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="463" who="S0337">erm that was nice</u>
<u n="464" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="465" who="S0337">and then on Monday we had the table delivered</u>
<u n="466" who="S0341">oh yes</u>
<u n="467" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="468" who="S0341">how does that look?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0337">have you <trunc>g</trunc>you got a picture?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0336">it looks really nice I don't think I <unclear/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0341" trans="overlap">are you happy with it?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0336">oh yeah I might do actually</u>
<u n="473" who="S0337">erm yeah I'll show you in a bit that's good erm and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> popped round like literally as we we'd finished putting it together and then mum and and grandpa popped round</u>
<u n="474" who="S0336">with the hoover she's donated us her upstairs hoover</u>
<u n="475" who="S0337">but apparently there's a hole in the tube so you can't use the well you can use the the nozzle but you've gotta like play around with it</u>
<u n="476" who="S0336">we're just grateful cos the house was starting to look really messy</u>
<u n="477" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="478" who="S0336">er like the messy that's like not messy just like</u>
<u n="479" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0337">just a bit of fluff on the floor</u>
<u n="481" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0337">and er</u>
<u n="483" who="S0336">obviously with it being a new carpet as well like and cream you just see absolutely everything and it's getting really frustrating and</u>
<u n="484" who="S0337">stuff in the tiles as well</u>
<u n="485" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="486" who="S0336">like went into Currys at the weekend and the Dysons all had a hundred quid off and we're like that is a really good offer but even with a hundred quid off they were still two hundred and fifty quid and we were like</u>
<u n="487" who="S0337"><unclear/> the cheap no the cheapest one was two hundred and fifty quid</u>
<u n="488" who="S0341">well er <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if the offer will still be on but there are a couple of hoovers in Tesco's for fifty pounds</u>
<u n="489" who="S0337">are they? what are they like?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0341">but they're new and they're they are the highest power</u>
<u n="491" who="S0337">that you're allowed these days?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="493" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="494" who="S0341">so</u>
<u n="495" who="S0337">they've made they've totally like zapped that haven't they?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0341">they have recently</u>
<u n="497" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0341">but obviously there's gonna be er retailers who've got stock of</u>
<u n="499" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0341">the higher powered stuff so</u>
<u n="501" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0337"><unclear>cos like</unclear> how much was yours? if you don't mind me asking was it er hundreds still?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0341">erm</u>
<u n="504" who="S0337" trans="overlap">cos er the <trunc>sma</trunc> <unclear/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0341">I think it was below two hundred</u>
<u n="506" who="S0337">ah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0336">er cos that we want yours like the little lightweight ones</u>
<u n="508" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0336">we can't find them anywhere</u>
<u n="510" who="S0337">er well no there there was one that it's the same as that but it was</u>
<u n="511" who="S0336" trans="overlap">was er wasn't lightweight though</u>
<u n="512" who="S0337">no it wasn't wasn't as light no</u>
<u n="513" who="S0341" trans="overlap">I saw it being advertised on the telly the other night and it was over two hundred pounds</u>
<u n="514" who="S0337">two yeah <trunc>w</trunc> yeah they were</u>
<u n="515" who="S0341">I mean I <trunc>j</trunc>I just don't know why it's that expensive</u>
<u n="516" who="S0337">I think they're head and shoulders above the rest</u>
<u n="517" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="518" who="S0337">they er they really are</u>
<u n="519" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah and we're we're really struggling to like between that oh do we buy one for the sake of having one? or do we</u>
<u n="520" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="521" who="S0336">hold out until we can afford a decent one that probably won't need replacing any time soon?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="523" who="S0336">cos that's that's kind of what's more important to us it's like</u>
<u n="524" who="S0341" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0336">okay so we might have a lot of expenditure over the next</u>
<u n="526" who="S0337">mm</u>
<u n="527" who="S0336">twelve months while we effectively like set up the house but once it's set up as long as long as you've bought decent stuff</u>
<u n="528" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0337" trans="overlap">it should be yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0336">in the next five years you shouldn't have to replace anything</u>
<u n="531" who="S0341"><unclear/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0337">oh and we've got a microwave don't know if you know</u>
<u n="533" who="S0336">microwave and</u>
<u n="534" who="S0337" trans="overlap">it's not it's <trunc>n</trunc></u>
<u n="535" who="S0336">we've got a toaster on the way as well</u>
<u n="536" who="S0337">yeah it wasn't a Panasonic they were a bit too expensive but it was on offer again at Currys</u>
<u n="537" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="538" who="S0336">a hundred and twenty quid</u>
<u n="539" who="S0337">it's silver and <trunc>le</trunc>leaves marks you leave them</u>
<u n="540" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0337">if you touch it it just leaves a smudge it's terrible</u>
<u n="542" who="S0336" trans="overlap">but it's a combination oven and it's got like a grill and everything as well you literally can do everything on there</u>
<u n="543" who="S0337">it's huge</u>
<u n="544" who="S0336">its even got a cake function which <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> loves</u>
<u n="545" who="S0337">huge</u>
<u n="546" who="S0336">we've not been able to take advantage of that I can't work it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> knows how to work it I don't know how to work it</u>
<u n="547" who="S0337">it's huge</u>
<u n="548" who="S0336">but it's massive yeah</u>
<u n="549" who="S0337" trans="overlap">I'm just gonna keep saying it's huge</u>
<u n="550" who="S0341">good</u>
<u n="551" who="S0336">but we're getting there slowly but surely</u>
<u n="552" who="S0341" trans="overlap"><unclear/> good I think you've done well so far</u>
<u n="553" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="554" who="S0336">well we've <trunc>indu</trunc> we indulged massively with the toaster cos erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s parents have got a De'Longhi one</u>
<u n="555" who="S0337" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="556" who="S0336">and it's just it's just a really nice toaster and it that was on offer in Currys it had like twenty or thirty quid off</u>
<u n="557" who="S0337"><unclear>had to</unclear> buy it</u>
<u n="558" who="S0336">still fifty quid</u>
<u n="559" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0336">but in the grand scheme of things we're like ah well all the cheaper toasters are naff I can't eat anymore <pause dur="short"/> so yeah we're getting there I've also bought our little shoe bench and coat rack this week because well obviously cos er cos it's been cold and we've had coats out and stuff you suddenly realise like how annoying it is to not have anywhere to put them like they're all living on the <trunc>b</trunc></u>
<u n="561" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="562" who="S0336">guest bed at the moment but as soon as one of us wears one</u>
<u n="563" who="S0337" trans="overlap">you don't wanna walk all the way upstairs mm</u>
<u n="564" who="S0336">it's downstairs somewhere yeah so it's <trunc>ha</trunc> hung over the bannister or it's just like hanging off a door somewhere which is just really irritating</u>
<u n="565" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="566" who="S0336">and all our shoes just keep gathering by the front door which just you just the <trunc>pla</trunc> makes the place look just look like a mess so I've ordered those they'll be coming next week so they should get delivered while <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s off which is quite nice</u>
<u n="567" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="568" who="S0336">and then after that like the house the house functions as it is now like to a certain extent like</u>
<u n="569" who="S0337">we've no bins</u>
<u n="570" who="S0336">still don't have any bins it's been nearly four weeks and we've not got bins</u>
<u n="571" who="S0337">we asked the sales department and you emailed the erm council</u>
<u n="572" who="S0336" trans="overlap">I emailed the council last week basically saying the developers did say that they put in an order for this but we haven't received any bins yet so if you have received an order from them can you please expedite it so we have our bins soon</u>
<u n="573" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="574" who="S0336">or if you haven't received an order can you treat this as an order for bins</u>
<u n="575" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="576" who="S0336">but I haven't heard I haven't had a response and bins haven't turned up so</u>
<u n="577" who="S0341">phone them up</u>
<u n="578" who="S0336">yeah but <trunc>t</trunc></u>
<u n="579" who="S0337">tell them we won't pay our council tax</u>
<u n="580" who="S0336">it's not like they've tried to charge us council tax yet</u>
<u n="581" who="S0337">they will</u>
<u n="582" who="S0336">well it's just irritating like we're still having to like do midnight skip runs because we're embarrassed that we're binning all our stuff in the skip</u>
<u n="583" who="S0337"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="584" who="S0336">you should've seen it this table and chairs right came in four separate boxes and I mean like giant boxes and er we were literally like how the hell do we get rid of all of this? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0337" trans="overlap">no it came in six boxes</u>
<u n="586" who="S0336">did it?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0337">two of them were the seats covers</u>
<u n="588" who="S0336">oh yeah</u>
<u n="589" who="S0341">you see you're not far from the tip are you? at <anon type="place"/> so</u>
<u n="590" who="S0336" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="591" who="S0337">not really</u>
<u n="592" who="S0341">just take your stuff round there <unclear/></u>
<u n="593" who="S0336" trans="overlap">well that's what we decided we decided that if we couldn't bin them we'd just take them to the tip but</u>
<u n="594" who="S0337" trans="overlap">we've we've binned them</u>
<u n="595" who="S0336">but we've binned them</u>
<u n="596" who="S0337"><trunc>w</trunc>we've got one box left</u>
<u n="597" who="S0336">well actually I spent ages cutting the boxes down like with a Stanley knife so I actually managed to get all of the boxes into two</u>
<u n="598" who="S0337">but these <trunc>bo</trunc> they're up like here and like that wide</u>
<u n="599" who="S0336" trans="overlap">I mean yeah they they're they're the size of</u>
<u n="600" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="601" who="S0336">two chairs</u>
<u n="602" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="603" who="S0336">so they are big erm but we <vocal desc="laugh"/> we dumped one in the skip the other <trunc>morn</trunc> the other night well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did and it was so obvious like it was basically er basically filled the whole tip like yeah they're not gonna notice that <vocal desc="laugh"/> but we were too scared to do both on the same night because it really would look ridiculous so we did one the other night and we've got one we might have to try and ditch tonight</u>
<u n="604" who="S0341" trans="overlap">so why don't they want you don't they want you <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0337" trans="overlap">no they said we can but it's just embarrassing</u>
<u n="606" who="S0336" trans="overlap">they have yeah they I mean</u>
<u n="607" who="S0341">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0337">yeah it is <vocal desc="laugh"/> it is it really is</u>
<u n="609" who="S0336">they have said like</u>
<u n="610" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="611" who="S0336">obviously until the bins turn up we <trunc>c</trunc>we can use the skips at our leisure and stuff and I don't think we're the only ones taking advantage of that like I think other people on site</u>
<u n="612" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="613" who="S0336">are taking advantage of having a skip on their doorstep but it is embarrassing like these boxes are so ridiculously big</u>
<u n="614" who="S0337">erm no one else is doing that</u>
<u n="615" who="S0336">they were</u>
<u n="616" who="S0337">who?</u>
<u n="617" who="S0336">both next door neighbours were when the skip was right opposite us</u>
<u n="618" who="S0337">mm yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="619" who="S0341">you er you are still <trunc>m</trunc> you are still moving in at the end of the day and it you know it should be expected if they if they don't provide you with rubbish bins you gotta put it somewhere</u>
<u n="620" who="S0336">I know there's a <trunc>coup</trunc> well there's a couple of irritating things that have happened as well like we've been <trunc>wait</trunc> basically until the windows were sorted last week we were still technically going through the site for everything whereas now we go through customer care if we've got any problems with the house</u>
<u n="621" who="S0337" trans="overlap">we're doing the survey <unclear/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="623" who="S0336">Hamptons survey yeah but there's a couple of gripes so like the toilet in our en suite doesn't work and we're not <trunc>com</trunc></u>
<u n="624" who="S0337" trans="overlap">it does work</u>
<u n="625" who="S0336">well it does work it doesn't flush properly</u>
<u n="626" who="S0337" trans="overlap">it does flush</u>
<u n="627" who="S0336">oh but basically once you've flushed it it continually er <trunc>f</trunc> tries to fill itself</u>
<u n="628" who="S0337"><unclear/> no no it doesn't quite fill itself properly and trickles down the back it trickles into the toilet pan so it just always you can hear running water</u>
<u n="629" who="S0341">so it's on all the time</u>
<u n="630" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="631" who="S0341">it</u>
<u n="632" who="S0337">but all you have to do is go up to the back of it and just tap it again and then it it kind of flicks it back into just filling the tank at the back someone forgot to do that this morning someone else walked in to the en suite this evening and it was still trickling since this morning</u>
<u n="633" who="S0336">anyway</u>
<u n="634" who="S0337">that's a lot of water</u>
<u n="635" who="S0336">and so apparently now we've got no outdoor water</u>
<u n="636" who="S0341" trans="overlap"><unclear/> is it is it water that is it water that you're just? it's coming from your</u>
<u n="637" who="S0337">the rain</u>
<u n="638" who="S0336">yeah it's not it's not</u>
<u n="639" who="S0341" trans="overlap">connected water</u>
<u n="640" who="S0336">it's not it's not us we're not spending a fortune on water but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like oh there's no water in the outdoor tap</u>
<u n="641" who="S0341"><unclear/></u>
<u n="642" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><unclear/> we've either emptied the the tank at the back or we've been using mains water I can't remember what setting we've got it on</u>
<u n="643" who="S0336">not sure</u>
<u n="644" who="S0337">yeah we'll have to look</u>
<u n="645" who="S0336">but the back doors also stick not stick they erm</u>
<u n="646" who="S0337">rub on the floor</u>
<u n="647" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0337">they're about a millimetre or two too low</u>
<u n="649" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="650" who="S0337">so when you're opening when you open one of them it it's a bit stiff and it's not very nice when you open the other one you can hear the plastic from where it goes down the door rubbing against the floor and then when you try and pull it up onto the frame where the metal is</u>
<u n="651" who="S0336" trans="overlap">it's horrible</u>
<u n="652" who="S0337">it screeches</u>
<u n="653" who="S0341">they need they need the the in the hinges</u>
<u n="654" who="S0337" trans="overlap">just to raise it slightly</u>
<u n="655" who="S0341">it just</u>
<u n="656" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="657" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="659" who="S0337"><unclear>but it's just</unclear></u>
<u n="660" who="S0341">but it er you know they need to do it</u>
<u n="661" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0341">because they are</u>
<u n="663" who="S0336" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="664" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="665" who="S0341">the professionals so</u>
<u n="666" who="S0336" trans="overlap">we're just biding our time a little bit because we kicked up such a fuss about that outdoor light and they were actually they ended up being quite nice about fitting it cos they they didn't they weren't obliged to do it at all and from all accounts head office</u>
<u n="667" who="S0337" trans="overlap">and their head office yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0336">basically told them not to do it we've been told not to mention it on the survey and stuff because</u>
<u n="669" who="S0337">mm</u>
<u n="670" who="S0336">they basically went against their orders</u>
<u n="671" who="S0337">but they did bend over backwards in the end after a bit of a fight</u>
<u n="672" who="S0336">yeah so</u>
<u n="673" who="S0337">mm</u>
<u n="674" who="S0336">I feel bad finding stuff</u>
<u n="675" who="S0341">you can't live with it as it is cos you'll actually do you more damage opening the doors</u>
<u n="676" who="S0336">I know</u>
<u n="677" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="678" who="S0336">I know</u>
<u n="679" who="S0341">and then you know <trunc>i</trunc>if it can be seen that you've ignored the problem you'll be charged for their labour to put it right</u>
<u n="680" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="681" who="S0341">or the replacement doors</u>
<u n="682" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="683" who="S0336">did get a little mini win as well erm so I don't know if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> mentioned it to you but like you know he's got a building mate that does all of his building stuff? they did the extension and done his patio and stuff like that</u>
<u n="684" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="685" who="S0336">from all accounts <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s about to spend a lot of money with him doing like various jobs like</u>
<u n="686" who="S0337" trans="overlap">no he's spent a lot of money</u>
<u n="687" who="S0336">well he has spent a lot</u>
<u n="688" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><unclear>no</unclear></u>
<u n="689" who="S0336">he is about to though as well he's booked him in for like a whole week in October</u>
<u n="690" who="S0337">but it I think it was from he'd spent a lot of money and he'd made him a lot of money</u>
<u n="691" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="692" who="S0337">because people kept calling up and wanting to well people have been round to see the extension</u>
<u n="693" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0337">and it's got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a lot more work and made him a lot of money</u>
<u n="695" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0337">so as a favour he turned round and said er dad mentioned that we want the obviously the drive extended slightly and er the patio made a bit bigger and then</u>
<u n="697" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="698" who="S0337">the bit round the side done and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s turned round and said well if you get us the materials <unclear>er meaning if</unclear> if I get the materials he'll do it for free</u>
<u n="699" who="S0341">good</u>
<u n="700" who="S0337">so that's amazing</u>
<u n="701" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="702" who="S0341" trans="overlap">that is good yeah</u>
<u n="703" who="S0336">I don't we've we've kind of tested having both cars on the drive with one car pretty much up to the house and it's not quite long enough</u>
<u n="704" who="S0341">no</u>
<u n="705" who="S0337">you have one <unclear>car slightly</unclear></u>
<u n="706" who="S0336" trans="overlap">you've got a very long car which doesn't help but even so you don't want to be right up to the house</u>
<u n="707" who="S0341">mm yeah</u>
<u n="708" who="S0337">no</u>
<u n="709" who="S0336">so I think what's more likely is that we're gonna have to</u>
<u n="710" who="S0337"><unclear>well</unclear></u>
<u n="711" who="S0336">make it slightly wider</u>
<u n="712" who="S0341" trans="overlap">wider</u>
<u n="713" who="S0336">but it's just</u>
<u n="714" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="715" who="S0336">I don't wanna go I don't wanna go crazy wide but obviously I don't wanna go so tight that we can't get in and out of the cars so it's just trying we're gonna have to do some maths I think to try and work out</u>
<u n="716" who="S0341">well what you would do is park one car forward facing and the other car</u>
<u n="717" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="718" who="S0341">reversed so you're both getting out</u>
<u n="719" who="S0337">I know we do well that's what we've done</u>
<u n="720" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="721" who="S0337">we've my car goes at the front and I drive over the bump off the drive onto the grass and then we inch forward to about so my car bonnet is on the last slab cos obviously there's two slabs</u>
<u n="722" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="723" who="S0337">so my car bonnet will go up to there so you can just walk past <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will reverse on we will literally be that close</u>
<u n="724" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="725" who="S0337">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will be on the drive if I drive up to that end patio slab there so I'm not actually on it so you can walk past quite easily</u>
<u n="726" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="727" who="S0337">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> pulls up really close she's just off the edge of the drive</u>
<u n="728" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="729" who="S0336">it's just it's just a little bit too short</u>
<u n="730" who="S0337" trans="overlap">slightly too <unclear/></u>
<u n="731" who="S0341" trans="overlap">but but what I meant was when you go in widthwise</u>
<u n="732" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah oh sorry</u>
<u n="733" who="S0341">if you extend it widthwise</u>
<u n="734" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="735" who="S0341">and you wanna park next to each other</u>
<u n="736" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="737" who="S0341">then one parks forward facing to the house</u>
<u n="738" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="739" who="S0341">and <trunc>forwar</trunc> the other one parks forward facing to the road</u>
<u n="740" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="741" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="742" who="S0341">so you both drivers <trunc>g</trunc> can get out</u>
<u n="743" who="S0337" trans="overlap">oh yeah doors yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="744" who="S0336">yeah and whoever <trunc>go</trunc> whoever gets there first is gonna have to like drive on and go to the left because obviously the bit down to the road it er it</u>
<u n="745" who="S0337" trans="overlap">it's a horrible angle</u>
<u n="746" who="S0336">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know but I I <trunc>f</trunc>from I don't know if that's gonna happen before Christmas</u>
<u n="747" who="S0341"><unclear/></u>
<u n="748" who="S0336">or not but <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="749" who="S0341">you probably wanna wait until they've actually given you er a proper <unclear>riser</unclear></u>
<u n="750" who="S0336">I don't think they'll do</u>
<u n="751" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><unclear>no</unclear> that's gonna be a long time</u>
<u n="752" who="S0341" trans="overlap">to the drive</u>
<u n="753" who="S0336">I don't think they'll do the roads until they've finished the site</u>
<u n="754" who="S0337">no</u>
<u n="755" who="S0336">which could be another like twelve to eighteen months</u>
<u n="756" who="S0341">so if <unclear>you</unclear> actually do extend it before then</u>
<u n="757" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="758" who="S0341">they probably have to give you a double riser</u>
<u n="759" who="S0336">yeah they might they might do</u>
<u n="760" who="S0337" trans="overlap">we could well we could see about doing it ourselves <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="761" who="S0336">what? just putting tarmac down on the road</u>
<u n="762" who="S0337">I don't know where I can get tarmac from <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="763" who="S0336" trans="overlap">no I don't think you're allowed to do that erm but yeah so we have to do some sums basically and <trunc>wha</trunc> cos I like having a lot of green out the front I think it's compared to cos everybody else basically on that estate if you have a drive round everybody else has just got drives out the front like nobody else gets a garden really</u>
<u n="764" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="765" who="S0336">like even the ones even the ones to the right of us haven't really got a garden they've literally like obviously the ones next to us literally have that little bit that joins onto us</u>
<u n="766" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="767" who="S0336">but nothing else there is a proper garden so I know we've got a proper luxury there by having a nice front garden I don't wanna then ruin it by putting this huge driveway in <pause dur="short"/> so I'm really like undecided about it I know it would be handy to have the extra parking space but I do like the green</u>
<u n="768" who="S0337" trans="overlap">er if we do go wider I still wanna <unclear/> out of that <unclear>sliver</unclear></u>
<u n="769" who="S0336">yeah I know cos it looks stupid</u>
<u n="770" who="S0337">it's just pointless</u>
<u n="771" who="S0336">but we'll see we'll see <unclear/></u>
<u n="772" who="S0337">we need to find out what how much this the stuff costs anyway cos the stuff that our drive's made out of apparently is shipped in from Ireland so it's like specially made stones</u>
<u n="773" who="S0336">great</u>
<u n="774" who="S0341"><unclear/></u>
<u n="775" who="S0336">yeah but everything seems to be expensive like</u>
<u n="776" who="S0337" trans="overlap">er yeah everything seems to be</u>
<u n="777" who="S0336">although saying that I popped into Porcelanosa to like check out how much it would cost just to have those bathroom tiles and I was pleasantly surprised it was something like</u>
<u n="778" who="S0337">twenty-eight pound a box no twenty-eight pound a metre</u>
<u n="779" who="S0336">per square metre</u>
<u n="780" who="S0337">per square metre</u>
<u n="781" who="S0336">and I think we worked out that we'd need two square metres and that's with like leaving a lot of space for offcuts</u>
<u n="782" who="S0341"><unclear>yeah yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="783" who="S0336">and all that whatever you need to do so I'm thinking mm fifty quid sixty quid isn't really bad I know we add labour on top of that but can't really complain about that</u>
<u n="784" who="S0341">thing is if you find if you find someone if you find a mate you know you can even ask <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> if any of his mates are tiling</u>
<u n="785" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="786" who="S0337">we we got someone to do the tiling at my er my mum and dad's tiling round the fire tiling in the porch <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="787" who="S0336">it's a weird one it doesn't really feel er</u>
<u n="788" who="S0341" trans="overlap">are you alright? has that really?</u>
<u n="789" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="790" who="S0341">has it bothered you?</u>
<u n="791" who="S0337">apparently so</u>
<u n="792" who="S0336">I think everything bothers</u>
<u n="793" who="S0337">oh yeah but I have</u>
<u n="794" who="S0341" trans="overlap">is it painful or just bubbly?</u>
<u n="795" who="S0337">er a little bit of both it's slightly painful erm but the lunch I had this morning no today was the dinner we had from last night absolutely fine it's evening meals evening meals just bad <vocal desc="cough"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="796" who="S0336">I don't even feel like that was a <trunc>substant</trunc> like it was filling but not substantial</u>
<u n="797" who="S0341" trans="overlap">no but er I just think I just think you're er <trunc>s</trunc> you are not passing it through</u>
<u n="798" who="S0337">no</u>
<u n="799" who="S0341">effectively do <trunc>y</trunc> if you see what I mean?</u>
<u n="800" who="S0337"><unclear>I know</unclear></u>
<u n="801" who="S0341">cos if it's sitting there and you're putting more food on top</u>
<u n="802" who="S0337">just sit and piles up yeah</u>
<u n="803" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0341" trans="overlap">it's it is just <pause dur="short"/> it's just sitting there isn't it?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0337"><unclear>yeah yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="806" who="S0341">waiting for a gap to come</u>
<u n="807" who="S0337">it's weird</u>
<u n="808" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="809" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="810" who="S0337">so I'm actually hungry cos it's not made it down</u>
<u n="811" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="812" who="S0337"><vocal desc="cough"/> <unclear>oh well</unclear></u>
<u n="813" who="S0336">that's just dangerous isn't it? that's what he said</u>
<u n="814" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="815" who="S0337">oh yeah</u>
<u n="816" who="S0336">so erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the other day said oh where are you gonna put your Christmas tree? and I I was like well A it's August but B like I don't think we intend to spend Christmas there do we? not that we're not gonna put a Christmas tree up cos that seems a bit like Grinch-like</u>
<u n="817" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="818" who="S0336">but I was gonna assume that we were welcome at Christmas <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="819" who="S0337">yeah <unclear>I was</unclear></u>
<u n="820" who="S0341">more than</u>
<u n="821" who="S0337" trans="overlap">I was gonna say er hopefully both both parents</u>
<u n="822" who="S0341" trans="overlap">I'm hopefully gonna have something in the bedroom by then</u>
<u n="823" who="S0336">yeah that'd be good <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="824" who="S0337">so you can chuck <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in there</u>
<u n="825" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="826" who="S0337">yeah need to work that out don't we?</u>
<u n="827" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="828" who="S0341">yeah I definitely erm</u>
<u n="829" who="S0336" trans="overlap">would you would you be would you be in any way up for like a big Christmas celebration where like maybe me you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> all went over? I haven't actually asked <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this so I'm kind of inviting us but if we all had like Christmas together was that something you'd be up for?</u>
<u n="830" who="S0341">mm yeah I don't mind</u>
<u n="831" who="S0336">kind of feel like that would be like</u>
<u n="832" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="833" who="S0336">best of both worlds cos then we get to spend the whole day with everyone</u>
<u n="834" who="S0337">I'm cool with that</u>
<u n="835" who="S0336">we'll see <unclear>you'll</unclear> actually have to ask your mum</u>
<u n="836" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="837" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="838" who="S0337">what happened last Christmas? I know we hate we ate the er</u>
<u n="839" who="S0336" trans="overlap">I think because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> weren't coming</u>
<u n="840" who="S0337" trans="overlap">I don't think they are this year</u>
<u n="841" who="S0336">your parents were like don't come here so I think we spent Christmas here Boxing Day at mine and then we had <trunc>Chr</trunc> a third Christmas Day</u>
<u n="842" who="S0337" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="843" who="S0336"><trunc>a</trunc> on the day after Boxing Day</u>
<u n="844" who="S0337" trans="overlap">no wasn't it? oh right yeah I remember</u>
<u n="845" who="S0336">or the Saturday even maybe I think it was like Wednesday was Christmas Day Thursday was Boxing Day then we had like a random just a Friday and then we had to <trunc>s</trunc> a Christmas Day on Saturday when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came down</u>
<u n="846" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="847" who="S0337">yeah <unclear>I can</unclear> remember</u>
<u n="848" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="849" who="S0336">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is at yours for Christmas</u>
<u n="850" who="S0337">is he?</u>
<u n="851" who="S0341">well it might be too much for your mum then cos she'll have <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to sort as well won't she?</u>
<u n="852" who="S0337">he's always</u>
<u n="853" who="S0341">erm</u>
<u n="854" who="S0337">er always at ours for Christmas always has been cos er growing up it was one set of grandparents would come on Christmas Day the other ones would come on Boxing Day and there'd be a switchover</u>
<u n="855" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="856" who="S0337">she'd like change the beds and stuff in the middle of it all</u>
<u n="857" who="S0341"><unclear/></u>
<u n="858" who="S0336">but it's something we can think about if not we'll do like a half day here and a half day there</u>
<u n="859" who="S0337">yeah we'll enquire</u>
<u n="860" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="861" who="S0337">is that a <trunc>h</trunc> is that a razor?</u>
<u n="862" who="S0341">yes</u>
<u n="863" who="S0337"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>right</unclear></u>
<u n="864" who="S0341">we found it in one of the bags in the garage and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has asked me to cut his hair so</u>
<u n="865" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="866" who="S0341">I've used used the old <trunc>w</trunc>when he was a kid it didn't matter I could just razz it round and</u>
<u n="867" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="868" who="S0341">but he's quite happy with what he looks like so</u>
<u n="869" who="S0337">do we do we say something? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="870" who="S0336"><unclear/></u>
<u n="871" who="S0341" trans="overlap">no it it looks fine seriously</u>
<u n="872" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><unclear>it was alright</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="873" who="S0341">it does look fine it's just it is on the it's it it was done on the longest erm</u>
<u n="874" who="S0337">setting mm</u>
<u n="875" who="S0341">setting er and he was quite happy that he didn't have to pay a tenner to erm</u>
<u n="876" who="S0337" trans="overlap">I need mine cut <unclear/></u>
<u n="877" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="878" who="S0341">to have his hair cut so erm</u>
<u n="879" who="S0337">short back and sides</u>
<u n="880" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I need a haircut I just don't know if I can justify how much it costs I need a proper cut like what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s been doing has been helpful cos it's saved me a little bit of money but I need a proper cut cos it's just frizzy and dead and</u>
<u n="881" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I like it I think it looks great</u>
<u n="882" who="S0336">what looks great about it?</u>
<u n="883" who="S0337">you look like a big lion</u>
<u n="884" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="885" who="S0337">with your mane</u>
<u n="886" who="S0336">it just like it's just I mean it's calmed down now but you should've seen it first thing this morning it was like out here somewhere it was horrible</u>
<u n="887" who="S0337">I like it</u>
<u n="888" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="889" who="S0337">and you've had people comment on</u>
<u n="890" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="891" who="S0337">the colour of it</u>
<u n="892" who="S0336">yeah everybody seems to like the colour</u>
<u n="893" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="894" who="S0336">I think it's because it does look ombré but because it is natural</u>
<u n="895" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="896" who="S0336">the line that you normally see when people have it done which makes it look fairly artificial</u>
<u n="897" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="898" who="S0336">you can't really see with mine it looks like a proper fade</u>
<u n="899" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="900" who="S0336">cos it is a proper fade</u>
<u n="901" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="902" who="S0336">but I think the blonde blonde's just dyed</u>
<u n="903" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="904" who="S0341">it is nice wahey</u>
<u n="905" who="S0337">shake it <unclear>then</unclear></u>
<u n="906" who="S0341"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="907" who="S0336"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> moved into her house yesterday so her and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are now living over in <anon type="place"/> somewhere</u>
<u n="908" who="S0341" trans="overlap">ah I thought she was already there</u>
<u n="909" who="S0336"><vocal desc="sigh"/> no she got the keys like a week she got the keys in between me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> getting our keys but her dad gave her a load of money to deck it out basically get it decorated I don't I don't know erm to what extent I don't think she had like new kitchens and bathrooms and all that thing kind of stuff but I think she got to paint and kind of just make it</u>
<u n="910" who="S0337" trans="overlap">carpets and stuff</u>
<u n="911" who="S0336">a bit nicer maybe</u>
<u n="912" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="913" who="S0336">so I'm seeing her on Saturday morning cos well we were faffing for ages and I was like look I'm really busy next week like weekend's really the only time I have time she's like oh well I need to go buy a microwave on Saturday if you wanna come with me?</u>
<u n="914" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="915" who="S0336">I'm like if that's all you can give me I'll take it so I think I'm going with her to try and find a microwave slash washer dryer situation she wants to go and look in <anon type="place"/> but I'm like <anon type="place"/> your only choice is Tesco isn't it?</u>
<u n="916" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="917" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="918" who="S0336">why? you wanna go over</u>
<u n="919" who="S0341" trans="overlap"><unclear/> there aren't any electrical outlets there</u>
<u n="920" who="S0336">no</u>
<u n="921" who="S0337">no</u>
<u n="922" who="S0341">Currys isn't there</u>
<u n="923" who="S0336">you wanna go to <anon type="place"/> I don't know why or not <anon type="place"/> the one that's er</u>
<u n="924" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> is er it's basically <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="925" who="S0336">the one that's across <trunc>i</trunc>is it both <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="926" who="S0341">erm</u>
<u n="927" who="S0337"><unclear>I dunno</unclear> might as well be</u>
<u n="928" who="S0336">what? is is</u>
<u n="929" who="S0337">I dunno if it's got a name</u>
<u n="930" who="S0336">is it <anon type="place"/>? no not <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="931" who="S0341">it is the <anon type="place"/> one</u>
<u n="932" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="933" who="S0336"><anon type="place"/> but I don't know what it's called but yeah Currys is her best bet especially if they've still got sales on from last week</u>
<u n="934" who="S0341">yes</u>
<u n="935" who="S0336">so I don't know</u>
<u n="936" who="S0337" trans="overlap">there's loads of sales <unclear/></u>
<u n="937" who="S0341"><unclear/></u>
<u n="938" who="S0336" trans="overlap">she's gonna come over to ours anyway so</u>
<u n="939" who="S0341">yeah there's a there is a erm you know the Hotpoint depot?</u>
<u n="940" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="941" who="S0341">in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="942" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="943" who="S0341">they they they sell</u>
<u n="944" who="S0337" trans="overlap">is that the one I drive past?</u>
<u n="945" who="S0336" trans="overlap">that's right near us yeah</u>
<u n="946" who="S0341">yeah they sell er they sell fridges and washing machines and all the white goods stuff there</u>
<u n="947" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="948" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="949" who="S0341">they sell it they sell what they call seconds</u>
<u n="950" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="951" who="S0341">you know it might have a dent in the door or something like that but it's pretty much</u>
<u n="952" who="S0336" trans="overlap">it works yeah</u>
<u n="953" who="S0341">you know rock bottom erm at rock bottom price</u>
<u n="954" who="S0336" trans="overlap">well we'll see</u>
<u n="955" who="S0341">but you er you kind of have to take it away with you on the day</u>
<u n="956" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="957" who="S0337">if erm if you really wanted to just go somewhere you should just go to Argos</u>
<u n="958" who="S0336">I know well she's coming cos I sort of said oh do you want me to meet you somewhere or do you wanna come to mine? and she was like oh I'll come to yours so I guess I can talk to her then about like oh have you thought about <trunc>thi</trunc> have you seen something you like specifically? or whatever we'll see</u>
<u n="959" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="960" who="S0336">we weren't gonna do much this weekend anyway but I do wanna see <unclear>her</unclear> I I feel like properly left out of the loop with my friends at the moment which I don't hugely mind it's not like I haven't been seeing other friends and whatnot but or just</u>
<u n="961" who="S0341">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="962" who="S0336">I've always kept one I've always</u>
<u n="963" who="S0337"><unclear>just the girls mm</unclear></u>
<u n="964" who="S0336">kept one hand in and now at the moment I feel like I don't even have that</u>
<u n="965" who="S0341">but I think er <trunc>d</trunc> you are all getting to that point aren't you? er of of actually settling down somewhere and</u>
<u n="966" who="S0337" trans="overlap">I dunno some of them are some of them are really</u>
<u n="967" who="S0341">doing your own thing you you really don't want to still be in the circle of going out and</u>
<u n="968" who="S0336"><unclear>no not really</unclear></u>
<u n="969" who="S0341">and <unclear/> at night do you?</u>
<u n="970" who="S0337" trans="overlap">no er no some of <trunc>the</trunc>some of them are really up for it still like when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> moved into hers they all went to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s but they'd left by nine o'clock so they could make it into town to go out</u>
<u n="971" who="S0336">so they drove all the way to <anon type="place"/> to go to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s housewarming party for like two hours and then drove back to <anon type="place"/> to go out</u>
<u n="972" who="S0337"><unclear/> cos we I was at hospital for my consultation and we got there about quarter past nine</u>
<u n="973" who="S0336">and they'd already gone</u>
<u n="974" who="S0337">and they'd already left to go out</u>
<u n="975" who="S0341" trans="overlap">that's bad</u>
<u n="976" who="S0336">it's really bad</u>
<u n="977" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="978" who="S0336">like that's that's the er that's the first and only time <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s gonna have like</u>
<u n="979" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="980" who="S0336">her very first housewarming do you know what I mean? and they weren't even there to like fully appreciate it</u>
<u n="981" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="982" who="S0336">so that's what like I'm really not that fussed about us having anything like that cos like</u>
<u n="983" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="984" who="S0336">they'd either blow it off or they'd come and then be like oh this is handy you're right in town</u>
<u n="985" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="986" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="987" who="S0336">so</u>
<u n="988" who="S0337">and they went well no one not all of them but a lot of them went to Ibiza as well</u>
<u n="989" who="S0336">yeah they've all come back from Ibiza</u>
<u n="990" who="S0337" trans="overlap">they're <trunc>s</trunc>they're still</u>
<u n="991" who="S0336">they're <trunc>d</trunc> they're they're <trunc>qu</trunc> er they're <vocal desc="sigh"/> there's a couple of them now that have got quite cliquey so like obviously <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s living with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s like best mates with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> bum <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as well so before you know it like those five are just inseparable at the moment</u>
<u n="992" who="S0337"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is doing her own thing with <unclear/></u>
<u n="993" who="S0336" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is very much doing her own thing I think that's kind of why I miss some of the other girls because like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> even <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't have any time for me at the moment like she's literally been to see us in the house once and it was just the most flyby visit ever</u>
<u n="994" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="995" who="S0336">and I know she's really busy at work and stuff but like it's even at weekends and stuff she's not it's not like she's putting any time aside to come and see us</u>
<u n="996" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="997" who="S0336">so I'm just er I slightly resent that cos I made quite a big deal about like her moving into her house it's just not</u>
<u n="998" who="S0337">we were there the day that she moved in</u>
<u n="999" who="S0336">yeah just not really felt the same kind of</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0337">love</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0336"><unclear>love</unclear></u>
<u n="1003" who="S0337">ah it's really weird I think your your girlfriends are always like that though</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0337" trans="overlap">like if you're if you're in at the time whatever it is like</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0336">you're in it in it</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0337" trans="overlap">there's er there's a lot of action and you're in it</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0337">but if you drop off a little bit then they they just carry on and</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0341" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0337">they forget <unclear/></u>
<u n="1012" who="S0336" trans="overlap">but like I think <trunc>w</trunc>what's upset me recently is like if I wasn't making the effort with them I'd fully appreciate them kind of saying oh well is she's not gonna make the effort I'm not going to but over the last couple of months it's always been me making the contacts it's always been me being like hi how are you? like can we catch up? blah blah blah and er especially <unclear>like</unclear> with people like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1013" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0336">who can't drive it's always you going to them so I've probably only seen her a handful of times since Christmas and every single time it's been me going to her</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0336">like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s exactly the same I appreciate <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s very busy like especially when obviously she's <trunc>w</trunc> at school and stuff but like it's constantly me ringing her or texting her</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0341" trans="overlap">she's <unclear>on</unclear> school holidays for the last six weeks though</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0336" trans="overlap">I know but she's been so busy with the house stuff erm but this is what I mean like everybody's got their own stuff going on which is fine but when it's constantly you going oh can we meet up?</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0336">like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s blown me off the last two or three times we've made plans she's coincidentally like double-booked herself and stuff so like I'll literally be texting her the morning that we're meant to be seeing each other and she's like oh I'm sorry I've made plans and it's like don't do that like</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0336">I've made the effort to come to you I haven't seen you in ages and now</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0336">you're blowing me off to like go and see someone or something that you see all the time</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0336">it's really annoying so that's what's kind of I think that's what's got on my nerves cos I just feel like it's constantly me and even it's kind of the same with the girls from uni like they all live in <anon type="place"/> so it's very very easy to a certain extent for them to all meet up so I said to them a couple of weeks ago like oh erm er what what's it like for you guys in the evening? like if I come up for the evening and can we all go out for dinner or something? and like in my head I was thinking like that is a bit of a task for me but if it was on like a Thursday or a Friday I wouldn't mind doing it they all organised to do it on a Monday and I was like really? are you taking the mick? like that's such a long day for me to like go to work then well actually get the train into work then get the train from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> have dinner with you all then get a very presumably very late train home from</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0336"><anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> to then have to get up and basically</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0336">carry on with the rest of the week</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0336">like that's just such a big ask and I was like</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0336"><unclear>just</unclear> kind of miffed <trunc>th</trunc>that they organised it all without me even though it was me that kind of initiated it and then like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> texted me afterwards saying like oh I think we're all gonna go to <anon type="place"/> like maybe like do you fancy it? and I'm like yeah I fancy it like I don't wanna feel completely like I'm not</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0336">and then I <trunc>f</trunc>then I feel bad cos I'm not making the effort to go down to <anon type="place"/> but it's so much easier for them to get across <anon type="place"/> than it is for me to get down there and then back <trunc>h</trunc> like from <anon type="place"/> down there and then all the way back home</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0341">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0336">and it's like they all know I've just moved into a house and not a single one of them's made the effort none like none of them have rang me to be like oh so how's it going? none of them have said oh can we come and visit?</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0336">so it's just like</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0336">I don't wanna be needy I don't wanna be the one going oh when are you gonna come and see me?</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0336">and I then don't also wanna make it feel like they're constantly coming to me but it's not like they're constantly coming to me</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0336">and er I almost feel like me making one journey to <anon type="place"/> is the same as them making one journey down to <anon type="place"/> like regardless of how many people are there like</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0336">do I have to go five times to <anon type="place"/> for every one time they come here? because</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0336">there's five of them in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1051" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0336">and just trying to coordinate cos like a couple of them seem to like only wanna do stuff when there's a big group of us and it's like it's so hard to coordinate six people who have very separate very busy lives like</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0336">it'd be fairly easy me for me to probably text <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and be like oh I don't suppose you're around this weekend? I've got nothing to do I I might come down to <anon type="place"/> for the day do you wanna do lunch or something?</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0336">it's fairly easy for me to text her and she'll say yes or no but if I text all of them it's like some people'll be like yes some people'll say no of those that say yes some people'll be free in the morning some people'll be free in the afternoon and before you know it you're running round headless trying to accommodate everybody else when actually you're the one making the effort to go down there so everybody should be accommodating you</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0336">so it's a tough one I had a really nice time when I went down in April but it's not cheap like</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0336">costs me twenty quid on the train for starters and then if we eat out and we have like I think last time we I had the train to pay for we didn't really do much in the day but we had breakfast at <anon type="place"/> which was like fifteen quid and then we walked around all afternoon which was cool and then we went and had a couple of bottles of wine</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0336">but like even a couple of bottles of wine between us was another fifteen twenty quid</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0336">and then we had dinner on top of that I think I spent one day in <anon type="place"/> it cost me seventy quid like</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0336">that's a huge commitment when I don't have a lot of like disposable income</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0336">I can't do that very often</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0336">and they just don't seem to appreciate that and actually it's quite a big undertaking to say ah well of my weekend I'm gonna spend the whole day on Saturday going to <anon type="place"/> and walking round <anon type="place"/> et cetera cos then before you know it the weekend's over and you're absolutely knackered cos you've ran around like a headless chicken</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0341">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0336">so I don't know I'm feeling a bit like</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0336">a bit left out of stuff at the moment and a bit <vocal desc="sigh"/> a bit disappointed cos I think it's one of those things like buying a house feels like the biggest thing in your life like you know it is one of the biggest things you'll ever do</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0341" trans="overlap">it is <unclear/> big a big step yeah</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0336">and it's <trunc>f</trunc> it fairly disappointing when your friends don't appreciate how big that is</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0336">but oh well</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0341">yeah it's just everybody's gonna be at different stages in their</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0341">lifetime <unclear/></u>
<u n="1082" who="S0336">it's <trunc>w</trunc> it is weird talking to my friends from <anon type="place"/> because they've just got a completely different perspective on things like</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0341" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0336">for them their number one priority is their job like</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0336">that's what they're pouring their heart and soul into is their job and they're working all the hours under the sun and they're making huge sacrifices to be able to do whatever it is that they're doing and they're loving it and that's great that's that's fab but they're sacrificing a hell of a lot to do it they're they're not they don't have a lot of personal time they certainly don't get a lot of time to do a lot of stuff in the evening they're paying a lot for the lifestyle to live in <anon type="place"/> et cetera</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0336">and I don't have a lot in common with that cos <trunc>w</trunc> I really enjoy my job</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0336">I'm very happy where I am but it's still a means to an end for me like</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0336">I go to work so that I can afford to do the other things that I like to do</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0336">in my life</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0336">and er it is it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and it's the house and it's</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0336">whatever else that actually</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0336">makes me happy so for me it's weird to think of a life that literally revolved around work</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0336">and for them the concept of owning a house is so kind of out of their reach in the</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0336">short-term because house prices there are so ridiculous it's not even on their radar</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0336">so I think to a certain extent a lot of them are quite freaked out by the fact that I've made such a commitment so young</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0336">because it's just not something that they've even considered</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0341">they can do mm</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0336">yeah so I don't I don't know if there's maybe a pang of even jealousy there</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0336">cos I know a couple of them made comments about the fact you know they're they're not gonna be owning a house anytime soon and I'm like well it is one of the it's another sacrifice that you make to work in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1113" who="S0341">and everybody everybody really you know you just have your own goals don't you? and you do reach a point in life and career and whatever that you're gonna go this way or that way and it it usually is job or</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0336">job or like home life effectively yeah</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0341" trans="overlap">family-centred</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0336">I just don't I at the moment am struggling to see a job that I could love so much that I would be prepared to like put it first</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0336">cos I just get so much more satisfaction from my relationships from my friends</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0336">from my family <pause dur="short"/> I get I get I er I get so much more from that than</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0336">from going to work <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0336">so I I think I find it hard to communicate with them on that level as well cos we have got very different lifestyles</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0337">hello</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0336">hello</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0341">alright?</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0337">mm</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0341">do you need another drink?</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0337"><unclear/> good thanks</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0336"><unclear/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sent me a link to a story at work today I don't know if you saw it? the</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0337" trans="overlap">BBC News</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0336">BBC News a woman who had erm a five thousand</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0337">three foot wasps' nest in her house</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0341">oh</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0336">three three foot wasps' <trunc>ne</trunc> that had formed on a spare bed</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0337">in her house</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0341">oh</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0337">so it had been there for at least three months and had five thousand wasps in it</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0341">oh good lord</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0337" trans="overlap">and the guy that <trunc>se</trunc>got sent got called round to deal with it said he was absolutely amazed and thought it was like really magnificent but was just one of the most dangerous things he'd ever seen</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah he they'd they'd basically it there was like a picture of this bed crocheted like er <pause dur="short"/> blanket type thing and then like it was just like a single bed <trunc>p</trunc>pillow or whatever er and like over the pillow just this huge like <trunc>w</trunc> it wasn't obviously wasn't a round wasp wasps' nest it almost looked like er half a dome</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0337" trans="overlap">just a big mound yeah</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0336">a big mound and erm the guy said that these wasps had like eaten through the mattress and through the pillows and stuff to make their nest bigger so this nest was like fully integrated into this bed he said that he had to go back through and shut the door cos obviously it would've been really dangerous if the wasps got into the er house but there was like five thousand odd he said it's the biggest thing he's ever seen</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0336">so dangerous this woman like it didn't really say much about the woman</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0337">no</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0336">so I don't know if she was elderly or what but</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0337">it was really obscure wasn't it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1152" who="S0336">it was just like oh yeah er like the only quote I think they had from her was like the the the this room was just unused and it hadn't been hadn't been gone into but I'm like who doesn't go into a room in their house for three months?</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0337" trans="overlap">who wouldn't hear a wasps' nest that big?</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0336">I know</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0341">yes er how do they come and go?</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0337">oh is it the window had been left ajar?</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0336">oh yeah one of like</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0337"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1159" who="S0336">a small window had been left slightly open</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0337">but that's all they need</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1163" who="S0341" trans="overlap">well it is all they need and it just</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0341">that's that's how they actually get into the loft spaces isn't it?</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0337" trans="overlap">lofts yeah</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0341">they er they kind of get er under the eaves and erm</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0337">find a tiny hole</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0341">can usually</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0336">but it literally made my scrin my scrin craw my <trunc>skr</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't talk my skin crawl</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0336">that's just horrible</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0341">yes</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0336">so yeah don't don't don't don't check your spare room</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0341" trans="overlap">no well no</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0337">D D D D D</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0336" trans="overlap">D D D don't don't not check</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0337">D D D</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1181" who="S0341" trans="overlap">actually <unclear/> an empty spare room <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> we know there's no wasps in there</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0336">I don't know if I like my room being called a spare room</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0341">it took a bit of cleaning around the windows</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0337" trans="overlap">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0341"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1187" who="S0336">oh yeah it was pretty gross <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1188" who="S0337" trans="overlap">someone opened their jewellery bag onto our bed and it was filthy covered full of like</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0336">you know those little like black bugs that were around</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0337" trans="overlap">thunder mites</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0336">thunder bug type things</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0337">thunder yeah thunder <unclear/></u>
<u n="1194" who="S0336">so I literally tipped like my bag of jewellery out onto the bed and there was just these black bugs everywhere I was like oh that's so gross</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0337">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1196" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0337">is it just clean a clean empty room now?</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0336">have you painted it yet?</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0341">no er tried got the stuff ready so erm just waiting for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to get some enthusiasm</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0341">he's <trunc>t</trunc> he was too tired last weekend he wasn't even getting up before two o'clock</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0336">how does he do that?</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0341">I just don't know he said to me on Friday wake me up when you get up tomorrow and I'll make a start on it so I did and then every hour after that</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0337"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1206" who="S0341">and eventually got up at two o'clock he said oh I might do it tomorrow the weather's gonna be bad tomorrow so then Sunday I woke him up at eleven thought that was a reasonable time and I think I left at one o'clock to go and meet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and er he was just getting up</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0337">absolute lad <pause dur="short"/> and then he was up all night</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0341">he probably is up during the night to watch er movies or stuff</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0337">well I used to do that so I can't say anything</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0336">yeah we're on slightly</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0341"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1212" who="S0336">different patterns at the moment like</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0336"><trunc>w</trunc> er when I get up early my alarm's going off at like six and I'm out of the house for seven so by the time ten o'clock comes round I'm <trunc>r</trunc>really flagging like really tired but obviously <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't get up till about like half past seven eight o'clock maybe</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><trunc>quar</trunc>quarter to eight</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0337">quarter to eight</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0336">so</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0336">when I'm trying to get him to come to bed at like half past ten he's not tired in the slightest</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0337">I get tired at eleven but you're already fast asleep</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0337">but</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0336">but like last night I was up yesterday morning six half past six whatever had a really long day then I had <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> round all evening and I still managed to stay up till about</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0336">half past eleven but</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0336">that meant I couldn't get up I wouldn't have been able to get up this morning at six</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0341">mm mm</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0336">it's hard hard trying to find the balance</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0337">yeah er</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0341">I can imagine</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0337">it's also weird for me to be woken up at six</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0337">and <trunc>act</trunc>actively woken up cos obviously en suite and hairdryer if you clean your hair and just general walking around so I'm not quite back to sleep then I fall back to sleep</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0337">and then I get woken up by my alarm</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0337">so we need to find an in-between today was nice today was so much better for me</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0336">he likes having me there in the morning which is fine and</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0336">in all fairness like I left at nine o'clock this morning and I was in for quarter to ten</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0336">and I left at half past five and managed to avoid I think some fairly long traffic but I still was home for half past six</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0341" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0336">which isn't the worst thing in the world</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0341">no</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0336">like that's not too late especially if he could get home and start making dinner</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0337" trans="overlap">and er I as you say I was already home and I I could've started cooking <unclear/></u>
<u n="1252" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1255" who="S0336">I imagine</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0341">school will start back next week</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0336">I imagine going forward I might have to adopt a late start because the early start getting on the road at seven I do still hit congestion and so it's not a very nice drive and you'd think leaving at half past three it would it would always be a cruise home but it's not always a cruise home even at half past three so it's like it's</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0337" trans="overlap">you've left a few times recently</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0337">and been in <trunc>s</trunc> in a bad place</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0341" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0336">so it's like there aren't there aren't that many perks to going in early other than I like the way my day forms so like if I start work at eight</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0336">and don't have lunch till one I've done the biggest part of my day before I've even had lunch</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0336">so after lunch I've only got a couple of hours left to work</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0336">which is much nicer than having like the biggest part of the day after lunch that being said like I think as as winter draws in I think I will find it harder and harder to get up early when it's like cold and not very nice and it's not very nice waking up on your own</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0336">when he's still in bed and stuff so I imagine moving forward I probably will work lates cos</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0336">it's one of those things as well like obviously as the nights draw in you're doing less and less in the evening anyway so there's no real need for me to rush home</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0341" trans="overlap">mm no</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0336">cos that's what I find er</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0341" trans="overlap">and also the weather earlier in the morning the roads aren't</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0336" trans="overlap">it's dangerous</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0341">quite as er</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0341">de-iced and whatever</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0336">I just</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0337"><unclear>driver-friendly</unclear></u>
<u n="1285" who="S0336">I just think I get home</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0336">like even like yesterday it didn't make much of a difference cos I had <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> coming over but I can be home for like quarter past half past four but to what end? like I'm still sitting round waiting for an hour until he gets back to like</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0337" trans="overlap">at least yeah</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0336">er to at least</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0336">to start thinking about dinner or whatever</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0337">so I don't get <unclear/> don't get in till about six</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0337">quarter past six</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0336">so my day isn't er like you know like er</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0336"><vocal desc="sigh"/> if I was getting up that time and having lunch early et cetera et cetera I should be eating early</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0336">but I can't eat early because I'm still kind of <trunc>w</trunc> having to wait for him so work</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0337" trans="overlap">and I can't get off or on <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1301" who="S0336">no</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0336">you will like minimum</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0337" trans="overlap">for at least half a hour just</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0336">yeah you'd be lucky to get home for half past five</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0337" trans="overlap">the the <anon type="place"/>'s killing us yeah</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0336">so</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0336">earlies doesn't have that many advantages to be honest so I think</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>I think</unclear></u>
<u n="1312" who="S0337">I think when the <anon type="place"/>'s completed slightly or at least that that</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0336" trans="overlap">slip road</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0337">slip road getting onto it</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0337">because you can't get off the estate for twenty twenty-five minutes</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0337">if you leave bang on five by the time you've got to your car</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0341" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0337">they're queuing up the road past</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0337">past where you used to work</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0337">and they're queuing right round mine until er until <trunc>m</trunc> to my front door</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0341">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah so er</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1328" who="S0341">it's not a nice er situation is it?</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0337">mm</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0336">no I'll er I'll have to find something like this this week I have been doing earlies and it it does help to get into a routine I E go in at the same time every day</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0337">mm</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0336">erm</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0337"><unclear>soon as</unclear> you choose the routine on a Monday</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0337">you should stick with it for the rest of the week</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0337">and then you can just choose it again <unclear/></u>
<u n="1339" who="S0336" trans="overlap">it's er it's actually easier to start off the week earlies and then if I get tired towards the end of the week switch to lates it's easier to do that because effectively like last night for example I got in at half past four I didn't go er I didn't leave the house till nine so you get like a nice rest it's easier to do that than to do lates and then</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0336">try and switch onto earlies because</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0336">you're getting home at like half past six and then you're leaving</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0337">you don't switch <unclear/></u>
<u n="1345" who="S0336">at half past six</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0336">so it's like I'm literally in the house for twelve hours which is just a bit depressing</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0336">so yeah you have to find <unclear>you</unclear> have to find the balance</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0336">it at the moment at the moment earlies are okay they serve a purpose because like I've had to be home for stuff if if I'm hosting if I'm expecting people to come over I'd much prefer to be home when so they can come over as soon as they've</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0336">finished work than expecting them to hang around town till like</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0336">half past six or whatever erm</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0337">but you don't wanna be lonely do you?</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0336">no and I don't like the mornings are tough like</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0336">and I'd I don't really look after myself as much in the mornings I'll literally like maybe get up at half past six and try and be out of the house for like ten to seven seven o'clock</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0336">so all I literally do is splash my face and get dressed and head out so I'm not even like waking myself up properly before I go I'm not having breakfast until I get to work</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0336">so it's like actually this morning was so lovely cos I actually took my time getting up I had a proper <trunc>showe</trunc> a nice long shower</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0336">washed my hair and everything got dressed</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0337" trans="overlap">sat down</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0336">sat down and had breakfast with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went I went and dried my hair</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0336">and headed off and I have like a proper like I guess hour-and-a-half</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0336">of like just getting ready and taking my time and eating my breakfast</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0336">and just waking up</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0341" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0336">so by the time I was in the car I was like I was ready to start my day properly</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0341" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0336">and actually today was really nice I I forced well I think this is what I'm gonna have to do I forced myself to wait until half past one for my lunch so I did three-and-a-half hours half an hour lunch three-and-a-half hours which feels nice like</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0336">that I can do</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0341" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0336">what I've found is sometimes when I do lates I somehow like I struggle to get going a little bit because like</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0336">everybody's already in their full flow when I get into work and I feel like I'm a bit behind</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0341" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0336">and then because it's ten o'clock already you almost feel like you get into this false state of saying to yourself oh well er it's only a few hours until lunch so what I found myself doing is being a bit bored and then going on an early lunch at say like twelve half twelve when I really didn't need to</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0341">mm mm</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0336">and so I'd come back and I'd have like four-and-a-half hours left to work and you're just like that's actually a bit</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0336">depressing like that's a long time to still be working</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0341">yeah</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0336">I don't know er I'll find er</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0341" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="yawn"/> oh goodness</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0336">I'll find a rhythm with it at some point I think I've <trunc>s</trunc> I've well I've <trunc>s</trunc> talked to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about it a bit recently but I think I've struggled this year cos of like the switchover of my jobs and like because I had to use a lot of holiday earlier in the year for like interviews and stuff like that I've really lost out this year on holiday</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0336">so I'm knackered just from the fact that I've not really had</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0341">yes</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0336">any like it's the whole house moving thing you know if I had proper holiday to use</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0341" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0336">I'd've taken the time off when we moved and I'd've actually like spent a few days just getting the house the way I wanted it but instead I had a weekend where we were trying to do everything rushed</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0336">then went back to work and then every weekend since it's been trying to do odd jobs because</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0336">I don't have the time to do it in the week</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0341" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0336">and like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got like ten days or something left to <trunc>l</trunc> use before Christmas</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0336">and I just think</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><unclear>winning</unclear></u>
<u n="1409" who="S0336">yeah I just think</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0336">oh it's like like I'm gonna have to deal with the fact that he's got those days that I haven't got</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0336">so there's gonna be at least a week-and-a-half when I've like got to go to work and he doesn't which is just and I'm knackered</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0341">yeah mm</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0336">erm <pause dur="short"/> never mind</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0341">and when does your leave year start?</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0336">January to January so it's fine like and er the thing is <vocal desc="sigh"/> what's kind of skewing it is because I've almost joined like the wrong half of the year like because I have to save four for Christmas</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0336">I got er <trunc>ha</trunc> basically half a year's like holiday allowance</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0337" trans="overlap">but four of it four days <unclear/></u>
<u n="1422" who="S0336">but four of it had to be allocated to Christmas so</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0336">immediately I had like less anyway and then it just so happened that we'd already booked that week as holiday basically a couple of weeks into me starting</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0341">mm</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0336">so that was a massive chunk straightaway gone</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0341" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0336">so it's just</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0341">let's go and have a seat in there for a while</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0336">yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
