<text id="SGAX">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:00:31</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Violence, TV shows, cartoons, films</topics>
		<activity>Matt and Claire talking</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0037">so it was a programme that was about like um <pause dur="short"/> it was a bit stupid it it followed much in the vain of like you know Dave Benson Phillips?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> well he was a presenter wasn't he?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0037">you know Get Your Own Back did you ever watch that?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0115">oh yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0037">so Dick And Dom In Da House pardon me had a segment that was very much like that</u>
<u n="6" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="7" who="S0037">like very like get your own back on your parents</u>
<u n="8" who="S0115">right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0037">and um my favourite bit was uh <pause dur="short"/> did they score then? My favourite bit was when they had um <pause dur="short"/> this section in it was called Bogey <pause dur="short"/> and so the kids and the parents had to like outdo each other by shouting bogey really loud</u>
<u n="10" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0037">so like they would go to like an aquarium and they'd be like looking at this you know you know those <pause dur="short"/> you know in the aquarium where like you go under a tunnel and the fish go over the to of you</u>
<u n="12" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0037">and um then they'd be like bogey like have to shout it really loud <pause dur="short"/> it's just so infantile it's just right up my street</u>
<u n="14" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> made for uh infants</u>
<u n="15" who="S0037">exactly</u>
<u n="16" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="17" who="S0037">but I love <pause dur="short"/> I love children's TV</u>
<u n="18" who="S0115" trans="overlap">in the tunnel? Why a tunnel though?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0037">but I love  I love  children's TV</u>
<u n="20" who="S0115">why a tunnel though</u>
<u n="21" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="yawn"/> Excuse me I love children's TV and <trunc>sti</trunc> even still</u>
<u n="22" who="S0115">well some of it's good I mean <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="23" who="S0037">have you seen Ooglies</u>
<u n="24" who="S0115">no I don't think so</u>
<u n="25" who="S0037">that's one of my favourites <pause dur="short"/> it's cos I get</u>
<u n="26" who="S0115" trans="overlap">used to like it yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's cos with going to work I get up still on a Saturday and Sunday at the same time <pause dur="short"/> I get up at seven and I'm like Whoohoo like Balamory's on <vocal desc="laugh"/> or whatever <pause dur="short"/> in fact I don't really like Balamory but</u>
<u n="28" who="S0115">oh you don't why not  why not?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0037">well it's just a little</u>
<u n="30" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you have such such high standards?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0037">well exactly <pause dur="short"/> no it's just a bit too young like I like the stuff that's more like for eight year olds <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> can I have some of this?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0115">of course</u>
<u n="33" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> the stuff that's for like eight like not like for babies</u>
<u n="34" who="S0115">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> not like Teletubbies</u>
<u n="35" who="S0037" trans="overlap">not like Teletubbies <pause dur="short"/> but have you seen?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0115">I mean that's that's totally sort of some you know um</u>
<u n="37" who="S0037">oh <pause dur="short"/> sorry?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0115">teletubbies is like being on some kind of strange trip or something</u>
<u n="39" who="S0037">mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0115">you know psychedelic</u>
<u n="41" who="S0037">have you ever seen I'm Sorry I've Got No Head?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Um no but I think is that like Horrible Histories?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I've told you about it <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit like Horrible Histories but it's like um <pause dur="short"/> excuse me <pause dur="short"/> it's not about  it's not about  history it's just like a sketch show <pause dur="short"/> it's like a sketch show for kids <pause dur="short"/> comedy</u>
<u n="44" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but but Horrible Histories is kind of a sketch show isn't it?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0037">yeah but <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I just said it's not like it's not about history</u>
<u n="46" who="S0115">oh <pause dur="short"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> not about history? What's it about?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0037">well just funny funny things <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="48" who="S0115">okay</u>
<u n="49" who="S0037">they've got um</u>
<u n="50" who="S0115">well it's a good title</u>
<u n="51" who="S0037" trans="overlap">some of the people in it like Marcus Brigstocke's in it</u>
<u n="52" who="S0115">oh yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0037">as is um what's he called the guy he's on some of the um NatWest adverts <pause dur="short"/> he was also in um Twenty Twelve as like a really bad athlete</u>
<u n="54" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um</u>
<u n="55" who="S0037">like he <trunc>wa</trunc> he really wanted a job they were sending him out to primary schools like he was really bad at even talk <pause dur="short"/> cos he's quite tall</u>
<u n="56" who="S0115">oh um from um Whites yeah?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0037">from Whites yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's in it and uh</u>
<u n="58" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like yeah he's like the second main guy in Whites after</u>
<u n="59" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0115">Alan Davies</u>
<u n="61" who="S0037">that's right</u>
<u n="62" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's a bit like a modern-day John Cleese</u>
<u n="63" who="S0037">yeah yeah yeah very <trunc>m</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> in fact did he not play John Cleese in that thing?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> in um was about the uh</u>
<u n="65" who="S0037">sorry?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0115">the Life Of Brian interview with the  with the  priests</u>
<u n="67" who="S0037">oh that's right <pause dur="short"/> that was good I'd like to watch that again</u>
<u n="68" who="S0115">yeah it was pretty much like it was him and Michael Palin and um <pause dur="short"/> it was written in in a way that</u>
<u n="69" who="S0037" trans="overlap">who was who played Michael Palin?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0115">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> it was written in a <trunc>i</trunc> like Michael Palin was was portrayed as being disappointed that Cleese didn't stand up enough for their cause</u>
<u n="71" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> I remember that bit <pause dur="short"/> I only seen the end of it</u>
<u n="73" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0115">so the end of the interview and where they sort of walked off <pause dur="short"/> and it had an element of uh Frost Nixon about it cos of the interview <pause dur="short"/> cos it was uh an interview although really it was a debate actually</u>
<u n="75" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="77" who="S0037">well supposed to be</u>
<u n="78" who="S0115">it was  it was  back in the sort of the blasphemy</u>
<u n="79" who="S0037">ah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0115">they they <pause dur="short"/> priests were accusing um accusing Monty Python of blasphemy for uh making The Life Of Brian</u>
<u n="81" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0115">blasphemy meaning insulting God is that what it is or?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> lord's name in vain?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0115">yeah um <pause dur="short"/> then there's another one which is uh is another thing called heresy isn't it which is that's the denial of the existence of God</u>
<u n="85" who="S0037" trans="overlap">not believing in God yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0115">these guys had uh blasphemy which was a big you know you could  you could  get uh <trunc>execu</trunc> executed for that in the old days</u>
<u n="87" who="S0037" trans="overlap">thing back then? Yeah it's a lot more relaxed now</u>
<u n="88" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="89" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> not Monty Python times though <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0115">no not in the seventies no but uh</u>
<u n="91" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0115">well not in I mean perhaps in in in certain other countries they have uh you know</u>
<u n="93" who="S0037">I dunno</u>
<u n="94" who="S0115">very strongly religious uh governments</u>
<u n="95" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Vatican City maybe <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="96" who="S0115">dunno <pause dur="short"/> but yeah um it's pretty weird if you think about <pause dur="short"/> well it's the sort of thing you see on Horrible Histories is is the  is the  fact that histories were horrible in in</u>
<u n="97" who="S0037" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0115">you know you'd get burned for like</u>
<u n="99" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> not agreeing</u>
<u n="100" who="S0115">mind you I suppose like a lot of the times they just made stuff up like if they didn't like someone</u>
<u n="101" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0115">they would make up you know trumped-up charges</u>
<u n="103" who="S0037" trans="overlap">telling them she's a witch yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0115">you know the classic uh</u>
<u n="105" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0115">trumped-up <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> You know</u>
<u n="107" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you just don't know</u>
<u n="108" who="S0115" trans="overlap">think they were sort of burned people being burned probably uh</u>
<u n="109" who="S0037">but um</u>
<u n="110" who="S0115">but if you wanna make money in these hard times televise public execution</u>
<u n="111" who="S0037">ah that's a horrible idea</u>
<u n="112" who="S0115" trans="overlap">pay pay <trunc>subs</trunc> you know subscription subscription service</u>
<u n="113" who="S0037">people would though wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0115">yep <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0037">voyeurism?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well I I'm not in favour uh I'm not in favour of it but I think in as people get increasingly desperate for money perhaps that's something that'll happen</u>
<u n="117" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but I mean the television's going like that anyway like some of that stuff that</u>
<u n="118" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah well I think we think I don't know if this is just because I'm getting old or</u>
<u n="119" who="S0037">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0115">which I am</u>
<u n="121" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0115">or if it genuinely is getting worse but <pause dur="short"/> but I do sometimes think you know that things are getting more desperate for money and more sort of violent</u>
<u n="123" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Ohh <pause dur="short"/> but did you see that thing in Syria? Where so it was the the rebels had captured some guy who was from the government <pause dur="short"/> and strung him to a tree?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0115">no I haven't no what what what have you  what have you  been reading?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0037" trans="overlap">maybe it was when I was abroad <pause dur="short"/> ah it's because I think it was when I was abroad because obviously I was just watching you know</u>
<u n="126" who="S0115">yeah <trunc>c</trunc> <trunc>per</trunc> perhaps they wouldn't show that in England because in England we we're only given sort of very positive views of the rebels we're <trunc>n</trunc> we're not given</u>
<u n="127" who="S0037" trans="overlap">foreign news <pause dur="short"/> and anyway the <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> it was on <trunc>C</trunc> aye it was on CNN and they were like</u>
<u n="128" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I don't  I don't  know if we'd be given any anything that negative about the rebels in England <pause dur="short"/> although I may be wrong</u>
<u n="129" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so it was on CNN and they were like um Oh they were like Oh you know they've captured this guy who's supposed to have <pause dur="short"/> I mean there was things that this guy's supposed to have done this army guy <pause dur="short"/> You know like killed a child and whatever <pause dur="short"/> but basically there was this footage on the news and before they put they said Oh by the way this might be slightly upsetting <pause dur="short"/> And it was like this man strung up from a tree and you could see his face it well nothing was blurred out <pause dur="short"/> nothing <pause dur="short"/> so it was his dead body like <trunc>w</trunc> swaying swaying in the breeze</u>
<u n="130" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh dead body <pause dur="short"/> so they'd already killed him extrajudicially like</u>
<u n="131" who="S0037">was he wasn't dying at that moment but he would <trunc>already</trunc> he had already died like but he was just</u>
<u n="132" who="S0115">they'd already killed him?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0037">and he was just hanging with his tree <pause dur="short"/> and they were all standing there with their weapons like posing next to him</u>
<u n="134" who="S0115">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0037">so</u>
<u n="136" who="S0115">very similar to medieval uh</u>
<u n="137" who="S0037">exactly</u>
<u n="138" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well not necessarily medieval</u>
<u n="139" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but what I'm saying is that was on the news <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="140" who="S0115">CNN but I dunno if it's <pause dur="short"/> well yeah I mean the Gadaffi thing was on uh</u>
<u n="141" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0115">the the shooting uh</u>
<u n="143" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0115">pretty pretty brutal really uh I don't know if um <pause dur="short"/> did they use to show that sort of stuff? I think things sort of got more censored <pause dur="short"/> I suppose like nowadays uh you know there's there's there is a tendency towards more um freedom of speech freedom of broadcasting and that that kind of does lead I think to to the or a lowering of the standards</u>
<u n="145" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but that's a bit extreme <pause dur="short"/> I don't think you need to see people hanging from trees <pause dur="short"/> and like <pause dur="short"/> when they killed</u>
<u n="146" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well it could get far worse and we only have to look back in into the horrible history to see just how horrible it could get again in this country</u>
<u n="147" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but I don't wanna see it <pause dur="short"/> I don't wanna see</u>
<u n="148" who="S0115" trans="overlap">remember Mussolini in <trunc>I</trunc> Italy I mean that was that may be they said he he deserved that but like that that that was like a</u>
<u n="149" who="S0037">no I know but</u>
<u n="150" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he was like strung up and his body was like passed around you know hung up <pause dur="short"/> decapitated and hung upside and stuff <pause dur="short"/> stuff like that</u>
<u n="151" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I know <pause dur="short"/> oh they used to do all sorts of things didn't they like <pause dur="short"/> drawing them and stuff so when they were like they would hang them but not till they died and then take them down and pull pull the middle bits out and</u>
<u n="152" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh well that's I mean that's that's supposedly illegal in the modern um <pause dur="short"/> supposedly uh uh illegal illegal to torture in the modern you know uh so called uh free Western world or whatever it is <pause dur="short"/> supposedly illegal to  supposedly illegal to  torture although they they do do it anyway but they just don't admit it <pause dur="short"/> so I guess it's like</u>
<u n="153" who="S0037">but I think</u>
<u n="154" who="S0115">there's there's always <pause dur="short"/> history's horrible <pause dur="short"/> I suppose the present will be horrible uh like if you</u>
<u n="155" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but you get horrible stuff anyway</u>
<u n="156" who="S0115">I think one of the big problems like violence <pause dur="short"/> look at that dive <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0037">I know it was proper dive wasn't it I was thinking that wasn't even a penalty no way</u>
<u n="158" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that's a real that uh <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0037">didn't he didn't give it though the referee so</u>
<u n="160" who="S0115">yeah fair enough</u>
<u n="161" who="S0037">doesn't matter</u>
<u n="162" who="S0115">oh yeah so</u>
<u n="163" who="S0037">it was the right decision</u>
<u n="164" who="S0115">no I mean I think like violence is is a  is a  huge problem and uh</u>
<u n="165" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ooh <pause dur="short"/> that was <unclear/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0115">and it comes from government it comes from individual it comes from you know mobs just just come up and uh</u>
<u n="167" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0037">I'm sorry I was just just a bit distracted by his glasses they seem really out of place</u>
<u n="170" who="S0115">no I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I think he's he's most of his face is a bit out of place and <unclear/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0037">no but I think those kinda strong glass you've gotta be have a certain sort of face to be able to like</u>
<u n="172" who="S0115">he looks like K C Jones from uh</u>
<u n="173" who="S0037">who's K C Jones?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0115">he's a business man that was on Dragon's Den <pause dur="short"/> he's from Birmingham and he had really thick glasses</u>
<u n="175" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is K C Jones not a song by the um</u>
<u n="176" who="S0115">I don't know well he called himself K C Jones so</u>
<u n="177" who="S0037">is K C Jones? Oh yeah I remember <pause dur="short"/> with the boiled egg timer?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he had very <trunc>th</trunc> he had thick he had <pause dur="short"/> no he didn't have the boiled egg timer</u>
<u n="179" who="S0037">oh</u>
<u n="180" who="S0115">um that's a good trick of memory isn't it the way people mix like</u>
<u n="181" who="S0037">yeah blend things</u>
<u n="182" who="S0115" trans="overlap">mix perhaps like a noun with a verb or whatever you might say</u>
<u n="183" who="S0037" trans="overlap">K C Jones? Was he the one with the microwave that he could microwave his shoes in?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0115">yeah he was the guy with the uh um</u>
<u n="185" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0115">it was funny that</u>
<u n="187" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I could do with one them let's be honest <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0115">he had these thick glasses and and he and his eyes were really</u>
<u n="189" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he was like You put them in a microwave <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0115">yeah that he really from Birmingham and he he had thick thick rim thick glasses that um</u>
<u n="191" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well all the best people are don't worry about it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="193" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh god them stairs in and out all the time</u>
<u n="194" who="S0115">population's growing in like some places</u>
<u n="195" who="S0037">ay? What?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0115">Birmingham</u>
<u n="197" who="S0037">what?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0115">its population's growing in like some places</u>
<u n="199" who="S0037">well yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0037">D'you not think his glasses look really odd?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0115">not really <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="203" who="S0037">I think he'd look better with some of them ones where you can't see the frame</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="204" who="S0037">God what they doing?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0037">in and out all the time</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115">yeah actually there is uh can be a bit of repeated uh</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't understand</u>
<u n="209" who="S0115">certain amount of repetition sometimes</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037">on a Saturday morning when I'm trying to have a lie in they're like boof boof boof boof up the stairs</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115" trans="overlap">what was I saying to you? Well I don't I think there's someone who who likes to sort of</u>
<u n="212" who="S0037">aye</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115">redo things</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037">have they got like loads of stuff like they're just carrying it up in shifts?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115">not sure <pause dur="short"/> um they they presumably</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> Is that are they out there now?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115">presumably</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037"><vocal desc="misc"/> Are they out there now? Have I said that really loud?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115">uh no I think I thought they left</u>
<u n="220" who="S0037">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> shh</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115">they can't just be like hovering there can they? <vocal desc="laugh"/> but that</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Is that too obvious? Oh well <pause dur="short"/> ah never mind</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0037"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0115">oh yeah so I was saying um</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037">stupid advert's got in me head</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that that that there's that violence is just  is just  it's so easy to get a situation of violence you know</u>
<u n="228" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115">even in  even in  the richest country in the world or or even in the most supposedly peaceful country in the world</u>
<u n="230" who="S0037" trans="overlap">if someone</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115">like Norway or something</u>
<u n="232" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115">which I believe has the highest standard of living in Europe in the world perhaps or in Europe or something <pause dur="short"/> and Norway has the highest uh per person wealth in Europe I believe</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037">oh right</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115">and probably one of the the world</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115">but but you know you get you got that shooting and <pause dur="short"/> in a country as peaceful as Norway to get a shooting like that</u>
<u n="238" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah but you get crackers peoples everywhere don't you?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0115">well it's the biggest attack in Norway since you know the Nazis</u>
<u n="240" who="S0037">yeah but you can't predict that like it's just <trunc>cr</trunc> you get crazy people all over the world</u>
<u n="241" who="S0115">no but I mean I guess that's part of my point that the violence violence seems to</u>
<u n="242" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="243" who="S0115">can just have <pause dur="short"/> like it just happens like people don't seem to <pause dur="short"/> there doesn't seem to be a way a mechanism of of humans to stop violence like <pause dur="short"/> if they were as great a species as as they claim to be <pause dur="short"/> well we <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I suppose my point that I was trying to make was that I don't need to see it on TV if someone like that that American guy who like shot all those villages right <pause dur="short"/> it's fine to tell me that an American guy went to a village and shot them and then once they were dead he tried to burn them <pause dur="short"/> I don't need to see the scorch marks on the ground or the bodies in the back of a van or a pool of blood like I don't think</u>
<u n="245" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well I <trunc>th</trunc> are you complaining about the coverage or the violence itself you seem to be complaining about the coverage</u>
<u n="246" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well both both really</u>
<u n="247" who="S0115">so you're happy with the violence but no as long as it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I've just said both haven't I <pause dur="short"/> I'm I'm complaining about both but what I'm saying is</u>
<u n="249" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is it cos I was talking about like the violence itself as</u>
<u n="250" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't see why you should perpetuate it on the TV I think it's like</u>
<u n="251" who="S0115">oh yeah well if you're taking the point that that that like that that can cause more violence yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well they say it don't they like they say if there's like a serial <pause dur="short"/> it glamorizes it doesn't it like?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it can  it can  yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah like like we saw on um Charlie Brooker's programme</u>
<u n="254" who="S0037" trans="overlap">if you're a serial killer <pause dur="short"/> and like they put the splash your face around everywhere and make him into some sort of demigod for like other crazy folk</u>
<u n="255" who="S0115">yeah indeed but then of course violence starts otherwise without TV <pause dur="short"/> um violence starts</u>
<u n="256" who="S0037">that's quite a good advert</u>
<u n="257" who="S0037">violence starts  everywhere I suppose</u>
<u n="258" who="S0037">I like those cars that have got them big sunroofs like that</u>
<u n="259" who="S0115">mm <pause dur="short"/> so I was thinking you know where where's where's the most violent places</u>
<u n="260" who="S0037" trans="overlap">me dad's got them</u>
<u n="261" who="S0115">and I looked and I found uh a lot of the violence is to do with um places where there's drugs produced or</u>
<u n="262" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Congo? Ah yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0115">also gangs and and in it involved in the transport of drugs um <pause dur="short"/> so so large amounts of money definitely <pause dur="short"/> particularly large amounts of black market money</u>
<u n="264" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0115"><trunc>Abs</trunc> absolutely attracts violence to it</u>
<u n="266" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like um like that programme we watched about that guy who was like he got done over <pause dur="short"/> and he <trunc>u</trunc> was that in Peru? Or Chile?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0115" trans="overlap">sorry I don't know what you mean</u>
<u n="268" who="S0037">he was like an American guy and he fell in love with that girl? And she was just using him</u>
<u n="269" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/> That was like Banged Up Abroad or something</u>
<u n="270" who="S0037">banged Up Abroad <pause dur="short"/> one of my faves</u>
<u n="271" who="S0115">well that's that's not a case of violence it's a case of stupidity and uh</u>
<u n="272" who="S0037">it's pretty stupid</u>
<u n="273" who="S0115">drugs <pause dur="short"/> it but it is something that goes on I mean uh what was he yeah he was from <pause dur="short"/> he he moved to Florida or something</u>
<u n="274" who="S0037" trans="overlap">hey look at <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="275" who="S0115">Florida seems to be a real hotbed of of just just craziness I think but uh um</u>
<u n="276" who="S0037">are you?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but <trunc>i</trunc> in the news obviously we we had the we've had the shooting in Florida just now and we've also have seen in the news you know like those two English guys that got drunk and ran into the wrong neighbourhood and got shot just for being just for simply being in the neighbourhood</u>
<u n="278" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah it's pretty bad <pause dur="short"/> it just makes you scared doesn't it? Makes me scared</u>
<u n="279" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so that's like yeah <trunc>Flori</trunc> Florida's like a bit of a  a but of a  I also read recently uh supposedly that some of the nine eleven hijackers were sort of partying in Florida before</u>
<u n="280" who="S0037">were they?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0115">carrying out the <pause dur="short"/> that's this is an allegation it may well  Anyway uh Florida's a bit of a magnet for trouble I think um</u>
<u n="282" who="S0037">well you can't say that just cos two things've happened and just cos that's you've heard about them</u>
<u n="283" who="S0115" trans="overlap">although I think <pause dur="short"/> three things yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0037">just cos you've heard about them like</u>
<u n="285" who="S0115">well I think it is because and uh this is what I'm on about is that the drugs route you see</u>
<u n="286" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh that looks good doesn't it?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0115">the drugs that</u>
<u n="288" who="S0037">oh right</u>
<u n="289" who="S0115" trans="overlap">America consumes an enormous amount of drugs and those drugs probably most of them are coming from South America yeah so obviously so anywhere along the <trunc>s</trunc> the south um so the Gulf of Mexico coast of America or the Mexican</u>
<u n="290" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0115">is is particularly I mean Florida particularly because perhaps it's got such a big coastline <pause dur="short"/> lots of places where um potential sort of smuggling can go on I think um <pause dur="short"/> and and obviously it attracts people from um <pause dur="short"/> I mean <trunc>y</trunc> looking at that guy you were talking about who got done over <pause dur="short"/> basically he was in Florida and and this this beautiful</u>
<u n="292" who="S0037">oh yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0115">this beautiful  girl you know <trunc>m</trunc> uh meets him and and gives him a story you know like like she's um she's</u>
<u n="294" who="S0037" trans="overlap">she's been</u>
<u n="295" who="S0115">she's been uh left or something</u>
<u n="296" who="S0037" trans="overlap">her husband had beat her up or something hadn't he? Or there was something</u>
<u n="297" who="S0115" trans="overlap">she she has to to</u>
<u n="298" who="S0037" trans="overlap">she needed somewhere to go um</u>
<u n="299" who="S0115">she desperately needs um</u>
<u n="300" who="S0037">escape from somewhere</u>
<u n="301" who="S0115">something it was she <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>I</trunc> initially basically basically the woman makes the guy fall in love with her</u>
<u n="302" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0115">then once he's fallen in love he becomes the perfect uh transporter for drugs</u>
<u n="304" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that's me next step of me plan <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0115" trans="overlap">because in the words of the guy like in the words  in the words  of one of those <trunc>guy</trunc></u>
<u n="306" who="S0037" trans="overlap">hey Matt d'you wanna go to um Peru? <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm just playing a long game <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah well <pause dur="short"/> no I mean yeah you know you you uh you're um</u>
<u n="308" who="S0037">I'm sorry I'm only joking</u>
<u n="309" who="S0115">you're uh <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't put it past you but uh</u>
<u n="310" who="S0037">ee <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0115">I mean <pause dur="short"/> you can't trust anyone but uh</u>
<u n="312" who="S0037">Don't be silly</u>
<u n="313" who="S0115">you know I think you can never trust anyone um</u>
<u n="314" who="S0037">of course you can</u>
<u n="315" who="S0115">it's uh</u>
<u n="316" who="S0037">do you really think that?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0115">if you'd done if you'd um <pause dur="short"/> if you'd decided to to go out with me for six years <pause dur="short"/> um in order to carry something out</u>
<u n="318" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0115">um I don't know I mean</u>
<u n="320" who="S0037">Don't be silly</u>
<u n="321" who="S0115">how could you make the money back and you'd have to be <unclear/> but uh</u>
<u n="322" who="S0037">I'll sell you into slavery or something</u>
<u n="323" who="S0115">and sort of sell all my uh</u>
<u n="324" who="S0037">organs yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0115" trans="overlap">organs yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's the only way to make the money back</u>
<u n="326" who="S0037">did you see about the guy in the news who'd got that full-on face transplant</u>
<u n="327" who="S0115">um don't remember</u>
<u n="328" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it was almost like a full-on head transplant <pause dur="short"/> he like his jaw</u>
<u n="329" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0037">his jaw  All like his upper and lower jaw <pause dur="short"/> all of his face <pause dur="short"/> part of his eye socket like <pause dur="short"/> I dunno like <pause dur="short"/> part of us is a  is a  bit unsympathetic cos I think he'd accidentally like shot himself in the face <pause dur="short"/> it was a shooting accident</u>
<u n="331" who="S0115">oh god</u>
<u n="332" who="S0037">if you're stupid enough to shoot yourself in the face you don't deserve a face <pause dur="short"/> really</u>
<u n="333" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="334" who="S0037">I hope that's the case <pause dur="short"/> I hope he we didn't just like <pause dur="short"/> injured</u>
<u n="335" who="S0115">well he presumably he is was that on uh American uh</u>
<u n="336" who="S0037">I think it was yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0115">NHS but I guess <pause dur="short"/> I guess you can't really charge someone for like if you've got no face <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0037">well I think it was destroying his life like he couldn't go out the house and stuff because obviously <pause dur="short"/> didn't really have a</u>
<u n="339" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I'm not not a big fan of shooting myself though I think <vocal desc="laugh"/> get it?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0037">waay</u>
<u n="341" who="S0115">no I mean that that was a  that was a</u>
<u n="342" who="S0037">no you gotta say Shooting myself myself <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0115">that I that wasn't deliberate but uh <pause dur="short"/> um no <pause dur="short"/> I would would be a bit</u>
<u n="344" who="S0037" trans="overlap">there was a few of them funny little things</u>
<u n="345" who="S0115" trans="overlap">very cautious around a gun I certainly wouldn't be like throwing it around</u>
<u n="346" who="S0037">na</u>
<u n="347" who="S0115">but if you've had a  you've had a  few beers</u>
<u n="348" who="S0037">I suppose if you go</u>
<u n="349" who="S0115" trans="overlap">if you decided to go for a few beers <pause dur="short"/> take the  take the  gun</u>
<u n="350" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> But I suppose if you grow up with them like if it's normal then</u>
<u n="351" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's uh <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0037">like</u>
<u n="353" who="S0115">yeah but if you're drunk you can still shoot yourself in the face</u>
<u n="354" who="S0037">shooting yourself in the face is not <pause dur="short"/> it's like on those cartoons where it's like Oh the bullet's stuck I'll just see what's wrong <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there's some bizarre <unclear/> Oh like um Elmer Fudd or something looking down the barrel  looking down the barrel  to see if there's</u>
<u n="356" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you know like in <pause dur="short"/> elmer Fudd yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then his moustache gets all singed and that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0115" trans="overlap">because uh sometimes they would  they would  pull the trigger and there'd be a pause <pause dur="short"/> and uh they'd look and they'd go</u>
<u n="358" who="S0037">oh <trunc>w</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> that's right yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> Or one of my favourite ones is when like it goes off and then he has like a cylindrical hole in his head <trunc>th</trunc> with like some some extra pieces like</u>
<u n="359" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cartoon physics uh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0115">big big <trunc>bis</trunc></u>
<u n="362" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like this like <vocal desc="misc"/> when they get banged on the head like</u>
<u n="363" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0115">there's a few  a few  of those sorts of gags like uh when they</u>
<u n="366" who="S0037">or like um in Tom and Jerry</u>
<u n="367" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you know Wile E Coyote on the  on the  edge of the cliff</u>
<u n="368" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Tom and Jerry like often his skin comes off or something</u>
<u n="369" who="S0115">yeah I mean it's it's it's horribly violent isn't it but <pause dur="short"/> that's there was an episode of the Simpsons that <trunc>de</trunc> that supposedly uh dealt with this <pause dur="short"/> it was um you know the Itchy and Scratchy</u>
<u n="370" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like the Marge complains it's too violent and wants it banned <pause dur="short"/> then they have a Venus De Milo</u>
<u n="372" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0115">or was it? No no Michelangelo's David</u>
<u n="374" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0115">um which is totally naked sculpture</u>
<u n="376" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0115">comes to America and someone says that if you're banning uh if you're in favour of banning the violence then you'll have to be in favour of banning nudity um</u>
<u n="378" who="S0037" trans="overlap">nudity?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0115">you know <trunc>w</trunc> which they called uh freedom of expression or something <pause dur="short"/> form of expression but uh <pause dur="short"/> no I would say well the violence is is is worse than nudity surely</u>
<u n="380" who="S0037">some of them Tom and Jerry ones are classic though I don't mean the violent ones</u>
<u n="381" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like you you can't equate  you can't equate  as I think that cartoon was trying to do</u>
<u n="382" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0115">you know freedom of expression nudity with with violence that that's stupid <pause dur="short"/> anyway that's that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I feel like um I was just gonna tell you about my favourite Tom and Jerry <trunc>c</trunc> cartoon but then I just thought to meself I've done a  I've done a  Nana Jean and I've come all the way back round to like <vocal desc="laugh"/> the original thing I was talking about which was children's TV <pause dur="short"/> like I've just gone on a like thirty-five minute tangent</u>
<u n="385" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah well that's been like a theme though that's that's been a theme though that's been <pause dur="short"/> like cos you can always link back to history and once you've got history you can link back to Horrible Histories</u>
<u n="386" who="S0037">but um</u>
<u n="387" who="S0115">you know there's plenty to say about that isn't there</u>
<u n="388" who="S0037">my favourite  my favourite  Tom and Jerry one <pause dur="short"/> have you got a favourite?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0115">um I <trunc>d</trunc> I didn't watch loads of them uh <pause dur="short"/> I think there's uh there's uh there's of the the ones where it's a concert</u>
<u n="390" who="S0037">ah that's a good one <pause dur="short"/> that's a classic</u>
<u n="391" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um I I I suppose I wasn't a massive fan of those short cartoons I tended to prefer</u>
<u n="392" who="S0037">the Hanna Barbera ones?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0115">I tended to prefer um longer films and uh <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> I remember having a conversation with a friend about um he liked shorter films I liked longer films <pause dur="short"/> that's one of the earliest conversations I can remember when I was about four or something</u>
<u n="394" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh is it? It's funny that you like longer things maybe that's your character</u>
<u n="395" who="S0115">but at that time I did <pause dur="short"/> I mean like <pause dur="short"/> I liked um quite quite quite liked The Pink Panther</u>
<u n="396" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you mean like serials? Series?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0115">no I mean like like films or</u>
<u n="398" who="S0037">oh I see</u>
<u n="399" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="400" who="S0037">must have had a good attention span</u>
<u n="401" who="S0115">no I dunno if I <vocal desc="laugh"/> uh I doubt it I don't  I don't  now so</u>
<u n="402" who="S0037">yeah you do</u>
<u n="403" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> there were some things that that um</u>
<u n="404" who="S0037" trans="overlap">for some things <pause dur="short"/> things that you like</u>
<u n="405" who="S0115">there were some films that I really liked actually but I think um that I wasn't allowed to watch them or something and that that made me frustrated um</u>
<u n="406" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0115">uh but I remember <pause dur="short"/> films like things like The Jungle Book could really really fascinate me as a child uh</u>
<u n="408" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that was my favourite one of my faves when I was younger <pause dur="short"/> in fact I got like the um <pause dur="short"/> I've showed you it haven't I I've got like the special collector's edition thing and like</u>
<u n="409" who="S0115">oh right <pause dur="short"/> there must be a lot of potential uh collections for that but actually <trunc>m</trunc> most of my watching those sorts of Disney films actually when I was sort of older and I was collecting films</u>
<u n="410" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0115">um collecting like my favourite films</u>
<u n="412" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I liked um <pause dur="short"/> I quite like the um Robin Hood one the the the Walt Disney one</u>
<u n="413" who="S0115">oh yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh and uh <trunc>w</trunc> uh that reminds me of Bedknobs and Broomsticks it's one of uh one of my favourites</u>
<u n="414" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't even know if I've seen it all the way though</u>
<u n="415" who="S0115">I tried to show it to you but uh</u>
<u n="416" who="S0037">I know what was years ago</u>
<u n="417" who="S0115">uh and I think you fell asleep</u>
<u n="418" who="S0037">that sounds about right</u>
<u n="419" who="S0115">it's uh yeah it's a pretty boring film</u>
<u n="420" who="S0037">but um</u>
<u n="421" who="S0115">no I really love the the the comedy uh like <trunc>ar</trunc> animate um football game in the middle of that <pause dur="short"/> bedknobs and Broomsticks</u>
<u n="422" who="S0037">oh</u>
<u n="423" who="S0115">when I saw it as a child I liked it</u>
<u n="424" who="S0037">is there an under the sea bit?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there is  there is  an under sea</u>
<u n="426" who="S0037" trans="overlap">there's some things I that I really should've seen</u>
<u n="427" who="S0115">it's it was like it was done after um Mary Poppins and I think a lot of people say</u>
<u n="428" who="S0037">Mary Bobbins</u>
<u n="429" who="S0115">A lot of people say that Mary Poppins <trunc>w</trunc> was better but uh</u>
<u n="430" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah I love Dick Van Dyke <pause dur="short"/> he's one of my favourites</u>
<u n="431" who="S0115">uh tremendous isn't he?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0037">and his son <pause dur="short"/> what's he called Barry Van Dyke <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's funny that they sort of do these kinda like <pause dur="short"/> it's kinda like like</u>
<u n="434" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he's <trunc>b</trunc> he's son's called Barry Van Dyke that's not even a joke</u>
<u n="435" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like like Grade Grade F sort of like drama series and</u>
<u n="436" who="S0037">everyone loves Dick Van Dyke</u>
<u n="437" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but yeah it makes loads of money</u>
<u n="438" who="S0037">I watched a really good one the other day Diagnosis Murder <pause dur="short"/> no no no <pause dur="short"/> I tell a lie it wasn't Diagnosis Murder <pause dur="short"/> but it <trunc>w</trunc> had Barry Van Dyke and Dick Van Dyke and <pause dur="short"/> barry Van Dyke's son</u>
<u n="439" who="S0115" trans="overlap">little Little Jimmy Van Dyke</u>
<u n="440" who="S0037" trans="overlap">three generations of Van Dykes in the same family in the same thing <pause dur="short"/> and it was about <pause dur="short"/> it was like</u>
<u n="441" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Great <pause dur="short"/> look at all that talent in one screen</u>
<u n="442" who="S0037">oh it was really bad like the acting was so terrible it was really good to watch like really cringey and rubbish <pause dur="short"/> it was something about like uh that's right</u>
<u n="443" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he was  he was  kind of good in um Mary Poppins but <trunc>nev</trunc> nothing else</u>
<u n="444" who="S0037">Mary Bobbins</u>
<u n="445" who="S0115" trans="overlap">can you imagine him playing like a serial killer or something?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="447" who="S0115">like like You talking to me?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well he's a good dancer though</u>
<u n="449" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no I suppose he could do like a</u>
<u n="450" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he he was  he was  a really good dancer you know</u>
<u n="451" who="S0115">that he he he like <pause dur="short"/> can you imagine him as like like The Godfather or something?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0115">you come come <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you come to me this day <vocal desc="laugh"/> The day of your daughter's <pause dur="short"/> the day of your daughter's wedding <pause dur="short"/> Bit of a Dick Van Dyke</u>
<u n="455" who="S0115" trans="overlap">imagine if if they took Lock Stock And Two Smoking Barrels and replaced some of the main  the main  characters with like Disney uh like Dick Van</u>
<u n="456" who="S0037" trans="overlap">with Dick Van Dyke</u>
<u n="457" who="S0115">the the <trunc>D</trunc> the Van Dyke generation</u>
<u n="458" who="S0037">or like um <pause dur="short"/> it's funny though how <trunc>u</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> oh aww it's in</u>
<u n="459" who="S0115">wow that's a weird goal</u>
<u n="460" who="S0037" trans="overlap">aww</u>
<u n="461" who="S0115">it wasn't a goal anyway</u>
<u n="462" who="S0037">was it? Was it offside? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> that was weird it was just it was like it was going in slow motion</u>
<u n="463" who="S0115">oh yeah he he's way offside there</u>
<u n="464" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0115"><unclear/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0037">oh it's awful</u>
<u n="467" who="S0115" trans="overlap">just goes and follows it</u>
<u n="468" who="S0037">like finger tipped it <pause dur="short"/> um but it's funny isn't it how Dick Van Dyke and Angela Lansbury ended up in the um both in those kind of early <trunc>afternoo</trunc></u>
<u n="469" who="S0115" trans="overlap">extremely rich <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> well a bit  a bit  a different end cos hers was like like quite high quality wasn't it Murder She Wrote?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but it's that both that early afternoon thing for like nanas</u>
<u n="471" who="S0115">oh yeah I suppose <pause dur="short"/> thinking uh</u>
<u n="472" who="S0037">but actually Angela Lansbury</u>
<u n="473" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there was a lot of money though though there were really really loads of viewers for that sort of thing like Colombo and</u>
<u n="474" who="S0037">but Murder She Wrote's really good yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there were like the some of the most viewed programmes on on TV</u>
<u n="476" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and <trunc>Mur</trunc> they survive like okay they look very eighties but they're still good</u>
<u n="477" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah there's there's loads of money in that like</u>
<u n="478" who="S0037">but Angela Lansbury was um a highly acclaimed Broadway actress <pause dur="short"/> little did</u>
<u n="479" who="S0115">well no I think she  I think she  is a was a is a good actor</u>
<u n="480" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I read um her Wikipedia page not so long ago</u>
<u n="481" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> no I <trunc>th</trunc> I thought she was a good actor I never thought she wasn't um</u>
<u n="482" who="S0037">what's her name in? What's the?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Dick Van Dyke <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'd only really seen him in</u>
<u n="484" who="S0037">Mary Bobbins</u>
<u n="485" who="S0115">I'd only really <vocal desc="laugh"/> seen him in that um</u>
<u n="486" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what's her name  what's her name  in um? What's her name in Murder She <trunc>Wro</trunc> Murder She Wrote?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0115" trans="overlap">chim chimeney chim chim <pause dur="short"/> Um</u>
<u n="488" who="S0037">there's a <unclear/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0115">Jessica Fletcher</u>
<u n="490" who="S0037">oh Jessica Fletcher <pause dur="short"/> I wish I'd remembered that</u>
<u n="491" who="S0115">ah but I <trunc>y</trunc> those pub quiz ones they always get you no matter how much information you think you've got in your head the <pause dur="short"/>  a new fact comes in and pushes an old fact out</u>
<u n="492" who="S0037">I know</u>
<u n="493" who="S0115">some <trunc>t</trunc> somehow <pause dur="short"/> like it seems that that  that that  is mechanically not the way the brain works but uh <pause dur="short"/> I definitely <pause dur="short"/> the brain leaks the brain definitely leaks</u>
<u n="494" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> but I suppose it has to be properly maintained</u>
<u n="496" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh I was gonna tell you about my Tom and Jerry favourite one <pause dur="short"/> have you seen that one where they put  they put  the taps on and then they open the freezer and everything freezes and they're like it's like a skating rink?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> maybe</u>
<u n="498" who="S0037">ah that's definitely the best one</u>
<u n="499" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is that your favourite one?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0037">I'm gonna look at that one after</u>
<u n="501" who="S0115">ah we watched a few cartoons actually we did we watched uh</u>
<u n="502" who="S0037">oh yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0115">Droopy</u>
<u n="504" who="S0037">Droopy</u>
<u n="505" who="S0115">uh that was funny <pause dur="short"/> hadn't seen that for a long time</u>
<u n="506" who="S0037">I like  I like  that the plot of that though how he's always like like This goes on for the whole cartoon you know like he he always</u>
<u n="507" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Do do a Droopy voice</u>
<u n="508" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he's like I get him in the end <pause dur="short"/> No I'm not doing my Droopy voice</u>
<u n="509" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah he's there's sort of</u>
<u n="510" who="S0037" trans="overlap">do your Droopy voice</u>
<u n="511" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Uh I think it's pretty stupid so but</u>
<u n="512" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0115">um they they always uh <pause dur="short"/> the it's like uh it's like the hare and tortoise thing</u>
<u n="514" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0115">like he always sort of tortoises them really quickly and then gets there before them</u>
<u n="516" who="S0037">it's funny</u>
<u n="517" who="S0115">and then he's tremendously sort of nonchalant about it or whatever</u>
<u n="518" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that one <pause dur="short"/> that one that we saw when he was like <pause dur="short"/> what was he trying to do? He was trying to escape <pause dur="short"/> ah ah that's right <pause dur="short"/> I saw a couple like</u>
<u n="519" who="S0115">he was <trunc>out</trunc> he was outsmarted by uh an a British fox</u>
<u n="520" who="S0037">tha's right <pause dur="short"/> and then there was another one where he was like um <pause dur="short"/> he was like <trunc>try</trunc> he was he a police dog or something?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0115">ah <trunc>y</trunc> yeah he was after a <trunc>c</trunc> criminal</u>
<u n="522" who="S0037">and he kept like and the guy like got on a train and on a bus and on a plane and</u>
<u n="523" who="S0115">he he would yeah he would release them and he'd say Wait in this room and then the guy says Oh yeah I'll just wait in this room and the runs runs and</u>
<u n="524" who="S0037" trans="overlap">then he was at like the North Pole runs to the North Pole and he's already there <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="525" who="S0115">and just Droopy just uh</u>
<u n="526" who="S0037">Droopy's already got there</u>
<u n="527" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah he's always sort of already there isn't he?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0037">it's funny</u>
<u n="529" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> and it's like a Pink Panther obviously you don't any words in that do you? There was a lot of cartoons though I mean</u>
<u n="530" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0115">I used to like Dastardly And Mutley you know uh</u>
<u n="532" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> catch The Pigeon <pause dur="short"/> me nana I remember like when I was when I used to stay with me nana</u>
<u n="533" who="S0115" trans="overlap">catch The Pigeon <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="534" who="S0037">um she had like this television in her bedroom that was black and white and um sometimes I would wake up really and obviously she would be like Aw <pause dur="short"/> are you joking? D'you know what I mean <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> it must've been like six thirty or seven <pause dur="short"/> and so she'd let us like turn the telly on the telly was next to her bed <pause dur="short"/> she's let us get in bed with her and she'd like cuddle us in and I'd she'd put the black and white telly on and it was always like Catch The Pigeon was on and I'd be like <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> Catch The Pigeon and me nana'd be like And be quiet <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0037">I used to watch it for ages <pause dur="short"/> I really liked that <pause dur="short"/> but it was all in black and white I remember thinking like oh nana stupid telly <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="537" who="S0115">ah yeah well I had a black and while TV till uh till I was about was it like eight or nine or something</u>
<u n="538" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well you can get like three <pause dur="short"/> excuse me <pause dur="short"/> you can get like 3D TV now that's like you don't need to wear the spectacles</u>
<u n="539" who="S0115">oh <trunc>h</trunc> you don't need to wear the spectacles?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0037">Nn nn <pause dur="short"/> saw it <pause dur="short"/> so you <pause dur="short"/> it's like a three</u>
<u n="541" who="S0115" trans="overlap">how does that work then? I don't know much about optics to be honest</u>
<u n="542" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I dunno it's just technical advances <pause dur="short"/> it's something about well you can already <pause dur="short"/> oh oh you can already get those like um <pause dur="short"/> who was it who had one? Where it was at Christmas one of the bairns had one where you could like <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="543" who="S0115">you could what?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0037">one of the bairns had one at Christmas it was like a Nintendo thing <pause dur="short"/> and that was 3D and you had like the slider switch and it made it like more and less 3D d'you remember?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0115">no</u>
<u n="546" who="S0037">at Christmas?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0115">uh don't</u>
<u n="548" who="S0037">like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had it I think <pause dur="short"/> it was like a dog that you stroked and like tickled and that</u>
<u n="549" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh I've probably been uh if if I'd have kept my distance</u>
<u n="550" who="S0037">no no I showed it to you cos I it was interesting</u>
<u n="551" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> no I don't  I don't  uh</u>
<u n="552" who="S0037">it as like a <trunc>Nin</trunc> little Nintendo DS thing and like um they had like a slider on the side <pause dur="short"/> and it made it like more or less 3D obviously to suit how you wanted it</u>
<u n="553" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Cos wouldn't you sort of always have it on like maximally 3D?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0037">no cos sometimes like it just looked a bit weird</u>
<u n="555" who="S0115">I don't think</u>
<u n="556" who="S0037">might be a bit <trunc>quea</trunc> makes you a bit queasy</u>
<u n="557" who="S0115">well I've only seen one thing ever on 3D and that was uh <pause dur="short"/> that was Avatar</u>
<u n="558" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that didn't really agree with you either</u>
<u n="559" who="S0115">it cost about twenty quid</u>
<u n="560" who="S0037">aye for both of us</u>
<u n="561" who="S0115">see um <pause dur="short"/> oh was it I thought it was just</u>
<u n="562" who="S0037">we're not gonna pay twenty pound each</u>
<u n="563" who="S0115">no it felt like  it felt like  a load of it felt like more money than than I was expecting</u>
<u n="564" who="S0037">no it was I think it was ten pounds each yeah which is a lot of money considering we could've probably bought it on DVD for five quid</u>
<u n="565" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it was a good  it was a good  film though</u>
<u n="566" who="S0037">was a good <trunc>fi</trunc> it was on the other night actually</u>
<u n="567" who="S0115">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0037">but then I  then I  sort of watching it again like it just made us think like Oh this is really cheesy <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's quite <pause dur="short"/> it's quite long isn't it?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0037">when it's like unobtainium <pause dur="short"/> you just think like</u>
<u n="571" who="S0115">well <trunc>th</trunc> yeah it was always <pause dur="short"/> I thought it was quite antiwar so <pause dur="short"/> I thought uh it's alright</u>
<u n="572" who="S0037">Liz was telling us she'd been to see that film Hunger Games <pause dur="short"/> have you heard about it? It's one of those ones that's like for <trunc>s</trunc> I don't know why exactly</u>
<u n="573" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="574" who="S0037">I I think it might have one of them vampire blokes in <pause dur="short"/> what's that series called? Twilight <pause dur="short"/> cullen Edward <trunc>C</trunc> James? Edward Cullen? Oh I'm so <trunc>in</trunc> I'm so rubbish</u>
<u n="575" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah I know  I know  who you mean</u>
<u n="576" who="S0037">you know who I mean? That kind of pasty-faced sort of</u>
<u n="577" who="S0115">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's sort of pale <pause dur="short"/> he's got a kind of longish nose</u>
<u n="578" who="S0037" trans="overlap">sort of spooky <pause dur="short"/> vampirey</u>
<u n="579" who="S0115">kinda scary scary eyes</u>
<u n="580" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well vampirey isn't he? Let's be honest <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="581" who="S0115">like what you imagine a vampire the the Romanian look</u>
<u n="582" who="S0037">so I think it might've had him in but I'm not sure</u>
<u n="583" who="S0115">guess Dracula tradition it has a sort of a long nose <pause dur="short"/> a long thin straight nose</u>
<u n="584" who="S0037" trans="overlap">aww what a goal</u>
<u n="585" who="S0115">wow <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="586" who="S0037">ah that was good</u>
<u n="587" who="S0115">that was uh Raul <pause dur="short"/> it was uh</u>
<u n="588" who="S0037">ah that's that's good uh they're not expected to win are they Schalke?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0115" trans="overlap">really long um really long strike</u>
<u n="590" who="S0037">that was really good</u>
<u n="591" who="S0115">against uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah that was from</u>
<u n="592" who="S0037">did it not come off his hand though?</u>
<u n="593" who="S0115">it's cos it was a volley as well so that made it um</u>
<u n="594" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it was like aye <pause dur="short"/> oh right in the corner</u>
<u n="595" who="S0115">A volley from the edge of the penalty area</u>
<u n="596" who="S0037">oh the goalie couldn't even see that like it was like too many people in the way</u>
<u n="597" who="S0115">wasn't happy <vocal desc="laugh"/> But it was</u>
<u n="598" who="S0037">I sometimes think some of these British commentators when it's a European match they're like Yeah <trunc>Scha</trunc> Schalke are winning <pause dur="short"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0115" trans="overlap">just bored of it <vocal desc="laugh"/> They're just <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean they they're either bored or sort of overly biased <pause dur="short"/> they they're not really able to get excited about</u>
<u n="600" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no they're not it's kind of flat</u>
<u n="601" who="S0115">got to get excited like <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="602" who="S0037">I feel like I should put the German commentary on</u>
<u n="603" who="S0115">well like Jeff Stelling was always sort of excited about like</u>
<u n="604" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he doesn't sound like he's from Germany does he Ral González</u>
<u n="605" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="606" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="607" who="S0115">well we we do we don't have like you know you are allowed to move country</u>
<u n="608" who="S0037">well that's true <pause dur="short"/> european Union</u>
<u n="609" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> and the whole whole world  the whole world  I mean</u>
<u n="610" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and you can call kids whatever you want</u>
<u n="611" who="S0115">Cos you've got uh  you've got uh  Messi from he's from uh Argentina isn't he?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="613" who="S0115">he he plays in Barcelona plays for Barcelona <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="614" who="S0037">you have to be allowed to work though</u>
<u n="615" who="S0115">sorry?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0037">not anyone can go anywhere</u>
<u n="617" who="S0115">oh you have to get a like visa</u>
<u n="618" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's loads of stuff like when Lucy moved to uh to New Zealand the first time like <pause dur="short"/> they did loads of checks on her like kept her at immigration for ages like probed all of her bank account like she had to prove this that and the other</u>
<u n="619" who="S0115">it's only New Zealand</u>
<u n="620" who="S0037">I know</u>
<u n="621" who="S0115">but uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah well there's just there are a lot of dodgy people <pause dur="short"/> like it's it's sort of <pause dur="short"/> it's like if you have a party that's a certain size then there's always gonna be like <pause dur="short"/> once you've got a certain number there's always gonna be some dodginess</u>
<u n="622" who="S0037">what d'you mean?</u>
<u n="623" who="S0115" trans="overlap">within that <pause dur="short"/> with the like just people are just  people are just  weird so you have enough people you're gonna have some</u>
<u n="624" who="S0037">yeah couple of weirdoes</u>
<u n="625" who="S0115">weirdness somewhere and uh I've</u>
<u n="626" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah that's that's true</u>
<u n="627" who="S0115">um in fact it's I I'd be surprised if people aren't even more weird than uh</u>
<u n="628" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="629" who="S0115">than we  than we  think they are really</u>
<u n="630" who="S0037" trans="overlap">maybe they're just keeping it on the inside</u>
<u n="631" who="S0115">yeah I think a lot of people are pretty <pause dur="short"/> people are just just hanging on you know</u>
<u n="632" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0115">literally uh literally on the edge of uh on the edge of reason <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="634" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="635" who="S0115">you seen that film?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0037">on the edge Edge Of Reason? Bridget Jones?</u>
<u n="637" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0037">have you? You a Bridget Jones fan underneath?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0115">um I don't think so I was like</u>
<u n="640" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I do like a nice Bridget Jones pant <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="641" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="642" who="S0037">but uh no <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>ha</trunc> yes I have seen it</u>
<u n="643" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and um</u>
<u n="644" who="S0037">it's very much a girls' film and I'm not really into girls' films</u>
<u n="645" who="S0115">right</u>
<u n="646" who="S0037">but I have seen it and I don't mind it <pause dur="short"/> it's quite watchable</u>
<u n="647" who="S0115">um what is it about girls' films that annoys you?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0037">oh they're kind of just saccharine just like floppiness <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> a lot in in in girls' films women are never</u>
<u n="649" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I guess it depends doesn't it? Oh yeah you mean the woman are floppy?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0037" trans="overlap">women women always are Oh oh help me and like Oh I've fallen in love and like</u>
<u n="651" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I don't  I don't  think that <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if they that is always</u>
<u n="652" who="S0037">well name name like a rom com where the woman's like</u>
<u n="653" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Meg Ryan</u>
<u n="654" who="S0037">oh right</u>
<u n="655" who="S0115">everything Meg Ryan's ever done</u>
<u n="656" who="S0037">I'm not sure if Meg Ryan's like a flagship feminist though</u>
<u n="657" who="S0115">well <pause dur="short"/> no I  no I  was the the that was I was just naming it uh <pause dur="short"/> when Harry Met Sally is like the ultimate sort of romantic comedy isn't it?</u>
<u n="658" who="S0037">yeah but is she on the back foot there at all? I haven't seen it <pause dur="short"/> I've seen that scene <pause dur="short"/> but I've not seen When Harry Met Sally <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know the plot so <pause dur="short"/> is she a <trunc>m</trunc> is she a?</u>
<u n="659" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh <pause dur="short"/> is a strong woman um I think I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I haven't seen it either  I haven't seen it either  I don't</u>
<u n="660" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Cos most of them are like <pause dur="short"/> like the the the plot of Bridget Jones like a successful</u>
<u n="661" who="S0115">she is successful you see I mean let let's be honest a lot of the sort of chick lit stuff</u>
<u n="662" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yes but her life is <trunc>unfufill</trunc> unfulfilled because she hasn't found a man</u>
<u n="663" who="S0115">yeah but you they wouldn't read about her life if she was fulfilled would they?</u>
<u n="664" who="S0037">well no but</u>
<u n="665" who="S0115">mind you they should have one they should have like Florence Nightingale The Movie</u>
<u n="666" who="S0037">you know and even all of the <pause dur="short"/> even the ones with stronger women characters I mean you know you've gotta look back to like Jane Eyre and stuff to find</u>
<u n="667" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they should  they should  have d'you think they should have it like Marie Curie <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0037">but even you know</u>
<u n="669" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but uh well they did have the Margaret Thatcher film actually</u>
<u n="670" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'm not really literature <pause dur="short"/> I'm not a very good critique <pause dur="short"/> critiquer?</u>
<u n="671" who="S0115">critic?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0037">critic</u>
<u n="673" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="674" who="S0037">ah god I'm so bad <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="675" who="S0115" trans="overlap">ahh <pause dur="short"/> there was nearly another one of those goals uh</u>
<u n="676" who="S0037" trans="overlap">otherwise know as critiquer</u>
<u n="677" who="S0115">ooh here comes a <pause dur="short"/> oh no he's just <pause dur="short"/> look <pause dur="short"/> look <pause dur="short"/> to aww</u>
<u n="678" who="S0037" trans="overlap">aww I thought that was in</u>
<u n="679" who="S0115">I know there was uh</u>
<u n="680" who="S0037">we need a 3D TV cos that  was going there</u>
<u n="681" who="S0115" trans="overlap">what I was saying was that they should have movies about you were saying like really strong women that really do a lot of stuff</u>
<u n="682" who="S0037">no I'm not saying <pause dur="short"/> look <pause dur="short"/> I'm</u>
<u n="683" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like they did do Evita didn't they? Evita</u>
<u n="684" who="S0037">I don't <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't wanna come across as sort of bra burner <pause dur="short"/> but what I mean <vocal desc="laugh"/> is</u>
<u n="685" who="S0115">look I <trunc>d</trunc> I didn't say you were I think you I think you're uh you you're being a bit sort of hard on <unclear/> your opinion</u>
<u n="686" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no but what I mean is <pause dur="short"/> I suppose what I mean is I don't like like uh you know even the girls that I know like people that are me friends I don't like people who are wet or like floppy or like</u>
<u n="687" who="S0115">uhhhh <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="688" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no but not really no but not not like Oh please help me <pause dur="short"/> I've broke a fingernail <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="689" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I don't know how many women really are that that way round like falling over and waiting for someone to pick them up</u>
<u n="690" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but why are they always like that in films? Jennifer Anniston all just smiling and fluffing like swishing her hair round</u>
<u n="691" who="S0115">yeah well in Friends she's not successful but look at Ally McBeal <pause dur="short"/> she's successful</u>
<u n="692" who="S0037">yeah but</u>
<u n="693" who="S0115">and she's a similar <trunc>p</trunc> personality to you know the Rachel character</u>
<u n="694" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and she's married to Harrison Ford</u>
<u n="695" who="S0115">oh yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0037">uh not in Ally McBeal <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="697" who="S0115">that's just an unusual alliance</u>
<u n="698" who="S0037">anything with Harrison Ford in I'd watch <pause dur="short"/> anything with <trunc>S</trunc></u>
<u n="699" who="S0115">oh so you like yeah you like uh</u>
<u n="700" who="S0037">anything with Stephen Seagull in</u>
<u n="701" who="S0115">nothing like a good</u>
<u n="702" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Anything with Stephen Seagull in</u>
<u n="703" who="S0115">Good old-fashioned</u>
<u n="704" who="S0037">or Bruce Willis <pause dur="short"/> bruce Willis <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="705" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="706" who="S0037">Don't mind a bit of Jackie Chan</u>
<u n="707" who="S0115">Steven Segal?</u>
<u n="708" who="S0037">I've said Steven Seagull</u>
<u n="709" who="S0115">oh did you?</u>
<u n="710" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>l</trunc> in fact that that film that we watched the other day was just</u>
<u n="711" who="S0115">uh what's uh um? That was  that was  too bad um even</u>
<u n="712" who="S0037" trans="overlap">amazing <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um <pause dur="short"/> I like a James Bond <pause dur="short"/> especially</u>
<u n="713" who="S0115">uh you know things like no brain  no brain  action films</u>
<u n="714" who="S0037">well I I like  I like  the new James Bonds quite a lot <pause dur="short"/> aww</u>
<u n="715" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah that's really good with Daniel Craig in</u>
<u n="716" who="S0037">but I also do like an old hairy-chested Sean Connelly <pause dur="short"/> connelly? Sean Connery <vocal desc="laugh"/> like an old nana <pause dur="short"/> Ooh that Sean Connelly <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="717" who="S0115" trans="overlap">connelly?</u>
<u n="718" who="S0037">that Peter Brosnan <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="719" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you're already a nana now like</u>
<u n="720" who="S0037">I know</u>
<u n="721" who="S0115">one that's you know one of those  one of those  ones that doesn't shut up <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="722" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's only gonna get worse <pause dur="short"/> that's not very nice</u>
<u n="723" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="724" who="S0037">alright sorry for being</u>
<u n="725" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like um</u>
<u n="726" who="S0037"><unclear/></u>
<u n="727" who="S0115">no no no no uh</u>
<u n="728" who="S0037">that's not very nice</u>
<u n="729" who="S0115">that's better than you know like I said like someone who just ah it's nothing worse than uncomfortable silences like</u>
<u n="730" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0115">like if you're sitting with someone and you you happen to be like going out with them or like living with them and it's just like  just like  like just endless like pin dropping silences</u>
<u n="732" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> I've never really had that as you say <pause dur="short"/> as you say I think I'm just</u>
<u n="733" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I guess you're not used to a <unclear/> family with uh I don't think there'd be ever more than a few seconds of quiet on your family</u>
<u n="734" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> there's not much quiet <pause dur="short"/> not with me brother <pause dur="short"/> me brother would just talk even if there's nobody there <pause dur="short"/> I I'm sure he just does</u>
<u n="735" who="S0115">he's a  he's a  a tremendous talker uh</u>
<u n="736" who="S0037" trans="overlap">chats away</u>
<u n="737" who="S0115">and I think  I think  <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>  <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>  are are the same like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well and you and your nana <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="738" who="S0037">oh me nana <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="739" who="S0115">is is really <unclear/></u>
<u n="740" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'm sure like when me granda was in hospital he must have just been like aahhh <vocal desc="laugh"/> like <pause dur="short"/> cos she wasn't going Arnie blah buh blah buh blah buh blah d'you want a fish finger or blah blah blah I bought these in Morrisons meh meh muh muh meh <pause dur="short"/> She really does talk all the time</u>
<u n="741" who="S0115">so yes so you're</u>
<u n="742" who="S0037">I wrote something like that because</u>
<u n="743" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so you don't  you don't  identify with with women like like Rachel from Friends or?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0037">not really it's not very me</u>
<u n="745" who="S0115">suppose not <pause dur="short"/> you you more uh like <trunc>Cor</trunc> you know Monica from friends or?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> well no I I can't say I have any like anything like the cleaning ethic of Monica</u>
<u n="747" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you're not that clean though <pause dur="short"/> you're not clean <pause dur="short"/> um or Phoebe so there isn't someone like you in uh in Friends is there?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I just don't like <pause dur="short"/> I suppose I don't like girls' I don't like the romance I just think it's cheesy like <pause dur="short"/> I suppose I just think</u>
<u n="749" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah but not <pause dur="short"/> but I think you do you can be quite sentimental some times</u>
<u n="750" who="S0037">I think I'm sentimental and I do think I'm an old</u>
<u n="751" who="S0115" trans="overlap">do you if you see uh if you see like you know something something nice on TV like like that programme with uh those you know they get a little kid and he's suffered a personal tragedy</u>
<u n="752" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="753" who="S0115">they build him a big house to make up for it <pause dur="short"/> you get really  get really  uh</u>
<u n="754" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ahh <pause dur="short"/> they're a bit silly though they're a bit over the top <pause dur="short"/> but no I know what you mean <pause dur="short"/> I yes I am sentimental I agree <pause dur="short"/> um and it doesn't take much to like set us off crying and that</u>
<u n="755" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="756" who="S0037">but that's something quite different to like <pause dur="short"/> kind of Bridget Jonesy sort of</u>
<u n="757" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="758" who="S0037">and those sort of stupid Marley And Me or like um</u>
<u n="759" who="S0115">things with Hugh Grant in?</u>
<u n="760" who="S0037" trans="overlap">clueless <pause dur="short"/> just like um</u>
<u n="761" who="S0115" trans="overlap">D'you like um Four Weddings And A Funeral which I think is the most successful British film um</u>
<u n="762" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't mind Hugh Grant but uh <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>a</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> what about Love Actually is that not more successful?</u>
<u n="763" who="S0115">no I think it's between <pause dur="short"/> the the biggest British film is uh</u>
<u n="764" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I I don't mind <pause dur="short"/> I only just saw Four Weddings And A Funeral <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>tie</trunc></u>
<u n="765" who="S0115">is it one of the recent ones?</u>
<u n="766" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no it's not Titanic that was an American one</u>
<u n="767" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Titanic's not a British film</u>
<u n="768" who="S0037">I know <pause dur="short"/> the James <trunc>B</trunc> one of the James Bonds maybe?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> no I don't think so</u>
<u n="770" who="S0037">ah <pause dur="short"/> slumdog <pause dur="short"/> that was a British film</u>
<u n="771" who="S0115" trans="overlap">possibly</u>
<u n="772" who="S0037">wasn't it?</u>
<u n="773" who="S0115">there have been some very very big ones recently um</u>
<u n="774" who="S0037">I'm gonna find out <pause dur="short"/> get the smartphone</u>
<u n="775" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like <pause dur="short"/> here we go yeah another one of these top you know lists</u>
<u n="776" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what d'you think it is?</u>
<u n="777" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I I like those lists <pause dur="short"/> like the top</u>
<u n="778" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what d'you think it is? What's your bet then?</u>
<u n="779" who="S0115">uh the the biggest grossing British so called British made film even though I believe often the money is <trunc>dis</trunc> the distribution is American isn't it but?</u>
<u n="780" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what about <trunc>S</trunc></u>
<u n="781" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the the <trunc>Brit</trunc> uh</u>
<u n="782" who="S0037">is it is Slumdog a British film?</u>
<u n="783" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="784" who="S0037">mm <pause dur="short"/> what about Pirates Of The Caribbean what about those ones?</u>
<u n="785" who="S0115">I don't think they're British</u>
<u n="786" who="S0037">no?</u>
<u n="787" who="S0115">Don't think so no <pause dur="short"/> although there maybe there is a lot of British actors in it but I don't think it's British</u>
<u n="788" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="789" who="S0115">eh uh the biggest British film of all time <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> well Four Weddings And A Funeral's gotta be in the top ten hasn't it? Things like</u>
<u n="790" who="S0037">hundred best</u>
<u n="791" who="S0115" trans="overlap">something with Hugh Grant in</u>
<u n="792" who="S0037" trans="overlap">top a hundred British films <pause dur="short"/> what <trunc>d</trunc> what's the top mean though like? Is that in terms of top grossing?</u>
<u n="793" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><trunc>Gro</trunc> it's the top grossing worldwide or?</u>
<u n="794" who="S0037">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> it's the British Film</u>
<u n="795" who="S0115" trans="overlap">what about stuff like like um Shakespeare In Love or uh? Um</u>
<u n="796" who="S0037">oh this is just a <trunc>i</trunc> a voters top British films like</u>
<u n="797" who="S0115">oh no I don't wanna see <pause dur="short"/> that's like the British Film Institute <pause dur="short"/> no I don't wanna see that</u>
<u n="798" who="S0037" trans="overlap">uh so it's biggest grossing? Is that what you would say d'you think?</u>
<u n="799" who="S0115">yeah biggest grossing British film like hold hold on let me give us  give us  a chance to work out some answers here</u>
<u n="800" who="S0037" trans="overlap">alright <pause dur="short"/> I'll I'll press it but I'll not open the link</u>
<u n="801" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh</u>
<u n="802" who="S0037">um</u>
<u n="803" who="S0115">press what?</u>
<u n="804" who="S0037">I've searched for it but I and I've got some pages but I'm not gonna <trunc>pr</trunc> open them</u>
<u n="805" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> alright so that sort of Love Actually is that the one with?</u>
<u n="806" who="S0037">I haven't seen it it's with that guy what's he called?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is it <trunc>F</trunc> Full Monty was really big though so</u>
<u n="808" who="S0037">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> that was a while ago <pause dur="short"/> and Billy Elliott</u>
<u n="809" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that was another one of them uh sort of uh what d'you call them like working class hero type films where</u>
<u n="810" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what about recently <pause dur="short"/> what about like <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="811" who="S0115">there was Lock Stock and Snatch like um</u>
<u n="812" who="S0037">yeah Lock Stock that was pretty big</u>
<u n="813" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they were quite quite very like critically acclaimed like uh they were <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>tr</trunc> you know trendy</u>
<u n="814" who="S0037" trans="overlap">were there any other? Um <pause dur="short"/> what about the Wallace and Gromit ones are they big?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0115">hold on hold on what about uh Harry Potter?</u>
<u n="816" who="S0037">oh yeah</u>
<u n="817" who="S0115">is that that cos that if that's British made then that would undoubtedly be like Harry Potter One and Harry Potter Two Harry Potter Three Harry Potter Four like the top</u>
<u n="818" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I can't <trunc>find</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> uK all-time top grossing films</u>
<u n="819" who="S0115">the top ten's just gonna be like all Harry Potter</u>
<u n="820" who="S0037">D'you think so? I dunno if they're British though</u>
<u n="821" who="S0115">uh Lord Of The Rings is not British made</u>
<u n="822" who="S0037">I think they were made here but is it <trunc>i</trunc> what does it what do you mean by British films like financed by British?</u>
<u n="823" who="S0115">that's something that I don't actually understand <vocal desc="laugh"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> made by a British production company but distributed maybe by American distribution studio</u>
<u n="824" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> Number One <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="825" who="S0115">I dunno</u>
<u n="826" who="S0037">ah hang on UK highest grossing movies but that is not just mean the highest <trunc>gros</trunc> grossing movies in the UK?</u>
<u n="827" who="S0115" trans="overlap">in the UK? Yeah that would that's what that would mean <pause dur="short"/> what we want is British made uh <pause dur="short"/> use the word British not not UK</u>
<u n="828" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I have <pause dur="short"/> I've got biggest grossing <trunc>Brish</trunc> British films</u>
<u n="829" who="S0115">have you gone to Google or Wikipedia?</u>
<u n="830" who="S0037">Google <pause dur="short"/> shall I go to Wikipedia?</u>
<u n="831" who="S0115">uh hold on um <pause dur="short"/> what you could do is get the British film industry on Wikipedia</u>
<u n="832" who="S0037">aww</u>
<u n="833" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> it's two all</u>
<u n="834" who="S0037">oh I didn't see that</u>
<u n="835" who="S0115">Athletico have uh pulled one back</u>
<u n="836" who="S0037">I quite like Athletico because well cos of the Sunderland link</u>
<u n="837" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="838" who="S0037">but I also wanted Schalke to win because they're the sort of underdogs <pause dur="short"/> Masshive underdogsh <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="839" who="S0115">oh right <pause dur="short"/> I like that <unclear/> uh <pause dur="short"/> shteve <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="840" who="S0037">what d'you think in the <trunc>be</trunc> well we'll come back to the best British</u>
<u n="841" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh have you got  have you got  British film industry on there cos</u>
<u n="842" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I've</u>
<u n="843" who="S0115">Cos if you go to British economy</u>
<u n="844" who="S0037" trans="overlap">british Film Institute?</u>
<u n="845" who="S0115">no not the British Film Institute it's just an organization</u>
<u n="846" who="S0037">no no <pause dur="short"/> no hang on</u>
<u n="847" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>may</trunc> maybe it's not even true maybe none of them were like <pause dur="short"/> but it's not even <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>g</trunc> I guess we're talking about British production companies</u>
<u n="848" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="849" who="S0115">like um <pause dur="short"/> that Channel Four um Channel Four Films that isn't there like a? And often the co uh there's sort of several</u>
<u n="850" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> joint</u>
<u n="851" who="S0115">several companies would work together like I think Slumdog Millionaire was a collaboration of uh different ones</u>
<u n="852" who="S0037">british Film Institute <pause dur="short"/> fist of <pause dur="short"/> Fifty films you should see by the age of fourteen <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="853" who="S0115">no but it's not uh d'you wanna um pass it here so I can have a go?</u>
<u n="854" who="S0037">no I'm alright I've got the British Film Institute open now</u>
<u n="855" who="S0115" trans="overlap">have you? No no there's no point the British Film Institute</u>
<u n="856" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's what you told me to search for</u>
<u n="857" who="S0115">no I didn't <pause dur="short"/> I said search for the British film industry</u>
<u n="858" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="859" who="S0115">the British Film Institute is just an organization that</u>
<u n="860" who="S0037">yeah well</u>
<u n="861" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="862" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Sorry</u>
<u n="863" who="S0115">D'you wanna pass it here?</u>
<u n="864" who="S0037">no I'm alright thanks</u>
<u n="865" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> if you go to the economy of the UK economy it might</u>
<u n="866" who="S0037">Don't be silly</u>
<u n="867" who="S0115">well <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="868" who="S0037">films would be in that article in but I'd have to weed through the whole thing wouldn't I?</u>
<u n="869" who="S0115">ay? D'you wanna pass it here?</u>
<u n="870" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'd have to weed through <pause dur="short"/> no I'm fine thanks</u>
<u n="871" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> okay I think we'll abandon this uh idea just say it's Harry Potter <trunc>s</trunc> Harry Potter one to seven followed by uh how many Harry Potters are there now? Uh</u>
<u n="872" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah right <pause dur="short"/> uh eight isn't there?</u>
<u n="873" who="S0115">uh Harry Potter one to eight and</u>
<u n="874" who="S0037">okay I'm on the British film industry page now</u>
<u n="875" who="S0115" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Billy Elliott under under that <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="876" who="S0037">so in the bit <trunc>th</trunc> here it says the British film <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>bri</trunc> in two thousand and nine British films grossed two billion worldwide and ensured a market share of seven percent</u>
<u n="877" who="S0115">ooh <pause dur="short"/> I suppose James Bond does count actually doesn't it?</u>
<u n="878" who="S0037">I dunno it just doesn't say there's not a list</u>
<u n="879" who="S0115">are you on the economy thing?</u>
<u n="880" who="S0037">yeah I've just got the British Film Institute has produced a poll ranking</u>
<u n="881" who="S0115" trans="overlap">did did did you Google it?</u>
<u n="882" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="883" who="S0115">did you Google it?</u>
<u n="884" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="885" who="S0115">if you go to Wikipedia Britain <pause dur="short"/> economy of Great Britain</u>
<u n="886" who="S0037">that seems like such an obscure way to go round it though</u>
<u n="887" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no because it'll mention cos because that's one quite a big aspect of <trunc>Bri</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> like it's quite</u>
<u n="888" who="S0037">really? I don't think it is</u>
<u n="889" who="S0115">I think it is <pause dur="short"/> d'you d'you want me to have a look?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0037">no I'm fine</u>
<u n="891" who="S0115">you you keep saying no but you sort of you keep failing to produce the</u>
<u n="892" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I'm just doing what you <pause dur="short"/> have they scored again?</u>
<u n="893" who="S0115">no</u>
<u n="894" who="S0037">have they?</u>
<u n="895" who="S0115">no they haven't</u>
<u n="896" who="S0037">no um</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="897" who="S0037">I'm just  I'm just  doing what you telled us</u>
<u n="898" who="S0115">there's no point doing that cos like you won't get <unclear/></u>
<u n="899" who="S0037">what?</u>
<u n="900" who="S0115">uh what I told you was to give it to me so <unclear/></u>
<u n="901" who="S0037">no but I'm just typing what you would type so I'm not doing anything wrong</u>
<u n="902" who="S0115"><unclear/></u>
<u n="903" who="S0037">because I wanna type cos I'll just be sitting here doing nothing if you were doing it</u>
<u n="904" who="S0115">yeah but we <vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="905" who="S0037">right</u>
<u n="906" who="S0115">you really are uh insane  holding that thing</u>
<u n="907" who="S0037" trans="overlap">economy of Great Britain <pause dur="short"/> what am I looking for? Films? Well it's my thing</u>
<u n="908" who="S0115">we're looking for the top <vocal desc="laugh"/> list of Britain's highest</u>
<u n="909" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know we are</u>
<u n="910" who="S0115">highest grossing British films <trunc>s</trunc> does that not bring that on Google?</u>
<u n="911" who="S0037"><trunc>N</trunc> no</u>
<u n="912" who="S0115">so you're on the economy of UK where are you?</u>
<u n="913" who="S0037">I'm up to history macroeconomic trends currency exports <pause dur="short"/> will it be in exports?</u>
<u n="914" who="S0115">uh could be yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean <trunc>i</trunc> is there not a section on sectors?</u>
<u n="915" who="S0037">um</u>
<u n="916" who="S0115"><unclear/> No</u>
<u n="917" who="S0037">sectors yeah <pause dur="short"/> agriculture hunting and forestry construction electricity manufacturing <pause dur="short"/> gotta be an arts one <pause dur="short"/> mining and quarrying gas industry service creative industries</u>
<u n="918" who="S0115">service yeah creative industry yeah yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0037">no it just says Creative industries account for seven percent and grew an average of six percent per annum <pause dur="short"/> key areas include London and Manchester <pause dur="short"/> That's all it says</u>
<u n="920" who="S0115">well that's that's quite a high percentage overall isn't it? Um <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="921" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> this is stupid</u>
<u n="922" who="S0115">go go to Harry Potter and we'll do it the other way round we'll <pause dur="short"/> go go to Harry Potter and then try to uh</u>
<u n="923" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Harry Potter? But is it made by a British company?</u>
<u n="924" who="S0115">well we'll find out</u>
<u n="925" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I could just look up the hundred best</u>
<u n="926" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> well that's not quite that wasn't what we were after</u>
<u n="927" who="S0037">um</u>
<u n="928" who="S0115">well I <trunc>c</trunc> I could have a go on the other computer maybe</u>
<u n="929" who="S0037">no it's alright <pause dur="short"/> harry Potter</u>
<u n="930" who="S0115">have <trunc>y</trunc> have you not Googled like British <trunc>m</trunc> made movies made in Britain or films made in Britain or something?</u>
<u n="931" who="S0037">alright <pause dur="short"/> I'll try that</u>
<u n="932" who="S0115" trans="overlap">or <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> well British film companies and then you can work out</u>
<u n="933" who="S0037" trans="overlap">british film <trunc>co</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> british <pause dur="short"/> what d'you want us to type? British what?</u>
<u n="934" who="S0115">british film company</u>
<u n="935" who="S0037">that won't give us any indication of like <pause dur="short"/> will it? That won't give us any indication of biggest <trunc>Brigi</trunc> British films</u>
<u n="936" who="S0115">I think they would just call them British films don't they? I'm surprised it's <trunc>d</trunc> it's that hard actually I I</u>
<u n="937" who="S0037" trans="overlap">biggest</u>
<u n="938" who="S0115">Cos normally there'd <unclear/></u>
<u n="939" who="S0037">well I'm not lying honestly</u>
<u n="940" who="S0115">alright that wasn't uh <pause dur="short"/> an an I wasn't suggesting that you were lying</u>
<u n="941" who="S0037" trans="overlap">biggest box office <pause dur="short"/> biggest box office flop of all time <pause dur="short"/> they're all like weekend box office figures</u>
<u n="942" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> why've you? You've gone for  you've gone for  <trunc>Bri</trunc> British um <pause dur="short"/> but is it  is it  uh?</u>
<u n="943" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'll close that now <pause dur="short"/> harry Potter <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> what did you wanna find from Harry Potter?</u>
<u n="944" who="S0115">uh just like what company made it?</u>
<u n="945" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> oh this is the book <pause dur="short"/> there film series</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="946" who="S0037">have you read them all the Harry Potter ones?</u>
<u n="947" who="S0115">oh I don't like it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="948" who="S0037">the films? Okay <pause dur="short"/> harry Potter</u>
<u n="949" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="950" who="S0037">Warner Brothers</u>
<u n="951" who="S0115">oh right <pause dur="short"/> well that's the studio that distributes it but I dunno about like</u>
<u n="952" who="S0037">produced by David Hayman distributed by Warner Brothers</u>
<u n="953" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the companies that <pause dur="short"/> they're the distributors but I don't know if they</u>
<u n="954" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Harry Potter is a British American film series <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="955" who="S0115">yeah I mean British like I think that's part of the problem <pause dur="short"/> um that it does tend to be a collaborated <pause dur="short"/> but uh <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> like if you go for um <pause dur="short"/> go go to Full Monty then maybe look at who made that and then maybe you can work out if that is truly British or</u>
<u n="956" who="S0037" trans="overlap"></u>
<u n="957" who="S0115">like</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="958" who="S0037">list of highest grossing films? I might get it from there <pause dur="short"/> what d'you think's the highest grossing film of all time?</u>
<u n="959" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="960" who="S0037">used to be Titanic didn't it?</u>
<u n="961" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Lord of the</u>
<u n="962" who="S0037">avatar?</u>
<u n="963" who="S0115">Lord of the Rings and or or um</u>
<u n="964" who="S0037" trans="overlap">avatar maybe?</u>
<u n="965" who="S0115">uh Harry Potter or Star Wars the um <pause dur="short"/> yeah like a</u>
<u n="966" who="S0037">highest grossing films</u>
<u n="967" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it was  it was  Titanic wasn't it?</u>
<u n="968" who="S0037">avatar <pause dur="short"/> I was right</u>
<u n="969" who="S0115">oh Avatar</u>
<u n="970" who="S0037">well it's difficult because of the adjustment like <pause dur="short"/> the highest grossing film in the fifties and the highest grossing film now <pause dur="short"/> titanic <pause dur="short"/> star Wars <pause dur="short"/> jaws and ET <pause dur="short"/> oh no <pause dur="short"/> harry Potter Titanic</u>
<u n="971" who="S0115">is that just in their own? Is that excluding <trunc>re</trunc> um?</u>
<u n="972" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no that was just I was reading them out <pause dur="short"/> so it goes Avatar Titanic Harry Potter Two Transformers</u>
<u n="973" who="S0115">that was a great goal actually the way they they sort of built up</u>
<u n="974" who="S0037" trans="overlap">aww</u>
<u n="975" who="S0115">some very good passing there <pause dur="short"/> I suppose they sort of <pause dur="short"/> was a little bit scrappy at the end but but they way they <pause dur="short"/> the guy passed it <trunc>w</trunc> right across <pause dur="short"/> but there was loads of space you see</u>
<u n="976" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they're not defending</u>
<u n="977" who="S0115">um can I have a go ah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="978" who="S0037">it wasn't a very nice <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't a very exciting goal though</u>
<u n="979" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so it it would have been  it would have been  Harry Potter wouldn't it if if that <trunc>w</trunc> if that counted</u>
<u n="980" who="S0037">but that it's a British American film</u>
<u n="981" who="S0115">I think they all are collaborative like <pause dur="short"/> and there's another Harry Potter another Harry Potter <pause dur="short"/> harry Potter <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's <trunc>i</trunc> I think it would have been all Harry Potters at the top <trunc>w</trunc> like before</u>
<u n="982" who="S0037">I want to say Harry Potter in my Dick Van Dyke voice</u>
<u n="983" who="S0115">Harry</u>
<u n="984" who="S0037">Harry Potter</u>
<u n="985" who="S0115"><trunc>Bo</trunc> Bodder</u>
<u n="986" who="S0037">hairy Bodder <vocal desc="laugh"/> Look Harry <pause dur="short"/> I've drawn this chalk drawing <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="987" who="S0115">ah but he actually would fit in into that</u>
<u n="988" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="989" who="S0115">he'd fit into that film</u>
<u n="990" who="S0037">I could imagine him being like an old wizard</u>
<u n="991" who="S0115">I think this film's grossed like the GDP of you know</u>
<u n="992" who="S0037">Ireland? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="993" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Italy or something <pause dur="short"/> uh Avatar grossed if this is correct</u>
<u n="994" who="S0037">whoa d'you think Schalke can come back from this?</u>
<u n="995" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh two point seven million <pause dur="short"/> billion in fact two point seven billion</u>
<u n="996" who="S0037" trans="overlap">gah two point seven billion?</u>
<u n="997" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="998" who="S0037">dollars?</u>
<u n="999" who="S0115">there are probably countries that uh</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0037">oh I'm sure</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0115">that that would struggle to have uh a positive uh you know Particularly countries that are in debt</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0115">struggle to turn over that <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1004" who="S0037">we saw one of the Harry Potters at Christmas though didn't we? Which one was that? D'you remember?</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0115">oh yeah cinema of the United Kingdom</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0037">the one where she winds where he winds a watch back?</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0115">which one's that?</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0037">hermione get like um that stopwatch?</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> no I <trunc>d</trunc> I didn't really  I didn't really  get into them and uh <pause dur="short"/> if I was gonna get into them I suppose I'd have to just watch them all</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0115">like one after the other and um</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0037">God that'll take ages there's eight of them</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> it's all um</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but by the time he's eighteen like surely that's quite a different film from like the first one?</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0037">I hate it when they do that you know when they roll around</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0115">the list of British <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> list of British film studios <pause dur="short"/> cos they used to do a lot in didn't they in the Hammer horror?</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0037">oh he's just wasting time isn't he?</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah he uh <pause dur="short"/> the film studios</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0037">see? He agrees</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1021" who="S0115">well yeah cos we've got sort of seven minutes left and</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0037">yeah he's just time wasting</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0115">but but it'll get added on though so <pause dur="short"/> I guess he gives them a chance to regroup or whatever</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> get their breath back</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh <pause dur="short"/> twickenham Film Studios <pause dur="short"/> I think I've heard of that <pause dur="short"/> ealing Studios of course</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1026" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0037">cor it's a big stadium</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there's a lot about uh some of the the harror <trunc>m</trunc> Hammer horror ones</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0037">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0037">are they <trunc>rem</trunc> remaking that did I see? Are they remaking that um what's that one in the shower? Psycho?</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0115">uh they well they've done it they they did um</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0037">recently?</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0115">they did uh no no not recently they did like a a new one a new Psycho</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure they're making a new one</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0115">that's a good way to make loads of money isn't it?</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0037">aww he's oh aww he nearly put that in there did you see?</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0115">highest grossing British films <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1039" who="S0037">I like it when the football players have really long names</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0115">like what?</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0037">like Popodofolofokofalouhlus</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0115">oh</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0037">and they have to like wrap it round all of their back?</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0115">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0037">aww <pause dur="short"/> You know</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0115">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> would have a double <trunc>ba</trunc> d'you would you have a double barrelled name then?</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0037" trans="overlap">in like a spiral <vocal desc="laugh"/> Na <pause dur="short"/> would you?</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0115">no <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0037">think it's stupid</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0115">it's better to <pause dur="short"/> I'd rather get my DNA profiled</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0037">I'd rather make up a new name</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0115">sorted and then</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0037">like get the two names and like make an anagram</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0037">or just choose a different name <pause dur="short"/> what about like Guacamole? Claire Guacamole</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0115">oh it says on this one Mamma Mia became the biggest grossing British film <pause dur="short"/> hey?</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0037" trans="overlap">there we have it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> found it <pause dur="short"/> it's only taken us twenty minutes</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0115">no no no that was only from two thousand and eight <pause dur="short"/> might've been overtaken</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> one of the James Bond ones</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh sorry what what did you say then?</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0037">I was just being stupid <pause dur="short"/> I said shall I change my name to Claire Claire Guacamole</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0115">Claire Guacamole <vocal desc="laugh"/> Ah here we are all-time highest grossing <trunc>mo</trunc></u>
<u n="1063" who="S0037" trans="overlap">turn it off</u>
</body>
</text>
