<text id="SGBT">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:19:24</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-05</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0567 S0622</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON's home, Milton Keynes, Buckinghamshire</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Food for a snack, the school day, what we are going to do, eating, being quiet/loud, being on stage, shared memories, computers, drawing on the computer</topics>
		<activity>Sisters talking.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, requesting, apologising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0567">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern English Accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lancaster</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>11 months (First year and half second year)</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0622">
				<exactage>8</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Milton Keynes</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Milton Keynes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>9_unknown</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Imogen has just started French and Spanish at school. At this point she only knows a few dozen words of these languages -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0567">right you could have a brioche roll you could have a slice of bread you could have a pain au chocolat you could have some crackers you could have some grapes some cheese a yogurt <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> are any of those taking your fancy? <pause dur="short"/> which one?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0622">mm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0567">have I got to guess? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0622">animal biscuits?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0567">animal biscuits er no that wasn't on the list was it?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0622">mm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0567">oh you can give me a sad face all you want <pause dur="short"/> or you can give me a cute face all you want you are still not getting them</u>
<u n="8" who="S0622">please</u>
<u n="9" who="S0567"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="10" who="S0622">why?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0567">you can have some after tea</u>
<u n="12" who="S0622">why?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0567">cos I don't want you to have too much sweet stuff before tea</u>
<u n="14" who="S0622">please</u>
<u n="15" who="S0567">erm <pause dur="short"/> and now I'm dropping crackers everywhere <pause dur="short"/> would you like some cheese?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0622">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0567">yeah?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0622">but I've already had one today</u>
<u n="19" who="S0567">cheese?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0622">mm <vocal desc="misc"/> okay</u>
<u n="21" who="S0567">what what did you say that you'd already had today?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0622">a banana</u>
<u n="23" who="S0567">a banana <pause dur="short"/> why aren't you allowed more than one banana?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0622">daddy said <unclear>birthday</unclear> and I'm quite sure and he wouldn't want me to be naughty</u>
<u n="25" who="S0567">oh right <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0622">can you cut me some cheese please?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0567">erm yes <pause dur="short"/> if you have a pepperoni you can only have one cracker with it</u>
<u n="28" who="S0622">erm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0567">oh they have Babybel I didn't know that</u>
<u n="30" who="S0622">I don't want <unclear/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0567" trans="overlap">and <unclear/> yes please</u>
<u n="32" who="S0622"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> it's cheddar</u>
<u n="33" who="S0567">it's age four cheddar <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> is that not what that means? <pause dur="long"/> now the little bit at the end might be dried cos if it's been out overnight it sometimes tends to <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> is that too much cheese? or is that?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0622">that's okay</u>
<u n="35" who="S0567">yeah? <pause dur="short"/> would you like a plate?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0622">mm hm <pause dur="long"/> thank you</u>
<u n="37" who="S0567">that's alright <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> oh no <pause dur="short"/> dad's goat's cheese is falling out everywhere all over the fridge <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="long"/> so what did you do at school today <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0622">erm <pause dur="short"/> well we did erm <pause dur="short"/> science and maths and literacy</u>
<u n="39" who="S0567">mm hm what did you do in <pause dur="short"/> literacy?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0622">we were erm like writing <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> well l can't remember</u>
<u n="41" who="S0567">you can't remember? <pause dur="short"/> it was only a couple of hours ago <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0622">I can only remember maths</u>
<u n="43" who="S0567">maths what did you do in maths then?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0622">erm <pause dur="short"/> well we had a sheet and it was like <pause dur="short"/> there was a word underlined like there's erm hundreds tens and units and we had erm to put the letter like T if it was tens if it was in the middle because hundreds tens and units the T goes in the middle so we had to put the T there that it was tens or hundred or unit or whatever</u>
<u n="45" who="S0567">so did you find that easy? hard?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0622">easy</u>
<u n="47" who="S0567">mm hm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0622">but I got mixed up because <pause dur="short"/> well I found it kind of easy and kind of in the middle I didn't really find it so hard</u>
<u n="49" who="S0567">mm <pause dur="long"/> so is that something you'd done <pause dur="short"/> last term? or is it or you started it this term?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0622" trans="overlap">I <pause dur="short"/> erm I think I started it this term <pause dur="long"/> I don't know what to do afterwards</u>
<u n="51" who="S0567">after what?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0622">after I</u>
<u n="53" who="S0567">have your snack well we could play a game if you want to? <pause dur="short"/> we could play erm <pause dur="short"/> uno or?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0622" trans="overlap">I want to do something that we don't usually do when you're here like</u>
<u n="55" who="S0567">oh right okay what would you</u>
<u n="56" who="S0622">like we made crackers when it was Christmas cos we made crackers and you brought your cracker stuff with you</u>
<u n="57" who="S0567" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm I didn't bring anything with me this time though</u>
<u n="58" who="S0622" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> except from your laptop and your</u>
<u n="59" who="S0567" trans="overlap">oh yeah I will look on my computer</u>
<u n="60" who="S0622">erm <pause dur="short"/> you might have brought something else but that's probably all you've brought <pause dur="short"/> and you might have clothes because then</u>
<u n="61" who="S0567">I might do yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0622">in your suitcase</u>
<u n="63" who="S0567"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> we could</u>
<u n="64" who="S0622">last time or one of the times I remember looking up a picture on your laptop and then drawing it out <pause dur="short"/> I remember doing that</u>
<u n="65" who="S0567">was that when we did the cat was it cat or was it a dog?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0622">it was a dog</u>
<u n="67" who="S0567">a dog <pause dur="long"/> do you eat all your bits of your dinner separately?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0622">erm <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> sometimes <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> because when I have erm pasta in sauce and chilli con carne I usually mush it up together</u>
<u n="69" who="S0567">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0622">like mash potato <pause dur="short"/> it's very quiet without <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0567"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> it is <pause dur="short"/> it's quite nice though</u>
<u n="72" who="S0622">mm hm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0567">you like being quiet don't you?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0622">well</u>
<u n="75" who="S0567">or sometimes anyway <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0622">it's just I don't really like being up on a big stage where you like are in front of lots of people</u>
<u n="77" who="S0567">mm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0622">and it's not just <pause dur="short"/> just you</u>
<u n="79" who="S0567">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0622">there's lots of other people thinking about because some people might have a different opinions anyway</u>
<u n="81" who="S0567">do you mean like if you are doing <pause dur="short"/> a show or something and it was just you?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0622">mm hm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0567">what if you were doing it with other people as well?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0622" trans="overlap">cos erm once I was working with erm this was before just before the Christmas erm holidays I was working with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos we were going to design a centre's workshop and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was my partner</u>
<u n="85" who="S0567" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> you were going to what? sorry</u>
<u n="86" who="S0622">we were going to design a centre design shop</u>
<u n="87" who="S0567" trans="overlap">design mm hm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0622">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was my partner</u>
<u n="89" who="S0567">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0622">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is very loud and I'm very quiet so we didn't really say my thing but we didn't really go together</u>
<u n="91" who="S0567">mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0622">because I'm just very quiet</u>
<u n="93" who="S0567">I think some times</u>
<u n="94" who="S0622" trans="overlap">and anyway when I started when I told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that because I was doing the menu and thinking of like <pause dur="short"/> snowball soup or something</u>
<u n="95" who="S0567">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0622">then erm I'd finished the menu and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was gonna do a card trick and she'd done the card trick and then she did it to lots of people and then I wanted a turn and then I just that just took my mind off what we were actually meant to be doing</u>
<u n="97" who="S0567">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> I think sometimes when you have a loud person and a quiet person it can be okay the quiet person doesn't like to do talking they like to do listening</u>
<u n="98" who="S0622">mm hm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0567">but sometimes the loud person can talk over the quiet person <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="100" who="S0622">or talk for the quiet person</u>
<u n="101" who="S0567">or talk for them yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0622">wait <unclear/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0567">mm <pause dur="short"/> do you want to put this one in the bin as well?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0622">I don't know what to do <pause dur="short"/> because you have not brought your craft things with you</u>
<u n="105" who="S0567">no I'm sorry I'll bring something at Easter maybe <pause dur="short"/> maybe I might bring a treasure hunt with me</u>
<u n="106" who="S0622">do you remember when we had a Halloween hunt?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0567">erm <pause dur="short"/> I do that was quite that was <pause dur="short"/> was that twenty thirteen? it must have been because it wasn't twenty fifteen because that was the Halloween that we just had <pause dur="short"/> and it wasn't twenty-fourteen cos I was in my first year of uni so I wouldn't have been here for Halloween <pause dur="short"/> so it must have been my last year of college</u>
<u n="108" who="S0622">I think so</u>
<u n="109" who="S0567">and how old would you have been?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0622">five</u>
<u n="111" who="S0567">you would have been?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0622">six</u>
<u n="113" who="S0567">six I think or nearly or <pause dur="short"/> you might have been five nearly six</u>
<u n="114" who="S0622">mm okay <pause dur="short"/> <unclear> because I always</unclear> remember November is near December it just goes November December <pause dur="short"/> I <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0567">do you remember being five?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0622">I can only remember one time when I was five or two <pause dur="short"/> when I was five</u>
<u n="117" who="S0567">which time is that?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0622">when erm I only can remember it on my birthday when I was five</u>
<u n="119" who="S0567">what on your fifth birthday or on your sixth birthday?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0622">fifth <pause dur="short"/> I think I remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got me this Hello Kitty kind of thingy but now I've like <pause dur="short"/> I've gave some of the beads to mummy and I don't know where the rest of the thingies are <pause dur="short"/> or I've just lost everything and I remember I got that little Hello Kitty Hello Kitty set that I got from <pause dur="short"/> somebody that Hello Kitty that I got for my birthday that we cleared out of my room</u>
<u n="121" who="S0567">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0622">I remember I think I got that for my birthday <pause dur="short"/> and I think I had a Hello Kitty cake which I</u>
<u n="123" who="S0567" trans="overlap">cake?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0622">once but <pause dur="short"/> I think then you might have realised I was very into Hello Kitty</u>
<u n="125" who="S0567"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> it's strange isn't it like when you were quite little you used to like Peppa Pig a lot <pause dur="short"/> and then you got into Hello Kitty and now you like Sylvanians and Lego Friends <pause dur="long"/> do a lot of your classmates like Lego?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0622">erm <pause dur="short"/> I think the boys are into boy Lego but</u>
<u n="127" who="S0567">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0622">I don't really</u>
<u n="129" who="S0567">well you could play with boy Lego if you wanted to it's not really boy Lego it's just Lego</u>
<u n="130" who="S0622">I don't have any</u>
<u n="131" who="S0567">but they do they've got sets like erm fire engines and police stations and stuff like that</u>
<u n="132" who="S0622" trans="overlap">helicopters</u>
<u n="133" who="S0567">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0622">I've nearly finished so we can go upstairs and do something</u>
<u n="135" who="S0567">okay what would you like to do? we could do some reading if you want</u>
<u n="136" who="S0622">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0567">drawing colouring <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0622">I like drawing but I'm not sure if <pause dur="short"/> okay let's just go upstairs and see what</u>
<u n="139" who="S0567"><vocal desc="laugh"/> do you want to finish your mouthful first? <pause dur="short"/> has it gone? <pause dur="short"/> come on then <pause dur="short"/> let me just put these things away <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0622"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0567">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0622">do you mind if I played on your laptop?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0567">sorry do oh do I mind if I if you what sorry?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0622">if I played on your laptop?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0567">if you coloured on my laptop?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0622">like <pause dur="short"/> don't you know where there's like a screen and you can make like <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="147" who="S0567">do you mean like paint?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0622">yeah like the painting where you draw stuff</u>
<u n="149" who="S0567">paint on the computer there I don't I don't actually think there is a paint on erm <pause dur="short"/> I haven't found one on my computer we can try and look for one I don't think there's one that comes ready installed but</u>
<u n="150" who="S0622" trans="overlap">do you know where Frizz is on?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0567">Frizz?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0622">Frip</u>
<u n="153" who="S0567">Frip</u>
<u n="154" who="S0622">is</u>
<u n="155" who="S0567">is that the typing thing you were doing before?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0622">it was the games thing</u>
<u n="157" who="S0567">oh the one with all the games</u>
<u n="158" who="S0622" trans="overlap">the one with lots of the games</u>
<u n="159" who="S0567">yeah I remember</u>
<u n="160" who="S0622">I really like laptops</u>
<u n="161" who="S0567">I see the laptop that mummy used to <pause dur="short"/> have but</u>
<u n="162" who="S0622">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0567">that she gave to me is downstairs</u>
<u n="164" who="S0622">did mummy give that to you?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0567">yeah the little black one <pause dur="short"/> well the big black one <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> just put my stuff back on my bed where someone made it all fall off I wonder who that might have been? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0622" trans="overlap">I wonder who that was</u>
<u n="167" who="S0567">I wonder who <pause dur="short"/> not that it was you or anything <pause dur="short"/> cos you would never do a thing like that would you?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0622">yes I would</u>
<u n="169" who="S0567"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you're not supposed to admit it was you</u>
<u n="170" who="S0622">or anyone</u>
<u n="171" who="S0567">right <pause dur="short"/> you want to you can put your feet under the covers if you want cos you</u>
<u n="172" who="S0622" trans="overlap">ow</u>
<u n="173" who="S0567">oh sorry <pause dur="short"/> you haven't got a</u>
<u n="174" who="S0622">it wasn't well you bringing the laptop <pause dur="short"/> naughty laptop</u>
<u n="175" who="S0567">naughty naughty laptop <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="176" who="S0622">Macbook Air</u>
<u n="177" who="S0567">Macbook Air <pause dur="short"/> that's so beautiful</u>
<u n="178" who="S0622" trans="overlap">what is that?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0567">er what's what? that thing?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0622">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0567">erm <pause dur="short"/> it's er a hinge for the <pause dur="short"/> lid you know like a door hinge <pause dur="short"/> that makes the door <pause dur="short"/> swing</u>
<u n="182" who="S0622" trans="overlap">yeah but I thought once you went like that</u>
<u n="183" who="S0567">oh I was just cleaning it</u>
<u n="184" who="S0622">oh</u>
<u n="185" who="S0567">because it gets dusty</u>
<u n="186" who="S0622">I thought it did something</u>
<u n="187" who="S0567">what's <trunc>tri</trunc> I can't remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I sign up to so many things and I can't remember what half of them are <pause dur="short"/> right what are you after? Friv did you say?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0622">no it was the paint</u>
<u n="189" who="S0567">paint right let's have a look for</u>
<u n="190" who="S0622">because there's that wasn't paint but I thought I think that's a kind of <unclear/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0567">erm <pause dur="short"/> cos I have looked for paint before <pause dur="short"/> and I can't</u>
<u n="192" who="S0622">remember</u>
<u n="193" who="S0567">well I do <pause dur="short"/> because on Windows which is the type of computer that mummy and daddy have got downstairs <pause dur="short"/> it's really easy to find paint but on here I don't think there's one that comes ready loaded onto the <pause dur="short"/> computer so we will have a look and see if there is an app for it</u>
<u n="194" who="S0622">oh there's lots of them</u>
<u n="195" who="S0567">there's lots of them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0622">wow</u>
<u n="197" who="S0567">but I don't want to pay for one particularly</u>
<u n="198" who="S0622">free</u>
<u n="199" who="S0567">erm <pause dur="short"/> let's try this one <pause dur="short"/> paint pen free <pause dur="short"/> like something like that? is that what you're looking for?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0622">I don't know what what that thing you are doing</u>
<u n="201" who="S0567">I think it's like you can do drawing with it so you've got like a paintbrush and different colours</u>
<u n="202" who="S0622" trans="overlap">do you do it with the mouse?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0567">yeah I've got an actual mouse if you want if you go in my suitcase <pause dur="short"/> down I think down near one of the wheels there's like an actual <pause dur="short"/> if you just open the lid <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm and do you want to get a book to rest it on because I don't have a <pause dur="short"/> mouse mat</u>
<u n="204" who="S0622">which one?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0567">erm probably one of the bigger ones maybe the <pause dur="short"/> yeah or one of</u>
<u n="206" who="S0622">this one do?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0567">erm maybe the sort of yellowy the whatever that one is kings and queens</u>
<u n="208" who="S0622"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> this one?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0567">that one yeah then you will have a lot of space to <pause dur="short"/> move the <pause dur="short"/> thing <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="210" who="S0622">I don't really know about that <unclear/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0567">so you'll you'll need to switch it on in a minute but <pause dur="short"/> well it says it's free we'll get it</u>
<u n="212" who="S0622" trans="overlap">okay do I?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0567">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and we'll see what it's like <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then</u>
<u n="214" who="S0622">er is this me doing that?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0567">that is you doing that yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0622">wow</u>
<u n="217" who="S0567">er what's my password that's the question don't click on anything just at the minute cos I'm typing and I don't want to</u>
<u n="218" who="S0622">wow <pause dur="short"/> there's an actual arrow</u>
<u n="219" who="S0567">ah oh right can you just keep it still <vocal desc="laugh"/> just for a second</u>
<u n="220" who="S0622">sorry <pause dur="short"/> woo</u>
<u n="221" who="S0567">no no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0622">sorry</u>
<u n="223" who="S0567">I'm just going to turn it off until I load up the thing cos we can't both control it</u>
<u n="224" who="S0622" trans="overlap">what are you doing to me?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0567">at the same time</u>
<u n="226" who="S0622">help</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
