<text id="SGHZ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:55:13</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-17</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0202 S0208</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Doncaster</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Friendships, Relationships, Making plans</topics>
		<activity>Friends chatting about general stuff</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, Announcing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0202">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0208">
				<exactage>19</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- advanced</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0208">appreciate it</u>
<u n="2" who="S0202">honestly don't even worry about it it's fine like cos originally when it happened I I mean we were talking about Valentine's Day and erm or like what are you gonna do for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? and they were just like erm well I don't know I'm thinking about sending her a card and some flowers but I don't know how I'm going to do it like in his broken English</u>
<u n="3" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh</u>
<u n="4" who="S0202">which</u>
<u n="5" who="S0208">it's so cute</u>
<u n="6" who="S0202">didn't make much sense</u>
<u n="7" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0202">but he tried erm so I were replying in French because he'd send like five six Snapchats saying what have you just said and I like</u>
<u n="9" who="S0208">oh</u>
<u n="10" who="S0202">erm okay give me five minutes and I were just translating it into French</u>
<u n="11" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0202">so my French were probably terrible but his English were just as terrible so we were sort of like talking in French and English to each other like trying to arrange it and erm I was like why aren't we even why aren't we using Facebook? we've both got Facebook</u>
<u n="13" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0202">we could use the Facebook message</u>
<u n="15" who="S0208">Snapchat's so long as well</u>
<u n="16" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="17" who="S0208">that's why when I came through with the roses I like hugged you because I just assumed like I didn't think that he would have done that and I hugged you thinking oh you've given it to me because you know that I'm like upset and that he's not here and when you were like pushed me away like that's not from me I was like</u>
<u n="18" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0208">what? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0208">just in such a state of shock like oh god</u>
<u n="22" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mind blown</u>
<u n="23" who="S0208">literally literally</u>
<u n="24" who="S0202">but yeah er I was like when he was when he were when we were talking about it I was like oh he's so sweet gonna love it he was so surprised oh</u>
<u n="25" who="S0208">cos er on Skype as well <pause dur="short"/> when I spoke and I said thank you properly and stuff he was like you have mm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to thank more than me cos she's you know organised it all she did everything for me and I just literally sat there and broke down again I was like I'm surrounded by so many nice people in my life right now</u>
<u n="26" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0202">oh bless him</u>
<u n="29" who="S0208" trans="overlap">literally loved it it's so amazing</u>
<u n="30" who="S0202">but erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah like he he didn't specify flowers and I were just like I'm just gonna go and get roses because the one flower that when he bought you the flower in France it were a rose and I thought if he was here he would buy you roses so</u>
<u n="31" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0202">I went and found the nicest bouquet that I could find</u>
<u n="33" who="S0208">it was beautiful</u>
<u n="34" who="S0202">and I were just like she'll love them and they're from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so it means more</u>
<u n="35" who="S0208">I did love them they were beautiful</u>
<u n="36" who="S0202" trans="overlap">so but yeah as if I'd do anything as cheesy as buy you flowers on Valentine's Day?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0208">well I didn't know</u>
<u n="38" who="S0202">if you didn't have a boyfriend I would have done that but</u>
<u n="39" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0202">you have a boyfriend so</u>
<u n="41" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and I knew that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wanted to buy you flowers so</u>
<u n="43" who="S0208">but roses do have a lot of meaning to me like because they're roses as well it's romantic</u>
<u n="44" who="S0202">your middle name</u>
<u n="45" who="S0208" trans="overlap">but also</u>
<u n="46" who="S0202" trans="overlap">as well</u>
<u n="47" who="S0208">yeah cos he always says do you remember when I told you that he was like you represent for me what a rose represents like all red and blah blah blah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0202"><trunc>y</trunc>yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0208">really cheesy</u>
<u n="50" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0208">but it had so much more meaning</u>
<u n="52" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0208">I was just like oh</u>
<u n="54" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I'm just being sick inside right now</u>
<u n="55" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0202">just from the cheese the pure cheese</u>
<u n="57" who="S0208">it's cool I haven't had a lot of cheese in my life <pause dur="short"/> first part of cheese was that first rose</u>
<u n="58" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well</u>
<u n="59" who="S0208">so</u>
<u n="60" who="S0202">there you go well or if I</u>
<u n="61" who="S0208" trans="overlap">making up for lost time <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0202">on Friday night me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm like cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> rang me on erm Thursday cos we were at home and he like erm I'm I'm bringing a certain DVD up and I don't know where it is and I was like so it's PS I Love You and it's like yes where is it?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0208">oh</u>
<u n="64" who="S0202">so I were like oh it's here and it weren't there so we ended up watching it online but I literally was an emotional wreck the whole way through I was just sat there crying my eyes out <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> even cried at it as well</u>
<u n="65" who="S0208">you can't not cry</u>
<u n="66" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you can't not cry at that</u>
<u n="67" who="S0208" trans="overlap">at that film it's beautiful</u>
<u n="68" who="S0202">no exactly</u>
<u n="69" who="S0208">it's beautiful</u>
<u n="70" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and I were just like I was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like it's so sad but it's so beautiful it just makes me so upset I was like oh</u>
<u n="71" who="S0208">it's like The Notebook</u>
<u n="72" who="S0202">I love The <trunc>Noteb</trunc> is that the one with the old man and the old woman?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0208">and it like goes back in time to tell their story</u>
<u n="76" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0208">basically every time I watch that film I literally I can't watch it alone I need to be</u>
<u n="78" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0208">surrounded by at least three people because I am literally so depressed</u>
<u n="80" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0208">sit there questioning life</u>
<u n="82" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0208">it was like <vocal desc="laugh"/> I need someone to hug me right now</u>
<u n="84" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0208">I love it</u>
<u n="86" who="S0202">no I'm the same with PS I Love You like I know it word for word I read the book a million times I've seen</u>
<u n="87" who="S0208" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0202">the film a million times and erm his nan and granddad got me it for Christmas actually one year like erm last year they got it me for Christmas</u>
<u n="89" who="S0208">oh</u>
<u n="90" who="S0202">because I'd said for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that I wanted it on DVD cos every time I watched it I'd illegally streamed it online</u>
<u n="91" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0202">erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I wanted it a a disc of it so they got like he told them that I wanted it so they got it me and it was so cute like</u>
<u n="93" who="S0208">that's so lovely</u>
<u n="94" who="S0202">oh I love you oh they were asking about you this weekend</u>
<u n="95" who="S0208">really?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0202">yeah and do you know what I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? erm he's French will he eat this will he eat any of this food? I can't</u>
<u n="97" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0202">you know he said the same thing to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos erm obviously <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is American and</u>
<u n="99" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0202"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is French so they just assumed that Americans and French people don't eat anything that English people eat and</u>
<u n="101" who="S0208" trans="overlap">they're</u>
<u n="102" who="S0202" trans="overlap">they just eat weird stuff</u>
<u n="103" who="S0208" trans="overlap">they're so thoughtful though</u>
<u n="104" who="S0202">well yeah they were so cute</u>
<u n="105" who="S0208">it's lovely</u>
<u n="106" who="S0202">they're like well will you eat any of this? and not he's never had a Yorkshire pudding</u>
<u n="107" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0202">never had a Yorkshire pudding and I'm like how have you never had a Yorkshire pudding? oh yeah those Yorkshire puddings yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0208">it's very English though</u>
<u n="110" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0208">isn't it?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0202">he he didn't have he's never had mint sauce with anything but lamb</u>
<u n="113" who="S0208">what?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0202">yes missing out big time or what</u>
<u n="115" who="S0208">freak</u>
<u n="116" who="S0202">so he had erm mint sauce with beef and his Yorkshire pudding</u>
<u n="117" who="S0208" trans="overlap">sounds good</u>
<u n="118" who="S0202">and gravy he asked us what the gravy were</u>
<u n="119" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0202">and I'm like how do you not know what gravy is? it's like one of those greatest creations that man has ever made</u>
<u n="121" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0202">and you have it with everything anything that you want it with you will have it with except pizza that would be weird</u>
<u n="123" who="S0208">I'd imagine it being quite nice actually</u>
<u n="124" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0208">I can imagine it being nice with pasta</u>
<u n="126" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0202">really calorific though</u>
<u n="129" who="S0208">we should try that one day <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0202">yeah but erm but yeah they were asking about you like erm cos obviously the weekend that you're in Doncaster is my nephew's christening</u>
<u n="131" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0202">I keep wanting to say funeral it's doing my head in</u>
<u n="133" who="S0208" trans="overlap">don't say that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0202">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't say that erm so yeah so they keep asking about you and like <trunc>ha</trunc> if you don't mind I've got a half I feel like asking them if you could go for Sunday dinner and they're like oh no sorry I can't I'm doing something else so <pause dur="short"/> but next next time <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s over and you're over you're invited to go</u>
<u n="135" who="S0208">oh that's lovely</u>
<u n="136" who="S0202">for Sunday dinner like you could come for Saturday dinner but it's not quite the same</u>
<u n="137" who="S0208" trans="overlap">it's not it's not the same</u>
<u n="138" who="S0202">so</u>
<u n="139" who="S0208" trans="overlap">it's not the same</u>
<u n="140" who="S0202">and I want to go that psychic and all that other stuff so</u>
<u n="141" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah I don't think we'll be able to do it this time but we could do it</u>
<u n="142" who="S0202" trans="overlap">we don't have enough time do we so</u>
<u n="143" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0202">but</u>
<u n="145" who="S0208">I'm really excited for our weekend at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0202">oh I'm I'm really excited as well well cos we went out on Saturday night and it were really good</u>
<u n="147" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0202">bumped into my ex-boyfriend</u>
<u n="149" who="S0208">really?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0202">yeah my first boyfriend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who used to</u>
<u n="151" who="S0208" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0202">erm and it were really weird cos he's got really massive like muscular and I were just like I'm so glad I'm not with you right now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0202">and he were massive and I was just like hi</u>
<u n="155" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0208">how are they doing?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0202">alright I think</u>
<u n="159" who="S0208">yeah?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0202">which which is nice to see cos even though I mean we were both just as bad as each other in that relationship it weren't just one sided it were me as well and I don't and that's not condoning anything he did or anything I did but it weren't just him I provoked him and I did the same to him as he did to me</u>
<u n="161" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0202">and I'm not gonna pass myself off as a victim because it weren't like that at all erm <pause dur="short"/> but erm yeah it's it I think he's doing fine like it he looks he he said that he were doing alright and stuff so I just hope that he's sorted sorted himself out a bit</u>
<u n="163" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0202">cos he weren't a bad guy you know we were both just as bad as each other and I think we were just destructive together</u>
<u n="165" who="S0208">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0202">but</u>
<u n="167" who="S0208" trans="overlap">but it's nice that you can see each other on good terms</u>
<u n="168" who="S0202">yeah well I bump into him like if I ever go out round <anon type="place"/> I bump into him and I'm just like er it's not all the time it's once in a blue moon that I bump into him or it was like hi how are you are you alright?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0202">and we'll talk and have a chat and stuff but <pause dur="short"/> yeah so <pause dur="short"/> so have you seen <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at all?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0208">erm <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="172" who="S0202">no <pause dur="short"/> I ain't seen or heard anything from her at all</u>
<u n="173" who="S0208">no</u>
<u n="174" who="S0202">I think I might invite her out on Thursday</u>
<u n="175" who="S0208">I was gonna say I think that things will be okay though</u>
<u n="176" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0208">cos like</u>
<u n="178" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it'll be awkward for a few minutes but then it'll fine</u>
<u n="179" who="S0208">cos I know this doesn't really mean anything but like she's liked some of my posts on Facebooks and photos and stuff and like if you were angry at someone you wouldn't</u>
<u n="180" who="S0202" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="181" who="S0208" trans="overlap">genuinely do I know it has like no meaning</u>
<u n="182" who="S0202" trans="overlap">no yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0208" trans="overlap">but it's true you wouldn't do that</u>
<u n="184" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0208">I think things are</u>
<u n="186" who="S0202">yeah I think</u>
<u n="187" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I think they're fine</u>
<u n="188" who="S0202">I don't want to lose her as a friend but I'm we needed to put our foot down we needed to say look</u>
<u n="189" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0202">we don't want to live with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and if you want to live with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> then you do that but you should have told us this months ago it's the fact that she let us down the day before we were going to</u>
<u n="191" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0202">view that fantastic house</u>
<u n="193" who="S0208">but to honest I think things will be okay because she must realise how awkward a situation it is and I think the reason that we haven't spoken for a while is because we're angry but she must be just as ashamed</u>
<u n="194" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0208">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0208">so I think if we make the first move to talk to her it will show her that we are okay and she doesn't</u>
<u n="198" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0208">need to feel embarrassed or</u>
<u n="200" who="S0202" trans="overlap">worry about yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0202">no she should feel embarrassed cos what she did were wrong but it shouldn't cost a friendship because</u>
<u n="203" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0202" trans="overlap">there's no need for it to cost a friendship we had an argument it's over that's it</u>
<u n="205" who="S0208">but you have</u>
<u n="206" who="S0202" trans="overlap">we're still friends</u>
<u n="207" who="S0208">you have arguments with friends</u>
<u n="208" who="S0202">exactly you're always gonna have arguments</u>
<u n="209" who="S0208" trans="overlap">and sometimes if you're not happy with something that's happening you need to say it</u>
<u n="210" who="S0202">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="211" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="212" who="S0202">because then you're just gonna build it up and then er all of a sudden you're gonna fall out and not talk to each other for months and months and months</u>
<u n="213" who="S0208">yeah it could end the friendship</u>
<u n="214" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0208">but no yeah we should invite her cos then at least she can turn it down if she wants to or</u>
<u n="216" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0208">just give her the option</u>
<u n="218" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0208">it would be nice</u>
<u n="220" who="S0202">definitely</u>
<u n="221" who="S0208">but I am I am looking forward to it cos if we can't get into <anon type="place"/> we can just go anywhere on <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0208">we'll go to that erm <anon type="place"/> cos <anon type="place"/> literally was so fun</u>
<u n="224" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0208">but it was later on in the night but I'm sure it will be fine</u>
<u n="226" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0208">earlier as well</u>
<u n="228" who="S0202">I mean we I'll I've got a student card now so</u>
<u n="229" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0202">I if er as long as I make sure I take that out with me with my passport we should be fine getting into places cos they were really funny that time weren't they when we didn't have our students cards</u>
<u n="231" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah but then</u>
<u n="232" who="S0202" trans="overlap">like they would not let us in</u>
<u n="233" who="S0208" trans="overlap">but then again when I went with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and stuff I went in without any ID or my student ID</u>
<u n="234" who="S0202">it might be because you were with me because I look older and I am older cos like they looked at my passport and then they asked for my student ID</u>
<u n="235" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0202">it might be because I'm older</u>
<u n="237" who="S0208">but also it might be because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her friends had already gone in and they came out to get me cos they thought that I'd gone home</u>
<u n="238" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="239" who="S0208">cos they saw that I was with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> at the smokers and I was like I'll meet you guys in there</u>
<u n="240" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0208">and then they obviously came back to smoke as I was gone cos I went to look for them</u>
<u n="242" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0208">so I think it was just like a misunderstanding and they thought that I'd left</u>
<u n="244" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0208">erm but then when I rang her and she came and got me so maybe because they'd already been in they let us back in</u>
<u n="246" who="S0202">yeah cos they thought yeah yeah do you have to pay to get in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0208">no</u>
<u n="248" who="S0202">no that's alright then cos <trunc>th</trunc>this is what really annoys me about going out round <anon type="place"/> you have to pay to get in everywhere like where I'm from you pay to get in one nightclub and that's only if you get there after midnight</u>
<u n="249" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0202">and that's only to <trunc>d</trunc>deter all the really drunk people I think</u>
<u n="251" who="S0208">isn't it</u>
<u n="252" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you know</u>
<u n="253" who="S0208" trans="overlap">that <anon type="place"/> place?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0202">yeah <anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0208">I'm happy to pay like it's the same for <anon type="place"/> like I'm really happy to pay to go in because I always have a good time</u>
<u n="256" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah I don't mind that but when you go somewhere new and you don't know what it's like and you've never been there before you don't know what sort of people are there you don't know <trunc>h</trunc> what the drinks are like you don't know all this or other stuff</u>
<u n="257" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0202">I don't like <trunc>p</trunc> it's like we paid seven pound each to go to <anon type="place"/> and it's like I had a such a shit night</u>
<u n="259" who="S0208">I did as well but I think that's a shame because erm all the stories that everyone's told me that always like <anon type="place"/> is my favourite place</u>
<u n="260" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I was really hyped to go</u>
<u n="262" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0208">I think it was just a bad night</u>
<u n="264" who="S0202">yeah I think it were just cos it was so busy we waited for forty minutes the buzz that we had from pre-drinking had gone</u>
<u n="265" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0208">so I think it's just a shame cos our first experience was a bad one but I'm I'm happy to give it another try</u>
<u n="268" who="S0202">yeah me too</u>
<u n="269" who="S0208" trans="overlap">but maybe a different time and a different night or</u>
<u n="270" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0208">or like</u>
<u n="272" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I I will give it</u>
<u n="273" who="S0208" trans="overlap">just get there a bit earlier maybe</u>
<u n="274" who="S0202">yeah or maybe just erm go a bit later on in term because if we go later on in term a lot people have work to do and it won't be oh yeah refreshers we're back at uni we're</u>
<u n="275" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0202" trans="overlap">away from our parents again sort of thing</u>
<u n="277" who="S0208">cos all everyone had just finished their exams I think that's why it was such a big night</u>
<u n="278" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0208">cos it was packed</u>
<u n="280" who="S0202">yeah cos that's the reason I went out that Thursday cos I'd just finished my exams</u>
<u n="281" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0202">so</u>
<u n="283" who="S0208">like erm <anon type="place"/> I I spent sixteen pounds on the ticket but I am so happy that I paid that much like I <trunc>f</trunc> really feel like I got my money's worth</u>
<u n="284" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0208">the best night I have had</u>
<u n="286" who="S0202" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0208" trans="overlap">in <anon type="place"/> so like by a long by a long way</u>
<u n="288" who="S0202">even better than the first week?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0208">it's it was <trunc>amaz</trunc> I can't even explain how amazing it was <pause dur="short"/> it was really worth it I think that you'd like it</u>
<u n="292" who="S0202">yeah we'd have to go we'll have to go</u>
<u n="293" who="S0208" trans="overlap">it was it was packed and obviously I was sober for about two hours where I didn't enjoy myself me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were just like I'm so bored this was a waste of money and then all of a sudden <pause dur="short"/> obviously and it was amazing</u>
<u n="294" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0208">and all the people like at first the people annoyed me because there were so many of them</u>
<u n="296" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0208">but then I <trunc>r</trunc> just everyone was like my best friend</u>
<u n="298" who="S0202">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0208">it's amazing</u>
<u n="300" who="S0202">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well we'll definitely have to do something like that cos I don't like if it's a special like night like an event like that I don't mind paying a bit extra</u>
<u n="301" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0202">but when it's every single Thursday you've gotta pay seven eight pound to get in it's like well hang on <pause dur="short"/> I'm <trunc>pay</trunc> I'm spending all our money in your bar and you're still charging me seven pound to get in</u>
<u n="303" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0202">I don't think so</u>
<u n="305" who="S0208">but again that's why I didn't mind because I spent sixteen pounds to get in but I didn't buy drinks all night</u>
<u n="306" who="S0202">right okay</u>
<u n="307" who="S0208">I I didn't buy anything I just got glasses of water</u>
<u n="308" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="309" who="S0208">it was totally worth it</u>
<u n="310" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0208">spent less that night there on a big night expensive to get in and stuff than I did on a normal night when we</u>
<u n="312" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0208" trans="overlap">go to like <anon type="place"/> or something and buy drinks</u>
<u n="314" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0208">actually turned out cheaper</u>
<u n="316" who="S0202"><anon type="place"/> is so so cheap though innit? it's like you pay money to get in but then the drinks are like two pound fifty</u>
<u n="317" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0202">for a treble</u>
<u n="319" who="S0208">and it's really nice the <anon type="place"/> environment it's never packed the people are friendly everything's really <anon type="place"/> like they don't let it go over capacity like they do in some</u>
<u n="320" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0208" trans="overlap">other places and that's why I don't mind spending money cos I know I'll have a good night</u>
<u n="322" who="S0202">yeah cos there's always loads of floor space as well ain't there there's like the bits in the middle that are like erm <pause dur="short"/> there's the bits in the middle like that are rammed like <trunc>j</trunc> closer to the DJ box</u>
<u n="323" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0202">and then there's places like but then there's places that you can stand away from it so like there's like I don't know if you've noticed it but there's a seating area some near bar somewhere</u>
<u n="325" who="S0208">yeah on the side bit</u>
<u n="326" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah and then there's like the bar which is never too rammed either</u>
<u n="327" who="S0208">but there's also a bar you know the stairs in the house music part?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0208">there are stairs that go upstairs and there's a whole seating booth area with erm another bar so you go there if you don't feel like dancing and you just want a quiet places to sit</u>
<u n="330" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0208">you still have the music but it's never packed because obviously everyone's dancing</u>
<u n="332" who="S0202">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0208">like when I went with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and we weren't drunk yet it would be like let's just go upstairs and play some more drinking games and stuff</u>
<u n="334" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0208">managed to get a seat by the bar it was empty and <pause dur="short"/> it was good</u>
<u n="336" who="S0202">that's really good that actually</u>
<u n="337" who="S0208">I like that I actually like that cos there's a place for everything and there's a</u>
<u n="338" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0208" trans="overlap">quiet area there's that outside area where you can go if you just wanna be away from everything</u>
<u n="340" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0208">two different rooms with two different types of music</u>
<u n="342" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0208">it's got everything you need</u>
<u n="344" who="S0202">it's good that innit?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0208">it's amazing</u>
<u n="346" who="S0202">oh I'm dreading this detox like <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>mi</trunc> I actually feel better already because I don't feel stodge</u>
<u n="347" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0202">do you know what I mean? I don't feel like cos <trunc>ev</trunc> all I've eaten today is salad that's all I've had and prawns and a bit of tuna erm and <trunc>th</trunc> I had I've a sachet of Ready Brek this morning with some strawberries which was nice</u>
<u n="349" who="S0208">ooh healthy</u>
<u n="350" who="S0202">yeah but the I can't have porridge on its own without anything cos it's just so vile</u>
<u n="351" who="S0208">it tastes horrible</u>
<u n="352" who="S0202">it's</u>
<u n="353" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I need sugar</u>
<u n="354" who="S0202"><trunc>v</trunc> oh yeah me too</u>
<u n="355" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I need a lot of sugar <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0202">that's why I bought the strawberries to go with it cos I thought if I buy it cos they're only one fifty from Asda they were like a little punnet</u>
<u n="357" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="358" who="S0202">erm l like I would put them in because then I can't taste the <trunc>cerea</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> the the <trunc>Read</trunc> the porridge sorry</u>
<u n="359" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0202">I can't taste the porridge so I'll be fine</u>
<u n="361" who="S0208">I like it with bananas</u>
<u n="362" who="S0202">mm yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0208">cos bananas are so so naturally sweet</u>
<u n="364" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0208">all through the year like</u>
<u n="366" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you don't need anything with the</u>
<u n="367" who="S0208" trans="overlap">cos strawberries sometimes when they're not in season</u>
<u n="368" who="S0202">they're a bit sour</u>
<u n="369" who="S0208" trans="overlap">they can be a bit tasteless</u>
<u n="370" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0208">but bananas are just always so nice</u>
<u n="372" who="S0202">mm well I've got some more grapes but I've got frozen grapes as well so</u>
<u n="373" who="S0208">okay</u>
<u n="374" who="S0202">the frozen grapes I'll just keep for wine because I think they</u>
<u n="375" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0202">if I take them out they're gonna go off straight away</u>
<u n="377" who="S0208">they won't be very nice like</u>
<u n="378" who="S0202" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="379" who="S0208">when when you freeze fruit and like defrost it it never tastes</u>
<u n="380" who="S0202" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="381" who="S0208" trans="overlap">very nice</u>
<u n="382" who="S0202">so we'll just keep them for erm the wine because while they it doesn't alter the flavour of the wine for a start but then when they've melted and you eat them they just taste like wine</u>
<u n="383" who="S0208">yeah I've had a few grapes</u>
<u n="384" who="S0202">so</u>
<u n="385" who="S0208" trans="overlap">from the punnet we have in the fridge</u>
<u n="386" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0208">but I've only had a few because I don't think they're quite ripe yet like they <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="388" who="S0202" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="389" who="S0208">they were still a bit sour</u>
<u n="390" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0208">and they're not starting to go off or anything I think I'm just gonna leave them</u>
<u n="392" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0208">for a few more days cos they were a bit sour</u>
<u n="394" who="S0202">yeah that's what I like though about shopping at there because you can buy stuff that are not quite ripe yet yeah fair enough you have to leave it a few days but at least you're not forced to eat them straight away either</u>
<u n="395" who="S0208">cos they're gonna go off</u>
<u n="396" who="S0202">because they're gonna go off</u>
<u n="397" who="S0208" trans="overlap">like when we bought it up the meat market</u>
<u n="398" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0208">I was quite disappointed in that actually</u>
<u n="400" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah I were disappointed in that</u>
<u n="401" who="S0208">things didn't last very long</u>
<u n="402" who="S0202">no</u>
<u n="403" who="S0208">I think we'll just stick to buying meat there</u>
<u n="404" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0208">erm</u>
<u n="406" who="S0202">yeah definitely I mean if I'm gonna cook something that night and I want some fresh veg something that I wouldn't <trunc>normall</trunc> ordinarily buy like I don't know an aubergine is an aubergine veg?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0202">yeah so like an aubergine or like something like that that I'm gonna cook that night then I'd buy it because you can just buy them singular</u>
<u n="409" who="S0208">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I'd probably buy something like that but for bulk for week I just I can't justify it cos you have it goes out of date so quick</u>
<u n="411" who="S0208" trans="overlap">well so we had to throw away whole peppers</u>
<u n="412" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0208">it's just such a waste of money</u>
<u n="414" who="S0202">yeah so and the</u>
<u n="415" who="S0208" trans="overlap">and we were really excited about it as well like oh this is going like good money it's going straight to the producers it's all fresh and stuff but</u>
<u n="416" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah but then it just went out of date it's like well</u>
<u n="417" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0202">that's money chucked down the brain basically</u>
<u n="419" who="S0208" trans="overlap">like it's like it's good out of principle but we can't really afford to do that right now</u>
<u n="420" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0208" trans="overlap">as a lifestyle choice <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it is so expensive to be healthy though ain't it?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0208" trans="overlap">we're not quite there yet it is</u>
<u n="424" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it is so expensive like <pause dur="short"/> I mean we we're we're quite lucky because we're clever with our money so we go to places like Aldi that most people look down their nose at</u>
<u n="425" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="426" who="S0202">I don't know why cos it's the same but like we're quite lucky that we've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because if we didn't have <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we'd have to get a bus there and then a bus back</u>
<u n="427" who="S0208">we just wouldn't do it</u>
<u n="428" who="S0202">and we wouldn't do it</u>
<u n="429" who="S0208">we literally wouldn't do it</u>
<u n="430" who="S0202">we'd just go to Morrisons or something</u>
<u n="431" who="S0208">yeah I do like Morrisons though like the whole Savers brand and stuff it is really cheap</u>
<u n="432" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="433" who="S0208">which is what I buy like toilet roll bread those kind like cereals and stuff</u>
<u n="434" who="S0202">yeah and we get free toilet roll</u>
<u n="435" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I get all of that on Savers so</u>
<u n="436" who="S0202">we get free toilet roll from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0208">though <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s used up most of the Cushelle</u>
<u n="438" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0208">yeah but she's</u>
<u n="440" who="S0202" trans="overlap">well I've got another thing in there</u>
<u n="441" who="S0208" trans="overlap">she was erm quite ill</u>
<u n="442" who="S0202">yeah she said</u>
<u n="443" who="S0208" trans="overlap">this weekend</u>
<u n="444" who="S0202" trans="overlap">that she weren't very well</u>
<u n="445" who="S0208">cos obviously you know that she's got like a really low metabolism so if I got a cold she would get flu</u>
<u n="446" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="447" who="S0208" trans="overlap">like erm your <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="448" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0208">starting to speak like a Yorkshire person</u>
<u n="450" who="S0202">I know</u>
<u n="451" who="S0208">your your <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0202">your <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> mate yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0208">yeah she was quite ill and obviously after that day of travel and stuff and</u>
<u n="454" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0208">she's got IBS like she's just found out she's got IBS</u>
<u n="456" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0208" trans="overlap">which is one of the reasons why she gets so irritated</u>
<u n="458" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="459" who="S0208">so the smallest thing just sets her off and she just gets sick all the time</u>
<u n="460" who="S0202" trans="overlap">god that's awful</u>
<u n="461" who="S0208">I felt so sorry for her cos like I've been fine all week and as soon as I get to <anon type="place"/> and what to do things I'm ill and blah blah blah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0202"><vocal desc="misc"/> ah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0208">and I was just like it's okay no one's judging you</u>
<u n="464" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I saw <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> earlier</u>
<u n="465" who="S0208">did you?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0202">yeah do you know erm the erm</u>
<u n="467" who="S0208" trans="overlap">can I have another one?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0202">yeah yeah do you know the medical er testing place where you get paid loads of money to like do</u>
<u n="469" who="S0208" trans="overlap">when you walk through uni?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0202">yeah that</u>
<u n="471" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0202" trans="overlap">car park thing</u>
<u n="473" who="S0208">would you like one?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0202">yes please erm well I was walking out there cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were waiting in the car for me and I just saw him like at the back of me and I just <trunc>shout</trunc> I just went <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do you want a lift?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0208">shouted <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I were like I were like yeah and he were like he looked at me and then and looked as his friends and he went to his friends and he went I was gonna take a lift guys</u>
<u n="477" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0202">see you back home <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0208">ah that's nice through</u>
<u n="480" who="S0202">yeah it was the first literally first time I've seen him</u>
<u n="481" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0202">since before way before Christmas</u>
<u n="483" who="S0208">I've seen him</u>
<u n="484" who="S0202" trans="overlap">at the ball the last time I saw him</u>
<u n="485" who="S0208">I've seen him obviously the first day he got back but he was busy so I literally just said hello in passing like</u>
<u n="486" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0208">happy Christmas blah blah the second time I saw him was by the place again walking to from uni but it was pouring rain so neither of us stopped to talk</u>
<u n="488" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0208">we were just like hi and then the last time was erm he was coming out of his bedroom as me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were leaving but we were running so late we were supposed to be at her friend <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s at nine and it was half nine and we hadn't eaten yet</u>
<u n="490" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="491" who="S0208">cos I took her down to TGI's and we were gonna eat there</u>
<u n="492" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="493" who="S0208">on Saturday night erm but we got there and they were like one hour waiting time and we were like <trunc>f</trunc>fuck that</u>
<u n="494" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0208">so just ended up going to Wagamama but obviously we had to walk home and change because we thought if we go for dinner now we can go like not dressed up</u>
<u n="496" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0208">come home and get dressed and get a taxi</u>
<u n="498" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0208">but seeing as we were halfway into town to <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s we had to go dressed up and stuff which is fine I mean we were wearing trainers and stuff like it didn't look too much</u>
<u n="500" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0208">but <pause dur="short"/> just took so much time and</u>
<u n="502" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah I know what you mean</u>
<u n="503" who="S0208" trans="overlap">we ended up being really late but it was cool cos we weren't pre-drinking that night obviously</u>
<u n="504" who="S0202">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0208" trans="overlap">so we just got there had a bit of time to chill and then left</u>
<u n="506" who="S0202">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm so jealous you've been to Wagamama</u>
<u n="507" who="S0208">mm <pause dur="short"/> I realised erm I was telling her that it's I've <trunc>spe</trunc> I've probably spent hundreds and hundreds of pounds there since I've moved here five months ago</u>
<u n="508" who="S0202">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0208">and she was like what? how? and I was like <pause dur="short"/> well go there quite a lot and I was like I haven't been a lot this term actually this is my third time she was like this is your third time?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0208">and I was like I've been here a month already she was like third time in a month?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0208">she was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're a student and was like <trunc>i</trunc> oh god yeah I am</u>
<u n="514" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we spend in one night at Wagamama what we spend in two weeks on food</u>
<u n="515" who="S0208">yeah well I don't any more cos obviously I don't eat as much as I did</u>
<u n="516" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0208">and I've just I've stopped like buying wine and stuff so I probably spend like ten to thirteen pounds in total</u>
<u n="518" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0208">which is better</u>
<u n="520" who="S0202">yeah me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were talking about this earlier actually cos we were saying that we want to go back to Wagamama at some point erm but we don't want to spend as much money as we normally do so my answer to that well well we need to sneak our wine in somehow because literally we'll get a sixty pound bill and twenty pound of it'll be wine</u>
<u n="521" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0202">cos it's so <trunc>ex</trunc> I don't know how they get away with charging that much money for a bottle of wine when er you can get a bottle of wine from the supermarket for three pound</u>
<u n="523" who="S0208">yeah I think erm well the other night obviously cos we were on our way we'd bought just a bottle of cider like to share</u>
<u n="524" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0208">cos obviously we couldn't drink much erm just to like get ourselves a bit</u>
<u n="526" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0208">in the mood and stuff erm and I had it in the Nisa bag and I just walked in with it</u>
<u n="528" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0208">and put it under the table like they didn't notice so you could probably get wine that way in</u>
<u n="530" who="S0202">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't think they'd be bothered cos most of the people that work there are students anyway</u>
<u n="531" who="S0208">I don't I don't think they'd care but I also don't think that they notice to be honest</u>
<u n="532" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="533" who="S0208">they might see it on a table and realise it's not on the bill but I mean by then it'll be too late so</u>
<u n="534" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="535" who="S0208">what are they gonna do?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0202">and that's only if they're like super super observant</u>
<u n="537" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0202">and actually care if they're jobs worthies then they'll mention it and we'd probably get told off and not to do it again but <pause dur="short"/> I doubt it</u>
<u n="539" who="S0208">I don't think it'll matter</u>
<u n="540" who="S0202">no</u>
<u n="541" who="S0208">but I'm quite happy like if we're going out for a meal I'm quite happy to not get alcohol because I think the meal is my treat</u>
<u n="542" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0208">and that's what I'm paying for so I think I'm happy to just to have dinner a bit earlier maybe go to Wagamama and then on the way back get a bottle of wine and have it after</u>
<u n="544" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="545" who="S0208">I think that would that would just be the better thing to do</u>
<u n="546" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0208">oh I've just realised what a busy few weeks I've got ahead of me obviously on Wednesday I'm going out to Newcastle for the night to see my mum and my nan</u>
<u n="548" who="S0202">oh yeah is that this week?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0208">yeah Wednesday so I get back on Thursday afternoon and then <pause dur="short"/> obviously got to catch up on work probably meet up with my group a bit</u>
<u n="550" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0208">for Thursday and Friday and then the Saturday I'm heading down to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s come back on the Sunday then I've got more work to do more uni that week and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s coming on the Thursday after that</u>
<u n="552" who="S0202">oh so you're not gonna be here this weekend then are you?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0208">not this Saturday and Sunday no</u>
<u n="554" who="S0202">yeah but this Saturday and Sunday I were talking about <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="555" who="S0208">oh god <pause dur="short"/> no no it's not this one it's the next one</u>
<u n="556" who="S0202">right okay</u>
<u n="557" who="S0208">like this this week I'm here</u>
<u n="558" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="559" who="S0208">but starting from next Wednesday I'm no it's this Wednesday what ah what date oh my god I'm so</u>
<u n="560" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I was saying well you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are coming down to <anon type="place"/> on the twenty-seventh aren't you? well the twenty-eighth</u>
<u n="561" who="S0208">it is this weekend cos we're Monday now I forget yeah so this this Wednesday I'm going to see my mum this Saturday and Sunday I'm going to see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="562" who="S0202">right okay er that's why</u>
<u n="563" who="S0208">and the next the week after <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s coming</u>
<u n="564" who="S0202">right okay</u>
<u n="565" who="S0208">so sorry about that I won't I won't make it to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0202">no no it's fine</u>
<u n="567" who="S0208" trans="overlap">obviously <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="568" who="S0202">no it's fine <trunc>serious</trunc> it were it were just like well we're going do you want to come sort of thing</u>
<u n="569" who="S0208">but thank you for the invitation I'll definitely take it up another time</u>
<u n="570" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0208" trans="overlap">cos that day session in <anon type="place"/> I know it was expensive but it was so much fun</u>
<u n="572" who="S0202">yeah I love <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="573" who="S0208">I loved it so much and hopefully we'll be able to meet up with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this time</u>
<u n="574" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0208">cos we couldn't last time cos he had all of his hockey and a mate coming up and stuff so it was just</u>
<u n="576" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0208">a bit last minute</u>
<u n="578" who="S0202" trans="overlap">too much yeah well what I'll have to do in summer before you go we'll have to arrange a day in <anon type="place"/> because <anon type="place"/> in the summer is absolutely beautiful honestly like cos when we were there it <trunc>w</trunc> it were raining it were miserable it were horrible but in summer it is honestly it's <trunc>s</trunc> everyone goes to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="579" who="S0208">I I went</u>
<u n="580" who="S0202">it is the place that everyone goes</u>
<u n="581" who="S0208">I went to <anon type="place"/> this summer with I took <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="582" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="583" who="S0208">when we were in England we were at my grandad's we went to <anon type="place"/> for the day</u>
<u n="584" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="585" who="S0208">that was lovely saw a film being filmed</u>
<u n="586" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0208">yeah well actually more of a series it was like a</u>
<u n="588" who="S0202" trans="overlap">Game of Thrones</u>
<u n="589" who="S0208">no</u>
<u n="590" who="S0202" trans="overlap">this they film that in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0208">do they?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0202">yeah <trunc>s</trunc> parts of it in <anon type="place"/> anyway</u>
<u n="593" who="S0208" trans="overlap">oh it wasn't Game of Thrones it was just it was a period drama so I saw women wearing like old</u>
<u n="594" who="S0202">oh it'll be like Downton Abbey I bet</u>
<u n="595" who="S0208" trans="overlap">dresses and stuff</u>
<u n="596" who="S0202">that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> watches</u>
<u n="597" who="S0208">it wasn't Downton Abbey either cos I've I also watched that and it wasn't that</u>
<u n="598" who="S0202">you watch Downton Abbey?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0208">I watch it with my mum okay? it's a bonding thing</u>
<u n="600" who="S0202">okay</u>
<u n="601" who="S0208">we watch it over Christmas together</u>
<u n="602" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="603" who="S0208">well I forced my mum to watch Family Guy which she doesn't enjoy so</u>
<u n="604" who="S0202">I watched Family Guy last night</u>
<u n="605" who="S0208">my punishment was to watch Downton Abbey with her</u>
<u n="606" who="S0202">oh right okay</u>
<u n="607" who="S0208">well it wasn't really a punishment cos after I got over how boring it was I actually started to enjoy the storyline</u>
<u n="608" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="609" who="S0208">I was like oh this is quite interesting what's gonna happen? are they gonna sell the house? oh oh my god they're going bankrupt they're gonna lose the castle I literally got so into it I was like</u>
<u n="610" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah it</u>
<u n="611" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I I'm ashamed of myself <unclear>right now</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="612" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it sounds really boring <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0208">well it was at first but the storyline is good like there's so much going on like with the servants and up there like one of the servants erm is gay and obviously back then it was</u>
<u n="614" who="S0202">no</u>
<u n="615" who="S0208">prohibido</u>
<u n="616" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="617" who="S0208">and erm yeah then like the masters find out and stuff cos he like someone who he's a horrible person and someone tricks him and says that this other guy is in love with him and he wants to arrange a date so he has to go into his bedroom at this time like when everyone's gone to sleep so obviously the gay guy goes in gets into bed with this guy</u>
<u n="618" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you're joking</u>
<u n="619" who="S0208">who's completely straight</u>
<u n="620" who="S0202">oh no</u>
<u n="621" who="S0208">and he gets fired it was so dramatic</u>
<u n="622" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="623" who="S0208">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously you can imagine back then like everything was</u>
<u n="624" who="S0202">well even so getting into bed with some random guy or even random girl is bad</u>
<u n="625" who="S0208">yeah but obviously</u>
<u n="626" who="S0202" trans="overlap">let alone being opposite sex</u>
<u n="627" who="S0208">he he thought he'd asked for it obviously he thought that he'd arranged the meeting so I felt <trunc>r</trunc> I actually felt really bad for him I was like oh that's horrible</u>
<u n="628" who="S0202">bless him</u>
<u n="629" who="S0208">but he's a horrible character</u>
<u n="630" who="S0202">is he?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0202">so is he in the show now then or not?</u>
<u n="633" who="S0208">mm <pause dur="short"/> I've only watched season one</u>
<u n="634" who="S0202">and were that the end of season one?</u>
<u n="635" who="S0208">er it just sort of happened through the season</u>
<u n="636" who="S0202">oh okay</u>
<u n="637" who="S0208">I don't I haven't watched any more</u>
<u n="638" who="S0202">and is er?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I watched a bit here and there with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos her family watch it at Christmas as well</u>
<u n="640" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="641" who="S0208">so I just watched a few episodes but I'm not I don't follow it</u>
<u n="642" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="643" who="S0208">intensively</u>
<u n="644" who="S0202">I couldn't believe it with that our one of our roof tiles just fell off from the storm</u>
<u n="645" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="646" who="S0202">I didn't think it were that bad I mean er it's only a roof tile it's not like it's the whole roof don't get me wrong but still just even that it's like</u>
<u n="647" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0202">that's never happened it's weird</u>
<u n="649" who="S0208">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s erm obviously he's a bit further down south and he's right on the coast in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="650" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="651" who="S0208">so obviously it's a bit worse but erm their whole fence in his house got blown over</u>
<u n="652" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="653" who="S0208">like the whole fence was just uprooted in the middle of the road and er his mum's house erm she also lives in <anon type="place"/> like a tree fell over erm into the garden but also onto next door neighbour's roof</u>
<u n="654" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="655" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="656" who="S0202">oh god</u>
<u n="657" who="S0208">so his mum was just like I'm just so glad it wasn't our house but I feel bad for the other people but I feel happy it's not my house</u>
<u n="658" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="659" who="S0202">you'd be devastated though wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="660" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="661" who="S0202">it's like it's like all them floods it's like what would you do? like I saw this picture on Facebook earlier basically someone's conservatory doors and the water was up there on the conservatory doors</u>
<u n="662" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="663" who="S0202">and it's just like I can't even imagine that like</u>
<u n="664" who="S0208">yeah well do you remember when we had to do that news report in my French seminar? the guy who was the foreign correspondent like down in London</u>
<u n="665" who="S0202">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="666" who="S0208">above the floods he showed a picture of his friend's house and the water was like up to here</u>
<u n="667" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0208">and there was just it was like a swimming pool inside their house <pause dur="short"/> and that was in London <pause dur="short"/> just what what would what do you do? like that takes so much time and money to repair</u>
<u n="669" who="S0202">well my uncle's house flooded cos the ones who live er the gay one with his boyfriend</u>
<u n="670" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0202">erm cos where they live they live just five minutes away from the town centre and basically they <trunc>l</trunc> the to stop the town centre flooding they flooded where they live instead so they redirected the water</u>
<u n="672" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="673" who="S0202">to where they live</u>
<u n="674" who="S0208" trans="overlap">lovely</u>
<u n="675" who="S0202">and flooded them instead so it took them two years</u>
<u n="676" who="S0208" trans="overlap">oh god</u>
<u n="677" who="S0202">of living a caravan and hotels for the insurance company to fix everything replace everything</u>
<u n="678" who="S0208">it's so horrible isn't it?</u>
<u n="679" who="S0202">cos the thing is with water you can't just like <trunc>l</trunc> you've got to let it dry out you've got to let all the beams and all the supports and all the foundations and everything else and the ground underneath to dry out</u>
<u n="680" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="681" who="S0202">and then once that's done then you can start like repairing stuff and fixing stuff and it just took it two years two years it took</u>
<u n="682" who="S0208">it's awful</u>
<u n="683" who="S0202">and the whole place was just like <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>I</trunc>it were like up to here in water</u>
<u n="684" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="685" who="S0202">it was so bad</u>
<u n="686" who="S0208">I remember years and years ago when I still lived in England <pause dur="short"/> I went up to my grandad's er in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="688" who="S0208">and there was a really really bad flood that year I was about five four or five erm so obviously I was really really small</u>
<u n="689" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="690" who="S0208">but I had to spend the day on my dad's shoulders because the water was up to his waist like</u>
<u n="691" who="S0202" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="692" who="S0208">I would've I would've drowned and I just <trunc>remem</trunc> I don't remember much of it obviously I was so young but I just remember a few bits like my <trunc>gra</trunc> cos he the whole area he lives is like a residential area of bungalows</u>
<u n="693" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0208">and all of those were evacuated</u>
<u n="695" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0208">er</u>
<u n="697" who="S0202">you can imagine though bungalows you've only got one floor</u>
<u n="698" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah plus they've all got air vents and stuff like</u>
<u n="699" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="700" who="S0208">it was horrible like the whole place <trunc>ev</trunc>everything was evacuated</u>
<u n="701" who="S0202">god</u>
<u n="702" who="S0208" trans="overlap">there was hundreds of houses in that area</u>
<u n="703" who="S0202">it's so bad innit cos it's like the I think the worse thing about it as well for the flood victims is the fact that all the politicians are going over there to like have photo opportunities and they're all safe in their nice little homes away from it and</u>
<u n="704" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="705" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and they're just going in their wellies and like oh wow look at this this is bad innit? and then going back to their nice safe home</u>
<u n="706" who="S0208">yes like I'm a part of this</u>
<u n="707" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="708" who="S0208">but they're not</u>
<u n="709" who="S0202">mm they're all sticking their noses in</u>
<u n="710" who="S0208">yeah I'm happy we're not in that area though</u>
<u n="711" who="S0202">yeah me too it would be like</u>
<u n="712" who="S0208">would've been such a hassle</u>
<u n="713" who="S0202">well <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> is on the top of a hill so it's very very <trunc>r</trunc> it would be very rare that I mean we would never flood <pause dur="short"/> er I think it's</u>
<u n="714" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0202" trans="overlap">pretty much impossible because because unless you're at the bottom of the hill obviously but because <trunc>w</trunc>where our university is and where our halls are we're at the top of it</u>
<u n="716" who="S0208">it's not gonna flood</u>
<u n="717" who="S0202" trans="overlap">sort of thing it's not gonna flood</u>
<u n="718" who="S0208">unlikely</u>
<u n="719" who="S0202">and even if we do flood we're not gonna flood on <trunc>for</trunc><trunc>for</trunc>fourth floor are we come on let's face it</u>
<u n="720" who="S0208">yeah we're fine</u>
<u n="721" who="S0202" trans="overlap">the only <trunc>w</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0208" trans="overlap">we've fine</u>
<u n="723" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> the only way that we're gonna flood is if someone above us like leaves a tap on like that guy did in <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s apartment</u>
<u n="724" who="S0208" trans="overlap">which has actually happened so</u>
<u n="725" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah let's not erm laugh too much about that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="726" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="727" who="S0202">oh</u>
<u n="728" who="S0208">don't tempt fate</u>
<u n="729" who="S0202">no let's not touch wood quick touch wood</u>
<u n="730" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0202">we do not flood <vocal desc="laugh"/> but year erm <pause dur="short"/> my er lecture today was so boring honestly</u>
<u n="732" who="S0208">was it?</u>
<u n="733" who="S0202">cos like I get the reason why we have to do reading and we do like self-study and all this sort of stuff but what I don't understand is them then repeating it in the lecture</u>
<u n="734" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="735" who="S0202">I suppose it's to reiterate and to help us understand more what's being said in the books <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> I don't I don't know it just</u>
<u n="736" who="S0208">well do you remember when I had my first lecture this term for my new module?</u>
<u n="737" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="738" who="S0208">and erm I did the reading before the lecture cos</u>
<u n="739" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="740" who="S0208">usually I do it before the seminar</u>
<u n="741" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="742" who="S0208">but I did it before the lecture cos I just had free time and erm it turns out that the lecture like our lecturer had basically just done her lecture based on that chapter of reading</u>
<u n="743" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="744" who="S0208">but it was in the same order the same bullet points the same titles like it was literally</u>
<u n="745" who="S0202">the same</u>
<u n="746" who="S0208">the whole of that chapter in lecture form and I was just like I'm not taking any new information from that like doing that reading didn't help me because the lecture then became pointless</u>
<u n="747" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="748" who="S0208">and it's actually been the same each time they've based it on the chapter they've given us to read</u>
<u n="749" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="750" who="S0208">so I mean I'm still doing the reading cos obviously I do get a bit more information</u>
<u n="751" who="S0202">yeah more details</u>
<u n="752" who="S0208" trans="overlap">and learning personally</u>
<u n="753" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="754" who="S0208">yeah like more examples and stuff</u>
<u n="755" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="756" who="S0208">erm but I find it more helpful to do what our seminar tutor's asked us to do is to like look up media articles</u>
<u n="757" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="758" who="S0208">erm to sort of put our topics into perspective like internationally</u>
<u n="759" who="S0202">yeah oh right okay yeah so</u>
<u n="760" who="S0208">if you know what I mean</u>
<u n="761" who="S0202">like in practice sort of thing?</u>
<u n="762" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="763" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="764" who="S0208">so it's like my topic er for our project is education</u>
<u n="765" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="766" who="S0208">and erm she asked us to find a media article to do with our topic but also the topic of the week</u>
<u n="767" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="768" who="S0208">so our topic when I did it last week was gender so I had to find an article that was to do with development and gender and education</u>
<u n="769" who="S0202">so you had to find all the all the different examples for the different things</u>
<u n="770" who="S0208">yeah and I think that's really good cos it's a lot more challenging because it's really hard to find an article that covers all of it</u>
<u n="771" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="772" who="S0208">erm I find that really helpful though cos it helps us to get a lot more examples in for our poster</u>
<u n="773" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="774" who="S0208">but I'm gonna I'm meeting up with people tomorrow erm I think so far there's three of us that have come back to me</u>
<u n="775" who="S0202">right okay</u>
<u n="776" who="S0208">out of the five but one of them we've never met so</u>
<u n="777" who="S0202">oh yeah it's that guy who got the email innit?</u>
<u n="778" who="S0208">basically just the four of is <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="779" who="S0202">oh</u>
<u n="780" who="S0208">and I</u>
<u n="781" who="S0202" trans="overlap">has he not been in touch with any of you as yet?</u>
<u n="782" who="S0208">no the our tutor gave all of our emails but I don't know like maybe he's dropped out or something cos I haven't seen him it's actually someone I didn't realise but I've met him before he was in one of my modules the last term</u>
<u n="783" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="784" who="S0208" trans="overlap">for the seminar group erm and it's a guy</u>
<u n="785" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="786" who="S0208">so that mystery has been solved</u>
<u n="787" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="788" who="S0208">but erm he came into one of the seminars last term and that's it</u>
<u n="789" who="S0202">yeah but if he dropped out then it it would have to have a a <trunc>lea</trunc> a exit interview</u>
<u n="790" who="S0208">well we would have been notified as well</u>
<u n="791" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="792" who="S0208">so I think that he's just not doing anything</u>
<u n="793" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="794" who="S0208">but that's fine cos I mean it's annoying because he's gonna get the same mark as we do and he's gonna have done none of the work</u>
<u n="795" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="796" who="S0208">but then I just sort of think well there's four of us</u>
<u n="797" who="S0202">it's one less person to organise innit?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="799" who="S0202">and if he's really that <trunc>bo</trunc> if he's if he's really that erm <pause dur="short"/> oh what were I gonna say? he's obviously not that bothered cos otherwise he would like turn up to the seminars and stuff like that do you really want someone on your <trunc>gr</trunc> in your group who turn who doesn't turn up and you arranged to meet him and he's like yeah I'll be there but then doesn't turn up and</u>
<u n="800" who="S0208">exactly so I kind of think like the fact that he hasn't got in touch and hasn't come like it doesn't bother me that much cos I'm in a group of people who are quite motivated are quite interested and stuff</u>
<u n="801" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0208">so I think it's okay but obviously you know I missed that seminar erm last week?</u>
<u n="803" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0208">well it turns out everyone else did as well like for <trunc>diff</trunc></u>
<u n="805" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="806" who="S0208">for different reasons and erm one guy went there</u>
<u n="807" who="S0202">oh yeah you said cos it were torture like you had to <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="808" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="809" who="S0202">outline what you'd done</u>
<u n="810" who="S0208" trans="overlap">we had to outline what we'd done so far and obviously we met up once and we've got some information but we haven't gotten a proper structure yet</u>
<u n="811" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="812" who="S0208" trans="overlap">cos we thought we have until the twenty-fourth of March</u>
<u n="813" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="814" who="S0208">erm so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the guy he text me and he was like oh I can't believe you guys did this to me it was torture I was completely by myself I had no one to back me up and I was just like I'm so sorry I'll make it up to you and he text me today and he was like so do you wanna meet tomorrow and he was like how are you gonna make it up to me? and I was like</u>
<u n="815" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="816" who="S0208">erm well if we meet at the old bar I'll buy you a drink</u>
<u n="817" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="818" who="S0208">and then he was like yeah okay kiddo that might work I was like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="819" who="S0202" trans="overlap">kiddo?</u>
<u n="820" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="821" who="S0202">how old is he?</u>
<u n="822" who="S0208">erm I think he's quite old</u>
<u n="823" who="S0202">oh okay right</u>
<u n="824" who="S0208">yeah he's a mature student</u>
<u n="825" who="S0202">ah okay</u>
<u n="826" who="S0208">like dunno maybe nineteen or twenty</u>
<u n="827" who="S0202">and you class that as a mature student <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="828" who="S0208">well</u>
<u n="829" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and he's saying kiddo?</u>
<u n="830" who="S0208">well you know what I mean it's just a term of endearment</u>
<u n="831" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="832" who="S0208">cos the first time he text me erm I didn't know who it was cos I hadn't saved any of the numbers like</u>
<u n="833" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="834" who="S0208">I'd given people my number er</u>
<u n="835" who="S0202" trans="overlap">but then they'd not text you like saying hi this is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or this is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="836" who="S0208" trans="overlap">exactly so I just got a number off some random person and it got to that point where it was so awkward cos I hadn't asked who it was yet and he was just talking to me and he was like okay pal yeah we'll meet here blah blah blah it's fine don't worry about it and I was like <pause dur="short"/> does he know who I am? because I don't know who he is so I was like I'm really sorry but erm <trunc>wh</trunc>who do I have the pleasure of speaking to?</u>
<u n="837" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="838" who="S0208">and he was like it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="839" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="840" who="S0208">and I was like ah hi <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and</u>
<u n="841" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> hi <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="842" who="S0208">I felt so awkward</u>
<u n="843" who="S0202">oh dear</u>
<u n="844" who="S0208">erm but I like this group <pause dur="short"/> I don't really like my group for the other one though</u>
<u n="845" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="846" who="S0208">yeah well there's that guy that I met that one time he was nice</u>
<u n="847" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="848" who="S0208">but I haven't been since so</u>
<u n="849" who="S0202">that's gonna be awkward for you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="850" who="S0208">but I mean I'm doing all the reading and I'm doing all the lectures and stuff so like I have information to contribute I'll just work really hard</u>
<u n="851" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="852" who="S0208">with them in the group</u>
<u n="853" who="S0202">well I've gotta catch up four weeks of lectures for my politics <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> because obviously I I cos I've not been transferred over onto it yet and then obviously other things happened so I've only really missed three weeks of lectures</u>
<u n="854" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="855" who="S0202">er or two are we week four?</u>
<u n="856" who="S0208">erm</u>
<u n="857" who="S0202">yeah we're week four so I've missed three weeks of lectures</u>
<u n="858" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="859" who="S0202">erm and then I'm going to tomorrow's lecture so I should be fine erm but I'm not gonna be able to go to this seminar group yet cos I've not assigned it so when I</u>
<u n="860" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="861" who="S0202">drop it in tomorrow the form I'm hoping that I get assigned a seminar group before I miss it</u>
<u n="862" who="S0208">well at least there's no group projects for that module</u>
<u n="863" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah no it's just as an exam</u>
<u n="864" who="S0208" trans="overlap">so at least you're not gonna be dropping in like that</u>
<u n="865" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah the only thing that I've got to do is erm a fifteen hundred word essay in week eight but it's unassessed</u>
<u n="866" who="S0208">okay</u>
<u n="867" who="S0202">so I think that's just</u>
<u n="868" who="S0208">like a practice</u>
<u n="869" who="S0202">yeah for the exam</u>
<u n="870" who="S0208" trans="overlap">that's good though</u>
<u n="871" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="872" who="S0208">it's like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has a lot of those like erm over Christmas she had one exam obviously she's doing law so it's it's like medicine like they don't have like we do like half term essays and stuff like that but erm all of the ones that she did so far have just been practices like you'll get a mark but it's not official</u>
<u n="873" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="874" who="S0208">they'll be like if this was assessed you'd get this grade sort of thing</u>
<u n="875" who="S0202">yeah if it were in the exam sort of thing</u>
<u n="876" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="877" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="878" who="S0208">and I think that's actually much better cos obviously law's quite hard</u>
<u n="879" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="880" who="S0208">and it would be really unfair to mark them like from the start</u>
<u n="881" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="882" who="S0208">do you know what I mean? cos she's on a four year course</u>
<u n="883" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="884" who="S0208">erm but she's doing quite well <pause dur="short"/> like she got a first in one of them</u>
<u n="885" who="S0202">really? wow</u>
<u n="886" who="S0208">yeah and then she was like damn it why isn't it marked?</u>
<u n="887" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="888" who="S0208">and then she got like other like a varied mark and she was like I'm actually quite glad none of these are marked now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="889" who="S0202">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="890" who="S0208">but I think she's doing well</u>
<u n="891" who="S0202">yeah that's good</u>
<u n="892" who="S0208">which is good and I was really happy to hear about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as well cos she's been doing really well</u>
<u n="893" who="S0202">yeah she sounds like it yeah</u>
<u n="894" who="S0208" trans="overlap"><trunc>g</trunc>getting two ones and firsts and stuff and I'm really find like really happy for her cos in a non-rude way she's never been academic</u>
<u n="895" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="896" who="S0208">but it's because like in France and stuff erm obviously you have to do every subject there's no choice like for GCSEs and stuff usually you can pick a few subjects that you want to do</u>
<u n="897" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="898" who="S0208">in France it was all of them just like the Bac</u>
<u n="899" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah you had to do it yeah</u>
<u n="900" who="S0208" trans="overlap">and erm that meant like all the ones that she wasn't good at and not interested in she still had to do and be like marked in</u>
<u n="901" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="902" who="S0208">and I just felt really sorry for her cos she struggled <pause dur="short"/> especially with maths and stuff</u>
<u n="903" who="S0202">it's just it's one of them things as well it's a vicious circle because if you're not if you don't enjoy something and you don't like something then you're not gonna put a lot of effort in but then you get a bad mark in it and you think well why should I <trunc>ev</trunc> do anything else because I'm obviously not very good at it so I'm not gonna try</u>
<u n="904" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="905" who="S0202">it's like a vicious circle innit like</u>
<u n="906" who="S0208">exactly and erm before she left France cos she didn't so the Bac she wasn't a college in France she left just after the <trunc>GCS</trunc> like the equivalent of GCSEs and erm she got a tutor for history geography and maths</u>
<u n="907" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="908" who="S0208">yeah and she did really well I mean she was full on for about two months before our exams</u>
<u n="909" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="910" who="S0208">and she did well <pause dur="short"/> but erm I think the reason why she's succeeding now is because she's chosen the subjects</u>
<u n="911" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="912" who="S0208">she loves the subject she's good at it it's like psychology and stuff it's what she's good at</u>
<u n="913" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="914" who="S0208">so I think that's why she's finally happy with her learning environment cos she's finally doing stuff that she's A good at and B enjoys</u>
<u n="915" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah yeah well my friend does that at erm <anon type="place"/> my friend the disabled one who I tell you about all the time <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="916" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="917" who="S0202">who you've not actually met yet even though she lives in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="918" who="S0208">well I still know everything about her</u>
<u n="919" who="S0202">yeah I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="920" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="921" who="S0202">soon as you meet her it'll be oh so you're <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> nice to meet you</u>
<u n="922" who="S0208" trans="overlap">it'll be like I know your life story here's mine</u>
<u n="923" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="924" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="925" who="S0202">no she's really nice she's a bit weird but I mean there were this one time</u>
<u n="926" who="S0208" trans="overlap">so are we though <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="927" who="S0202">yeah but she's like weird in a different way so this one time erm her friend dies and it was really horrific how he died his brother were drunk and driving like</u>
<u n="928" who="S0208">oh no</u>
<u n="929" who="S0202">and he was drunk and they had an argument as they were coming off the hard <trunc>should</trunc> er coming off the erm the motorway onto the hard shoulder onto a junction and he basically lost control of the car and went straight into a tree</u>
<u n="930" who="S0208">oh no</u>
<u n="931" who="S0202">the driver didn't die but his brother did and his brother had just had a baby and</u>
<u n="932" who="S0208">oh god</u>
<u n="933" who="S0202">and like it were awful and erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were like really like messed up over it erm</u>
<u n="934" who="S0208">I can imagine</u>
<u n="935" who="S0202">and cos it were one of her close friends erm and that like a few nights after it happened we went out drinking like summer barbecue then went out around town and stuff erm and she were really drunk and she started talking to people that weren't there like we were waiting for the taxi and she was stood talking to this guy called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="936" who="S0208">oh my god</u>
<u n="937" who="S0202">and it was really freaky it were just like <pause dur="short"/> it it were just weird like really weird</u>
<u n="938" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="939" who="S0202">like you know</u>
<u n="940" who="S0208">that is strange</u>
<u n="941" who="S0202">and like she were really upset about it all night and I were and I were just like I didn't know whether he were a really close friend or she just considered him a <trunc>cl</trunc>close friend or what because she's told me she'd not seen him for a year like a year or two years and like well how close can he be if you've not seen him for that long? but I don't know whether it were like her way of dealing with it or what but it were just really weird like I I can't even like explain it</u>
<u n="942" who="S0208">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's always</u>
<u n="943" who="S0202" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="944" who="S0208" trans="overlap">horrible when you're in control like you're sober or you're okay and someone else is completely off their face because you sort of see things differently</u>
<u n="945" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="946" who="S0208">like if there are two of you and you're both really really drunk you're in the same boat</u>
<u n="947" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="948" who="S0208">but if one of them's really drunk and doing weird things</u>
<u n="949" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="950" who="S0208">you notice it</u>
<u n="951" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="952" who="S0208">it's like sometimes when erm I'm with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he's smoked or whatever but I haven't</u>
<u n="953" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="954" who="S0208">ah I get really I'm I like fear for him cos I know that he's fine but because I'm seeing him high</u>
<u n="955" who="S0202" trans="overlap">from a sober point of view</u>
<u n="956" who="S0208"><event desc="unintelligible"/> and I'm completely sober I'm just like what the fuck?</u>
<u n="957" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="958" who="S0208">like when we were at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s erm I hadn't had any of the joint they were both high <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was fine but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> obviously isn't used to that like cos he gets <pause dur="short"/> oh dear erm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="959" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="960" who="S0208">he gets like solid stuff which is</u>
<u n="961" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="962" who="S0208">not as strong as like actual</u>
<u n="963" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah it's different yeah</u>
<u n="964" who="S0208" trans="overlap">green weed</u>
<u n="965" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="966" who="S0208">and erm it was the first time he'd actually had it this summer</u>
<u n="967" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="968" who="S0208" trans="overlap">like the first time ever and he just went really weird on it like he had a coughing fit and I thought that he was like dying I was really worried and</u>
<u n="969" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="970" who="S0208">then he started laughing by himself and he was just leaning on a post and like laughing like talking to himself and I was like he's obviously having a nice time</u>
<u n="971" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="972" who="S0208">but I am really really scared right now</u>
<u n="973" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="974" who="S0208">I was just like are you okay? are you okay yeah? shall I take you home? yeah let let let's let's go home</u>
<u n="975" who="S0202" trans="overlap">let's go home <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="976" who="S0208">you need to sleep this off really bad <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="977" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh shit <pause dur="short"/> this bracelet honestly it ruins so many of my clothes</u>
<u n="978" who="S0208">but it's so pretty</u>
<u n="979" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it is so pretty they're ten pound each them</u>
<u n="980" who="S0208">I love them</u>
<u n="981" who="S0202">from erm Debenhams John Rocher I was like ten pound?</u>
<u n="982" who="S0208">I like it</u>
<u n="983" who="S0202" trans="overlap">like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> paid for them but I was just like ten pound really?</u>
<u n="984" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I can get two <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="985" who="S0202" trans="overlap">ten pound? well I got three <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="986" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="987" who="S0202">he made me buy three and he were like buy three and like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they are ten pound each I could get these from Primark for one pound</u>
<u n="988" who="S0208">yeah but they wouldn't last as long</u>
<u n="989" who="S0202">well no but</u>
<u n="990" who="S0208" trans="overlap">and the gems would fall out after a day</u>
<u n="991" who="S0202">well I'm only wearing them once</u>
<u n="992" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="993" who="S0202">I'm I've not really worn them again properly cos they ruin everything that I own</u>
<u n="994" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="995" who="S0202">but</u>
<u n="996" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="997" who="S0202">I'm really good actually cos erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum does a lot of my washing from time to time and I had this really nice dress and I can't find it anywhere now</u>
<u n="998" who="S0208" trans="overlap">is it that that Topshop one you were telling me about?</u>
<u n="999" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah it's that Topshop one and it were it weren't expensive but I can't find it anywhere</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0208">have you lent it to someone?</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and no I haven't because</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0208" trans="overlap">have you like maybe accidentally left it somewhere?</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0202">no and I think what has happened is because it's a smaller dress than what I would usually buy I think that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum <trunc>w</trunc>would have thought it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s his brother's girlfriend</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0208">oh</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0202">and has sent it to her by accident</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0202">and she's just thought it was something she forgot she had or someone else's</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0208">yeah that's possible</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0202">and I'm like I told <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to text <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> last night and get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to look for it but I don't know whether <pause dur="short"/> he's actually like done that but <pause dur="short"/> like whether</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0208">just just</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0202" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s told her to look for it or not</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0208">yeah just chase up on it a little bit</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0202" trans="overlap">but I'm gutted though cos it was such a nice dress like it I love that dress it like I'd wear it on a day to day basis like I just met my mate for a drink I'd just put that on</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0202">and it was summer so I didn't wear tights but like I'd wear tights with my Converse with it or my Uggs and it just</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0202">looked really nice it were just one of them casual things you could er wear it on a night out or you could wear it through the day and I just loved it</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0208">yeah I</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0202">and now I'm gutted</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0208" trans="overlap">fell in love I've fallen in love with a type of <trunc>dre</trunc> it's a smock dress</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0208">so it's like straight up straight down</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0208">and it's completely plain but I found one in Topshop that I fell in love with but I couldn't justify paying thirty pounds for it just cos it came from Topshop</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0208">but then the ones in New Look and Primark and everywhere else that I looked they just weren't nice</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0208">like obviously Topshop they'd put the effort in to make the sizes right to make it nice</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0208">that's why it's expensive</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0208">but I I really couldn't justify it like paying all that</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0202">how much did the other dress cost though? twenty-seven?</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0208">twenty-seven</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0202">so it were only three pound more</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0208">yeah but <pause dur="short"/> you've seen the dress like it's not plain</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0202">no</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0208">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0208">it's got a pattern it's nice it's something I could wear casual and something I can dress up</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0208">and obviously Primark's one erm the Topshop I know it will last long</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0208">but I know that I get my money's worth when I go there</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0208">that's why I don't go very often</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1048" who="S0208">it's the first time I've been since I've moved here</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0202">yeah it's really expensive</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0208">I'm very proud of myself</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0202">I don't I don't like the</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0208" trans="overlap">cos I have an addiction to Topshop so</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I I don't like the Topshop in <anon type="place"/> I I think it's like it's so confusing cos the Topshop it where I'm from it's like you walk in and there're just sections</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0202">like it's not all glittery and fancy like it is in there like the one in <anon type="place"/> is so glittery and fancy you can't find anything</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0208">have you been to the one in the <anon type="place"/>? cos there's</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0202">I don't know</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0208">I think there's three I know there's one in town somewhere that's massive like giant I went there with my dad</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0208">when I came for the open day</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0202" trans="overlap">oh yeah it's the erm it's the one in the er new centre the new shopping centre innit?</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0208">the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1063" who="S0202">is that what the new centre's called?</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0202">I think it's the <anon type="place"/> one that I went into</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0208">oh cos that's the first time I'd been there and I like that one</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0208">but it's on three floors but it's all relatively well organised</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0202">yeah well I went with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum so I might have just thought oh well this is a bit too much like for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0202">sort of thing</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0208">but there's also</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0202" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0208">a small one erm I can't remember what centre it's called but it's the one</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0202">the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0208">I don't I honestly don't know it's really small</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0208">erm it's where do you remember we went into Dorothy Perkins and you got that top?</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0202">oh yeah it's on that road <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0208">there's there's a small Topshop in that centre and then a massive massive one further in town and then a new one in the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1083" who="S0202">right yeah I've been to I think cos the one in <anon type="place"/> starts on a <trunc>sh</trunc> on a normal road don't it and you get in and then when you come out at the other side it's in the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1084" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0202">and there's like three floors</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0208" trans="overlap">it <trunc>st</trunc> it starts on the high street yeah</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0202">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0208">but I liked it there</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0202">yeah I know which one</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0208">I found so much stuff that I like cos erm Topshop like it's really hit and miss cos it's style a lot I used to love it</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0208">but now it's all like really weird stuff</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0202">it's hipster innit?</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0202">it's like really <trunc>co</trunc> like like extreme hipster like</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0202">really fashionable</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0208">like vibrant colours and</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0208">just stuff that I don't particularly like so find it really hit and miss when I go in there but</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0202">yeah I do</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0208">generally I do find stuff that I fall in love with</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0202">yeah I generally like I only go to Topshop for my jeans I don't like buying dresses and stuff from there because</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0202">the sizing for me is wrong</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0208">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0202">because my boobs and my bum it just takes into consideration if you're small and skinny</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you know it like if I buy a size ten in there which I am a size ten like because of the size of my boobs it just does not look right or does not fit right</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0202">so I have to get the next size up but then it fits over my boobs but then everywhere else is baggy and it's just like well I'm not paying this much money for something that doesn't fit me how I want it to fit me even</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0202">you know</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0208">but I think that's why I like Topshop is they have a petite range</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0208">so like I can get a size eight and it will be a size eight for small people</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0208">because they have a tall section as well but the normal if I buy a size eight like skirt or something it will just be a bit too long like look a bit wrong</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0208">and then I go into the petite section and it's the same size that fits like the same but it's just made shorter</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0208">obviously for small people</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0208">that's where I got my dress when I got it from the petite section</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0202">did you?</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0208">because I originally picked one up from normal</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0208">and it was just too long like it went over my knees and it was a</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah a bit too conservative</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0208">it's a body-con one so it's supposed to like <trunc>f</trunc> be tight around the legs</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0208">and it just wasn't</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0208">and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went and got me the right size</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0202">ah</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0208">it was nice but I like that that they have the petite range</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0202">yeah it's they have a tall range don't they as well</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0202">which I think is good like for me personally cos my jeans when I go to the normal I can't get jeans in there that fit me <pause dur="short"/> so I have to go to the tall bit and get jeans from there</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0202">because I like wearing my jeans quite high waisted as well</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0202">so because I'm tall I don't they just don't look right</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and they end up being like ankle grazers and I don't want ankle grazers I want them to go over my ankle</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0208">but that's why I love Topshop because you can get a different sized waist plus different size leg</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0202">yeah I love that</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0208">whereas normal jeans it's like a size eight is this long and I have to fold up all of my jeans</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0208">because I'm like I'm small but I'm a size eight so please</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0208">fix that</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1156" who="S0208">well now I'm a size ten which is even longer</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0202">yeah they are long yeah</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0208" trans="overlap">but at least now I can get like waist whatever like</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0202">yeah waists whatever leg whatever</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0208" trans="overlap">and the leg like for it's</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0208">a twenty-six like a size four</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0202" trans="overlap">is that it?</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0208" trans="overlap">because I'm short</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0202">oh my god</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah literally</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0202">I'm a size thirty-three in leg</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0208">I think I'm like a twenty-eight</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0202">like long leg</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1171" who="S0202">or whatever</u>
<u n="1172" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hey mate</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0202">hi</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0208">hello</u>
<u n="1175" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">you alright?</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0202">yeah are you?</u>
<u n="1177" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah good</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0202">oh baguettes</u>
<u n="1179" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0208">mm bread</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0202">that I <trunc>di</trunc> I when someone walked in my bedroom now like hello who is that and I forgot that you've got keys oh carbs I want carbs so much</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0208" trans="overlap">oh my god I forgot to tell you the other night it was Friday night and we'd just gotten back from <anon type="place"/> me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we were in bed</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0208">just chatting and getting ready for sleep and stuff and then someone opened my door without asking like without knocking or anything like yo <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I was like who is this? and they were like it's a secret it's a secret and then left again and I was just like what the actual fuck like that's really rude and I was like I know that I hadn't</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0202" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just just wait a second I want to ask you something go on</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0208">and like I know that I hadn't been loud cos we were talking we were whispering we weren't drunk at all so I know we hadn't woken them up I was just like</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0208">what are they doing? like I could have been asleep right now</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0202">could have been naked you could have just got out of the shower or anything</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0208">but I don't I didn't recognise the voice it was really weird <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like who was that? and I was like I don't know I know for a fact it wasn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1191" who="S0202">yeah cos then you know their voices don't you?</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0208">yeah and it I don't think it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> either cos I know his voice</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0208">it's quite distinctive I was just like who is this person? it's really weird</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0202">erm sorry erm how did it go at the office have you got everything that you need?</u>
<u n="1196" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">er yeah just fucking annoying</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0202">why?</u>
<u n="1198" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">well I only had time to get there and back and that's all I done</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="1200" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0202">well how how long have you been gone?</u>
<u n="1202" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">er an hour and a bit just to drive there and back</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0202">really? that's stupid <pause dur="short"/> with traffic?</u>
<u n="1204" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="1206" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">and then my fucking phone just the data just disappeared so I needed the sat nav to go somewhere somewhere else and it just died it just won't come back on so fuck knows anyway I'm gonna go and cook some food</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0202">yeah alright then well well just wait two minutes and I'll come and do it</u>
<u n="1208" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no I just wanna start it myself alright</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0202">right alright then</u>
<u n="1210" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you can join me whenever you're ready</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0202">alright bye</u>
<u n="1212" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">bye then</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0202">erm <pause dur="short"/> well that's bang out of order that's why I started locking my door because</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0202">like it only happened three or four times but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s kept coming into my room and shouting</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0202" trans="overlap">or like they'd like push my door open and run away or whatever and that's why now every time I go to bed I lock the door</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0202">like</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0208">well one night a few weeks ago everyone was pre-drinking in our flat and I was just on Skype to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like my door wasn't locked cos you know I just thought people were like respectful and stuff</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0208">and then I just heard a girl like running down the corridor like backwards and forwards and she was screaming and she was like let's check whose doors are open and I was like <pause dur="short"/> what? what? like why would you do that that's so inconsiderate like seriously you're a grown up now act like one so I went and locked my door straight away I was like there's no way I'm having some blonde probably bimbo in my bedroom</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0208">pissing me off <pause dur="short"/> and it was like midnight or something and I was like they've got to be leaving soon so I just locked the door got on with it kept up with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and then I heard banging on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s door and it opening and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was shouting like what are you doing what are you doing? and like could hear it was him</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0208">and they were just like oh calm down calm down and he was like get out and I was just like that's so rude at midnight he wasn't going out he could have been asleep for all they all they know</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0208">it's like why do people do that and why do they think that's okay?</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0202">it's cos it's all their friends like this is</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0208" trans="overlap">so immature</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0202">the all of them are just so rude and immature it's none of them have been away from home they you know they're all so immature that they don't know how to act around people</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0202">and they think it's okay that you can just go and do that well actually no it's not and that's why I lock my door and I had a go at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for it because I was like look that is out of order I'm not being funny or anything but this is my room this is my personal space if I invite you in here then you're lucky to be here because you know this is my space it's not a shared space and I don't appreciate people running in my room at half one in the morning who I don't know who I've never met before shouting oi because they think it's funny it's like no have some</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0208" trans="overlap">it's not funny</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0202" trans="overlap">respect and nuance about you and you know</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0208">I just don't understand how people can do that like if you're drunk fair enough sometimes you don't realise what you're doing but even when I'm drunk I still what's right and what's wrong</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0202">I will never go and like do that unless it like your door and I knew you'd been out <trunc>some</trunc> with someone else and then I'd be like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I'd probably come and knock on your door but</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0208">but you'd still knock</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0202">I'd still knock I wouldn't just walk in</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0208">no</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0202">it's just so rude like I don't understand why all them are so rude like I've never known anything like it <pause dur="short"/> it's like even <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <trunc>s</trunc> times before we put boundaries down he was rude like that</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0208">he was like he used to</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0202" trans="overlap">like</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0208" trans="overlap">walk into my bedroom in the middle of the night and I'm like</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and get in bed with you as well like that time he got in bed with me and you when we <trunc>w</trunc> it's like well what are you doing? no one's</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0208" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0202">invited you in why are you here?</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0208">but I did start locking my doors after that but then I stopped because I was just like I'll lock my door when I want privacy and stuff but I'm like this is my flat too I shouldn't have to lock myself in my bedroom like</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0208" trans="overlap">just to feel like I can have some private space</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0208">and like ever since we have put boundaries down with them lot and we've stopped hanging out with them like it doesn't generally happen</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0208">so I leave it unlocked cos I just think in case of a fire or something</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0208">it's just a bit safer</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0202">yeah no it's just so inconsiderate innit it's just like what are you doing really come on</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
