<text id="SGMM">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:01</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-31</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0482 S0483</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Life, family, work</topics>
		<activity>Talking while cooking.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0482">
				<exactage>37</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Guildford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Post Doc Researcher, Health Pyschologist</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Rudimentary; French -- almost  conversational</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0483">
				<exactage>37</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Bromsgrove</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Assessment Manager (Education)</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Rudimentary; German -- Rudimentary; Spanish -- Rudimentary</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0483">how was erm <pause dur="short"/> how was looking after the girls?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0482">yeah fine yeah they were <pause dur="short"/> they were on quite good form generally</u>
<u n="3" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0482">they went a bit loopy when erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came</u>
<u n="5" who="S0483">yeah was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> joining in much was he able to enjoy?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0482">well poor guy he's sort of in-between worlds isn't he?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0483">yeah yeah too too young for the too old for the young ones and young for the yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0482" trans="overlap">he was more he was more of an adult I think when basically like we did them we we sort of got them out in the garden a little bit and gave them a erm a <unclear/> treasure hunt which is</u>
<u n="9" who="S0483" trans="overlap">oh lovely they like that yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0482" trans="overlap">yeah it's a a nice and easy one</u>
<u n="11" who="S0483">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0482">without any erm just literally like we went and hid the <unclear/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0482">and erm you know and in fact it was good that they they liked it they enjoyed it and stuff but erm er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> saw one of them and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> stopped and said no no let them find it</u>
<u n="15" who="S0483">ah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0482">and it was like he had to come and like ah I can't join in in anything so it's it</u>
<u n="17" who="S0483" trans="overlap">ah that's rubbish isn't it? yeah no that is rubbish</u>
<u n="18" who="S0482">it is tough though because at the same time</u>
<u n="19" who="S0483">no you know when there's that many to <trunc>p</trunc> find you've got to let the older ones find things haven't you? ah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0482">he's not really the older one he's like he is an adult really I mean it terms of</u>
<u n="21" who="S0483">no he's not oh come on</u>
<u n="22" who="S0482">no I mean in terms of compared to them</u>
<u n="23" who="S0483">yeah I know but even so you know</u>
<u n="24" who="S0482">he's in the kitchen talking to us</u>
<u n="25" who="S0483" trans="overlap">he's still allowed I think he's still allowed to find something</u>
<u n="26" who="S0482">it's quite sweet he arrived er early cos his mum dropped him off</u>
<u n="27" who="S0483">oh right oh really <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0482">yeah so I cos I saw somebody walking down the drive and I thought oh right it's them but then didn't see a car so I thought oh okay and then I saw his mum and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> out the front door so I thought well I I've seen him now I can't you know can't I I didn't know if they deliberately were waiting there cos he</u>
<u n="29" who="S0483">no well I don't know yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0482">you know but</u>
<u n="31" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and did erm food go down well?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0482">yeah it did actually yeah it was good they seemed to like the sort of things <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0483">well that's er</u>
<u n="34" who="S0482">yeah I fed them twice</u>
<u n="35" who="S0483">really? oh that's really good no that's lovely that's good</u>
<u n="36" who="S0482" trans="overlap">well yeah I think you know we both figured that</u>
<u n="37" who="S0483">absolutely yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0482" trans="overlap">they're going to eat well they didn't have anything to do at home</u>
<u n="39" who="S0483">yeah no that's lovely I'm really I'm really pleased</u>
<u n="40" who="S0482" trans="overlap"><unclear/> for the day I just did then a very straightforward dinner</u>
<u n="41" who="S0483">no but it's it's really nice to have you know erm yeah hang out and cook together that's good excellent you did you erm work much over the weekend?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0482">erm well I did probably about <pause dur="long"/> three or four hours in the evenings Friday night Saturday night maybe maybe more closer to three</u>
<u n="43" who="S0483">right okay well bless you yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0482">you know I I really didn't want to be doing it</u>
<u n="45" who="S0483">no of course not I know I know who does?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0482">cos you sort of you know tired and all the rest of it but I so I ended up having quite a late night cos I didn't want to do it so after work you know I haven't really eaten and so I I had some food and then er and the sort of watched a film you know</u>
<u n="47" who="S0483">was that the only thing you watched just that Batman?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0482">no I watched erm Serenity</u>
<u n="49" who="S0483">oh no I told you I wanted to watch that again</u>
<u n="50" who="S0482">really? oh right</u>
<u n="51" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yes you do</u>
<u n="52" who="S0482">well I was I</u>
<u n="53" who="S0483">you were taking liberties you were</u>
<u n="54" who="S0482">I'm not</u>
<u n="55" who="S0483">you are</u>
<u n="56" who="S0482">I was looking through erm what was available on Amazon</u>
<u n="57" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0482">and erm you know it was just really I've either seen or the good stuff or haven't seen all the other stuff cos it wasn't any good I didn't really find many things that I hadn't seen that I'd wanted to see or things that <pause dur="short"/> you know you know what it's like with Amazon you can look so quickly at the IMDB rating and that's quite handy</u>
<u n="59" who="S0483">yeah no that's fair enough that's fair enough so erm I've had an answer about erm er tiles erm he says have we got concrete floors so you're using any non-combustible tile but I think I think actually now I remember you sort of said you can put more or less anything down because you know it's already on the tile so I think I think</u>
<u n="60" who="S0482" trans="overlap">okay so well it's essentially double tile they'll be a bit that isn't double tiled</u>
<u n="61" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah no I I think we'll erm I think we'll just go and get you some things</u>
<u n="62" who="S0482">no no let's check though</u>
<u n="63" who="S0483">well well the thing is everything I buy from those places I can take back anyway so I can just buy for <unclear/> and then you know</u>
<u n="64" who="S0482" trans="overlap">no no I know but but not all of it us some of it will be on carpet</u>
<u n="65" who="S0483">yeah but I mean we're talking a fraction we're talking and inch so</u>
<u n="66" who="S0482">okay but if but technically that might be</u>
<u n="67" who="S0483">we'll see er er well I do when when he was looking at it he didn't seem to think it was a problem erm so you know</u>
<u n="68" who="S0482">yeah I know I saw it <pause dur="short"/> there's no photos of the inside</u>
<u n="69" who="S0483">how big is it?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0482">he said it's like really well but I mean they are they're grimy now it's probably one of those things</u>
<u n="71" who="S0483">how did you know about it what have you been doing?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0482">no I just I just looked at it erm <pause dur="short"/> yesterday? saw what it was like we only had four photos yeah so there was like an exceptionally well renovated three bedroom</u>
<u n="73" who="S0483" trans="overlap">well that's Bush for you Bush yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0482" trans="overlap">house and like okay can I see the house?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0483">yeah Bush are like that though aren't they don't bother doing those things</u>
<u n="76" who="S0482">I know and it's really hard to fathom out the pictures so if a <trunc>ga</trunc> of like couldn't quite work out what's what there okay and then there's a picture of a field which isn't part of the property which is</u>
<u n="77" who="S0483">oh no I think that's the fence</u>
<u n="78" who="S0482">what?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0483">that fence look like here</u>
<u n="80" who="S0482" trans="overlap">yeah yeah but like yeah but okay</u>
<u n="81" who="S0483">and then a picture of the</u>
<u n="82" who="S0482">and it's like okay where's that?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0482">if you're going to go on about how great the house is inside</u>
<u n="85" who="S0483">yeah where's the plan? oh it's a teeny bedroom that's not a bedroom <pause dur="long"/> that's tiny five foot five is the dimension</u>
<u n="86" who="S0482">that's tiny</u>
<u n="87" who="S0483">that's smaller than</u>
<u n="88" who="S0482">that's really tiny</u>
<u n="89" who="S0483">that's smaller than</u>
<u n="90" who="S0482">one point six jeez that's er that's like shorter than you</u>
<u n="91" who="S0483">yeah I know that's what I'm saying like you <pause dur="short"/> you'd get a bed in there and that's it you won't be able to open the door mm oh well <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't think I want it</u>
<u n="92" who="S0482">good job the erm the one that <unclear/> early you'll get nothing at it's still the same you know I mean I I guess if I was in their shoes I guess you you'd wait to see what the best offers were and then make a decision you know?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0482">you probably don't want to go on your first offer do you?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0483">no <pause dur="long"/> no that's fair enough</u>
<u n="96" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0483">so I'll erm I'll just er</u>
<u n="98" who="S0482">do you want a can of something?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0483">I don't know what are you going to have to drink?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0482">a can of something</u>
<u n="101" who="S0483">a can of something? er yeah I'll have a fizzy water please <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0482">run out of diet coke <pause dur="long"/> it's cold enough out there really</u>
<u n="103" who="S0483">yeah it is <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="104" who="S0482">oh erm could you put some rice on?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0483">ah yes okay yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0482" trans="overlap">cos we don't have noodles</u>
<u n="107" who="S0483">no we were going to do noodles so I don't need to</u>
<u n="108" who="S0482">have we got noodles?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0483">yeah I ah I said to you that I got loads of noodles they were on cheap it's Chinese New Year</u>
<u n="110" who="S0482">oh right cool oh they're the meaty ones as well that's nice <pause dur="long"/> do you want to smell my do you want to smell some fish sauce?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0483">oh that's horrible er</u>
<u n="112" who="S0482">ah rank oh jeez</u>
<u n="113" who="S0483">oh god</u>
<u n="114" who="S0482">so many shades of grey</u>
<u n="115" who="S0483">gone off my food now <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0482">fry these fair a bit <pause dur="long"/> yeah we should get coriander by default <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0483">so erm did you <pause dur="short"/> you did erm swimming lesson presumably yesterday?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0483">that go alright?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0482">yeah yeah it was good I invited <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> round <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0483">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0482">em round possibly the weekend after next</u>
<u n="123" who="S0483">er weekend after next oh er I've <pause dur="short"/> er I'm supposed to have erm <pause dur="short"/> been in contact with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum she contacted me and said oh yes yes let's fix a date and then I've forgotten again drat I hate it when that happens</u>
<u n="124" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0483">something just drops off your radar and then you're you know you're being rude <pause dur="short"/> never mind <pause dur="short"/> oh well</u>
<u n="126" who="S0482">yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> what am I doing here?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0483">that's interesting cos I logged on to er Facebook when I was at my sister's on her thing you get an alert and it says I logged on for your account's been logged into and it just says near <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> was it you?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0482">er okay cos it's on a device you don't normally do it?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0483">yeah yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> er right <pause dur="long"/> so that's true</u>
<u n="130" who="S0482">so did you see anyone else when you went down? just seeing your sister?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0483">no no no no no no no <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0482">anyone on the man front?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0483">no not really no no no no no that cat's going crazy again what's up with you? oh dear oh he's got wet feet as well oh <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> psst come here <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> have you seen that he's left a massive <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="134" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0483">ah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0482">ah he can dry his feet on the carpet</u>
<u n="137" who="S0483">ah <pause dur="short"/> yeah well he's not on the carpet he's on our sofa</u>
<u n="138" who="S0482">yeah hopefully not our new sofa <pause dur="short"/> I think I think it'll work fine I think you know it's difficult to imagine it if we don't have it yet</u>
<u n="139" who="S0483">no that's true where's the erm when's half-term?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0482">I don't know should be up on the</u>
<u n="141" who="S0483">yeah hold on a second erm I think it was the twelfth but er <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> fifteenth no that's fine</u>
<u n="142" who="S0482">why?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0483">I was just erm gonna go and see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm on Friday the twelfth</u>
<u n="144" who="S0482"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0483"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0482">why?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0483">cos she's coming to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0482">no I mean is it oh right yeah yeah yeah so <pause dur="short"/> er but I'm not</u>
<u n="149" who="S0483">well</u>
<u n="150" who="S0482">oh I see in in the daytime</u>
<u n="151" who="S0483">yes yes</u>
<u n="152" who="S0482" trans="overlap">oh Monday's a <unclear/> I'd like to it'd be nice to see her</u>
<u n="153" who="S0483">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0482">how come she's here?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0483">erm</u>
<u n="156" who="S0482">just sort of catching up with people?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I dunno I shall put <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0482">bit of fish sauce <pause dur="long"/> er we should really call her by her proper name cos she's not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is she?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0483" trans="overlap">still <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>ye</trunc> ah yeah yeah true</u>
<u n="160" who="S0482"><vocal desc="laugh"/> sauce?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0483">yeah erm so <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0482">yeah shall we sit down and sort out CP tonight?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0483">erm I don't know <pause dur="long"/> I I really don't know I to be honest I'd rather just sit sit down in front of the TV and not doing anything I'm quite tired</u>
<u n="164" who="S0482">I know but it's just I'm gonna have to work like I'm choosing not to work today</u>
<u n="165" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0482">erm and you know this week there's a clash of deadlines I can't really afford so it's fine but we risk losing you know spaces for things just saying <pause dur="long"/> the longer we leave it cos you know what it's like we we did it quite far in advance</u>
<u n="167" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah I know I know I know I know</u>
<u n="168" who="S0482">when is it? oh we're doing it bit later on April?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0483">er yeah yeah yeah but</u>
<u n="170" who="S0482">okay but still probably</u>
<u n="171" who="S0483">yeah yeah but I mean I'm not I'm not interested in doing that much anyway</u>
<u n="172" who="S0482">fair enough well I know but I thought the things we did last time actually worked really well</u>
<u n="173" who="S0483">yeah some of them did and some of them didn't you know?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0482">well what didn't?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0483">well the entertainment thing was fine but I don't necessarily want to do that again and the oh have I got a drink?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0482">you said something about fizzy water?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0482">right this is never fizzy do you want fresh fizzy water?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0483">yeah thing is I <trunc>no</trunc> I want water that is fizzy</u>
<u n="180" who="S0482">okay</u>
<u n="181" who="S0483">as you seem to have gone out and got yourself a drink and not thought about me</u>
<u n="182" who="S0482" trans="overlap">sorry I didn't really I thought</u>
<u n="183" who="S0483">no that's fine that's not a problem <pause dur="short"/> just when someone says what do you want to drink you kind of expect a drink at the end of it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0482">sorry I thought you'd sort of said oh I'll just have fizzy water like it was there or something okay</u>
<u n="185" who="S0483">right yeah I'll do it myself</u>
<u n="186" who="S0482" trans="overlap"><unclear/> on the tick</u>
<u n="187" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0482">although not <unclear/> ooh there you go</u>
<u n="189" who="S0483">cheers right so anyway do you want to watch that film tonight?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0482">I still don't know what it's about</u>
<u n="191" who="S0483">erm I dunno a man had some something bad and then he becomes good is it that?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0482">well yes I suppose</u>
<u n="193" who="S0483">let me let me check</u>
<u n="194" who="S0482">well IDMB it or something</u>
<u n="195" who="S0483">I can't remember what it's called erm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0482">I think I did IMDB it when I saw it</u>
<u n="197" who="S0483">it's something like it's got a number in it like</u>
<u n="198" who="S0482">oh it's to do with erm like Helsinki or something</u>
<u n="199" who="S0483">yeah maybe</u>
<u n="200" who="S0482">no it was like erm not Iceland but somewhere Sweden or Norway?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0483">certainly it's certainly er Scandi erm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0482">is it about a murder?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0483">my <trunc>pa</trunc> maybe a murder erm I don't know literally I I'm I know it's supposed to be good whatever it is <pause dur="short"/> let's see so it is is it something like Reykjavik or not Reykjavik er Oslo thirty first of August</u>
<u n="204" who="S0482" trans="overlap">exactly that's what yeah something to do with</u>
<u n="205" who="S0483">okay so it says everybody deserves a second change Oslo August thirty-first is about one man's past mistake and his last chance for salvation it's described as a staggering work of genius</u>
<u n="206" who="S0482"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0482">okay</u>
<u n="209" who="S0483">so I mean there you are you know</u>
<u n="210" who="S0482">don't raise my expectations</u>
<u n="211" who="S0483">well no I mean you know it's got four stars</u>
<u n="212" who="S0482" trans="overlap">staggering genius</u>
<u n="213" who="S0483">from everyone er seven point six out of ten on IMDB that's not brilliant is it?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0482" trans="overlap">well pretty good well yeah for a foreign film cos they're biased</u>
<u n="215" who="S0483">recovering <trunc>drud</trunc> <trunc>addit</trunc> <trunc>re</trunc>recovering drug addicts I'm trying to find out how long this thing is there's only so much of that we can take er rehab clinic yes one hour thirty-five minutes it's mercifully short Norwegian</u>
<u n="216" who="S0482" trans="overlap">can I see it sorry?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0483">ouch</u>
<u n="218" who="S0482">sorry</u>
<u n="219" who="S0483">er yeah so oh er there there's one customer review er on Amazon an excellent film I nearly gave up on it at the beginning but I stuck with it very thought-provoking and moving oh tissues at the ready then so there we are that's what we've to sounds fun doesn't it?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0482">sounds like a classic Sunday</u>
<u n="221" who="S0483">sounds uplifting well you know if we start it soon we might have time to top it off with comedy if it's gonna be that depressing it might need a little something to er</u>
<u n="222" who="S0482">don't think we've got time for a film and comedy</u>
<u n="223" who="S0483">we have it's only an hour and a half and it's only eight o'clock</u>
<u n="224" who="S0482">oh as in like a comedy</u>
<u n="225" who="S0483">yeah a half-hour one</u>
<u n="226" who="S0482">cos I put some I put some sort of comedy shows on our watchlist which I think we should definitely attempt to watch</u>
<u n="227" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0482">yeah?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0483">yeah maybe depends what they are</u>
<u n="230" who="S0482">by the tone of your voice</u>
<u n="231" who="S0483">it depends if they're any good</u>
<u n="232" who="S0482">well they were like comedians that we would like</u>
<u n="233" who="S0483">right okay</u>
<u n="234" who="S0482">Sean Lock Eddie Izzard</u>
<u n="235" who="S0483">are they short?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0482">well no they're like they're shows</u>
<u n="237" who="S0483">oh I see right oh</u>
<u n="238" who="S0482" trans="overlap">they're probably like they're like you know releases for probably a whole show in a tour erm there was another guy I think we've we've quite enjoyed found him quite funny forgotten what his name is and er Hunter D Thompson no Hunter S Thompson Reginald D Hunter whatever his name is</u>
<u n="239" who="S0483">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0482">he's one we</u>
<u n="241" who="S0483">yeah no it all sounds</u>
<u n="242" who="S0482">did we go and see oh no we didn't see him in <unclear/> but you know</u>
<u n="243" who="S0483">all sounds good all sounds positive</u>
<u n="244" who="S0482">basically</u>
<u n="245" who="S0483">no I was watching erm Tracy Ullman's show erm just a sketch show I don't know if we've seen some of her stuff before but it was quite it was quite funny there was a couple of sort of good you know characters so I've seen episode three so we could watch episode one and two tonight they've got erm and American couple that are you know obviously on holiday here and and generally sort of going into everywhere sort of saying oh my god it's so quaint it's so amazing you know look looking at all this naff stuff erm <pause dur="short"/> so that's quite quite a good sketch <pause dur="short"/> erm I think you have to see it</u>
<u n="246" who="S0482">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you'd like it though no it is</u>
<u n="248" who="S0482">good</u>
<u n="249" who="S0483">I'd watch it again so I was nattering through it so</u>
<u n="250" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0483">if you like the first and second one I'd happily watch the third one with you</u>
<u n="252" who="S0482" trans="overlap">that's the problem with watching anything with that's the thing that annoys me is like when when your sister comes we'll often spend a lot of time watching TV when I would normally want to just chat</u>
<u n="253" who="S0483">mm</u>
<u n="254" who="S0482">but then you just chat through TV but not about anything</u>
<u n="255" who="S0483">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we remember</u>
<u n="256" who="S0482" trans="overlap">so I'm there going well I'm either going to watch this or join in the chat</u>
<u n="257" who="S0483">we're quite working class</u>
<u n="258" who="S0482">er you're not working class</u>
<u n="259" who="S0483">well it's a working-class habit isn't it?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0482">you're an aspiring working-class person</u>
<u n="261" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well you know if I was that aspiring I wouldn't be talking in front of the TV would I?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0482">well it's what people do</u>
<u n="263" who="S0483" trans="overlap">hang on a minute hang on a minute how many packets are you doing here?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0482">three I always do three</u>
<u n="265" who="S0483" trans="overlap">mm mm go on then</u>
<u n="266" who="S0482">check erm yeah but like you know Gogglebox has normalised talking through TV</u>
<u n="267" who="S0483">well you basically well no it I think it shows the quality of the TV you're watching if you're watching something really decent if you were watching a decent Scandi murder then we're not going to be talking through it are we?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0482">yeah but often we are watching things that you have to pay attention and then you do oh I don't know what's going on and it's like because you were talking</u>
<u n="269" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no no <vocal desc="laugh"/> once or twice once or twice that's happened but mainly we just watch something crap and then you can talk through it</u>
<u n="270" who="S0482" trans="overlap">yeah I agree on something like that yeah but <pause dur="short"/> sure</u>
<u n="271" who="S0483">oh my gosh <vocal desc="yawn"/> <pause dur="short"/> I'm really tired <pause dur="long"/> garden looking alright out the back <pause dur="short"/> have you done it <unclear/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0482" trans="overlap">is that a question or?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0483" trans="overlap">well I don't well I don't know just because erm you know I haven't really been out there a while so</u>
<u n="274" who="S0482">yeah it's fine</u>
<u n="275" who="S0483">fence holding?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0482">just about yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0483">it's a bit bulgy at the top isn't it?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0482" trans="overlap">looking a little bit</u>
<u n="279" who="S0483">I know</u>
<u n="280" who="S0482">but it's very low that strut</u>
<u n="281" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I know I know I know I know</u>
<u n="282" who="S0482">erm but but the fact that it's low means it's out of the way</u>
<u n="283" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0482">erm no I think the garden's fine I did a tiny bit of weeding</u>
<u n="285" who="S0483">did you? where?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0482">yeah check me out</u>
<u n="287" who="S0483">I know</u>
<u n="288" who="S0482">around the erm <pause dur="short"/> the place where we've put those er chippings</u>
<u n="289" who="S0483" trans="overlap">oh yes yeah yeah I saw those yeah I ignored it yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0483">fair enough yeah I mean they weren't weeds they were erm like bulbs sort of</u>
<u n="292" who="S0482" trans="overlap">yeah grass I think</u>
<u n="293" who="S0483">no I think it was <trunc>wu</trunc> bulbs</u>
<u n="294" who="S0482" trans="overlap">I think it was grass actually</u>
<u n="295" who="S0483" trans="overlap">but it doesn't matter you know whatever it was it's wasn't meant to be there</u>
<u n="296" who="S0482" trans="overlap">you know when like grass is deprived of of er sun</u>
<u n="297" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0482">it goes like really thick and</u>
<u n="299" who="S0483">yeah no they they were they were bulbs but it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="300" who="S0482">they weren't bulbs</u>
<u n="301" who="S0483">they would have been I looked at them</u>
<u n="302" who="S0482">they weren't bulbs</u>
<u n="303" who="S0483">that's it it's not a thick grass</u>
<u n="304" who="S0482" trans="overlap">they were like they were multiple no</u>
<u n="305" who="S0483">yeah yeah I know I know</u>
<u n="306" who="S0482">okay then they're not a bulb I've ever seen</u>
<u n="307" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah but they're quite</u>
<u n="308" who="S0482" trans="overlap">a new bulb maybe I found a new species of bulb</u>
<u n="309" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no they come up like when they come up blind like that when they come up fully</u>
<u n="310" who="S0482">okay maybe but</u>
<u n="311" who="S0483">you know basically they've just spent too long trying to find their way out of the ground</u>
<u n="312" who="S0482" trans="overlap">I didn't it didn't feel like I was pulling anything big up</u>
<u n="313" who="S0483">no no no no no I know but bulbs are you know some bulbs are big some bulbs are small</u>
<u n="314" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0483">they'll have probably been erm er <vocal desc="misc"/> er what have we got down there loads of bluebells and things looks a bit like that</u>
<u n="316" who="S0482">maybe yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0483">but anyway it doesn't matter it was you know I would have pulled them up myself had I had more time yesterday</u>
<u n="318" who="S0482">oh do you think some er pineapple?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0483">oh yeah there is yeah yeah yeah bung that in</u>
<u n="320" who="S0482">chuck chop that in? has it it's not been there for months?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0483">no no no it's only been there for two days sound good</u>
<u n="322" who="S0482"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I like the fact we're both pineapple is one of those things you go ooh</u>
<u n="323" who="S0483">ooh yeah well it's exotic isn't it?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0482">it's exotic <pause dur="short"/> okay shall I just chuck it all in?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0483">erm yeah I guess so</u>
<u n="326" who="S0482">well there's only two two rings not exactly a crazy <pause dur="short"/> crazy thing</u>
<u n="327" who="S0483">two two rings no I think two rings is a good amount of pineapple <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0482">so it's a little bit random this curry I'm not gonna put in the erm I'll put in these bits of broccoli but I'm not going to put anything else</u>
<u n="329" who="S0483">okay fine</u>
<u n="330" who="S0482">like that cabbage is a bit sloppy</u>
<u n="331" who="S0483">er</u>
<u n="332" who="S0482">if I fried this cabbage there's no chance it would <unclear/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0483">yeah no no no no no no no no no</u>
<u n="334" who="S0482">no</u>
<u n="335" who="S0483">no you know best the last one you made was absolutely lovely I don't know what was different about that one compared to</u>
<u n="336" who="S0482">erm it had fish in it</u>
<u n="337" who="S0483">what did you do?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0482">as opposed to prawns</u>
<u n="339" who="S0483">oh yes that's right er what did we put in it?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0482" trans="overlap">we put erm put er</u>
<u n="341" who="S0483">oh that erm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0482">pollack</u>
<u n="343" who="S0483">pollack yeah that was amazing that was truly amazing yeah I liked that did you eat that mackerel? or is that still lingering</u>
<u n="344" who="S0483">no it's still I think we probably have to chuck it it's a shame</u>
<u n="345" who="S0482" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0482">well I dunno yeah I mean</u>
<u n="347" who="S0483">how far out of date is it? it's not that far out of date</u>
<u n="348" who="S0482" trans="overlap">that's the thing I wish they'd have you a kind of indication of how long their best before date is so you know what proportion of time</u>
<u n="349" who="S0483">well you have a use by and a best before so</u>
<u n="350" who="S0482">whatever cos used by</u>
<u n="351" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I no no no no but yeah I mean so I use by you're not supposed to go past but a best before you are supposed to go past if that would be a use by and something like that it will be a use by</u>
<u n="352" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0483">so and use by when? what was it twenty-ninth?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0482">twenty-seventh</u>
<u n="355" who="S0483">oh</u>
<u n="356" who="S0482">if it was like</u>
<u n="357" who="S0483">ooh</u>
<u n="358" who="S0482">you know if they like if you could if you bought it on the <trunc>tw</trunc> I don't know twenty-seventh of December</u>
<u n="359" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0482">and the use by the twenty-seventh of January</u>
<u n="361" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0482">then like three days over doesn't feel very much cos all of the variables of fridge <unclear/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0483">yeah yeah I see what you mean yeah yeah yeah no I no and you're right and your right they you can't get those with a good month on them</u>
<u n="364" who="S0482" trans="overlap">but sometimes it's like</u>
<u n="365" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0482">they only have two days on them</u>
<u n="367" who="S0483">you could easily buy that with a month on it</u>
<u n="368" who="S0482">yeah exactly so so</u>
<u n="369" who="S0483">so I think it's probably a wider window</u>
<u n="370" who="S0482" trans="overlap">that's what I mean</u>
<u n="371" who="S0483">well what are we on today? it's the twenty <trunc>si</trunc> twenty-seventh so twenty-eight twenty-nine thirty thirty-one you're only four days overdue so if you think about er maybe you could buy that with a month on it so it's like I don't know I can't actually do the maths but you know</u>
<u n="372" who="S0482">you can</u>
<u n="373" who="S0483">I can't</u>
<u n="374" who="S0482">three days how many days in a month?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0483">four days</u>
<u n="376" who="S0482">well okay just say three it's easier</u>
<u n="377" who="S0483">uh</u>
<u n="378" who="S0482">how many days in a month?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0483">twenty-eight in February twenty-nine this February</u>
<u n="380" who="S0482" trans="overlap">oh for god's sake right this is why you're bad at maths</u>
<u n="381" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> am I over thinking it?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0482">roughly thirty days</u>
<u n="383" who="S0483" trans="overlap">shall I say thirty okay yes</u>
<u n="384" who="S0482">okay</u>
<u n="385" who="S0483">is that well you can just tell me the answer if you want if you've got an answer in mind</u>
<u n="386" who="S0482">right three and thirty do they ring a bell in terms of</u>
<u n="387" who="S0483">yes ten yes</u>
<u n="388" who="S0482" trans="overlap">right yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0483">so ten percent</u>
<u n="390" who="S0482">ten percent overdue erm well</u>
<u n="391" who="S0483">if it was three days and and if you're saying it's four days then you just kind of go well it's a third more so probably thirteen percent</u>
<u n="392" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah we're heading we're heading into twenty percent overdue category aren't we?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0482">well we're closer to ten percent than twenty</u>
<u n="394" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well it sounds a bit ropey</u>
<u n="395" who="S0482">the <trunc>po</trunc>point is we're not going to eat it today</u>
<u n="396" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no exactly so it's gonna be a minimum of five</u>
<u n="397" who="S0482" trans="overlap">or Tuesday cos I'm going well you can eat it Tuesday but you probably won't on your own</u>
<u n="398" who="S0483">so we've got to eat it tomorrow</u>
<u n="399" who="S0482">yeah basically</u>
<u n="400" who="S0483">at at about fourteen percent over</u>
<u n="401" who="S0482">fine well it will be sixteen roughly sixteen percent if it's five days is it was a month but that's a that's an assumption we've made we don't know that that these this on in particular has a month on it</u>
<u n="402" who="S0483">oh god</u>
<u n="403" who="S0482">the smoked salmon has a lot longer on it</u>
<u n="404" who="S0483">oh this is scary stuff I think we should bin it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="405" who="S0482">yes yeah it's difficult</u>
<u n="406" who="S0483">it is difficult <pause dur="short"/> I mean the thing is we've got no one to ask advice from either like your mum would say eat it</u>
<u n="407" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0483">erm there's there's just no one is there? my parents wouldn't go near it there's no on for a balanced view</u>
<u n="409" who="S0482">I don't know who do we need</u>
<u n="410" who="S0483">I don't know</u>
<u n="411" who="S0482">your brother?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0483">Delia? no not my brother he doesn't know anything about things</u>
<u n="413" who="S0482">yeah you're right</u>
<u n="414" who="S0483">erm no I dunno</u>
<u n="415" who="S0482" trans="overlap">well no that's that's the irony about him he knows a lot about things</u>
<u n="416" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah I know but not about anything like that so I think to be on the safe side bin it</u>
<u n="417" who="S0482">yeah I'd be a bit much to make these phone calls</u>
<u n="418" who="S0483">maybe we could erm at least open it and sniff it</u>
<u n="419" who="S0482">we could do a Facebook poll that's the sort of thing</u>
<u n="420" who="S0483">yeah we could do no no open it sniff it taste it</u>
<u n="421" who="S0482" trans="overlap">okay yeah but then you have to have to hand an alternative meal option</u>
<u n="422" who="S0483">we can open it now let's do it</u>
<u n="423" who="S0482">no but then that's silly then you really do accelerate it's Berlin to hell</u>
<u n="424" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we <pause dur="short"/> could save it for harvest festival</u>
<u n="425" who="S0482" trans="overlap">you really live on the edge don't you? yeah we could give it to someone else that's a good plan</u>
<u n="426" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> fudge the date on it give it to old people's home</u>
<u n="427" who="S0482">yeah just write seventeen after the January date</u>
<u n="428" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0482">yeah they freezed this is like you know like vacuum packed you can just sort of</u>
<u n="430" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah the chances of doing a film and a er comedy are looking slimmer now</u>
<u n="431" who="S0482" trans="overlap">I know they are</u>
<u n="432" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0482">there's also an issue of do you know what I'm going to say?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0483">what?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0482">the eating</u>
<u n="436" who="S0483">oh eating and subtitles don't start this again ah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0482">it's</u>
<u n="438" who="S0483">do you want me to put well do you want me to put English thing on do you want it dubbed?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0482">no</u>
<u n="440" who="S0483">if you can't cope with a sub do you want a dub?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0482">no no dub I don't do dub</u>
<u n="442" who="S0483">hey maybe you can recycle those hey hey hey</u>
<u n="443" who="S0482">really?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0483">yeah no not that in that one in the in the plastic bags one</u>
<u n="445" who="S0482">well you put it in then?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0483">I will do not right now look it's even got a recycling symbol so it's bad plastic not currently recyclable but if you put it in with your things they recycle it</u>
<u n="447" who="S0482">well look it's the it it itself says it's not currently recyclable</u>
<u n="448" who="S0483">no</u>
<u n="449" who="S0482">didn't you just say?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0483">yeah but plastic bags aren't but they shred them down and they do something with them they're saying it's not currently recyclable in the sense that you can't put it in the recycling tub but they can't take them</u>
<u n="451" who="S0482">yeah they bin them</u>
<u n="452" who="S0483">no they shred them they shred them and make it into plastic matting or something</u>
<u n="453" who="S0482">okay I'm not I'm not like it was just cos I didn't think it was the right kind of you know polyurethane or whatever it's called</u>
<u n="454" who="S0483">I don't know any plastic they take according to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0482" trans="overlap">it's plastic film cos it's film it's not like plastic cartons</u>
<u n="456" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I don't know oh bin it then if you I don't know</u>
<u n="457" who="S0482" trans="overlap">no no no I don't want to be you know guilty of ruining the polar bears' habitat</u>
<u n="458" who="S0483">well you know <pause dur="long"/> I'm pretty sure it's alright <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0482">we're not back to the mackerel again are we?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no no <vocal desc="laugh"/> although the mackerel probably is alright oh this looks good oh where did that go?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0482">what?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0483">I dunno you splattered something somewhere</u>
<u n="463" who="S0482">splattered something somewhere <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0483">right okay I'll go and get that film set up</u>
<u n="465" who="S0482">I feel like I've forgotten an ingredient</u>
<u n="466" who="S0483">can I stop this from erm just pressing the cross there or do I have to sign in</u>
<u n="467" who="S0482">press the stop button</u>
<u n="468" who="S0483">oh hold on hold on hold on yeah I can see it I'm gonna to press that stop button</u>
<u n="469" who="S0482">no that's the cross</u>
<u n="470" who="S0483">alright hang on a minute stop oh no hang on</u>
<u n="471" who="S0482">don't press the cross</u>
<u n="472" who="S0483">don't press the cross stop button</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
