<text id="SGN8">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:11:30</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-05</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0192 S0198</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In my new flat, Sussex</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Study, tomorrow's plans, cooking, smoking, selling CDs, the internet, cataloguing, children, beer and cigarettes, master's degrees, linguistics, visiting home, family, Basque, jobs, South Korea, grammar, budgets, pheromones</topics>
		<activity>Relaxing after a day's studying</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0192">
				<exactage>28</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bedford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>English Language Instructor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2>Spanish</l2>
				<fls>Korean -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0198">
				<exactage>27</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Gillingham, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South Easten</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>27</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0198">so you've finished studying then?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0192">yeah I just finished</u>
<u n="3" who="S0198">mm good</u>
<u n="4" who="S0192">tired</u>
<u n="5" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><unclear/> slog yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0192">yeah how many hours have we done today?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0198">a few a good few</u>
<u n="8" who="S0192">what did we do like eight till ten thirty?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0198">yeah we did two and a half I'm sure we did like maybe six or seven hours today</u>
<u n="10" who="S0192">I reckon seven</u>
<u n="11" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I guess we've got to take that chance while we're erm while we're not actually at uni</u>
<u n="12" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah get as much research done as possible</u>
<u n="13" who="S0198" trans="overlap">make the most of this time</u>
<u n="14" who="S0192">what did?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0198">cos tomorrow we're not gonna really get chance are we?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0192">no no I don't think so</u>
<u n="17" who="S0198"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> gonna arrive at some point maybe <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so</u>
<u n="18" who="S0192">we're not gonna have any time to study tomorrow do you think?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0198">I don't know well I've gotta do some cleaning <pause dur="short"/> and sort myself out but I mean whilst I'm cleaning you can be studying probably</u>
<u n="20" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0198">we might have some time tomorrow it depends she hasn't told me the exact train she said she was checking and that was about two hours ago so I guess she just hasn't decided on</u>
<u n="22" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> hasn't booked it yet</u>
<u n="23" who="S0198">but either way I mean I guess we're gonna get up quite early but we need to take out like carry out rubbish I think</u>
<u n="24" who="S0192">yeah I'll take the that cardboard and the plastic to the bins round the corner</u>
<u n="25" who="S0198">and I'll take out the rubbish bag and then I wanna clean the bathroom and the kitchen and</u>
<u n="26" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="27" who="S0198">hoover and all that jazz but then it shouldn't take more than a couple of hours</u>
<u n="28" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but how long's that gonna take yeah?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0198">probably just a couple of hours but then we've got to go to the shop what are we having for lunch tomorrow? we haven't decided that</u>
<u n="30" who="S0192">I guess we should get everything done and then if we have time we can still</u>
<u n="31" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and then we have time yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0192">what are we having for lunch tomorrow?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I mean once we've taken out the rubbish yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0192">I don't know I haven't even thought about it</u>
<u n="35" who="S0198">probably shouldn't have are we freezing some of those sausages?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0198">we should do shouldn't we?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0192">I guess we could have some more sausages tomorrow and then freeze the rest</u>
<u n="39" who="S0198">freeze the rest maybe although that was some of our I mean even if it is our meat for the week we can still get it out to defrost</u>
<u n="40" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0198">during the week</u>
<u n="42" who="S0192">yeah might wanna freeze six of them did we get twelve?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0198">how many did we cook? three?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0192">yeah so cook another three tomorrow</u>
<u n="45" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0192">just have the same again if we go out grab a can of beans</u>
<u n="47" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0192">I don't mind beans eggs and sausages</u>
<u n="49" who="S0198">not much veg on the plate is there?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0192">beans are veg</u>
<u n="51" who="S0198">oh I don't know if they are <vocal desc="laugh"/> by the time they come out of a tomato tin can <pause dur="short"/> but that's fine</u>
<u n="52" who="S0192">it's high in protein it's not a</u>
<u n="53" who="S0198" trans="overlap">won't do it often</u>
<u n="54" who="S0192">it's not it's not a high carb meal it's a high protein meal</u>
<u n="55" who="S0198" trans="overlap">no no yeah it's a high protein meal</u>
<u n="56" who="S0192" trans="overlap">eggs sausages beans</u>
<u n="57" who="S0198">not much fruit or veg there veg helps break things down in the body doesn't it?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="59" who="S0198">no?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0192">helps pass things</u>
<u n="61" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0192">yeah fibre</u>
<u n="63" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0192">I mean we eat enough fruit</u>
<u n="65" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0192">erm I could do with upping my veg intake</u>
<u n="67" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we need to keep up our veg fried rices and vegetable soups which we've not haven't done yet</u>
<u n="68" who="S0192">that's cos we don't have all the ingredients yet</u>
<u n="69" who="S0198">no no well we've got most of the ingredients what are we missing for a soup?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so we've got soy sauce we didn't have any lemon or lime noodles</u>
<u n="71" who="S0198">we've got some dry noodles you bought some didn't you?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0192">mm some dry ones er we got everything then now</u>
<u n="73" who="S0198">yeah spring we bought spring onions especially for lunches</u>
<u n="74" who="S0192">do we have more spring onions?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0198">yeah we bought a pack didn't we?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0192">we'll do that for tomorrow then if that's what you want noodle soup</u>
<u n="77" who="S0198">noodle soup</u>
<u n="78" who="S0192">haven't got anything to go in it though</u>
<u n="79" who="S0198">ginger carrots</u>
<u n="80" who="S0192">no meat I mean</u>
<u n="81" who="S0198">broccoli oh no meat just have to have eggs and <unclear/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0192">put a sausage in it</u>
<u n="83" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0198">yeah that's just a waste of a sausage isn't it?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0192">it is just float it around in there</u>
<u n="86" who="S0198" trans="overlap">you don't need a just an egg you don't need meat in it make sure you have a nice meaty dinner</u>
<u n="87" who="S0192">mm I the problem is it gives it flavour</u>
<u n="88" who="S0198">yeah well</u>
<u n="89" who="S0192">it's not the fact that I need meat I don't need very much meat it's just the fat in it that gives the broth flavour <unclear/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0198">well enjoy the flavour without the fat</u>
<u n="91" who="S0192">yeah but even when I make tomato soup right that has two things of chicken stock in it</u>
<u n="92" who="S0198">yeah well then put some stock in it</u>
<u n="93" who="S0192" trans="overlap">like the meat gives flavour I could put some stock in it</u>
<u n="94" who="S0198">put vegetable stock in it or something</u>
<u n="95" who="S0192">do we have any vegetable stock?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0198">I don't know probably not <unclear/> got thrown away</u>
<u n="97" who="S0192">we've got beef stock at the minute</u>
<u n="98" who="S0198">yeah well put some beef stock in it that's what you want</u>
<u n="99" who="S0192">you want it beefy?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0198">whatever</u>
<u n="101" who="S0192">I mean I can do I might put a beef stock in it if you don't mind?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0198">no okay</u>
<u n="103" who="S0192">just makes it more flavoursome for me</u>
<u n="104" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0192">I don't need the actual meat just the the rendering <pause dur="short"/> the fat the gravy</u>
<u n="106" who="S0198">the the the gravy</u>
<u n="107" who="S0192">mm that lamb gravy you made was tasty</u>
<u n="108" who="S0198">ah that was really good linking the plate that's not something you do often is it?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0198">are we having a beer this evening?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0192">er yeah I want a beer do you want a beer?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0198">I'm tempted to have a beer and a cigarette now and then</u>
<u n="113" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you want your cigarette oh we're not doing very well at quitting are we?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and then <pause dur="short"/> no well I have <trunc>f</trunc> I never was addicted until I until I moved in here with you</u>
<u n="115" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0198">I was addicted but I wasn't I didn't smoke I was going days at home but</u>
<u n="117" who="S0192">I didn't smoke a lot but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got out those cigars</u>
<u n="118" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0192">so I smoked like pretty much a whole massive cigar with him</u>
<u n="120" who="S0198">I think erm I'm just gonna try and gradually break down the barriers and quit next week I'll take it even more seriously</u>
<u n="121" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0198">this week has been a bit of an interlude still the week before that I didn't even really smoke much I smoked on Friday night and then I smoked again when I came here</u>
<u n="123" who="S0192">that's good see I was smoking with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when I saw him</u>
<u n="124" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0192">and even my brother smokes from time to time so</u>
<u n="126" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0192">not easy</u>
<u n="128" who="S0198">no I feel like the the next week we need to go a couple of days without <pause dur="short"/> smoking</u>
<u n="129" who="S0192">what like anything?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0198">yeah I mean</u>
<u n="131" who="S0192">doesn't that happen in the third week?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0198">maybe <vocal desc="laugh"/> maybe we should test run it midweek next week just have a day on like Wednesday or something when oh no that's too stressful</u>
<u n="133" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0198">Friday Friday Thursday <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s coming so she smokes</u>
<u n="135" who="S0192">on a Friday?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0198">yeah why?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0192">Friday's my my good day it's the day I'm allowed to smoke Friday and Saturday</u>
<u n="138" who="S0198" trans="overlap">no it's not we're not at work anymore <pause dur="short"/> any day can be Friday although it is Friday so I'm gonna have a beer and smoke a rollie and then we've gotta count your CDs</u>
<u n="139" who="S0192">if that's alright?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0198">yeah I think I'd rather have a beer first though</u>
<u n="141" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0198">just to relax</u>
<u n="143" who="S0192">do you mind going through the CDs? or</u>
<u n="144" who="S0198">no I suppose not what are we doing exactly? just counting them? is there any purpose to what we're about to do?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0192">I've already told you A I want to count them B I wanna go through the CDs have a look at the CD</u>
<u n="146" who="S0198" trans="overlap">are you gonna catalogue them?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0192">it's as simple as is the case too damaged? is the CD too scratched?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0198">don't wouldn't it if we're gonna go through them wouldn't it be beneficial to start cataloguing them though?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0192">I mean yeah but that would take a lot longer</u>
<u n="150" who="S0198">well I mean otherwise we've got to do it all again</u>
<u n="151" who="S0192">I mean yeah but the first time you do it it's really quick it's just open the boxes have a look at the CD check the CD that one's fine put it in that box quickly quickly quickly</u>
<u n="152" who="S0198">but yeah I know but then I've gotta go back and do it all again rather than just</u>
<u n="153" who="S0192">well otherwise I'm cataloguing CDs that might be too damaged to sell</u>
<u n="154" who="S0198" trans="overlap">we don't have to do them we don't have to do them oh right well no you check it and if it's good you catalogue it if it's bad it goes in the bad pile</u>
<u n="155" who="S0192">but then I have to</u>
<u n="156" who="S0198">and we just we don't have to do them all tonight just</u>
<u n="157" who="S0192">that's more effort though isn't it?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0198" trans="overlap">mark the boxes but if that's the inevitable purpose of your CD doing this I don't what's the point in just what am I doing?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0192">it's even more detail than that though because</u>
<u n="160" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh no</u>
<u n="161" who="S0192">you've got to write down the ISBN number on the back</u>
<u n="162" who="S0198">oh</u>
<u n="163" who="S0192">so you don't really need to write down the details all you need to write down ISBN number and then you have to go to Amazon marketplace type it in and then it'll tell you the product</u>
<u n="164" who="S0198">oh any any number on the back?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0192">well yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0198">what number the ISBN?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0192">like the barcode number</u>
<u n="168" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0198">you'll type that into Amazon and it'll tell you what product it is?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah it'll tell you the product</u>
<u n="172" who="S0198">for any product</u>
<u n="173" who="S0192">pretty sure</u>
<u n="174" who="S0198">so if I grab a book off the shelf and type in it's number Amazon will tell me?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0192">pretty sure</u>
<u n="176" who="S0198">grab a book off the shelf I want to see this in action</u>
<u n="177" who="S0192">I mean I don't know if it'll work just on Amazon normal search</u>
<u n="178" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0192">but it on Amazon marketplace I'm pretty sure that's how you do it</u>
<u n="180" who="S0198">oh right is that where you go? how do you just go on Amazon marketplace?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0192">I don't remember haven't looked at it in a while alright you can try this ISBN then just try typing it in</u>
<u n="182" who="S0198">oh</u>
<u n="183" who="S0192">here zero dash</u>
<u n="184" who="S0198">zero dash</u>
<u n="185" who="S0192">five eight six</u>
<u n="186" who="S0198">five eight six</u>
<u n="187" who="S0192">dash</u>
<u n="188" who="S0198">dash</u>
<u n="189" who="S0192">two one seven seven four</u>
<u n="190" who="S0198">two one seven seven four</u>
<u n="191" who="S0192">dash six</u>
<u n="192" who="S0198">dash six two one seven seven four double it</u>
<u n="193" who="S0192">there you go</u>
<u n="194" who="S0198">woah it worked</u>
<u n="195" who="S0192">course it works it's a catalogue</u>
<u n="196" who="S0198">oh so that's just oh right yeah it's not this number though is it?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0192">that's the ISBN number</u>
<u n="198" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0192">that's what I said</u>
<u n="200" who="S0198">what does ISBN stand for exactly?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I don't know? google it</u>
<u n="202" who="S0198">what does ISBN stand for?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0192" trans="overlap">international something or other</u>
<u n="204" who="S0198">something bar number</u>
<u n="205" who="S0192">bar yeah bar number sounds about right <pause dur="short"/> iSBN definition or acronym description</u>
<u n="206" who="S0198">meaning whatever good <unclear>ol</unclear> the international standard book number</u>
<u n="207" who="S0192">there we go</u>
<u n="208" who="S0198">ah so the</u>
<u n="209" who="S0192">that was on books then what about CDs?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0198">yeah so it'll be ISCN</u>
<u n="211" who="S0192">I don't know</u>
<u n="212" who="S0198">international standard CD number</u>
<u n="213" who="S0192">have to see when we get a CD won't we?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0198">lets type C in see what happens <pause dur="short"/> acronym what does ISCN and international system for human citogenics no that's not right is it?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0192">I mean</u>
<u n="216" who="S0198">it probably is slightly different</u>
<u n="217" who="S0192">if you hold this and keep talking I'll go and see</u>
<u n="218" who="S0198">go and have a look at it</u>
<u n="219" who="S0192">yeah just have a quick look</u>
<u n="220" who="S0198">cos you've got a few CDs me dear</u>
<u n="221" who="S0192">we should draw these curtains now shouldn't we?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0198">yeah make it private in here</u>
<u n="223" who="S0192">yep double curtain</u>
<u n="224" who="S0198">gotta have it looking respectable we got we got upper class folk coming tomorrow</u>
<u n="225" who="S0192">oh don't scare me</u>
<u n="226" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0192">with our dodgy double curtains and our</u>
<u n="228" who="S0198">our <unclear>no</unclear> bed I don't care <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't mind they're <trunc>stu</trunc> well they they've been students too <pause dur="short"/> it's a nice flat I'm looking forward to having them come up and look at it</u>
<u n="229" who="S0192">first visitors at our</u>
<u n="230" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it's a good size I think I think the first place they were renting in <anon type="place"/> was considerably smaller</u>
<u n="231" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it was quite tiny toot</u>
<u n="233" who="S0192">okay I can just grab this little box</u>
<u n="234" who="S0198" trans="overlap">lets get the CDs out</u>
<u n="235" who="S0192">shall I?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0198">no that's my CDs but yeah alright then</u>
<u n="237" who="S0192">I mean they're our CDs aren't they?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0198" trans="overlap">our CDs sorry but I'm not <trunc>sa</trunc> sure if anything that good's there but yeah grab that box cos you're only looking for an example aren't you?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0192">yeah I'll just grab these too <unclear/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0198" trans="overlap">why are you grabbing so many? are you gonna start cataloguing them?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0192">maybe</u>
<u n="242" who="S0198">ah are you gonna do it with your computer? you want a spreadsheet do you?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0192">I wanted to know how many we had <pause dur="short"/> just I wanted to know how many CDs I had</u>
<u n="244" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0192">cos I've never counted</u>
<u n="246" who="S0198">I wonder if any of <trunc>th</trunc> them double up some of ours might be the same might they?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/> The Prodigy <pause dur="short"/> no it doesn't have an ISBN</u>
<u n="248" who="S0198">oh so how are you gonna type that in?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0192">I guess you can just search that number</u>
<u n="250" who="S0198">what the barcode? I don't know if that would work I don't know</u>
<u n="251" who="S0192">let's try one a bit more classic <pause dur="short"/> try this number</u>
<u n="252" who="S0198">okay who is it what which artist is it?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0192">I'll tell you after we've done it just to see if it works zero six</u>
<u n="254" who="S0198">oh hang on I've gotta get back on Amazon have I?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0198">just let me type that in first this computer is working infinitely better</u>
<u n="257" who="S0192">good</u>
<u n="258" who="S0198">is that correct? right zero six</u>
<u n="259" who="S0192" trans="overlap">zero six</u>
<u n="260" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0192">zero two five</u>
<u n="262" who="S0198">yeah three seven nine nine zero</u>
<u n="263" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="264" who="S0198">oh 0 seven</u>
<u n="265" who="S0192">zero six zero two five</u>
<u n="266" who="S0198">sorry it was picking up another number yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0192">it's picking up loads of numbers one seven</u>
<u n="268" who="S0198">one seven</u>
<u n="269" who="S0192">three two</u>
<u n="270" who="S0198">it's lost it</u>
<u n="271" who="S0192">zero</u>
<u n="272" who="S0198">zero</u>
<u n="273" who="S0192">one zero nine</u>
<u n="274" who="S0198">one zero nine it got a bit edgy in the</u>
<u n="275" who="S0192">yeah there we go</u>
<u n="276" who="S0198">oh <unclear/> right that's nice</u>
<u n="277" who="S0192">so all you have to do is type in those <unclear>things</unclear></u>
<u n="278" who="S0198"><unclear/> actually own CDs</u>
<u n="279" who="S0192">so look this one somebody's selling it for forty-four pence used</u>
<u n="280" who="S0198">ah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0192">great one</u>
<u n="282" who="S0198">well what were you gonna sell it for? I bet that's that person isn't it? under <trunc>su</trunc> under sells everyone</u>
<u n="283" who="S0192">undercuts everyone let's have a look warehouse deals seven hundred and sixty no that's one pound there you go Zoverstocks</u>
<u n="284" who="S0198">oh is that who does it?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0192" trans="overlap">forty-four pence</u>
<u n="286" who="S0198">Zoverstocks</u>
<u n="287" who="S0192">but this one's got free delivery so it's actually one pound seventy</u>
<u n="288" who="S0198">oh whereas they charge for the delivery</u>
<u n="289" who="S0192" trans="overlap">look how many sellings they have</u>
<u n="290" who="S0198">wow</u>
<u n="291" who="S0192" trans="overlap">over four million ratings</u>
<u n="292" who="S0198">wow that's crazy</u>
<u n="293" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0198">I've never seen so many on marketplace <pause dur="short"/> wow that's crazy</u>
<u n="295" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but it just means that I really can't sell my CDs very well</u>
<u n="296" who="S0198" trans="overlap">two total ratings fifty percent positive that'd be you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0198">that's your own personal number</u>
<u n="299" who="S0192">one good one crap</u>
<u n="300" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0192">if it's fifty percent positive and there's only two voters</u>
<u n="302" who="S0198">ah experience what happy memories <pause dur="short"/> probably</u>
<u n="303" who="S0192">but do you know what I mean though? If I don't</u>
<u n="304" who="S0198">oh that smells like my old bedroom that's really weird</u>
<u n="305" who="S0192">CD smells like it?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0198">yes</u>
<u n="307" who="S0192">I mean what's like DJ <unclear>Foo</unclear> surely something like I've got some music in here that's surely worth a little bit more can you type this one in?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> er what are the numbers? hang on bear with me one moment <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="309" who="S0192">you can just read it off yourself otherwise I'm just reading numbers</u>
<u n="310" who="S0198">yeah numbers yeah okay did you put that number in front before?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0192">what number?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0198">the five</u>
<u n="313" who="S0192" trans="overlap">five yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0198">you put the big number?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0198">will it be a lucky CD? <pause dur="short"/> two eight go</u>
<u n="317" who="S0192">one can hope</u>
<u n="318" who="S0198">ah Kaleidoscope oh two pound ninety-four</u>
<u n="319" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that's good somebody selling at two pound ninety-four used how much is it who's doing that? Zoverstocks again?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0198">mm so if you could sell it but how much does it cost you need to know how much one CD costs to send in the post</u>
<u n="321" who="S0192">yeah I know</u>
<u n="322" who="S0198">need to like take one and do a trial one</u>
<u n="323" who="S0192" trans="overlap">go and sell it to myself</u>
<u n="324" who="S0198">I assume like over a pound like as much as Amazon charges you postage or whatever</u>
<u n="325" who="S0192">some of these CDs are brand new really because</u>
<u n="326" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I know cos you never use them</u>
<u n="327" who="S0192">cos</u>
<u n="328" who="S0198">you upload them to an MP3 player</u>
<u n="329" who="S0192">yeah not the old ones but some of the later ones</u>
<u n="330" who="S0198">oh it's such a shame all these all the leaflets you get inside <pause dur="short"/> it's like a complete art form that we don't have any more</u>
<u n="331" who="S0192">I know</u>
<u n="332" who="S0198">ah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0192">do miss it to a certain degree but I mean what's the point?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0198">cor that almost looks like which country is that?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0192">we live abroad</u>
<u n="336" who="S0198">yeah I know</u>
<u n="337" who="S0192">are we gonna be able to take these with us? <pause dur="short"/> the only purpose is to have them on your wall and as I've said before my music taste developed so quickly <pause dur="short"/> that yeah I'm sure I'll always like these CDs but <pause dur="short"/> they're a bit outdated aren't they? just got a bunch of outdated CDs on your wall</u>
<u n="338" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0192">like how much is this one? Joanna Newsom Have One On Me</u>
<u n="340" who="S0198">ah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0192">it's a three disc</u>
<u n="342" who="S0198">I don't know</u>
<u n="343" who="S0192"><unclear>lovely</unclear> CD</u>
<u n="344" who="S0198">don't know how much it would be I've got some weird <unclear/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0192" trans="overlap">where's the ISBN on this one?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0198">don't know oh the cardboard one's always cool</u>
<u n="347" who="S0192">it literally doesn't have one</u>
<u n="348" who="S0198">doesn't want you to sell it</u>
<u n="349" who="S0192">it literally doesn't have one can you type it in? Joanna Newsom Have One On Me see what comes up</u>
<u n="350" who="S0198">wait erm is Joanna with an H or without an H?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0192"><trunc>Jo</trunc> without an H</u>
<u n="352" who="S0198">H or <unclear>no H</unclear></u>
<u n="353" who="S0192">no H</u>
<u n="354" who="S0198">Joanna Newsom</u>
<u n="355" who="S0192">oh there are some good CDs in here <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="356" who="S0198">now you're looking at them in the face you can't do it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0192">I know</u>
<u n="358" who="S0198">your babies my babies</u>
<u n="359" who="S0192" trans="overlap">what does that say? <pause dur="short"/> how much is that selling for?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0198"><unclear>bells</unclear> of Bengal</u>
<u n="361" who="S0192">see that was still selling for ten pounds</u>
<u n="362" who="S0198">yeah nobody's selling that</u>
<u n="363" who="S0192" trans="overlap">see that one's used somebody's selling some of these for twenty pounds</u>
<u n="364" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0192">see it depends on which version I've got <pause dur="short"/> see I reckon I've probably got some CDs in here that are worth a little bit</u>
<u n="366" who="S0198">bit yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0192">and then loads of CDs that are worth nothing</u>
<u n="368" who="S0198">nothing yeah dynamite records</u>
<u n="369" who="S0192" trans="overlap">dynamite records nine ninety-five</u>
<u n="370" who="S0198" trans="overlap">mm nobody's selling it to that <unclear>supler</unclear> then</u>
<u n="371" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="372" who="S0198">good fuck you</u>
<u n="373" who="S0192">there are certain discs that I think I have that like what's this one?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0198">Bells of Bengal so many cool CD covers I'd forgotten about look they make such an effort</u>
<u n="375" who="S0192">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0198">ah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0192">how much is just like tall</u>
<u n="378" who="S0198" trans="overlap">look how much material what the hell is this?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0192">Dave Gunn he's the guy from Depeche Mode</u>
<u n="380" who="S0198">oh that was one</u>
<u n="381" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><trunc>wha</trunc> <unclear/> this is clearly some of my CDs in here</u>
<u n="382" who="S0198">that one you got on a promo did you?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0192">probably</u>
<u n="384" who="S0198">most of these</u>
<u n="385" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah it says it on here</u>
<u n="386" who="S0198">yeah most of these are mine I think you probably gave that one to me to listen to and I never got round to it</u>
<u n="387" who="S0192" trans="overlap">can you check this one and just type in tall <unclear>aenema</unclear> and see how much that one goes for? <pause dur="short"/> bloody Bright Eyes ninety-nine P at least it's better than a penny I guess</u>
<u n="388" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> hang on</u>
<u n="389" who="S0192">that's not quite the right spelling see that's still going for a fiver</u>
<u n="390" who="S0198" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0192">and we've got two copies of those</u>
<u n="392" who="S0198">yeah have we?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0192">and potentially if you've got the older version here is look if you've got the tall two thousand and one version it's thirty-two quid</u>
<u n="394" who="S0198">yeah why is that?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so it depends which version you have cos they had different versions</u>
<u n="396" who="S0198">you checked yours your one didn't you? let me check I want to look at the paper nineteen ninety-six</u>
<u n="397" who="S0192">oh since</u>
<u n="398" who="S0198">that's the one you have isn't it?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0192">think so <pause dur="short"/> don't really know</u>
<u n="400" who="S0198">ah good old Bill Hicks on the front cover on the inside cover</u>
<u n="401" who="S0192">oh careful with the CDs</u>
<u n="402" who="S0198">but <unclear>that</unclear> is I mean it was second hand when I bought it though</u>
<u n="403" who="S0192">was it scratched?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0198">no it's alright I mean it's got markings</u>
<u n="405" who="S0192">see I guess we need to oh I do elfin <unclear>sadle</unclear></u>
<u n="406" who="S0198">oh it's such a nice cover oh one of my</u>
<u n="407" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/> fears</u>
<u n="408" who="S0198">this is what I liked oh Black Rebel Motorcycle Club</u>
<u n="409" who="S0192" trans="overlap">can we do Neutral Milk Hotel?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0198">that is fucked CD I remember that being fucked before</u>
<u n="411" who="S0192">what am I gonna do with all of these?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0198">oh it doubled up as an ashtray</u>
<u n="413" who="S0192">oh that's completely buggered yeah that's gone get rid of that</u>
<u n="414" who="S0198">no Bob Marley's alright <shift new="singing"/> one life <pause dur="short"/> let's get together and be alright <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0192"><shift new="singing"/> and be alright <shift new="normal"/> <unclear>mano negras</unclear> Spiritualize</u>
<u n="416" who="S0198">I've got a bunch of Prodigy got <unclear/> theirs</u>
<u n="417" who="S0192"><unclear/> the air</u>
<u n="418" who="S0198">stand and <unclear>Westwood</unclear> you gave me didn't really like that</u>
<u n="419" who="S0192">sorry</u>
<u n="420" who="S0198">that's alright Nina Simone that's again I bought off that stall</u>
<u n="421" who="S0192">the Stratosphere google this one</u>
<u n="422" who="S0198">Stratosphere</u>
<u n="423" who="S0192">yeah it's gotta be fairly obscure <pause dur="short"/> just wanna see if obscure means more money or if it just means presumably obscure means more money right?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0198">yeah I presume so it also means slower <pause dur="short"/> selling time perhaps</u>
<u n="425" who="S0192">or harder to sell</u>
<u n="426" who="S0198">are people still collecting CDs? I mean somebody's buying them</u>
<u n="427" who="S0192">somebody's unless everyone's just sitting there waiting for people to buy them?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0198">oh this album is used for four pound fifty-eight</u>
<u n="429" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="430" who="S0198">I take it you can't lie and say it's new? I mean how do they like you just say like new do you?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0192">well if it's not brand new out of the shops it's not new is it?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0198">yeah unless you're a shop</u>
<u n="433" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0198">but then are these people shops that are selling new CDs or what? cos surely they're not</u>
<u n="435" who="S0192">I guess they've never been opened <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0198">yeah so they just call it new</u>
<u n="437" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0198">you could lie couldn't you?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0192">I mean maybe with some of them maybe if I looked at it and thought that's brand new</u>
<u n="440" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I suppose you don't wanna get <pause dur="short"/> yeah you don't want to be getting a bad rating if you're gonna be selling a few of these online</u>
<u n="441" who="S0192">told me it was new but I mean this you know this one looks basically brand new</u>
<u n="442" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0192">it's probably been opened like two times provided there were no scratches on the CD at all</u>
<u n="444" who="S0198">at all</u>
<u n="445" who="S0192">that one's got a slight scratch</u>
<u n="446" who="S0198">it's a double</u>
<u n="447" who="S0192">what's that one?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0198"><unclear/> russ I wanna say that no I swear sometimes there'd be like secret things behind the</u>
<u n="449" who="S0192">oh yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0198">behind the casing and stuff like that</u>
<u n="451" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh careful try not to break them at this stage</u>
<u n="452" who="S0198"><shift new="singing"/> money money money <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0192">what do you think?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0198">I mean you're right if we're gonna keep I mean it's nice that they exist but are you going to <pause dur="short"/> digress back to using a CD player?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0192">I don't even own a CD player</u>
<u n="456" who="S0198">does that not have a CD drive on it?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0192">yeah I think it does</u>
<u n="458" who="S0198">there you go you've got the CD player but do things sound better on CD? they don't do they? they sound better digital pixies</u>
<u n="459" who="S0192">do you think it's worth the effort?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0198">not for a few quid</u>
<u n="461" who="S0192">but it kills a erm</u>
<u n="462" who="S0198">you feel like that's another</u>
<u n="463" who="S0192">there you go <pause dur="short"/> that's basically brand new look at that one Leo Sayer</u>
<u n="464" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0192">doesn't look used at all</u>
<u n="466" who="S0198">ah such good covers</u>
<u n="467" who="S0192">I reckon you could sell some of these as brand new you know</u>
<u n="468" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0192">cos I basically bought them burnt them and then put them in a CD box</u>
<u n="470" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and then you didn't touch them again</u>
<u n="471" who="S0192">didn't touch them</u>
<u n="472" who="S0198">I mean you looked over them a few times</u>
<u n="473" who="S0192">yeah had a quick look</u>
<u n="474" who="S0198">LCD Soundsystem I think you've got that on oh no it should save <unclear/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so I mean I'm tempted let's say <pause dur="short"/> I think what we need to do is erm <pause dur="short"/> basically document them all</u>
<u n="476" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="477" who="S0192">which ones are new which ones are used which ones are not sellable</u>
<u n="478" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="479" who="S0192">and then we need to check on Amazon and see what kind of money can we make from doing this</u>
<u n="480" who="S0198">mm and then</u>
<u n="481" who="S0192">is it worth it?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0198">calculate whether or not it's gonna make a profit</u>
<u n="483" who="S0192">yeah is it worth it?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0198">how much of a profit?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0192">basically</u>
<u n="486" who="S0198">when did we graduate? like</u>
<u n="487" who="S0192">two thousand and eight</u>
<u n="488" who="S0198">cor my parents have got aged since then look at my dad there he looks kinda chunky well definitely compared to now</u>
<u n="489" who="S0192">oh he does look fat doesn't he there?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0198" trans="overlap">he looks different <pause dur="short"/> yeah he looks quite rounded my mum looks younger too</u>
<u n="491" who="S0192">your mum definitely does look younger</u>
<u n="492" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="493" who="S0192">so do you</u>
<u n="494" who="S0198">I mean yeah but it wasn't that how many years ago was that? eight years?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0192">oh when we graduated just six years ago wasn't it?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0192">two thousand and eight</u>
<u n="498" who="S0198">is that all it's been? <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh that's taking care of my nan took its toll although my mum still looks good for her age she is fifty-seven now</u>
<u n="499" who="S0192">yeah she does look good</u>
<u n="500" who="S0198">so she looks fine</u>
<u n="501" who="S0192">maybe she looked better with brown hair?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0198">yeah dunno why she's going blonde</u>
<u n="503" who="S0192">no I'm not sure either</u>
<u n="504" who="S0198">but she likes it she likes it my hair not that's something <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to me actually cos there's a picture of my graduation photo the professional one up on the in the living room and she said to me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> why's <pause dur="short"/> why have you coloured your hair? and I was like I haven't coloured my hair this is my normal colour my natural colour she was like ah it's just in that photo it's very different I don't think my hair looked that much different but obviously she picks up on things kids pick up on things like that</u>
<u n="505" who="S0192">mm yeah they really do don't they?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0198" trans="overlap">much blonder in that picture she was like you look different</u>
<u n="507" who="S0192">they really do</u>
<u n="508" who="S0198">expecting me to look like a picture that was taken eight years ago</u>
<u n="509" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah why do you look different? <pause dur="short"/> cos time has passed how about these ones like Omar Rodriguez Lopez? do you wanna sell those?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0198">not really</u>
<u n="511" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="512" who="S0198">I wanna beer</u>
<u n="513" who="S0192">alright okay I'm struggling to get this back in the box which is kind of annoying now</u>
<u n="514" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I don't know if I do wanna count CDs <unclear/></u>
<u n="515" who="S0192">don't know if you do wanna what?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0198">count CDs</u>
<u n="517" who="S0192">well we're not going to are we? you already said so</u>
<u n="518" who="S0198">yeah we will do</u>
<u n="519" who="S0192">no we're not going to we'll document them another time I'm just worried about when we're gonna actually get time to do these things</u>
<u n="520" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I'll have a beer and then I might be quite happy to do it <pause dur="short"/> now's a good time to do it while we're chilling</u>
<u n="521" who="S0192">yeah I know</u>
<u n="522" who="S0198">let's have a beer and then we'll start processing them basically</u>
<u n="523" who="S0192">what by processing you mean writing them down? I didn't wanna do all of that tonight</u>
<u n="524" who="S0198">I guess we can count them then to give you a rough idea of everything is that what you wanna do?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0192">well there's no point in taking all the boxes out today either is there?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it won't take us that long <pause dur="short"/> what to count them?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0192">yeah there's just so many we're gonna have to put them back</u>
<u n="528" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and get them back out again this is why they need documenting</u>
<u n="529" who="S0192">I don't see any point I guess we do need to get them out a box at a time and to document them and write them down</u>
<u n="530" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0192">just a bit of a mission isn't it?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0198">just do a box in here and then I mean we've got all year whenever they go or don't go so it just depends really doesn't it?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we do have all year but we'll probably get busier and busier and busier as the year goes on I think I'd like to get rid of them before I you know before we go to Saudi</u>
<u n="534" who="S0198">yeah I know I know I know I know</u>
<u n="535" who="S0192">so</u>
<u n="536" who="S0198">so you may as well do it sooner</u>
<u n="537" who="S0192" trans="overlap">just cos they're not <unclear>storage</unclear> do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0198">this one is er five pound fifty used</u>
<u n="539" who="S0192">oh that's pretty good and that one?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0198">oh I haven't looked up this one yet old money</u>
<u n="541" who="S0192">see a few of them we've looked at now have been about five quid</u>
<u n="542" who="S0198">yeah which I mean that would be a <unclear>postage</unclear> I mean that'd add up</u>
<u n="543" who="S0192">I mean you'll get five quid for it your the postage'll cover the postage</u>
<u n="544" who="S0198">this one's four pounds three ninety-five used</u>
<u n="545" who="S0192">so I mean that's pretty good</u>
<u n="546" who="S0198">not really making any money back on them though are you jesus</u>
<u n="547" who="S0192">oh no you're not making any money on them</u>
<u n="548" who="S0198">you've got all these copies no legit digital copy what if something breaks and gotta download it all again?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0192">that's something you got I wouldn't do something illegal like download</u>
<u n="550" who="S0198">no you can download from Itunes</u>
<u n="551" who="S0192">it's too expensive</u>
<u n="552" who="S0198">you just go without music</u>
<u n="553" who="S0192">no I just borrow music off my friends indefinitely</u>
<u n="554" who="S0198">I suppose so</u>
<u n="555" who="S0192">I really don't understand why that's illegal</u>
<u n="556" who="S0198">yeah I know</u>
<u n="557" who="S0192">borrowing music off my friends</u>
<u n="558" who="S0198">never used to be what's this big one used to be able to lend each other CDs didn't you?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah I mean <pause dur="short"/> trojan dub <pause dur="short"/> well think about it you used to be able to record off the bloody radio</u>
<u n="560" who="S0198">I know</u>
<u n="561" who="S0192">that was alright wasn't it?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0198">yeah it was fine</u>
<u n="563" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and I could give a cassette to my friend that was fine</u>
<u n="564" who="S0198">erm yeah it was all about making tapes for each other</u>
<u n="565" who="S0192">what they don't didn't like was the fact that you could very quickly share it with everyone</u>
<u n="566" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="567" who="S0192">not just people around you because now suddenly you could share it with the whole world</u>
<u n="568" who="S0198" trans="overlap">the whole world mm just upload it to something and you stop making money</u>
<u n="569" who="S0192">but so what?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0198">I know</u>
<u n="571" who="S0192">artists have got to realise that they make money in other ways</u>
<u n="572" who="S0198" trans="overlap">they make money from their art which is performing</u>
<u n="573" who="S0192">memorabilia art performance <pause dur="short"/> but without their music effectively what are they? <pause dur="short"/> it's like a footballer just I don't know you just pay so the footballer plays regardless of whether you actually see the damn thing</u>
<u n="574" who="S0198">seeing the thing</u>
<u n="575" who="S0192">you know what I mean? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="576" who="S0198">I mean they get paid thousands don't they?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but without without them playing there is nothing they're making money off</u>
<u n="578" who="S0198">yeah I need to get some water</u>
<u n="579" who="S0192">no reason yeah I need water too</u>
<u n="580" who="S0198">and <unclear>try</unclear> a beer</u>
<u n="581" who="S0192">and a beer shall I roll a cigarette then?</u>
<u n="582" who="S0198" trans="overlap">do that it's Friday night isn't it?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0192">where are the cigarettes?</u>
<u n="584" who="S0198"><shift new="singing"/> it's Friday night at the movies <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0192">yeah this is our Friday night studying have a beer and a cigarette</u>
<u n="586" who="S0198">don't go crazy</u>
<u n="587" who="S0192">where are they?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0198">er I don't know darling? you're the one that <unclear>deals with</unclear> tobacco</u>
<u n="589" who="S0192">ah I found it</u>
<u n="590" who="S0198">you got it?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0198">losing things round the house you got it? ah it's where I thought it was</u>
<u n="593" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah it's here should put this there that should be alright shouldn't it?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0198">and we've got another spider it's the same one I'm <unclear/> concerned</u>
<u n="595" who="S0192">you're worried it's just going to be an explosion of spiders?</u>
<u n="596" who="S0198">I'm worried there's a nesting somewhere go on go out of the house</u>
<u n="597" who="S0192">just move him out with your hand <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>probably</unclear> just freaked <vocal desc="laugh"/> were you proper freaked out then?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0198">no he was on the floor it's not very useful is it?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0192" trans="overlap">should have cupped him out</u>
<u n="600" who="S0198">but you said just brush him out so I just went to brush him out</u>
<u n="601" who="S0192">yeah but not quite like that</u>
<u n="602" who="S0198">oh you left the bedroom light on again</u>
<u n="603" who="S0192">is that my fault? did I do that last time?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0198">ah</u>
<u n="605" who="S0192">where are you off to?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0198"><unclear/> to bedroom <pause dur="short"/> so we've got two more clear weeks and that's it it's not very long is it?</u>
<u n="607" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="608" who="S0198">it's coming around quickly</u>
<u n="609" who="S0192">obviously it's gonna the <trunc>cour</trunc> the thing is the course is gonna start <pause dur="short"/> I mean obviously it's gonna be busy from the word go</u>
<u n="610" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="611" who="S0192">but it's gonna be less busy in the first six weeks than it is in the second six weeks</u>
<u n="612" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0192">so we're still gonna have plenty of time for study that won't be a problem</u>
<u n="614" who="S0198">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="615" who="S0192">what beer have we got then?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0198">Grolsh Grolsh</u>
<u n="617" who="S0192">nice</u>
<u n="618" who="S0198">I guess yep we are I mean there must be some people there's always got to be a couple of people hasn't there that go into these things completely unprepared?</u>
<u n="619" who="S0192">yeah always pretty much</u>
<u n="620" who="S0198">there usually is isn't there?</u>
<u n="621" who="S0192">I reckon and hopefully there'll be other people that read the book</u>
<u n="622" who="S0198" trans="overlap">or people that aren't quite prepared</u>
<u n="623" who="S0192">and they'll be like oh my god I don't understand this</u>
<u n="624" who="S0198">erm I don't know? at least I hope so but then who goes into an MA in linguistics lightly?</u>
<u n="625" who="S0192">that's what I also think</u>
<u n="626" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="627" who="S0192">I thought that like oh you just get your <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>s and what not</u>
<u n="628" who="S0198" trans="overlap">you wouldn't though would you?</u>
<u n="629" who="S0192">but like you're doing an MA in applied linguistics</u>
<u n="630" who="S0198">it's not the same as a Celta or Tefl course</u>
<u n="631" who="S0192">mm maybe yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0198">it's a bit more something to do you don't just stumble into a <unclear>Delta</unclear> there's prerequisites before you even get that far so</u>
<u n="633" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah no you <unclear>have to understand</unclear> them you do however stumble into a Celta so</u>
<u n="634" who="S0198">yeah but not a Delta unless an MA is comparable</u>
<u n="635" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="636" who="S0198">anyway I'm kinda hoping that at least someone or they they're just people that have just got in I mean they accepted us without any queries</u>
<u n="637" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0198">so I'm confident that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we had fairly strong background</u>
<u n="640" who="S0198">I mean how hard they can't make it too unrealistically hard surely? otherwise nobody would get qualified in anything</u>
<u n="641" who="S0192">to MA standard yeah I guess <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't really</u>
<u n="642" who="S0198">it's just with all the reading it's a bit overwhelming to know how expert we're meant to already be</u>
<u n="643" who="S0192">erm I think we're certainly meant to recognise everything whether or not you have the ability to just use it randomly I don't know? that I don't know?</u>
<u n="644" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="645" who="S0192">I think they'll expect us to recognise it</u>
<u n="646" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="647" who="S0192">certainly</u>
<u n="648" who="S0198">that's okay</u>
<u n="649" who="S0192">do you recognise pretty much everything?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0198">I mean I don't know? no you still oh if you there's just so much that I'm trying to I recognise it when I read it and I understand everything and I'm much more comfortable with a lot of things so yeah it's okay but I still can't when I'm put on the spot I still don't think I can give a good definition of stuff textbook definition it'll take me minute to think about it and think of a good answer perhaps</u>
<u n="651" who="S0192">that's okay</u>
<u n="652" who="S0198">I guess stuff just hasn't you know some normally with education you some core things are drummed into you from quite a young age so even the basics are kinda covered but when it's something new it takes a little while longer for that to get so drummed into me</u>
<u n="653" who="S0192">it is an entirely new topic for us but it's not cos we've been working in the field so</u>
<u n="654" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="655" who="S0192">so hopefully we're alright</u>
<u n="656" who="S0198">and yeah the erm <pause dur="short"/> I'm doing second language acquisition as well so</u>
<u n="657" who="S0192">that's still within your field</u>
<u n="658" who="S0198">still within the field</u>
<u n="659" who="S0192">I mean like pidgins and creoles who the hell has studied pidgins and creoles before now?</u>
<u n="660" who="S0198" trans="overlap">well they've got people the er <unclear/> sit down there <pause dur="short"/> we've got they've got they reference people in my was it the dialectology book I was reading? or something else? maybe it was that talking about or language variation there are some people that have gone out to you know did their research in Bolivia or did their research in Peru although I don't know if they were studying creoles actually I think they were studying language variation no yeah sorry I'm confused it just made me think</u>
<u n="661" who="S0192" trans="overlap">there's no creoles there I don't think <pause dur="short"/> I just meant like</u>
<u n="662" who="S0198">that some people do go out and do that</u>
<u n="663" who="S0192">people of our no of course people go out and do it but I mean just more like</u>
<u n="664" who="S0198">no I mean the cigarette</u>
<u n="665" who="S0192">peers <pause dur="short"/> I am <unclear>rolling</unclear> a cigarette</u>
<u n="666" who="S0198">ah yeah</u>
<u n="667" who="S0192">for</u>
<u n="668" who="S0198">what do you mean peers? <pause dur="short"/> what do you mean peers?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0192">what do you mean this? I don't really understand</u>
<u n="670" who="S0198">no I just thought actual with the drum only that's fine</u>
<u n="671" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="672" who="S0198">what do you mean by peers?</u>
<u n="673" who="S0192">if that's what you want then I'll I'll make that what do I mean by peers?</u>
<u n="674" who="S0198">peers</u>
<u n="675" who="S0192">your people that you're you know studying with</u>
<u n="676" who="S0198">no I know who what peers means <vocal desc="laugh"/> I mean who what why why did you mention them?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0192">cos I was talking about I'm sure nobody else would have studied pidgins and creoles before</u>
<u n="678" who="S0198">oh right as in the people in your class</u>
<u n="679" who="S0192">you know you're starting talking about dialectology and people going to Bolivia and stuff and I'm talking about knowing my peers</u>
<u n="680" who="S0198">okay sorry <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm sure you're right I'm sure not too many people have that's why especially seeing as it's a year three module</u>
<u n="681" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0198">she does say in that discovery and book doesn't she that <unclear/> undergraduate students <pause dur="short"/> so I guess it's something that linguistic courses definitely incorporate and it's something that some people on our course would have definitely studied</u>
<u n="683" who="S0192">and you should know</u>
<u n="684" who="S0198">you should know yeah</u>
<u n="685" who="S0192">yeah which I why I wonder what that actual course is gonna be like but it's still thirty credits so they can't make it that easy</u>
<u n="686" who="S0198">no I mean it's not gonna be easy is it? it might just be quite heavy I don't know if I should have done it</u>
<u n="687" who="S0192">it might be difficult in the sense that it covers everything therefore I need to do a lot you know</u>
<u n="688" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's why I still like language variation like have you seen the like week to week thing it's like so this week I'm meant to be an expert in dialectology but the following week I need to be an expert in something else discourse analysis or something do you know what I mean? I'm like what? <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's very varied I guess language variation is varied</u>
<u n="689" who="S0192">yeah that's quite a bit topic to be covering</u>
<u n="690" who="S0198">yeah I assume I mean it's like anything I suppose they just focus you in on certain key features you pick one of those you have I have to do a when's I <unclear>that</unclear> week oh no it's the twenty-fifth of November I have to hand in a literature review and then in assessment week one which I think is the first week is that week of the two weeks</u>
<u n="691" who="S0192" trans="overlap">in January yeah</u>
<u n="692" who="S0198">in January I have to hand in the actual <pause dur="short"/> er er I dunno essays mini dissertation whatever the literature review is on basically</u>
<u n="693" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0198">so the first I guess the first eight weeks you're <pause dur="short"/> gearing up to researching this literature review of some area or the other and then you produce a bigger paper on it</u>
<u n="695" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0198">but what <pause dur="short"/> whether I wonder how much guidance they give</u>
<u n="697" who="S0192">I have no idea like presumably enough <vocal desc="laugh"/> I hope</u>
<u n="698" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="699" who="S0192">I don't know anything about <pause dur="short"/> I mean mine are gonna be completely different mine are gonna be exams so</u>
<u n="700" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="701" who="S0192">I don't know if I'm gonna have much to do until</u>
<u n="702" who="S0198">until yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="703" who="S0192">apart from read <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know what I mean? read</u>
<u n="704" who="S0198" trans="overlap">that's nice</u>
<u n="705" who="S0192">and well no I'll have to read and probably do example questions and I'm like</u>
<u n="706" who="S0198">yeah you do have to what's your seven hundred words?</u>
<u n="707" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I do have two two seven hundred and fifty word analysis papers in each module</u>
<u n="708" who="S0198">okay</u>
<u n="709" who="S0192">so I'm gonna have something to hand in</u>
<u n="710" who="S0198" trans="overlap">in each of the three modules?</u>
<u n="711" who="S0192">I think so definitely in two of them</u>
<u n="712" who="S0198">what about the core module we're both doing? what's the assessment for that? it's just</u>
<u n="713" who="S0192">mm I'm not sure actually grab me my computer</u>
<u n="714" who="S0198">mm <pause dur="short"/> should get all this stuff handy on the erm <pause dur="short"/> on the handheld thing really <pause dur="short"/> that's what it's designed for isn't it? <unclear/></u>
<u n="715" who="S0192">what all our documents and well just both of our</u>
<u n="716" who="S0198">yeah module handbooks and all the textbooks</u>
<u n="717" who="S0192">I'll just put both of our MA applied linguistics folders plus all the the textbooks</u>
<u n="718" who="S0198">just for referencing and makes it more convenient</u>
<u n="719" who="S0192">so what am I looking for here? I quite like that background</u>
<u n="720" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="721" who="S0192">I quite like the fact that it goes in like er here you can see it around a folder</u>
<u n="722" who="S0198">oh yeah</u>
<u n="723" who="S0192">do you know what I mean? which is a bit strange cos even if you make the folder smaller it's not actually the background behind it they've taken a colour out of the background and like</u>
<u n="724" who="S0198">oh yeah and just made it as a border</u>
<u n="725" who="S0192">what am I looking for?</u>
<u n="726" who="S0198">erm the language oh no the core module assessment</u>
<u n="727" who="S0192">researching languaging <unclear/></u>
<u n="728" who="S0198">yeah I'm pretty sure it must be some sort of</u>
<u n="729" who="S0192">bet your folders aren't this neat</u>
<u n="730" who="S0198">no I mean they're not bad they're not bad</u>
<u n="731" who="S0192">did you emulate mine?</u>
<u n="732" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="733" who="S0192">workload</u>
<u n="734" who="S0198">so what is it? why does it say Wednesday? does it say Wednesday?</u>
<u n="735" who="S0192">this is old</u>
<u n="736" who="S0198">oh</u>
<u n="737" who="S0192">this is the we don't have the new one</u>
<u n="738" who="S0198">oh yeah of course we don't</u>
<u n="739" who="S0192">this is just the two thousand and thirteen one</u>
<u n="740" who="S0198">I wonder if he's contactable now he's got his picture up? cos he hasn't</u>
<u n="741" who="S0192" trans="overlap">he he might be do they have his email address on there?</u>
<u n="742" who="S0198">ah I don't know? two pieces of coursework due thirty-first of October and the fifth of December</u>
<u n="743" who="S0192">oh crap so that's due pretty much when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> arrive</u>
<u n="744" who="S0198">so that'll be set pretty early on that'll be something whatever that exercise is whatever that is ah they're both due before Christmas</u>
<u n="745" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="746" who="S0198">each worth fifty percent</u>
<u n="747" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="748" who="S0198">oh</u>
<u n="749" who="S0192">it's only a fifteen credit module but still</u>
<u n="750" who="S0198">yeah I don't imagine they'll be too big then</u>
<u n="751" who="S0192"><vocal desc="yawn"/> I don't know? Can't collaborate evaluation course evaluation questionnaire <pause dur="short"/> reading week</u>
<u n="752" who="S0198">I imagine I mean there must be enough time yeah I haven't I haven't looked at this module enough yet</u>
<u n="753" who="S0192">erm they've got quite a reading list</u>
<u n="754" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="755" who="S0192">it's all like research and stuff if you have a look in my one here these are the books that I've got from my book list I've done this now for them all so this is what I've read or got this is what I've got this is from the reading list</u>
<u n="756" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="757" who="S0192">this is what I need from the reading list</u>
<u n="758" who="S0198">so much reading</u>
<u n="759" who="S0192">yeah I know but we've already got that</u>
<u n="760" who="S0198">yeah yeah I know</u>
<u n="761" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so you could just copy this you have exactly the same thing</u>
<u n="762" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="763" who="S0192">I've already read those I'm reading this one now and I've read that one</u>
<u n="764" who="S0198" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="765" who="S0192">and then we need and also I've made an additional list of books that I've read that could go in a bibliography</u>
<u n="766" who="S0198">yeah of course anything that we've read basically so far</u>
<u n="767" who="S0192"><trunc>excep</trunc> well not anything</u>
<u n="768" who="S0198" trans="overlap">no cos it's got to be relevant</u>
<u n="769" who="S0192">pidgins and creoles has got no relevance to this but like all the general linguistics books that we've read they can definitely go up here</u>
<u n="770" who="S0198">but even so even in the pidgins and creoles book if it talks about research and the practicalities of research you might find some of those books cross over</u>
<u n="771" who="S0192">yeah I guess it hasn't I mean no it's not really taken out figure out feed <unclear>field</unclear> I don't know? I just didn't put it in I guess? but that's still quite a big</u>
<u n="772" who="S0198">that's a start</u>
<u n="773" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah that's a start I've got those to read</u>
<u n="774" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="775" who="S0192">I don't know if I even need to get some of those I mean I hope not <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="776" who="S0198">I'll get some well they</u>
<u n="777" who="S0192">how many books are you really expected to read per module?</u>
<u n="778" who="S0198">I don't know what cover to cover? not that not that many</u>
<u n="779" who="S0192"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="780" who="S0198">I mean a few a few core books but I think a lot of the others you will be just referencing chapters you're skimming</u>
<u n="781" who="S0192" trans="overlap">dipping in and out of</u>
<u n="782" who="S0198">out of and my bibliography for my dissertation was quite you know it was a few pages <pause dur="short"/> or <trunc>journ</trunc> well it's probably a page and so of books and then a page or so of journal articles and then primary resources</u>
<u n="783" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I've never used journal articles do I have to use them? I can't use books</u>
<u n="784" who="S0198">I think you need to include journal articles as well I think they'll definitely expect you to do that</u>
<u n="785" who="S0192">why?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0198">because it <vocal desc="misc"/> it's pardon me it's another source of information</u>
<u n="787" who="S0192">but if those sources are just published in books you know there are books of effectively journals</u>
<u n="788" who="S0198" trans="overlap">they're not <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="789" who="S0192">some of these books are edited and it's effectively just journals</u>
<u n="790" who="S0198">but some of the stuff doesn't make it into a book</u>
<u n="791" who="S0192">so it's just surely if it's worth</u>
<u n="792" who="S0198">it's a useful way of getting er like a</u>
<u n="793" who="S0192">was it just?</u>
<u n="794" who="S0198" trans="overlap">a snippet of a counter argument and stuff like that</u>
<u n="795" who="S0192">are all the journals you were using no I suppose they were quite old weren't they? cos what's the point in going back?</u>
<u n="796" who="S0198" trans="overlap">no some of them are new</u>
<u n="797" who="S0192">but surely the whole idea of journals is just for new stuff that hasn't yet gone into books cos I mean if you're looking at</u>
<u n="798" who="S0198" trans="overlap">but other stuff hasn't gone into books that maybe you might find cos people get <trunc>p</trunc> that's how people publish isn't it? through journal articles someone could do quite a good piece of research that hasn't been referenced in a book yet</u>
<u n="799" who="S0192">surely it would be if it was a good piece of research then it would be put in a compendium</u>
<u n="800" who="S0198">it might just be a bit particular or</u>
<u n="801" who="S0192" trans="overlap">be talked about in other people's</u>
<u n="802" who="S0198">I think you need journal articles I think it's a it's a</u>
<u n="803" who="S0192" trans="overlap">cool <pause dur="short"/> I don't I don't know anything about it <unclear>about them</unclear></u>
<u n="804" who="S0198">unexpected and</u>
<u n="805" who="S0192">where did you get those from?</u>
<u n="806" who="S0198">they're in the they're in the library library and have a library of journals</u>
<u n="807" who="S0192">so what you just look up a specific</u>
<u n="808" who="S0198">they'll have a way</u>
<u n="809" who="S0192">very very specific topic for a journal</u>
<u n="810" who="S0198" trans="overlap">they have a way of I mean you have to get you have to browse things and take snippets from bits and bobs</u>
<u n="811" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="812" who="S0198">and work it together into some sort of argument that benefits you basically</u>
<u n="813" who="S0192">I keep I'm keeping my book list now so at least at the end when I make whatever it is I've got to make I've got all the references and everything here done</u>
<u n="814" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="815" who="S0192">they reference slightly different to how I've been referencing</u>
<u n="816" who="S0198">oh do they?</u>
<u n="817" who="S0192">only very slightly just like brackets italics</u>
<u n="818" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="819" who="S0192">a little bit it's</u>
<u n="820" who="S0198">there is a rule about what you italic and what you don't</u>
<u n="821" who="S0192">yeah yeah well I followed the rule the Harvard one that's on the website</u>
<u n="822" who="S0198">oh yeah</u>
<u n="823" who="S0192">but it does tell you to</u>
<u n="824" who="S0198">check with your courses</u>
<u n="825" who="S0192">check with your core lecture but that'd be annoying if I have to go and</u>
<u n="826" who="S0198">I assume the way they're referenced in er reading lists is the way you have to reference the text</u>
<u n="827" who="S0192">ah surely not?</u>
<u n="828" who="S0198">is that not the same?</u>
<u n="829" who="S0192">I mean it's pretty similar but not exactly the same <pause dur="short"/> see I put brackets here and I just put W I wouldn't put Lebov William I'd put Lebov well you see here I put Ray <trunc>Vor</trunc> oh let's get one that's just one Mayer comma C dot open brackets two thousand and two they don't she doesn't put the brackets she puts a full stop and then I put that in italics cos they told me to on the thing</u>
<u n="830" who="S0198">ah I mean</u>
<u n="831" who="S0192" trans="overlap">otherwise it's the same it's in the same order it's just a bit of punctuation</u>
<u n="832" who="S0198" trans="overlap">mm as long as you've got the information there then</u>
<u n="833" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean I think it</u>
<u n="834" who="S0198">it's something you might have to change I think the way you you're doing it is the way that I did it for history</u>
<u n="835" who="S0192">yeah surely as long as it's consistent</u>
<u n="836" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="837" who="S0192">and correct <pause dur="short"/> and you know I'm consistent I'm not using different</u>
<u n="838" who="S0198">different styles or yeah</u>
<u n="839" who="S0192" trans="overlap">different ones then surely it'll be fine it'd be annoying to have to go and delete all the brackets out of all of these just because she doesn't want some brackets</u>
<u n="840" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="841" who="S0192">it just seems a bit silly doesn't it?</u>
<u n="842" who="S0198">oh we'll have to erm we can clarify immediately with the lecturers</u>
<u n="843" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="844" who="S0198">and get their feedback I wanna go in and er with a good lot of questions and things prepared <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="845" who="S0192">yeah about that reading that first week</u>
<u n="846" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah what it is</u>
<u n="847" who="S0192">whatever's the topic is</u>
<u n="848" who="S0198" trans="overlap">the topic is</u>
<u n="849" who="S0192">so what is the topic in this first week?</u>
<u n="850" who="S0198" trans="overlap">well language variation is language variation that's the first week's topic and I'm like</u>
<u n="851" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so just general question</u>
<u n="852" who="S0198">well what aspect of yeah of that it's a big topic what am I supposed to be asking? I don't know I'll make some questions then</u>
<u n="853" who="S0192">yeah so like <pause dur="short"/> this first week is just lecture on research and linguistics</u>
<u n="854" who="S0198">mm <unclear>what is it</unclear> then?</u>
<u n="855" who="S0192">and then a week later is the seminar finding and processing literature I mean what are you meant to say about that?</u>
<u n="856" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> the different ways in which people find and process literature</u>
<u n="857" who="S0192">linguistic evidence argumentation</u>
<u n="858" who="S0198" trans="overlap">see it's all preparing you for a linguistics review</u>
<u n="859" who="S0192" trans="overlap">data collection yeah I know this is just</u>
<u n="860" who="S0198">it's blatantly what they're gonna do</u>
<u n="861" who="S0192" trans="overlap">this is just one of two modules preparing you for it</u>
<u n="862" who="S0198">I mean that's nice cos I have to do a literature review for variation so the two combined</u>
<u n="863" who="S0192">so you wanna be able to er</u>
<u n="864" who="S0198" trans="overlap">help me double up on something then</u>
<u n="865" who="S0192">I'll be able to do that</u>
<u n="866" who="S0198">but this is held on a Monday at in the afternoon</u>
<u n="867" who="S0192">yeah four till six</u>
<u n="868" who="S0198">yeah so <pause dur="short"/> I don't know when to need to sign up to the bloody language class <unclear/></u>
<u n="869" who="S0192">have you decided which ones?</u>
<u n="870" who="S0198">I don't know? can I go well what would it be like going into beginners Spanish?</u>
<u n="871" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so this is your <pause dur="short"/> this is your timetable here erm</u>
<u n="872" who="S0198">what do I start? I don't want to be learning numbers</u>
<u n="873" who="S0192">it will be pretty beginner</u>
<u n="874" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="875" who="S0192">it's gonna be hello how are you? what's your name?</u>
<u n="876" who="S0198" trans="overlap">because we do distinguish more here between beginner er</u>
<u n="877" who="S0192">elementary's elementary</u>
<u n="878" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="879" who="S0192">I would say at the height of my Spanish speaking ability I was lower intermediate</u>
<u n="880" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="881" who="S0192">maybe pushing intermediate in certain areas like <pause dur="short"/> confidence</u>
<u n="882" who="S0198">see I don't know if I'd get classified as a false beginner in the sense that you seemingly know a little bit but actually when you get me down to the nitty and gritty I'm not very good</u>
<u n="883" who="S0192">I mean</u>
<u n="884" who="S0198">it depends what beginner is though isn't it?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you have quite a bit of vocabulary don't you?</u>
<u n="886" who="S0198">I'd like to yeah I think I'd recognise it whether or not I can produce it is different</u>
<u n="887" who="S0192">so when were the times you were looking here? language variation</u>
<u n="888" who="S0198">there was one on a Tuesday that was six to eight er six six to eight thirty</u>
<u n="889" who="S0192">so</u>
<u n="890" who="S0198">oh no but I only finish at six no six thirty to eight they're all six they're all six thirty to eight</u>
<u n="891" who="S0192">so we would not have dinner together at this time I don't know when you'd have dinner?</u>
<u n="892" who="S0198">just when I</u>
<u n="893" who="S0192">got home at</u>
<u n="894" who="S0198">yeah I'd eat different</u>
<u n="895" who="S0192" trans="overlap">nine o'clock</u>
<u n="896" who="S0198">yeah I'd eat differently that day I would have a like a slightly bigger lunch and a slightly like I'd probably swap my lunch for my dinner that day</u>
<u n="897" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="898" who="S0198">and then have something smaller in the evening</u>
<u n="899" who="S0192">that's fair</u>
<u n="900" who="S0198">but that day we wouldn't see each other at all would we? you go off to uni at nine and I'd come home at eight well later than eight don't really want to be cycling home at</u>
<u n="901" who="S0192">no I don't think you should cycle on those days just don't think you should cycle on those days</u>
<u n="902" who="S0198"><unclear/> got like it depends on the cycle route</u>
<u n="903" who="S0192">I don't know if you should be cycling in winter if it's dark after you get back</u>
<u n="904" who="S0198">I know I've got lights and everything for my bike though I haven't got a front brake apparently which I need to ask my dad about before he comes up <pause dur="short"/> I would like a brake I don't know if he mentioned it and I was just like whatever he just forgot</u>
<u n="905" who="S0192">yeah I mean not having a brake on your bike is a bit of a negative <pause dur="short"/> isn't it? it's not the safest thing</u>
<u n="906" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="907" who="S0192">I've got a book <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gave me on bicycle maintenance</u>
<u n="908" who="S0198">oh really? <unclear/></u>
<u n="909" who="S0192">might be able to do it ourselves but then we have to go buy a new brake cable and all the stuff that attaches to it</u>
<u n="910" who="S0198">I know well I'm not doing</u>
<u n="911" who="S0192">oh well the brake cable's there is it?</u>
<u n="912" who="S0198">no the <trunc>ca</trunc> there's no <trunc>ca</trunc> there's nothing there it's naked it is bare</u>
<u n="913" who="S0192">there's nothing?</u>
<u n="914" who="S0198">no there's I don't think there's any cabling I don't know how you I don't even know why you would have removed a brake cable?</u>
<u n="915" who="S0192">oh no I don't know?</u>
<u n="916" who="S0198">just <unclear>break</unclear> stuff</u>
<u n="917" who="S0192">just did whatever he wanted to do fixed it up</u>
<u n="918" who="S0198">have you messaged to dad about his birthday?</u>
<u n="919" who="S0192">yeah he said erm</u>
<u n="920" who="S0198">did you say about going out?</u>
<u n="921" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah he said he'd like it if I came up he said we could go out for a meal erm <pause dur="short"/> but then sent me a picture of this propagator and I I kinda need to say to him like either or I don't know if I can afford to buy you a gift and come down so I guess which would you prefer?</u>
<u n="922" who="S0198">what's a propagator?</u>
<u n="923" who="S0192">erm it's a way do you want another cigarette?</u>
<u n="924" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="925" who="S0192">no? it's a way of propagating do you want to shut the door or?</u>
<u n="926" who="S0198">mm yeah</u>
<u n="927" who="S0192">a way of propagating plants so that they erm</u>
<u n="928" who="S0198">oh right of course</u>
<u n="929" who="S0192">they grow <pause dur="short"/> but it's only about twenty-five pound for the propagator which I would I would happily buy him</u>
<u n="930" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="931" who="S0192">but if I go down and visit you're talking another twenty pound to get home plus I'll probably pay for the meal I guess</u>
<u n="932" who="S0198">oh I dunno yeah if you're gonna go out for dinner</u>
<u n="933" who="S0192">but I mean I'll be able to record so I can make some money from that</u>
<u n="934" who="S0198">depends how much I mean yeah you would your dad's pretty good but I mean dinner could it depends if you're going to go out for dinner who pays for that?</u>
<u n="935" who="S0192">yeah I really don't know? if it's that kind of price I guess we'll see</u>
<u n="936" who="S0198">talk to your brother as well can't so he's going to Spain this week?</u>
<u n="937" who="S0192">he's not gonna be there yeah</u>
<u n="938" who="S0198">oh no that weekend? no oh he's gonna be in uni by then</u>
<u n="939" who="S0192">yeah he'll be in uni</u>
<u n="940" who="S0198">oh so he's gonna be in Kent that weekend</u>
<u n="941" who="S0192">yep <pause dur="short"/> erm so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got one one day of work sorry one week of work</u>
<u n="942" who="S0198">oh right which he's using to go to Spain</u>
<u n="943" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and then he used it to go to Spain yeah</u>
<u n="944" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> dear oh dear</u>
<u n="945" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="946" who="S0198">did you ask him how much he spent in Thailand in the end in total?</u>
<u n="947" who="S0192">no I didn't</u>
<u n="948" who="S0198">oh</u>
<u n="949" who="S0192">I can work out roughly how much he spent</u>
<u n="950" who="S0198">yeah more than we did I'm sure quite a lot more</u>
<u n="951" who="S0192">erm yeah I would I mean I spent I lived off a thousand pounds for nine weeks</u>
<u n="952" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="953" who="S0192">er</u>
<u n="954" who="S0198">he spent that in the first couple didn't he?</u>
<u n="955" who="S0192">yeah he</u>
<u n="956" who="S0198">well maybe not best three weeks</u>
<u n="957" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I reckon he spent close to two thousand pounds maybe fifteen hundred maybe fifteen hundred pound</u>
<u n="958" who="S0198">but yeah so but he's going when's he going to Spain? the thirteenth or</u>
<u n="959" who="S0192">this Sunday</u>
<u n="960" who="S0198">not this Sunday?</u>
<u n="961" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="962" who="S0198">oh it's a couple of days</u>
<u n="963" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="964" who="S0198">are they gonna stay in a guest house or are they is she is he staying with her family or?</u>
<u n="965" who="S0192">I have no idea</u>
<u n="966" who="S0198">no she's a student isn't she?</u>
<u n="967" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="968" who="S0198">to be a doctor or did I make that up? no I made that up <pause dur="short"/> is it something like that? or a nurse or no?</u>
<u n="969" who="S0192">I can't remember what she's a student for</u>
<u n="970" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh no she's doing she's studying science or something is she?</u>
<u n="971" who="S0192">biology maybe something like that</u>
<u n="972" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="973" who="S0192">rings a bell biology I really don't know</u>
<u n="974" who="S0198">maybe it's just clashing wherever she lives</u>
<u n="975" who="S0192"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="976" who="S0198">whereabouts in Spain?</u>
<u n="977" who="S0192">erm kind of the north west just north of Portugal not Pays Basque</u>
<u n="978" who="S0198">okay</u>
<u n="979" who="S0192">but erm <pause dur="short"/> near there</u>
<u n="980" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="981" who="S0192">near Basque country but further closer to Portugal I believe there's no French influence</u>
<u n="982" who="S0198">no I don't know if I read yeah it's funny isn't it? Basque country as <trunc>Fre</trunc> is it French?</u>
<u n="983" who="S0192">influence um</u>
<u n="984" who="S0198">influence but it's not <trunc>Sp</trunc> is there then their <trunc>nat</trunc>?</u>
<u n="985" who="S0192">I believe their language is</u>
<u n="986" who="S0198">what are they taught at school?</u>
<u n="987" who="S0192">what what language do they?</u>
<u n="988" who="S0198">what is their standardised language do we know?</u>
<u n="989" who="S0192">let's have a look shall we?</u>
<u n="990" who="S0198" trans="overlap">is it Spanish?</u>
<u n="991" who="S0192">I know that Catalan is kind of it's Spanish but it's got a lot more French words in it a lot more of a French mixture and I thought that</u>
<u n="992" who="S0198">the <trunc>pronoun</trunc></u>
<u n="993" who="S0192">Paes Basque might have been similar</u>
<u n="994" who="S0198" trans="overlap">well I know yeah cos that girl that was from the other couple we met she was she just spoke French</u>
<u n="995" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="996" who="S0198">she didn't speak</u>
<u n="997" who="S0192">so I think they speak like French or Spanish or both or what erm Paes Basque <unclear>goes</unclear> it's an autonomous community lets see where does it say where they speak the languages? official languages Basque and Spanish</u>
<u n="998" who="S0198">oh dear so what's Basque when you break it down?</u>
<u n="999" who="S0192">Basque as a language <unclear>isolate</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0198">is it autonomous or is it?</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0192">it's spoken in north eastern Spain and south western France</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0198">oh</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0198">so is it mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> I did read something today that was saying <vocal desc="cough"/> the reference like a poet in the thirteenth fourteenth century think it's the fourteenth century</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0198">who noted the difference between northern <pause dur="short"/> france and the dialect of <pause dur="short"/> northern and south France</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0198">they pronounce the oui differently or something that's <unclear/> thing</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0192">according to this it's a language isolate</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0192">it's the last remaining descendant of the pre indo European languages of western Europe</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0198">wow</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0198">mm so is that what a language isolate is then?</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0192">mm I guess that when</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I guess an isolated language</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0192">yeah it's like a member of the family</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0198">but pre indo European <pause dur="short"/> I thought</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0192">that puts it back pretty far doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0192">I thought pre indo European was some proto language that they didn't really know <pause dur="short"/> demographic</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0198">mm go to Basque country and do your linguistics stuff</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0198">might help knowing the language <vocal desc="cough"/> I assume you have do you have you have we you don't have to know the language of course you don't otherwise we'd never transcribe tribes and things but <pause dur="short"/> surely for somewhere like that you'd be expected to just know the language for something that accessible</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0192">it was saying in the book that the first way that they erm figure out new languages like back in the day was with minimal pairs</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0192">so they make all the sounds and then they replace the sound and give them the same word and say is this a word in your language basically it was a very long and laborious process of like hat is that a word? and they'd go yes yeah hat and then you pat is that a word?</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0198">a word yeah</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0192">and they'll say it so you keep and then if pat's a word is pap a word? is pag a word?</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0198">oh</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0192">is puck a word?</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0198">just done it through minimal pairs</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0198">once they found a er erm</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0192">it was to isolate a phony</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0198" trans="overlap">a phony</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0192">yeah was to isolate a phony</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah it worked</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0192">and decide whether they have difference in meaning or not</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0198">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0192">that must have been laborious</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0198">exist or don't exist</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0192">must be</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0198">yeah like I said when I was reading today and I talked about I didn't really we've read about lots of the research that was done pre I don't know? whatever nineteen something or other I don't know when the first tape recorder was was invented</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0192">no I don't know?</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0198">nineteen forties thirties I don't know? no we've had recording <unclear>things</unclear> since then</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah well</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0198">but to be accessible to the public</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0198">anyway the fact that before then people were just writing it and everything he said in an interview had to write down they probably had some sort of short form</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0192">what's a stenograph?</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0198">I don't know? sounded crazy</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0192">that word has come into my head <pause dur="short"/> related to what you're talking about</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0198">although initially the recording equipment would have been incredibly heavy <pause dur="short"/> which they also talk about kind of trials and tribulations of the <pause dur="short"/> pre digital age <pause dur="short"/> linguistics researcher</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0192">ah a stenograph is a keyboard machine for reproducing letters in the shorthand system</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0198">oh right is that what you were thinking of?</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0192" trans="overlap">nothing to do with what you were saying</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0198">where would that be used?</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0192">for erm minutes I guess</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0198" trans="overlap">would have been used yeah courts</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0198">they have to take minutes and somebody's typing away on it</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0192">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0198">I wonder if you get paid well for doing that job?</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0192">it's gotta be pretty tiring</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0198">yeah I thought it'd be</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0192">kinda boring</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0198">just programmed and is at that point you're thinking surely now there's a machine that does that do people still type in courts? you see it on films but</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0192">are so many jobs not just really repetitive?</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0192">I know like okay lets take some of the highest jobs out there some of the highest regarded regarded jobs being a doctor or being a lawyer</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0192"><unclear>those</unclear> are pretty highly regarded <pause dur="short"/> do they vary that much? you know once you're a doctor <pause dur="short"/> sitting in a GP practice</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0198">yeah well a GP's different to</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah but most doctors are in GPs right?</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0198">I wouldn't have thought so well maybe yeah</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0192">I mean hospitals or GPs</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0198">yeah I mean is I don't know if there are more I guess in <trunc>ho</trunc> er I don't know?</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0192">I mean is it not <pause dur="short"/> okay you have different patients with different problems but you're not House <vocal desc="laugh"/> you're not working on a team of some crazy like</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0198">no</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0192">you're just dealing with the same stuff over and over and over and over again and like as a lawyer I'm sure a lot of their cases are like very boring very normal and run of the mill</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0198">I imagine being a GP is terrible in some ways</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0198">you'd have to</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0192">but like in our field I don't just mean teaching but teaching abroad</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0192">it's changing just from a middle school to a high school changing countries changing the type of people that you're teaching their age their level it's there's a whole load of variation on top of the fact that you have different students each time you're not seeing one</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0198" trans="overlap">mm the requirements of each</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0192">yep</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0198">each department is different let alone each institution</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0192">what you actually teach you could be teaching English and then you could be teaching how to teach English and then you could be teaching linguistics</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0198">that's why it's kind of an entire field rather than just a job</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0198">if that makes sense?</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0192">yeah it's a series of jobs</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0192">I guess you could argue that a doctor could become a surgeon could become a whatever</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0198">yeah there is of course there is that <unclear/></u>
<u n="1099" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but do they move that fluidly in between them? I think you once you have to be fairly good in your field don't you? you can't just be a surgeon for a couple of years and then be like no I wanna go work with children or something do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I mean they can do if they wanna be a especially if they were a surgeon for children</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0192" trans="overlap">takes quite a bit of training like you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is a paediatrician</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0192">and she'll remain a paediatrician for quite a while because once you're a good paediatrician</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0198">there's no reason to well there is a reason to</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I'm sure it'd be kind of difficult for her after five years of being a paediatrician to be like I wanna be a surgeon</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0192">so that's quite a different set of skills really</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0198">oh right to be a surgeon</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0192">to like go from being a paediatrician</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0198" trans="overlap">see I think a surgeon can go down</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0192">a paediatrician to an oncologist or something even just a different area</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0192">takes quite a lot of specialised knowledge that I don't know if</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0198">I don't know if the</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you could change I'm sure as a doctor you can change but I don't think it's that easy I don't think you could change become an oncologist and then a year later change again and become something else you'd be like no you just become an oncologist you need to spend two or three years just training in oncology</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0198">I think that's just the nature of that particular job though</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0198">isn't it? having to be an expert in something before you can practise it <unclear/></u>
<u n="1121" who="S0192" trans="overlap">to be a lawyer <pause dur="short"/> I mean I never really understood this as a lawyer are you what's the opposite of a defendant?</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0198">prosecutor</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0192">a prosecutor are you one or the other or are you both depending on the case?</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0198">case yeah I feel from my <vocal desc="laugh"/> from movies I thought <pause dur="short"/> that you you were either famous for one or the other</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0192">yeah because you develop a reputation</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0198">but I don't but I think that's because</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0192">and it takes different skills</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0192">but so do they change around very much? I guess what I'm saying is in our field</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I think lawyers do do both</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0192">it's common to change around a lot of people don't like <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will stay in the same kind of job for ages but</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0192">and like even in schools in England you don't get a middle school teacher that does the work works in a bit for a college and then works in a high school and works in an elementary school</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0198" trans="overlap">no no only qualified for their particular area</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0192">and then works in a uni you know what I mean? they become trained in whereas in our field okay there are prerequisites for example the company will say you need</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0198" trans="overlap">and it depends who</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0192">three years of children experience to work with children</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah yeah it depends who you're who you're getting in the job with as well</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0192">but once you've got</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0198" trans="overlap">there's requisite get <unclear/></u>
<u n="1141" who="S0192">those bases of experience</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><unclear/> if you go up but that's only because some <unclear/> somewhere else along the line like you <vocal desc="laugh"/> have no experience have no experience in experience in that area</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0192">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's also the problem with our field is it's inundated with inexperienced people that there are jobs you can do that require very little experience under the teaching English <unclear>banner</unclear></u>
<u n="1144" who="S0198" trans="overlap">there are <pause dur="short"/> well you're just going to you need to just work your way into institutes where that doesn't happen</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0198">or work yourself into institutes where that doesn't happen <unclear/></u>
<u n="1147" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you know they every institute I bet especially foreign not so much in Western Europe I don't think but further afield will hire last minute</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1149" who="S0192">they'll hire but something will happen someone'll drop out or somebody won't resign or something will happen and they'll just</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0198" trans="overlap">there's always last minute positions</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0192">and then they'll need to hire someone late and they'll just seem to go for whoever at that point</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0192">again I was quite surprised by unis in Korea that you know are quite strict when they put out the formal advert but then they hire people like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who was really young and had no experience whatsoever</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> mind it's yeah <pause dur="short"/> convenient when necessary</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0192" trans="overlap">whereas we had to have three years of experience really to be properly considered</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0198">considered yeah well they <unclear/> I don't know oh <pause dur="short"/> most people did that got hired</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0192" trans="overlap">in Korea yeah it was</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0198">when we were hired <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had quite a bit of experience</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0192">so did erm</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0198"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got her MA</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0192">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had her MA to support her I suppose</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> all three of them did</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0192">all had their MAs we got hired because we didn't have an MA but because we did have three years of Korea experience</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0198" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> experience</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0192">in public schools</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0192">erm and then like what's her face got hired just kinda last minute I reckon</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0198">who <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1170" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know they liked her video</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0192">hired from abroad</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0198">but yeah I don't know?</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0192">not last minute she wasn't last minute she was just I guess same as us she filled a quota</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0192">so <unclear/> just did it really quickly</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0198">would have been fine good as a conversation she liked her is enough</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0192">yeah they could have erm had a more thorough hiring process</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1179" who="S0192">though we may not have got through</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0198">have to remember that during that time though like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> applied for our positions didn't get it and he was living in <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had some of his friends actually make videos teaching the students</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that's true</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0198">and they didn't get in either</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0192">and they were from direct references</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0198">so <pause dur="short"/> it probably just means that they're going a bit on appearance also</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0192">the thing is who referenced <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at that point?</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0198">I don't know and yeah what from the</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0192">no one maybe maybe <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1190" who="S0198">maybe <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would have done and also <pause dur="short"/> er when the er those two <trunc>sis</trunc> er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and whoever I know is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and someone</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0192">oh yeah when they were there did they know him?</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0198">they they may <trunc>hav</trunc> they were good <trunc>fr</trunc> they were friends with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> friends enough that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that they <unclear/> vouch for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so I'm sure she knew <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she would have known <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1193" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0198">I think they were friends <pause dur="short"/> but that would have been the only person <pause dur="short"/> I wonder how they are getting along?</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0192">yeah I don't know</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0198">I wonder if anyone's in our flats?</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0192">deleted them I deleted a bunch of people whoops</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> deleted</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0192">I deleted <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1200" who="S0198">oh yeah I need to delete them I actually looked at something today and <unclear/></u>
<u n="1201" who="S0192">I kept <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I mean I just you know if anyone asks I cull <unclear/> like</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah keep my numbers down</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0192">I've er I'll be honest <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I didn't think we were going to stay in contact so I mean what do you say?</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0198">I've only ever re added someone once and we never saw her for the entire yeah</u>
<u n="1205" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1206" who="S0198">and that was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and the only reason I re added her was cos I was certain we were gonna bump into her</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0198">and it's just like well whatever I don't care that much</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0192">no well you just say you know</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0198">I deleted you and re added you</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0192">I mean for all they know you could be like I shut down my account for a while</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0198" trans="overlap">I'm pretty sure I deleted her again so</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0192">stopped using Facebook for a bit</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0198">yeah yeah exactly I was travelling around for a year</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0192">but erm people use Facebook differently don't they?</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0198">yeah depends on the purpose</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but the problem is when they see you posting on like <vocal desc="laugh"/> other people's things and they're like oh they click on you then</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0198">they are active</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0192">and they can't now look at your wall anymore it says you're not <unclear>free</unclear></u>
<u n="1220" who="S0198" trans="overlap">my <unclear>brother</unclear> got Facebook a couple of weeks ago and he's like he adds people and he looks on their walls be he doesn't there's no other he doesn't do anything he hasn't <trunc>comp</trunc> like done anything else on it I don't think he thinks it's really weird cos most people and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is the same has an account that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> set up for him doesn't doesn't even carry his mobile phone on him most of the time</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1222" who="S0198">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> not very up to date my family <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1223" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's not necessarily a bad thing</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0198" trans="overlap">my mum's the most the most tech savvy of them all how's that?</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and she and she couldn't even open my computer</u>
<u n="1226" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1227" who="S0198">she's alright on her mobile phone though</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0198">she knows everything on that she showed me something actually which is quite good</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0192">what has she shown you?</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0198">that when you type a message on my Samsung Iplayer cos she has a Samsung phone whenever you go to write a message you have to press the arrow that points upwards I mean that's probably the same on all Iphone things <pause dur="short"/> you press this arrow to get the upper case and when you hit it once it goes back to lower case but if you wanna write something just in upper case you have to keep pressing this arrow for every letter but if you just tap it quickly twice it locks it in upper case</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1233" who="S0198">that was good I didn't realise it did that</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0192">why did you need to write in upper case?</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0198">there was something I wanted to just keep in upper case I can't remember what <pause dur="short"/> like when it's like a initialism or</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0198">an abbreviation or something</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0192">I find it crazy that we have two cases</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0192" trans="overlap">like there aren't many languages I can think of that</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0198">have an upper case and a lower case that just adds a bit surely learners are just like why?</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0192">it's a whole nother alphabet</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0192">just for</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0198" trans="overlap">they get it wrong my <trunc>s</trunc> my university students they would start sentences with the wrong thing always</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no no definitely yeah</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0198">like because or something and then write it in lower case</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0198">and then do some upper case thing somewhere it was quite bad actually</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0192">yeah as I said they always wrote insubordinate er subordinate clauses</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0192">and then yeah wooden</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0198">it's like they just I guess they're just translating <unclear>that</unclear> much</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0192">the capitalisation was incorrect</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0198">the most relevant part which is possible</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0192">yeah but there's no harm correcting them I correct it I'm pretty thorough with my correction</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0198">yeah you do need to correct them</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0192">and I know people are like er you know puts puts them off like you gotta and I'm not going to correct everything like but if I'm going around class and I see stuff that's wrong quite often they're not writing very much it's just like a paragraph or something</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0192">you know what I mean like?</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0198">if that</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0192">couple of lines I'll correct that because that's accuracy as far as I'm concerned</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0192">if it's fluency then I won't correct it so harsh</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0192">so I take that er correction to writing also</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0192">but like I definitely correct their capitalisation and their commas and all that kind of stuff I teach punctuation a little bit</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0192">yeah just simple stuff you know about erm conditional sentences if they're reversed not putting a comma in it</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0198">a comma in yeah they seem to like knowing information like that</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0192">I teach them about clauses and once you're talking about clauses you have to talk about commas you can't not talk about punctuation</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0198" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> punctuation yeah</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0192">erm they understand a question mark they don't have a problem with that</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0198">no just forming questions can be difficult <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1276" who="S0192">really difficult</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0192">has nobody taught them?</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0198">W H movement <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1280" who="S0192" trans="overlap">transformation or <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0198">is that what it's called? is it called something else?</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0192">Chomsky's syntactic theory transformational grammar universal grammar I'm not sure it's like</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1284" who="S0192">transformational <unclear>X bar</unclear> theory I think was an old name but they don't seem to use <unclear>X bar</unclear> anymore it's very confusing cos I told you how very</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it's cos of Xbox I reckon it just makes people go oh X bar</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0192">yeah so erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah if only they'd have taught them about W H movement and Noel subjects and all that kind of stuff and it might be alright</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0198">maybe they are taught it in Korean but it doesn't seem to pass it over</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0192">I mean I need to have a look at some more indirect question er cos I had problems teaching erm sorry object questions direct object questions</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0192">subject questions are a piece of piss</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0198">yeah but direct object</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0192">because you just replace the subject pronoun with the the answer or whatever it is</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0198">no it's very easy</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0192">who eats ice cream? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> eats ice cream it's very easy just replace the who with the who</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0198" trans="overlap">just the pronoun and the relative pronoun</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0192">but if you have a question like</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0198">is that <unclear>right?</unclear></u>
<u n="1298" who="S0192">how do you wear your clothes? <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1299" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1300" who="S0192">if you're getting them to make that question</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0192">so how do you wear your clothes? I wear my clothes <pause dur="short"/> no the the original the sorry the deep structure would be you how do you wear your clothes? you wear your clothes how?</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0198">how? yeah</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0192">you wear your clothes how? and then do is one of those <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>auxiling</unclear> areas can't use a dummy one it just comes out</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it's a dummy yeah</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0192">it just appears because it doesn't have an auxiling</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it does do</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0192">how do you wear your clothes? do you wear your clothes how? you wear your clothes how? <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then you just change the subject pronouns for yourself I wear my clothes <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="1309" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1310" who="S0192">be simpler</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I've just be waiting for you to <unclear>actually</unclear> answer the question how do you wear your clothes? I wear my clothes off the side no</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0192">I thought well was fine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1313" who="S0198">well yeah I wear my clothes vintage <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1314" who="S0192">needs an adverb doesn't it? that one</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0198">erm</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0192">I wear my clothes</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0198">swimmingly</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0192">yeah I wear my clothes appropriately</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0198">swimmingly</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0192">I wear my clothes dependent on the context and situation</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0192">that might be my answer</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0198">doesn't sound right</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0192">yeah that book's gonna be a bitch <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1325" who="S0198">which one?</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0192">analysing English sentences and minimalist approach</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0198">oh it's the bottom one</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0192">I can't read that until <unclear/></u>
<u n="1329" who="S0198">it looks massive</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0192">should be fun should be fun</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0198">getting back to the books</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0192">and now you're actually studying it like you're definitely doing that module you can't allow yourself to be like er <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1333" who="S0198">oh yeah you've just gotta deal with it</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0198">figure it out</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0192">cos I mean maybe before when I read read through the whole books I might get to bits and I was like oh my god this is dragging this bit</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0198">I'll worry about this later</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0192">I know it's just like no I've gotta learn this I have to actually know this</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0198">that's why we've spent the last two days just reading</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0198">that's still <unclear/> but it's gone quickly <unclear>dear</unclear></u>
<u n="1342" who="S0192">yeah too quickly how much input have you had? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1343" who="S0198">maybe too much and not enough at the same time I feel like a student on erm finals week in Korea</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0198">I'm gonna start becoming we're gonna start waking up at six AM and studying until eleven PM</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0192">well that's the thing as well if we erm if we realise we don't have have enough time we might just have to cut some sleep time</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0198">yeah basically <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1348" who="S0192">we do get a good amount of sleep time so</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0192">if we're going to bed at eleven and waking up at seven</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0198">I was on seven <trunc>ho</trunc>hours I wasn't sleeping more than seven hours before once I got back recently in the last couple of months</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you could get down to six and be okay</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0192">I wouldn't wanna go much below six</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0198">no anything five and a half sounds er</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0192">yeah it's horrible</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0198">sounds groggy</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0192">yeah six hours I reckon I could survive on it'd probably start to wear me out after a little while</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0198">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1360" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0198">I used to think five was good</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> as long as you've got five</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0198" trans="overlap">six at the weekend and after five I didn't I could get heavy headed from dreaming too much</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0198">I like to be in that nice sedated period between one and er between bedtime and five mm</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0198"><unclear>nice</unclear></u>
<u n="1368" who="S0192">was it worth it or not?</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0198">what?</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0192">a third cigarette</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0198">maybe</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0192">it's just terrible</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0198">I do need a wee</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0192">one beer three cigarettes do you?</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0198">yeah but I can hold it in for a little while longer</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0198">well well</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0192">don't need to go right <unclear/></u>
<u n="1379" who="S0198">well</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0192">this is directional this thing so <pause dur="short"/> that way's probably not the best <unclear>idea</unclear></u>
<u n="1381" who="S0198">how much can I go or can I not go?</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0192">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0198">to the toilet</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0192">erm if you just give it another minute</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0198">until it's at ten</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0198">no that's fine</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0198">yeah okay fair enough</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0192">maybe a little bit over so we get a bit more</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0198">just to get that extra roundness of figures</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0192">yeah because sometimes it's under</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0198">yeah and sometimes it's over</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0192">I don't</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it's good to underestimate for everything though isn't it? budgets timings</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0198">any other <unclear/> er</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0192"><unclear/> leftover money budget's working out okay we need to check the budget and <pause dur="short"/> see next week yeah if I can have all that money at the beginning of next week</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0198">are we gonna set up a bank account then?</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0192">are you happy to?</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0198">yeah when would we need to do that?</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0192">Monday or Tuesday depends on how many</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0198">we should yeah make that one of our I mean Monday might be good cos we shouldn't have to get any food in we'll do another shop on Saturday or Sunday oh no we shouldn't have to do well might have to <pause dur="short"/> ah it doesn't really matter does it? any day's the same apart from Monday cos my parents are coming up</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0192">I've just thought about how</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0198">so Tuesday maybe unless we do it first thing Monday morning before they arrive</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0192">Monday morning</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0198">nine o'clock sort of thing</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0192">what time do they arrive?</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0198">they won't be here before <pause dur="short"/> ten thirty I don't think?</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0192">oh so it's quick cos the banks don't open till nine</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0198">mm should be doable though shouldn't it? <pause dur="short"/> look there's another spider there we're making a they know they like sending a been sending a message out to each other to bloody well come</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/> not too bad <pause dur="long"/> here is safe</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0198">come and live in our house they start figuring out spider <unclear>mones</unclear></u>
<u n="1414" who="S0192">spider mones</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0198"><unclear/> to spiders</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like pheromones</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0198"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1418" who="S0192">why can't they just release pheromones?</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0198">well they can release pheromones <vocal desc="laugh"/> of course they can <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why I would have a different name</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0192">humournomes</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0198">yeah I didn't just mean like mm male humans have pheromones is it the same one?</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0192">erm that's a good question I believe we have pheromones I believe a pheromone is any kind of smell that transmits information erm <pause dur="short"/> usually sexual but not always I don't think</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0198"><unclear/> would be called this one just yeah</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0192">and I guess it is usually sexual might indicate I don't know? like when you're dying do you release any kind of pheromone? <vocal desc="laugh"/> is it purely sexual?</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0198">yeah or are there other names for other smells?</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0192">I'll google it</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0198">that we release?</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
