<text id="SGV4">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:25:59</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-02-16</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0618 S0619</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>The Jana Hotel in Tarnow, Poland</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Discussing films, Australia, teaching/marking, sleep, learning a language, private students, gym/strength. </topics>
		<activity>Two friends talking about various topics (see 9 above) in the Jana Hotel in Tarnow, Poland.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T06</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0618">
				<exactage>42</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge/Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months on and off</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>unemployed/ Some part-time private TEFL teacher/ Semi-retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0619">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury, Lancashire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Nort West: Lancs, Greater Manchester</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>nearly 4 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher of English as a foreign Language</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0618"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0619">hello</u>
<u n="3" who="S0618">here were are</u>
<u n="4" who="S0619">we're talking about we're talking about the film The Castle</u>
<u n="5" who="S0618">The Castle</u>
<u n="6" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0618">well you were yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0619">it's Australian it's completely ridiculous er <pause dur="short"/> anyway it's about er a family who live in a house and the local airport wants to extend the runway and get rid of their house</u>
<u n="9" who="S0618">uhu</u>
<u n="10" who="S0619">er and tries to buy it off them anyway but the dad <pause dur="short"/> he's a bit of er character anyway and in one scene he's trying to someone asks if he wants to buy some things I can't remember what er and he goes tell <pause dur="short"/> him he's dreaming</u>
<u n="11" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0618">is he Irish?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0619">no he's Australian</u>
<u n="14" who="S0618">Australian</u>
<u n="15" who="S0619">and since then it's the family phrase</u>
<u n="16" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="pol"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0618"><foreign lang="pol"/></u>
<u n="18" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="pol"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0618">yeah <foreign lang="pol"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0619">this thing please</u>
<u n="21" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay</u>
<u n="22" who="S0619">thank you so much</u>
<u n="23" who="S0618">so should have done prep for that anyway</u>
<u n="24" who="S0619">er I like this lady <pause dur="short"/> I once saw her and I was with like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0618" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="26" who="S0619">and she gave me the most sympathetic look <vocal desc="laugh"/> like I know I'm so sorry help me help <vocal desc="laugh"/> funny</u>
<u n="27" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> that was an Australian thing going on there as well then <pause dur="short"/> with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0619">what do you mean I hate Australians?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no well I'm just sort of linking into the conversation about the castle</u>
<u n="30" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh right so Australia</u>
<u n="31" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0619">oh dear</u>
<u n="33" who="S0618">I didn't like Australia I've got to say I found it too restrictive of freedoms and rights and too much authoritarian stuff of</u>
<u n="34" who="S0619">oh yeah I've heard similar things</u>
<u n="35" who="S0618" trans="overlap">walk here and don't walk here and walk on the left and no skateboards and dogs on leads and seemed to be rule after rule</u>
<u n="36" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="37" who="S0618">and then I went to New Zealand and it was like do what you like mate</u>
<u n="38" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0618">it's like anything goes just generally be kind to people and</u>
<u n="40" who="S0619" trans="overlap">it's a good rule</u>
<u n="41" who="S0618">you'll get along fine</u>
<u n="42" who="S0619">yeah it's a good rule for life <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0618">yeah it's good</u>
<u n="44" who="S0619">good</u>
<u n="45" who="S0618">so yeah thank you for coming round the other night</u>
<u n="46" who="S0619">it was really nice</u>
<u n="47" who="S0618">do you know it was lovely and do you know what? after I'd gone I thought yes those are the kind of friends you need they fuck off in time for Match of the Day</u>
<u n="48" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0618">so yeah that was great so you went and I think I had not really that long until match of the day was on and Arsenal beat Leicester in the ninety-fifth minute and got the winning goal</u>
<u n="50" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yay</u>
<u n="51" who="S0618">brilliant game erm so yeah thoroughly enjoyed those highlights anyway that was good</u>
<u n="52" who="S0619">good</u>
<u n="53" who="S0618">yep</u>
<u n="54" who="S0619">I've just got really no news just trying to tick off all of these things that I've got to do for</u>
<u n="55" who="S0618">you sound a bit overwhelmed <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0619">only cos I've got you know setting tests and marking tests and I'm getting all of these kids to actually write the essays</u>
<u n="57" who="S0618">oh god</u>
<u n="58" who="S0619">that they are supposed to have written in sort of in December or November er and then they hand them in and I'm like I don't want them because it means I have to read them</u>
<u n="59" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0619">on top of the twenty-eight that I have to mark from the mock exam</u>
<u n="61" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0619">and they send it by email and I've just got this constant stream of like emails that I've got to do <vocal desc="laugh"/> just <pause dur="short"/> don't care</u>
<u n="63" who="S0618" trans="overlap">is your work email different to your personal email? what I did with mine because it's the same was I on my Iphone hid it in a folder that I had to</u>
<u n="64" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="65" who="S0618">do about four swipes to get to the folder so whenever I open my phone for everyday functions and purposes I didn't see the growing number of emails</u>
<u n="66" who="S0619">nice</u>
<u n="67" who="S0618">yeah I think it's just a psychological thingy to give you a break from that I guess</u>
<u n="68" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0619">and I'm making <unclear/> like a kind of needs analysis by email I think because it's <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I think there's something in the <pause dur="short"/> this type of way of communication they've got to email me they've got to start with hi <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's not like they're filling in a worksheet with how they feel about the course and stuff and da da da</u>
<u n="71" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm hm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0619">uh they're just like answering these questions by email and I think it sort of doesn't break down a barrier necessarily but it makes us a bit more one to one with each student er</u>
<u n="73" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and are you emailing them back?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0619">yeah and they always try and add</u>
<u n="75" who="S0618" trans="overlap">that's cool</u>
<u n="76" who="S0619">even if it's oh thanks so much we'll look at this</u>
<u n="77" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0619">er I've got this I'm getting quite stressed about two of them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0619">and like going home and going how can I solve this problem? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0618">yeah what's the</u>
<u n="82" who="S0619">and they're just they're shy</u>
<u n="83" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="84" who="S0619">so I said I was trying to talk to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yesterday and she was like well you can't change their personalities</u>
<u n="85" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0619">er so not really sure what you want to do? it's like I don't want them to fail <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0618">ah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0619">erm but they're you know they're so shy there's a couple of boys like this and they just won't look er at the person they're talking to</u>
<u n="89" who="S0618">mm hm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0619">and they sort of look straight ahead or they look at the table and this boy yesterday he's so sweet and so nice and I just bullied him and I was like right you get a point every time you look at your partner and he was like doing sort of the quickest movements so he didn't have to look at the person sat next to him</u>
<u n="91" who="S0618" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0619">and I was like <pause dur="short"/> yeah they just need more social skills and social interaction</u>
<u n="93" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm hm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0619">and you can see the difference between boys and girls because girls are much more open and personable er the boys are slightly more er</u>
<u n="95" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> reticent</u>
<u n="96" who="S0619">for sure yeah they're just a little bit oh I can't look at someone in the eye it would be weird <vocal desc="laugh"/> what?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0618">yeah that's what people do which is normal everyday</u>
<u n="98" who="S0619" trans="overlap">they kind of have this like attitude yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0619">something attached to it sort of too erm emotional or too <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I don't know how to explain it <pause dur="short"/> but it's definitely a difference at this age between guys and girls and the girls are like so tell me more tell me more and the boys like <vocal desc="laugh"/> just don't look at anywhere apart from at her face</u>
<u n="101" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0619">and then these girls are like well done you're trying your best and these boys are just not responding to you</u>
<u n="103" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> not getting it yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0619">just like grab their head and look at them at each other</u>
<u n="105" who="S0618"><unclear/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0619">yay tea</u>
<u n="107" who="S0618">oh lovely</u>
<u n="108" who="S0619">oh dear</u>
<u n="109" who="S0618">drink here</u>
<u n="110" who="S0619">tonight <pause dur="long"/> thank you</u>
<u n="111" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><foreign lang="pol"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0619">okay nice</u>
<u n="113" who="S0618">great <unclear>posture</unclear></u>
<u n="114" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0618">she either has a lower back injury or she does a lot of yoga <pause dur="short"/> one of the two</u>
<u n="116" who="S0619">I didn't notice I don't think</u>
<u n="117" who="S0618" trans="overlap">have you ever had lemon with your mint tea?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0619">no</u>
<u n="119" who="S0618">no me either <pause dur="short"/> hm <pause dur="short"/> ah hang on a minute this is mint-flavoured black tea</u>
<u n="120" who="S0619">ah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0618">which will keep me up at night so I'm going to have a mostly watery <pause dur="short"/> lemony <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0619">ah ha</u>
<u n="123" who="S0618">hessian infusion in fact I might just have water and lemon <vocal desc="laugh"/> and take my tea back home for the morning</u>
<u n="124" who="S0619">that's nice yes waste not want not</u>
<u n="125" who="S0618">I'll do that that's why you get the lemon but no too late for me to have caffeine not after six o'clock <pause dur="short"/> funny thing though my sleep patterns since I've kind of sort of I don't know said to my body right do your own thing do what you need to do</u>
<u n="126" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0618">and some nights I'll sleep for ten plus hours and it's wonderful</u>
<u n="128" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="129" who="S0618">and other nights I'll sleep for five hours and it's wonderful <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0619">good</u>
<u n="131" who="S0618">and I'll wake up as refreshed on five hours as I will on ten but it's great</u>
<u n="132" who="S0619">try this lemon tea do you want a dunk of my tea back just for a bit of flavour?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0618">no lemon will be flavour enough thank you <pause dur="short"/> wonder where my tea bag got to <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0619">sorry I've eaten it</u>
<u n="135" who="S0618">there will probably be a full scale search later</u>
<u n="136" who="S0619">yeah like we've thrown it and stuck it to the ceiling</u>
<u n="137" who="S0618">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah stuck it down the side of the sofa or something</u>
<u n="138" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0618">she's just locked us in</u>
<u n="140" who="S0619">has she?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0618">yeah what's the time? oh shit we need to keep an eye on that I need to run for my bus well take a leisurely amble for my bus in about fifteen minutes</u>
<u n="142" who="S0619">sure <pause dur="short"/> cool</u>
<u n="143" who="S0618" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> I'll double check that time oh</u>
<u n="144" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0619">yeah of course</u>
<u n="146" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay</u>
<u n="147" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0618">last orders</u>
<u n="149" who="S0619">at five to nine</u>
<u n="150" who="S0618">five to nine I know <pause dur="short"/> I'll have water with lemon please <pause dur="short"/> right where's my bus app thing? er <pause dur="short"/> twenty-one twenty-six cool <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="151" who="S0619">yes I just going to do a little bit of Spanish when I get home and then go to bed</u>
<u n="152" who="S0618">oh good for you</u>
<u n="153" who="S0619">I had a week off and this app is so unforgiving if you take time off you've basically gotta do</u>
<u n="154" who="S0618">this duo lingo?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0619">uhu you got to do every skill again</u>
<u n="156" who="S0618">nasty</u>
<u n="157" who="S0619">er and it's just gonna take me for ever <vocal desc="sigh"/> I need like a day off just to do that</u>
<u n="158" who="S0618">you're very good though persisting</u>
<u n="159" who="S0619">yeah I'm going to get a teacher <pause dur="short"/> at some point in April when I get paid in April</u>
<u n="160" who="S0618">yeah?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0619">get paid in March contact lenses get paid in April conversation teacher</u>
<u n="162" who="S0618">uhu <pause dur="short"/> cool</u>
<u n="163" who="S0619">yep and then I'm going to get extra personal training some <pause dur="short"/> april May June</u>
<u n="164" who="S0618">good for you</u>
<u n="165" who="S0619">so by the end of June when I go <trunc>t</trunc> away I'm going to be able to speak Spanish be so strong and er be able to see <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0618">yay great so</u>
<u n="167" who="S0619">all of these things are great</u>
<u n="168" who="S0618">maybe that's the issue with these young men not making eye contact maybe their eyesight is so good <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0619">well so they're sat next to someone and they look in someone's eyes and it's so HD that they go blind</u>
<u n="170" who="S0618">it could be it it could be it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0619">funny</u>
<u n="172" who="S0618">we've got a few more years of degeneration on them so maybe you don't see so deeply</u>
<u n="173" who="S0619">degenerating <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's rubbish</u>
<u n="174" who="S0618">I agree it's all belief</u>
<u n="175" who="S0619">yeah and my nose has just been so bad after this cold</u>
<u n="176" who="S0618">oh yeah how are you getting on with your squirty thing?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0619">I started again but with a it's the same active ingredient but a much weaker</u>
<u n="178" who="S0618">mm hm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0619">thing er <pause dur="short"/> so I'm doing two both nostrils at morning and night</u>
<u n="180" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0619">just until this</u>
<u n="182" who="S0618">till you get your lungs sorted again</u>
<u n="183" who="S0619">yeah maybe until Thursday when I finish all of this medication</u>
<u n="184" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0619">erm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0618">I think it would be crazy to be still trying to come off of that when you're quite clearly breathing is a bonus at the moment yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah so after the end of this week I'll have to start that again so it's just I'm really trying to sort of in a positive way be like yes this is the final purge</u>
<u n="188" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yay <pause dur="short"/> mm hm yeah definitely</u>
<u n="189" who="S0619" trans="overlap">but at the same time I'm like this is fucking wank because I've been ill for a week and it's set back this this and this I've had to take loads of time off so I'm losing er money but I suppose I'm making back money with this girl</u>
<u n="190" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0619">so</u>
<u n="192" who="S0618">private students are fab definitely recommended and that feeling that you said that you had about</u>
<u n="193" who="S0619">oh god I feel awful should I got her purse out at the end</u>
<u n="194" who="S0618">you need to get over that because I remember that exact same feeling of like oh my god I've just had a fantastic hour of what brilliant conversation and I would be sort of buzzing at the end of it and then I get paid for it but</u>
<u n="195" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0618">I think now yeah you know I want all of my paid employments forever more to feel this way</u>
<u n="197" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="198" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0619">that's a good way to think about it</u>
<u n="200" who="S0618" trans="overlap">you know whether that's in language teaching or whatever it is</u>
<u n="201" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0618">I still want that woohoo kind of a feeling and that yeah love this and I'm getting paid for it how good is life?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0619">oh shit</u>
<u n="204" who="S0618">yes good sometimes I come out of lessons and I feel sort of realty happy</u>
<u n="205" who="S0618">yeah good</u>
<u n="206" who="S0619">er sometimes I don't <vocal desc="laugh"/> sometimes I just hate them</u>
<u n="207" who="S0618">Mondays</u>
<u n="208" who="S0619">my Monday class though is it's getting better</u>
<u n="209" who="S0618">you said they were improving</u>
<u n="210" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0618">good</u>
<u n="212" who="S0619">yesterday was good <pause dur="short"/> yesterday was really nice</u>
<u n="213" who="S0618">good</u>
<u n="214" who="S0619">so</u>
<u n="215" who="S0618">that's great</u>
<u n="216" who="S0619">yeah yeah yeah there's just a couple with a bit of attitude and a couple who are shy and you know even if they're sat outside the room waiting to start they don't talk to each other</u>
<u n="217" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0619">where as in all the other classes</u>
<u n="219" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0619">they do</u>
<u n="221" who="S0618">you can't shut them up and yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0619">yeah and they just sort of chat away to each other but these ones they're just</u>
<u n="223" who="S0618">hm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0619">there's <pause dur="short"/> I don't know no connection between them</u>
<u n="225" who="S0618">what day is this? is this Tuesdays?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0619">Monday</u>
<u n="227" who="S0618">Monday and is this</u>
<u n="228" who="S0619">the first one in the basement</u>
<u n="229" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah in the basement</u>
<u n="230" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0618">you could set them a homework next week of erm when you arrive and you're waiting to come into the classroom next week learn something about somebody you've never spoken to and that can be your beginning of the class thing who did you talk to and what did you learn</u>
<u n="232" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah even if they do it in Polish like I just want them to talk to each other</u>
<u n="233" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0619">erm cos they don't know who they're going to be with in the exams so they and you know they perform much better in the exam if they get on well with the person</u>
<u n="235" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm hm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0619">it's just common sense you feel comfortable you feel more relaxed you have this good relationship and you get scored</u>
<u n="237" who="S0618">certainly level of trust</u>
<u n="238" who="S0619">you get marked on the relationship you have with the other person</u>
<u n="239" who="S0618">mm hm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0619">er so if people come in as friends they do better than people who don't but</u>
<u n="241" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0619">anyway</u>
<u n="243" who="S0618">can you do any sort of physical icebreakers with them?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0619">not in that room</u>
<u n="245" who="S0618">oh crikey yeah not in the basement hm <pause dur="short"/> or maybe see if once a month can you change room for a bigger room?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0619">I don't know I've already asked before</u>
<u n="247" who="S0618" trans="overlap">do swapsies with somebody</u>
<u n="248" who="S0619"><unclear/> could have a different room but</u>
<u n="249" who="S0618">who else works on that evening? <pause dur="short"/> who's in <trunc>ele</trunc> erm not eleven or twelve what are the upstairs rooms called?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0619" trans="overlap">five and six</u>
<u n="251" who="S0618">because they're quite yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0619">all kids they won't move the kids</u>
<u n="253" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh bugger no they won't</u>
<u n="254" who="S0619">and it's at half three so it's</u>
<u n="255" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh jeepers who</u>
<u n="256" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0618">yeah who is on the middle floor?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0619">kids there's only one big classroom</u>
<u n="259" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> cripes</u>
<u n="260" who="S0619">and it's the one with chalk wallpaper</u>
<u n="261" who="S0618" trans="overlap">all of the other classrooms are filled with kids</u>
<u n="262" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0618">bloody hell <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="264" who="S0619">children are small they take up less space <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0618">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0619">why do they get the nice big classrooms with projectors and <pause dur="short"/> tVs</u>
<u n="267" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah interactive whiteboards</u>
<u n="268" who="S0619">and we get the shitty one</u>
<u n="269" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0619">with twelve big people who don't fit</u>
<u n="271" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> couldn't do a trade with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for a week?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0619">no cos I have a lesson five minutes later</u>
<u n="273" who="S0618">ah okay</u>
<u n="274" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0618">bugger it's just not happening is it?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0619">I know so I'm just going to struggle on through until the end of the year</u>
<u n="277" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0619">with Easter I lose a class</u>
<u n="279" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="280" who="S0619">er I think I lose a few classes actually because it's on a Monday and er <pause dur="short"/> it finishes end of May anyway so it won't be long <pause dur="short"/> seven minutes <pause dur="short"/> what time do we have to get this to?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0618">oh ten it's fine</u>
<u n="282" who="S0619">oh okay</u>
<u n="283" who="S0618">erm so no quarter past nine <unclear/> erm no hang on no I said ten past didn't I?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0618">there or thereabouts <pause dur="short"/> better if I'm a couple minutes late</u>
<u n="286" who="S0619" trans="overlap">cool I'll be home by twenty-five past in my pyjamas</u>
<u n="287" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> by half past</u>
<u n="288" who="S0619">yep</u>
<u n="289" who="S0618">yay</u>
<u n="290" who="S0619">my room is so tidy</u>
<u n="291" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh wow</u>
<u n="292" who="S0619">I put my bed away <pause dur="short"/> and turned it into a sofa</u>
<u n="293" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh for your <pause dur="short"/> for your <unclear/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0619">it looks fucking great in here</u>
<u n="295" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0618">did you think I should do this more often</u>
<u n="297" who="S0619">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0618">I often do and I really tidy things</u>
<u n="299" who="S0619">like god it looks so nice</u>
<u n="300" who="S0618">like if I make my bed properly and fold my blankets and stretch my sheet out again and pop my pillows up I think ah it's very inviting</u>
<u n="301" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="302" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's good</u>
<u n="303" who="S0619">yeah it looks great <pause dur="short"/> so I think it is good cos it means you know once a week I really have a motivation to deep clean</u>
<u n="304" who="S0618">good</u>
<u n="305" who="S0619">not that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sort the person who would notice</u>
<u n="306" who="S0618">no</u>
<u n="307" who="S0619">she's one of those like young people who's like I hate cleaning it's the worst</u>
<u n="308" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but that's another advantage of private students I found it sort of helped me keep on top of stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> yeah because again I don't really care that much of other people's opinions but I just feel you know to be a professional I need to be offering a professional environment <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0619">yeah so it was it was nice <pause dur="short"/> she's just she's not shy she's really outgoing she's just really just unsure about her English</u>
<u n="310" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0619">like she just doesn't think she's good</u>
<u n="312" who="S0618">that seems to be a common trait in Poland lack of confidence</u>
<u n="313" who="S0619" trans="overlap">it's just a yeah it's just a cultural thing I suppose</u>
<u n="314" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0619">er and I was thinking about this today and I was gonna ask on Twitter so you know in England <pause dur="short"/> if you if you're doing something would you say oh I'm really not very good at this <pause dur="short"/> like as a preface like you know before you do it would you sort of give this disclaimer?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0618">some people do</u>
<u n="317" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0618">I tend not to hang around with people like that <pause dur="short"/> cos it just seems to me like a little bit of a <pause dur="short"/> control drama</u>
<u n="319" who="S0619" trans="overlap">it's too self-defecating</u>
<u n="320" who="S0618">yeah and they're being a bit of a victim and expecting some kind of rescuer to say oh no you're not you're great</u>
<u n="321" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> uhu</u>
<u n="322" who="S0618">erm</u>
<u n="323" who="S0619">yeah it's people who go oh I'm so fat <vocal desc="laugh"/> well either you you are fat or you're not fat so <vocal desc="laugh"/> er</u>
<u n="324" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0619">so you know <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I don't think I'm sort of person who would do that but at the same time I don't think <unclear/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I don't think you are</u>
<u n="327" who="S0619">is that erm I don't think I do things that I can't do or that I'm not very good at I either get good or stop doing it</u>
<u n="328" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> I'm just thinking about</u>
<u n="329" who="S0619"><unclear/> good at persevering</u>
<u n="330" who="S0618">you at the gym and <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0619">that's not me going <pause dur="short"/> I don't say</u>
<u n="332" who="S0618">come on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you can do it and me telling him to fuck off</u>
<u n="333" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no I don't say erm I'm not very good at this</u>
<u n="334" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0619">I just go I can't do this it's fucking stupid because I know my limits and I know I can't actually do it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0618">so it's a little bit different saying I can't do it before you've even tried</u>
<u n="337" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I but I would never go in and be like oh I'm not very strong I'd just go in and be like I am so strong I'm the strongest girl here <vocal desc="laugh"/> even if it's not true sometimes I have too high an opinion of like my own er what's the word?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0618">physical capabilities</u>
<u n="339" who="S0619">thank you</u>
<u n="340" who="S0618">you're welcome</u>
<u n="341" who="S0619" trans="overlap">physical capabilities er <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I'm like yeah I can do that <vocal desc="laugh"/> I tried to do a pull up the other day I was like right I want to be able to do a pull up by April he was like well have a go now <vocal desc="laugh"/> he he he and I just sort of hung there</u>
<u n="342" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0619">he was like go on go on you can do it <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was just like <pause dur="short"/> hanging like a pomegranate is what I thought</u>
<u n="344" who="S0618">oh pomegranate they're in season and in the shops</u>
<u n="345" who="S0619">are they?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0618">just speaking of pomegranates yes I bought one of the other day</u>
<u n="347" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> makes me think of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I don't know it's just like I'm just hanging here like a fucking sack of potatoes <vocal desc="laugh"/> can't move</u>
<u n="348" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but you will you will</u>
<u n="349" who="S0619">yeah I will I will move even if I can just do one by April I'll be so enthused</u>
<u n="350" who="S0618">god <pause dur="short"/> I used to be so strong I suppose I think sort of age eighteen to thirty-one</u>
<u n="351" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="352" who="S0618">I used to work for this <trunc>re</trunc>recycling organisation lugging washing machines up four flights of stairs with no lift and I went to the gym as well and I used to do pull ups and</u>
<u n="353" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0618">and those dip things</u>
<u n="355" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="356" who="S0618">all sorts knock ten out no problem</u>
<u n="357" who="S0619">mm hm mm hm</u>
<u n="358" who="S0618">yeah few sets</u>
<u n="359" who="S0619" trans="overlap">it's taking me forever</u>
<u n="360" who="S0618">but that's life back in the day</u>
<u n="361" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="362" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0619">it's gonna it's taking forever to build that kind of <pause dur="short"/> I think you know that's that's real strength</u>
<u n="364" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="365" who="S0619">like being able to move yourself around and it's fine being able to do these kind of assisted things or doing things with</u>
<u n="366" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm hm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0619">bar bells or doing things with weights but <pause dur="short"/> that's like the real test of strength in my opinion</u>
<u n="368" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0619">so struggling with it <pause dur="short"/> but I know that everything will come together eventually</u>
<u n="370" who="S0618">do you have any core condition classes yoga or Pilates or anything like that? that might <pause dur="short"/> I mean seriously</u>
<u n="371" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0618">give some thought to some Pilates particularly <pause dur="short"/> as my experiences is that everything comes from the core</u>
<u n="373" who="S0619" trans="overlap">the core yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0618">so if your core is really strong you'll find it so much easier to do every single other exercise</u>
<u n="375" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu and my core isn't strong er in fact my core is incredibly weak it's probably the weakest part so it really affects my balance</u>
<u n="376" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="377" who="S0619">so if I do anything that requires balance like lunges or squats</u>
<u n="378" who="S0618">mm <pause dur="short"/> then maybe some yoga</u>
<u n="379" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> I'm all over the place so</u>
<u n="380" who="S0618">yoga's a lot of balance</u>
<u n="381" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0619">but I'm at the moment I'm every other day that I'm not training with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm doing this core day like core and cardio</u>
<u n="384" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> good for you yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0619">it's awful er</u>
<u n="386" who="S0618">I don't necessarily just mean you know like do a hundred sit-ups or whatever</u>
<u n="387" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah I know but it's</u>
<u n="388" who="S0618">but you know proper stuff like planks and</u>
<u n="389" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0618">I suppose Pilates gets into such technicalities and such tiny tiny movements <pause dur="short"/> that can hurt like hell but</u>
<u n="391" who="S0619">mm hm</u>
<u n="392" who="S0618">yeah that might be the difference</u>
<u n="393" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0619">mm <pause dur="short"/> so it's all gonna come together though I've got my sort of deadlines</u>
<u n="396" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yay</u>
<u n="397" who="S0619">so I'm just working towards them basically I can't get less fit I can't less strong</u>
<u n="398" who="S0618">mm hm</u>
<u n="399" who="S0619">so</u>
<u n="400" who="S0618">indeed <pause dur="short"/> that's good</u>
<u n="401" who="S0619">mm <pause dur="short"/> and he said we're trying something new on Friday <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0618">oh</u>
<u n="403" who="S0619">I was like what? like</u>
<u n="404" who="S0618">salsa</u>
<u n="405" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0619">it's a surprise I was like oh what is it? <vocal desc="laugh"/> he's so cryptic you need to come prepared what are you going to do? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0618">oh well keep the intrigue</u>
<u n="408" who="S0619">yes absolutely okay let's get the bill</u>
<u n="409" who="S0618">yeah ten past nine so it's about right what's tomorrow? Wednesday is it Wednesday tomorrow?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0619" trans="overlap">have you got any students tomorrow</u>
<u n="411" who="S0618">yes yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="413" who="S0619">and he's definitely my favourite I love <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0619">how old is he?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0618">er bit younger than me what's he? <vocal desc="misc"/> thirty-six seven eight something like that such a nice guy</u>
<u n="416" who="S0619">good</u>
<u n="417" who="S0618">and just really funny he laughs a lot I love that great trait</u>
<u n="418" who="S0619">good it is in any human</u>
<u n="419" who="S0618" trans="overlap">and he's <pause dur="short"/> and he's so funny and he's also <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> student twice a week and he said oh I got my test results from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> ninety-eight percent I said I bet you were gutted</u>
<u n="420" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0618">and he was he was kicking himself that he'd got a couple wrong</u>
<u n="422" who="S0619">oh bless</u>
<u n="423" who="S0618">yeah he's such a perfectionist he won't accept anything less than a hundred percent</u>
<u n="424" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> what level is he?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0618">erm he's technically speaking he's pre-intermediate but there are aspects of his conversations that I'd put it upper intermediate</u>
<u n="426" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah sure</u>
<u n="427" who="S0618">he's really is pretty fluent he's got a pretty big vocabulary erm falls down on prepositions particularly</u>
<u n="428" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="429" who="S0618">and particles sometimes but I can see an improvement just in the time I've known him and idioms that he likes he tends to remember and it's delightful when he just throws and idiom into the conversation I really like that</u>
<u n="430" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu uhu <pause dur="short"/> yeah my students are really impressing me at the moment in some of their writing</u>
<u n="431" who="S0618">good</u>
<u n="432" who="S0619">it's just yeah really great <pause dur="short"/> sing their praises like hats off to the director of this film</u>
<u n="433" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0619">it just really make me chuckle some of these these er things that they say</u>
<u n="435" who="S0618">cool</u>
<u n="436" who="S0619">okay bye</u>
<u n="437" who="S0618">right there we are yes nice talking again</u>
<u n="438" who="S0619">bye</u>
<u n="439" who="S0618">oh no find the off button now</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
