<text id="SH79">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:28:48</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-17</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0058 S0179</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's car</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Traffic, future plans</topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T03</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0058">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Corpus Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0179">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harpenden, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years, 7 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Consultant engineer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0058">there we are that's er</u>
<u n="2" who="S0179">you don't always pay for fuel <pause dur="short"/> I occasionally refuel by myself</u>
<u n="3" who="S0058" trans="overlap">true <pause dur="short"/> yes but</u>
<u n="4" who="S0179">whereas you never refuel without me</u>
<u n="5" who="S0058">true true</u>
<u n="6" who="S0179">wow <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0058">what's very exciting?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0179">they're rather imposing having three story houses at the end of this road you know</u>
<u n="9" who="S0058">is it a little bit <pause dur="short"/> it would be far nicer if there had just been erm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0179">two stories</u>
<u n="11" who="S0058">two stories yeah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0179">oh can you see the Coach house and if you look back down that way <pause dur="short"/> it's almost finished</u>
<u n="13" who="S0058">oh</u>
<u n="14" who="S0179">I think we should go in and look</u>
<u n="15" who="S0058">it's an interesting design <pause dur="short"/> it's got the erm</u>
<u n="16" who="S0179" trans="overlap">it's got <pause dur="short"/> it's got this one has got windows at the back as well <pause dur="short"/> the others haven't <pause dur="short"/> this has got a window in the kitchen and window</u>
<u n="17" who="S0058" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> that's interesting</u>
<u n="18" who="S0179">that one is actually might be quite steel</u>
<u n="19" who="S0058">yeah that's much better</u>
<u n="20" who="S0179" trans="overlap">it's freehold</u>
<u n="21" who="S0058">that is much better <pause dur="short"/> so you all you get a garage presumably and the top <pause dur="short"/> windows at the back</u>
<u n="22" who="S0179" trans="overlap">you get a garage a parking space erm and you have five windows not three</u>
<u n="23" who="S0058">oh that's better</u>
<u n="24" who="S0179">so there's still no window into the hallway <pause dur="short"/> but you get a window into the main bathroom and the</u>
<u n="25" who="S0058">what was the other?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0179">and the kitchen</u>
<u n="27" who="S0058" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0179">are you tempted?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> if we were buying again then that sounds er</u>
<u n="30" who="S0179">we wouldn't want to move away from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0058">ah <pause dur="short"/> it wouldn't be exactly miles away from them <pause dur="short"/> ah dear <pause dur="short"/> it wouldn't be worth getting out all the boxes and packing up again</u>
<u n="32" who="S0179">no <pause dur="short"/> er yeah thought so <pause dur="short"/> that was just a highlight that I was actually going to be on that corner of the road</u>
<u n="33" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0179">I don't clip a corner please</u>
<u n="35" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0179">ugh</u>
<u n="37" who="S0058">hmm <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> nice one</u>
<u n="38" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0058">do you think I should buy that iPod today?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="41" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it'll be it is</u>
<u n="42" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/> that jacket please</u>
<u n="43" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0058">erm I did that while I was out at bank <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah <pause dur="short"/> so a hundred pounds net cost <pause dur="short"/> which you know <pause dur="short"/> in all fairness when I rang to say about that Marks and Spencer's just had this extended guarantee is there anything you can do? She said well we do only have a one year guarantee but you know if anything happens after that we would of course you know give you customer service and try and help you and you know <pause dur="short"/> which was an a nice response</u>
<u n="46" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="47" who="S0058">erm and I think it's true <pause dur="short"/> I think if you went in and there was some kind of issue they would do their best <pause dur="short"/> but of course they just couldn't <pause dur="short"/> they can't give you unlimited</u>
<u n="48" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0058">warrantee cos it's not quite the same thing <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean er they probably have improved them a lot since my my first one so</u>
<u n="50" who="S0179" trans="overlap">well we know that</u>
<u n="51" who="S0058">well er I mean I guess they've had to</u>
<u n="52" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0058">they can't habitually break after a year any more</u>
<u n="54" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="55" who="S0058">because you'd never</u>
<u n="56" who="S0179">they never used to</u>
<u n="57" who="S0058">I heard some bad stories <pause dur="short"/> maybe it was my particular one was a had a particularly bad erm <pause dur="short"/> cos it <trunc>w</trunc> had like a disk <pause dur="short"/> like in sort of word <pause dur="short"/> cos there was a sort of rotating part</u>
<u n="58" who="S0179">erm hang on <pause dur="short"/> two things <pause dur="short"/> firstly can you pick my water bottle up <unclear/>floor <pause dur="short"/> which is really annoying <pause dur="short"/> and secondly you mean it was a hard drive not a flash drive</u>
<u n="59" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="61" who="S0058">erm which I mean possibly was there was more bits to break and more bits to overheat and</u>
<u n="62" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> much <pause dur="short"/> actually an interesting question I'm not sure if it uses hard or flash <pause dur="short"/> I assume flash</u>
<u n="63" who="S0058">I assume so <pause dur="short"/> you mean the new classic</u>
<u n="64" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0058">interesting to ask <pause dur="short"/> it's not something I've ever particularly looked at</u>
<u n="66" who="S0179">I'm pretty sure it must be</u>
<u n="67" who="S0058">it must be <pause dur="short"/> surely <pause dur="short"/> why would you have a hard disk like erm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0179">because it stores <unclear/> er much more mature technology <unclear/> would cooperate</u>
<u n="69" who="S0058">huh <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm sure it'll be fine</u>
<u n="70" who="S0179">well someone's keen</u>
<u n="71" who="S0058">ha ha they look quite intrepid don't they?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0058">going for a walk around the area <pause dur="short"/> which we should do at some point</u>
<u n="74" who="S0179">possibly <pause dur="short"/> I think there's just more interesting places to walk</u>
<u n="75" who="S0058">I know it's just if we're not particularly doing anything it's just a very kind of it's a way of doing a walk without much <pause dur="short"/> you know we wouldn't have to drive very far</u>
<u n="76" who="S0179" trans="overlap">but when are we not particularly doing something?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0058">no true</u>
<u n="78" who="S0179">if we ever become bored yes</u>
<u n="79" who="S0058">ha yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe unlikely</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="80" who="S0179">actually I'll give <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a ring when we're in town <pause dur="short"/> cos he might like a lift out if he's going to see his friend first</u>
<u n="81" who="S0058">oh right oh is he <anon type="place"/>? Ah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0058">yeah true actually if he's sort of leaving anyway then er</u>
<u n="84" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0058">was he gonna drive through though? So he has his car all through the night?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0179">well he doesn't have a car so</u>
<u n="87" who="S0058">I could have sworn Dan had a car <pause dur="short"/> okay good that's fine then <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> why did I think Dan had a car?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0179">Cos his friend has a car?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0058">no no I just</u>
<u n="90" who="S0179">well he might do <pause dur="short"/> I don't think he does</u>
<u n="91" who="S0058" trans="overlap">no no maybe not <pause dur="short"/> um I'm I'm not sure why I thought that <pause dur="short"/> I just kind of assumed <pause dur="short"/> maybe it's just erm associated with engineers cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> both have cars <pause dur="short"/> and you obviously <pause dur="short"/> ha</u>
<u n="92" who="S0179">yes well</u>
<u n="93" who="S0058">no car  Was he getting erm the bus out do you think?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0179">I've no idea but</u>
<u n="95" who="S0058">yes um he might choose to cycle but he's a long way from where he</u>
<u n="96" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well anyway <pause dur="short"/> either way <pause dur="short"/> yeah give him a ring on <pause dur="short"/> oh there's the other thing you were going to look for in John Louis was  gloves</u>
<u n="98" who="S0179">actually I could look in another sports shop</u>
<u n="99" who="S0058">yeah well Sports Direct is very close to John Louis</u>
<u n="100" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0058">which does you know I know you'll hate being in there but it does brand stuff at non brand prices <pause dur="short"/> hurray <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0179">yes but they also bought the Newcastle stadium <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah cos</u>
<u n="103" who="S0058">yeah we like that <pause dur="short"/> we wanna support Sports Direct as far as possible <pause dur="short"/> it's really funny <pause dur="short"/> oh my God</u>
<u n="104" who="S0179">it is quite funny</u>
<u n="105" who="S0058">but they're just such an embarrassment to themselves <pause dur="short"/> it was like when they were doing really badly and they released their new away strip which was yellow and orange stripes <pause dur="short"/> and you're like you're not doing yourself any favours you know <pause dur="short"/> a nice blood red or a a deep green or something yeah fair enough <pause dur="short"/> ha but no</u>
<u n="106" who="S0179">right erm <pause dur="short"/> it might be worth holding it</u>
<u n="107" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="108" who="S0179">just cos it's they might say it's only <trunc>vibr</trunc> only vibration from the seat</u>
<u n="109" who="S0058">fair enough</u>
<u n="110" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="111" who="S0058">oh</u>
<u n="112" who="S0179">I said hold not drop</u>
<u n="113" who="S0058">ha <pause dur="short"/> oh no it it was the water that was dropping</u>
<u n="114" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="115" who="S0058">ah <pause dur="short"/> ha ha <pause dur="short"/> you do like this song</u>
<u n="116" who="S0179">yep</u>
<u n="117" who="S0058">A bit too much <pause dur="short"/> ha ha</u>
<u n="118" who="S0179">I look forward to tomorrow</u>
<u n="119" who="S0058">yeah it should be fun</u>
<u n="120" who="S0179">er it might be dry actually</u>
<u n="121" who="S0058" trans="overlap">erm yeah so <pause dur="short"/> ha <pause dur="short"/> so when we go to Morrison's we'll erm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0179">get stuff for lunch as well</u>
<u n="123" who="S0058">get stuff for lunch <pause dur="short"/> yeah which I was thinking about just making erm a load of different rolls <pause dur="short"/> so we'll get a load of ham and a load of tuna <pause dur="short"/> erm does that sound good?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0179">I like cheese and sweet apple <unclear/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0058">cheese is good yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I was thinking about just making a variety</u>
<u n="126" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0058">A few of each <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> and and a few bars of chocolate?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0179">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="129" who="S0058">and some apples? We could buy apples</u>
<u n="130" who="S0179">yeah that's good and some crisps as well</u>
<u n="131" who="S0058">we've got crisps so we don't need to buy those</u>
<u n="132" who="S0179">oh yeah true</u>
<u n="133" who="S0058">so <pause dur="short"/> we've got loads of bags of crisps actually so that will be a really good way of using them up <pause dur="short"/> cos we don't eat them very quickly so yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm a few bags of crisps <pause dur="short"/> we might wanna buy a a <trunc>bo</trunc> a pack of bottled water <pause dur="short"/> cos we don't have enough for everyone</u>
<u n="134" who="S0179">oh I've got a flask which is a canteen so</u>
<u n="135" who="S0058">oh okay fair enough</u>
<u n="136" who="S0179">which is what I'll be planning on using</u>
<u n="137" who="S0058">Cos then we don't yeah we don't have very many bottles at all <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know if that'll be enough for everyone but</u>
<u n="138" who="S0179">well I've got two er more <pause dur="short"/> I've got two and each one is equal to four small bottles of water</u>
<u n="139" who="S0058">okay fair enough yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0179">which brings us to well over ten bottles</u>
<u n="141" who="S0058">that should be fine yeah <pause dur="short"/> and we're not exactly in the wilderness</u>
<u n="142" who="S0179">er <pause dur="short"/> well you say that but we're still going prepared as if we are <pause dur="short"/> so you've got all of your survival kit yeah?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0058">erm my survival kit I've got my blanket whistle and compass yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0179" trans="overlap">blanket whistle and compass <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0058">next week one lunchtime I'm gonna go down and try and find something for Heather <pause dur="short"/> erm my dad suggested</u>
<u n="146" who="S0179">oh for a birthday present</u>
<u n="147" who="S0058">my dad suggested something</u>
<u n="148" who="S0179" trans="overlap">when's her birthday?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0058">Wednesday when she's here</u>
<u n="150" who="S0179">Wednesday circuits</u>
<u n="151" who="S0058">circuits yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was thinking we could maybe cook some</u>
<u n="152" who="S0179">and Will a big shout out to the birthday girl</u>
<u n="153" who="S0058">yep <pause dur="short"/> erm I mean at work</u>
<u n="154" who="S0179" trans="overlap">we need to get her induction sorted</u>
<u n="155" who="S0058">well I was wondering actually whether it would just make more sense to do it on Monday <pause dur="short"/> we can do a session and she can have an induction <pause dur="short"/> because I'm not sure if she's gonna feel like doing that after <pause dur="short"/> I mean I can talk to her about it</u>
<u n="156" who="S0179">well she can the induction weren't take very long <pause dur="short"/> she can stay out <pause dur="short"/> it just seems to be better value for money <pause dur="short"/> if she's staying for an induction to get it as early then she can have it</u>
<u n="157" who="S0058">well I mean I don't think she'll particularly do you know what I mean? I don't think she'd really miss out on <pause dur="short"/> I dunno erm I'll I'll have a chat to her about it</u>
<u n="158" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="159" who="S0058">I don't think I mean you know if she just doesn't go on Sunday it's pointless just booking it for her <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>whe</trunc> whereas if she might wanna get it out of the way so</u>
<u n="160" who="S0179">well we'll see when they can do it <pause dur="short"/> because</u>
<u n="161" who="S0058">yeah true <pause dur="short"/> we can ask today about when they can fit it in and then</u>
<u n="162" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0058">yeah no I mentioned this erm <trunc>ye</trunc> someone asked how old she was and I said well she's actually twenty-two on the Wednesday that she's here <pause dur="short"/> and they all went oh bless <pause dur="short"/> and I said yeah I'm gonna have to work on her birthday <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> erm so they they said you know great can we have some cake? It's a great excuse and erm and they're gonna get a card and sign it as well which is very sweet</u>
<u n="164" who="S0179">this is really giving a bad impression of the world of work</u>
<u n="165" who="S0058">it's pretty much what publishing is like <pause dur="short"/> ha <pause dur="short"/> every department has</u>
<u n="166" who="S0179" trans="overlap">it's pretty much what your <unclear/> of publishing is like</u>
<u n="167" who="S0058">well no in all fairness Bloomsberry was exactly the same <pause dur="short"/> there was cake for <trunc>ev</trunc> during the two weeks I was there <pause dur="short"/> and celebrations <pause dur="short"/> I think there was two different cake events <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think it's a fairly standard thing</u>
<u n="168" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="169" who="S0058">erm <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah so I met somebody erm yesterday who used to work at CUP as an admin assistant</u>
<u n="170" who="S0179">yeah?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0058">and erm she actually got another job at CUP</u>
<u n="172" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0058">but she was  she was  applying for jobs everywhere <pause dur="short"/> and she applied for one at Bloomsbury <pause dur="short"/> got the one at CUP <pause dur="short"/> accepted it <pause dur="short"/> but then got the one at Bloomsbury</u>
<u n="174" who="S0179">yeah?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0058">so that they <trunc>obv</trunc> they obviously preferred that one <pause dur="short"/> I said obviously <pause dur="short"/> she preferred that one <pause dur="short"/> it must have been a better job and erm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0179">and that would be quite good hand in your notice before you start</u>
<u n="177" who="S0058">yeah that's what she did <pause dur="short"/> yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> she er never really started it <pause dur="short"/> and erm so now she's working in Bloomsbury <pause dur="short"/> I said oh well you know I've been in Bloomsbury for a couple of weeks <pause dur="short"/> um and they've moved out of the old building <pause dur="short"/> the out the er that I did work experience in <pause dur="short"/><unclear/> it was really nice</u>
<u n="178" who="S0179">interestingly there erm that was an example of er safety overriding legality <pause dur="short"/> so I wanted to drop to a safety gear</u>
<u n="179" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0179">but I in doing so I went over the speed limit</u>
<u n="181" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="182" who="S0179">erm cos I was breaking down in forth and I wanted to actively be in third so I don't want it clutched into third but the erm acceleration imparted there in took me slightly over the limit</u>
<u n="183" who="S0058">mm but it was safer to do that</u>
<u n="184" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="185" who="S0058">and not do that <pause dur="short"/> yep</u>
<u n="186" who="S0179">so if people perpetually ask but how can it be safe to brake how would you well how would you ever justify breaking the law in the interest of safety <pause dur="short"/> you just really haven't thought about it have you?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0058" trans="overlap">well I'd just say it's a I was gonna say I'd er that's pretty straight forward I'd say to that</u>
<u n="188" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0058">um <pause dur="short"/> anyway yeah so um Bloomsbury have erm moved from their old premises</u>
<u n="190" who="S0179">oh right</u>
<u n="191" who="S0058">which I was quite sad about <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she seems to like it and said everyone was really nice <pause dur="short"/> erm she's in digital base so it's completely different to what I was in <pause dur="short"/> ha</u>
<u n="192" who="S0179">well if you wanted to work at Bloomsbury like  The easiest way for you to do it</u>
<u n="193" who="S0058" trans="overlap">come to work with you <pause dur="short"/> so <unclear/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0179" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="195" who="S0058">sorry</u>
<u n="196" who="S0179">yeah the problem is that there's no fast train</u>
<u n="197" who="S0058">ah that is true</u>
<u n="198" who="S0179">you'd go much quicker from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0179">which I could detour by to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0058" trans="overlap">well no but it seems daft that you drop me off <pause dur="short"/> but I could can I bus to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0179">well that's doable <pause dur="short"/> erm what I was actually gonna say was</u>
<u n="203" who="S0058">mm?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0179">because going into <anon type="place"/> you end that that'd be a nightmare</u>
<u n="205" who="S0058">that's a nightmare that's not yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0179">what you should do is er go and stay with my parents during the week</u>
<u n="207" who="S0058">that'll be interesting yeah <pause dur="short"/> it would be even yeah it'd be good <pause dur="short"/> er the alternative is bus to <anon type="place"/> which is perfectly possible</u>
<u n="208" who="S0179">er <pause dur="short"/> traffic? Morning? Really?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0058">well you'd have to leave so early that</u>
<u n="210" who="S0179">well no it's just as bad as er <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> getting into <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure where the bus goes to in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I'm not aware that there's a station particularly <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0058" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I think actually I think they do go close to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I remember there being a little rail sign on the erm on the timetable <pause dur="short"/> there might not be</u>
<u n="212" who="S0179" trans="overlap">well actually what you should do is learn to drive</u>
<u n="213" who="S0058">well <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how much parking at <anon type="place"/>' station would cost</u>
<u n="214" who="S0179">get there earlier</u>
<u n="215" who="S0058" trans="overlap">I'm sure you could find somewhere to <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> of course I'm not working at Bloomsbury's so <pause dur="short"/> haha <pause dur="short"/> I don't have any particular</u>
<u n="216" who="S0179">well actually that would only get you to Kings Cross <pause dur="short"/> at which point you're gonna have to get across London</u>
<u n="217" who="S0058" trans="overlap">across London <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's not <pause dur="short"/> I I I I could she said it's just round the corner from where it's used to be which was a fair old step from</u>
<u n="218" who="S0179">yep</u>
<u n="219" who="S0058">from erm <pause dur="short"/> so it was a you know it was a bus ride away <pause dur="short"/> erm you could walk it but it was much easier to get the bus <pause dur="short"/> you could get the tube but I really wasn't keen on that</u>
<u n="220" who="S0179">where am I driving to?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0058">the centre</u>
<u n="222" who="S0179">Good right <pause dur="short"/> it just occurred to me <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>liter</trunc> I just blanked out where we were going</u>
<u n="223" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> haha</u>
<u n="224" who="S0179">er <pause dur="short"/> I'll give my dad a call this afternoon</u>
<u n="225" who="S0058">I was gonna give my dad a quick ring as well and just see how my grandpa is</u>
<u n="226" who="S0179">oh yes</u>
<u n="227" who="S0058">erm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0179">have you told him yet?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0058">about the er nose thing?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0058">I haven't no <pause dur="short"/> I was gonna sort of tell him you know sort of on the boat <pause dur="short"/> so I'll erm I'll tell him that as well</u>
<u n="232" who="S0179">that is a cool looking house</u>
<u n="233" who="S0058" trans="overlap">classic <pause dur="short"/> it's really cool isn't it <pause dur="short"/> I love all the ivy</u>
<u n="234" who="S0179">they need to get some better cars</u>
<u n="235" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0179">I can't believe those things are still road legal</u>
<u n="237" who="S0058">ha ha yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0179">they used to be cool flats <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0058">three belts I'm assuming <pause dur="short"/> kind of weird looking thing outside but I can bet they are pretty cool inside <pause dur="short"/> might be a bit old and tiny but it's hard to know <pause dur="short"/> could either be really nice or a little bit tatty</u>
<u n="240" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0058">busy isn't it</u>
<u n="242" who="S0179">little bit yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0058">I wonder if there's just some kind of hold up <pause dur="short"/> it's not normally like this <unclear/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0179" trans="overlap">just a bit to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0058">well if this is the queue to get into the centre <pause dur="short"/> then it just seems odd like it's never like this is it?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0058">is it? Oh</u>
<u n="248" who="S0179">Cos it takes what ten minutes to walk from <anon type="place"/> and I think that might be faster</u>
<u n="249" who="S0058">if yeah if we're blocked up back to here then yeah <pause dur="short"/> if these are all basically going to the car park <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's a green light out <pause dur="short"/> don't know if it's been held up at the lights but</u>
<u n="250" who="S0179">no er it's red actually</u>
<u n="251" who="S0058">alright <pause dur="short"/> well this one's green but the one ahead is</u>
<u n="252" who="S0179">yeah well that's just a pedestrian crossing</u>
<u n="253" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> what do you reckon? Think <anon type="place"/> would be quicker?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0179">just for sheer density of traffic</u>
<u n="255" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0179">Cos even if they start <unclear/> road <pause dur="short"/> we should still be closer to them</u>
<u n="257" who="S0058">yeah no definitely <pause dur="short"/> yeah if everyone's go they must be going into the centre and hence they must be going to the car park</u>
<u n="258" who="S0179" trans="overlap">just after lunch <pause dur="short"/> rainy day they're going into <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0058">yeah fair enough <pause dur="short"/> okay well <anon type="place"/> then</u>
<u n="260" who="S0179">okay <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> we're going to <anon type="place"/> </u>
<u n="261" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> blimey I've never don't remember seeing it like this</u>
<u n="262" who="S0179">that's what I'm thinking <pause dur="short"/> there's pedestrian routes down there but no road short cuts</u>
<u n="263" who="S0058">I yeah I don't think you can get through</u>
<u n="264" who="S0179">no you can't</u>
<u n="265" who="S0058">just the yeah <pause dur="short"/> and the back they're coming down past Church Hill as well <pause dur="short"/> gosh</u>
<u n="266" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we're not going to the centre</u>
<u n="267" who="S0058">we're not you know we're not <pause dur="short"/> jesus <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> there we go <pause dur="short"/> yeah um what was I gonna say? Yeah and so my dad sent me a couple of articles um one is um a sort of debate <pause dur="short"/> they often have debates in the art section um and this one is um about Morrissey <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="268" who="S0179">what about how much of a tit he is?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0058">yeah well basically yeah <pause dur="short"/> is he? What was it? Is he still a national treasure or something? Or is he a national treasure?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0179">he was ever a national treasure?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0058" trans="overlap">um which is interesting <pause dur="short"/> well it depends who you talk to I guess <pause dur="short"/> or well you know so it was something like that</u>
<u n="272" who="S0179">national embarrassment</u>
<u n="273" who="S0058">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> um so that I'm quite looking forward to reading that <pause dur="short"/> and the other one is about um the British library is is doing a project um a <trunc>j</trunc> like an oral history project <pause dur="short"/> so collecting it's on coordinate conversation <pause dur="short"/> which is quite interesting <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> it's</u>
<u n="274" who="S0179">I love that fast into the city centre</u>
<u n="275" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> not so much <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0179">what were you saying sorry?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0058">um yeah so so it's an oral history project um for the British library and they're getting people to submit conversations on the website</u>
<u n="278" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0058">which is pretty interesting <pause dur="short"/> and I did look into this actually I think looking at some of the things in the</u>
<u n="280" who="S0179" trans="overlap">do you get paid?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> it's looking at some of the things in the past and we can't have access to it because it's from well ours is for commercial gain <pause dur="short"/> purely and simply <pause dur="short"/> um and they're the whole point of theirs is it's not for commercial gain</u>
<u n="282" who="S0179">ooh <pause dur="short"/> that's arguable</u>
<u n="283" who="S0058">well yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0179">it's promoting the profile of the <unclear/> which is going to get more visitors <pause dur="short"/> it might not directly be for commercial</u>
<u n="285" who="S0058">yeah it it's for just kind of preserving storage of the</u>
<u n="286" who="S0179" trans="overlap">this has took us we've literarily come ten yards</u>
<u n="287" who="S0058">that's it isn't it <pause dur="short"/> unless we've got another option yes?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0179">but I'm concerned about getting to <anon type="place"/> as in</u>
<u n="289" who="S0058">it should clear up a little bit now but that pedestrian crossing just <unclear/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0179" trans="overlap">we'll go to the bank first  cos that will close</u>
<u n="291" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="292" who="S0179">the pedestrian crossing is now on red <pause dur="short"/> does the park and ride bus go down <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="294" who="S0179">yes it does</u>
<u n="295" who="S0058"><trunc>Does</trunc></u>
<u n="296" who="S0179">I've had <pause dur="short"/> it certainly used to</u>
<u n="297" who="S0058" trans="overlap">possibly <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> I can't honestly can't remember</u>
<u n="298" who="S0179">I remember coming in <pause dur="short"/> one day me and my mum came to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think we came on the train <pause dur="short"/> and we spent er the day just before we had a list of colleges and we just went and had a wonder round</u>
<u n="299" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0179">like four or five colleges</u>
<u n="301" who="S0058">that's nice</u>
<u n="302" who="S0179">that was a nice day</u>
<u n="303" who="S0058">hmm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean we did that when we were on holiday round here <pause dur="short"/> just had a little wonder round <pause dur="short"/> I really liked <anon type="place"/> actually <pause dur="short"/> and mainly cos I had dreams of being on University Challenge and being announced as <anon type="place"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> which does sound good <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Or <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0179">it is just <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <trunc>G</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0058"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/>yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="306" who="S0179">it'll be actually no I'm not good at pronunciation</u>
<u n="307" who="S0058">erm</u>
<u n="308" who="S0179">this is ridiculous</u>
<u n="309" who="S0058">it is ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> okay well mental note <pause dur="short"/> ha</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="310" who="S0179">I'm also a little bit annoyed about how much of this traffic to the left is being let in</u>
<u n="311" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0179">Cos it's</u>
<u n="313" who="S0058">the yeah it's that's moving far faster than er</u>
<u n="314" who="S0179">well admittedly there was less of it <pause dur="short"/> but on the other hand they can all wait for it</u>
<u n="315" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah people are just letting them go <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe been largely taxi drivers</u>
<u n="316" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="317" who="S0058">they are a bit mental in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0179">I think it's better however <pause dur="short"/> has it yeah there was the</u>
<u n="319" who="S0058">so they yeah so they</u>
<u n="320" who="S0179">so ten cars back and we would sort of hadn't cleared at all</u>
<u n="321" who="S0058" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0179">so mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> drop that in the mix</u>
<u n="323" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0179">right <pause dur="short"/> normally I'd say let in one person <pause dur="short"/> everyone let's in one <pause dur="short"/> under these circumstances that's a bit er <unclear/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0058" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="326" who="S0179">yep we're going down here <pause dur="short"/> a little bit of creative driving and we nearly got there</u>
<u n="327" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0179">damn it <pause dur="short"/> oh Jeez I would have got that if I had been a bit quicker</u>
<u n="329" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> so I mean that's still snarled up that's clear so <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> Centrefold</u>
<u n="330" who="S0179">yeah I'm actually um we'd have to thread right the way round into the centre <pause dur="short"/> we're not just all</u>
<u n="331" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no it's a long way</u>
<u n="332" who="S0179">right <pause dur="short"/> for anyone considering driving into <anon type="place"/> centre don't</u>
<u n="333" who="S0058">yeah basically <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ha</trunc> handily having a learner there <pause dur="short"/> haha</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="334" who="S0179">this is a twenty speed limit and you're not quite making it <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="335" who="S0058">okay so that was a little bit early for a signal there <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> As in <unclear/> that pink car</u>
<u n="336" who="S0179">that is a driving school car <pause dur="short"/> cos it's got L plates on the side as well</u>
<u n="337" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0179">I'm sorry <pause dur="short"/> I can't be bothered <pause dur="short"/> pure efficiency dictates going at a little bit faster than the speed limit</u>
<u n="339" who="S0058">Don't fancy playing football in this weather <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> play</u>
<u n="340" who="S0179">yeah thought so</u>
<u n="341" who="S0058">wow two buses <pause dur="short"/> there was no uni on the weekend</u>
<u n="342" who="S0179">oh what a shock</u>
<u n="343" who="S0058">so that's a very late bus</u>
<u n="344" who="S0179">Jesus <pause dur="short"/> nearly took out another bike then honestly <pause dur="short"/> dog eat dog</u>
<u n="345" who="S0058">what really annoys me <pause dur="short"/> oh you've got no idea how much this annoys me <pause dur="short"/> cos I cycle relatively you know I'm in the I'm I'm sort of faster than maybe two thirds of cyclists</u>
<u n="346" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="347" who="S0058">but I obey the laws <pause dur="short"/> so I stop at red lights <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>v</trunc> and you know et cetera et cetera</u>
<u n="348" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0058">I don't just just go through red lights <pause dur="short"/> I just wait at the stop line that kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> and erm so I when I cycle into town from work I leap frog people</u>
<u n="350" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0058">and it's just massively annoying you know you they I I overtake them <pause dur="short"/> a <trunc>f</trunc> two minutes later I stop at a red light they go past me at the red light</u>
<u n="352" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0058">two minutes time I overtake them again <pause dur="short"/> I'm like just go faster and stop at red lights like <pause dur="short"/> ar <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It really annoys me <pause dur="short"/> just a waste of my time</u>
<u n="354" who="S0179">okay well we'll take Anne's car park if it's quiet enough</u>
<u n="355" who="S0058">yeah sure <pause dur="short"/> full of taxis <pause dur="short"/> ha</u>
<u n="356" who="S0179">they <unclear/> in all fairness</u>
<u n="357" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="358" who="S0179">well I mean if had only been if I had only been twenty that would have been fine</u>
<u n="359" who="S0058">haha well</u>
<u n="360" who="S0179">is Anne's car park free or?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0058">ooh it looks fairly busy actually erm</u>
<u n="362" who="S0179">let's go to  then</u>
<u n="363" who="S0058">yeah  might be your best bet er <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's full</u>
<u n="364" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> crazy times</u>
<u n="365" who="S0058">it is crazy</u>
<u n="366" who="S0179">there was a very interesting thing about priority there</u>
<u n="367" who="S0058">what did you say?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0179">I said there was a very interesting thing about priority at those um</u>
<u n="369" who="S0058">I was looking at the erm thing I wasn't so what what happened? So you were turning right</u>
<u n="370" who="S0179">hang on <pause dur="short"/> oh God it's a big <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0058">oh it's leaving weekend <pause dur="short"/> that's why it's so busy <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="372" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="373" who="S0058">that makes sense <pause dur="short"/> I was gonna say</u>
<u n="374" who="S0179">okay so</u>
<u n="375" who="S0058">okay so good erm</u>
<u n="376" who="S0179">see if we can find a space <pause dur="short"/> to be fair we could probably get in in kind of one of those garages</u>
<u n="377" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="378" who="S0179">damn it</u>
<u n="379" who="S0058">haha nice try <pause dur="short"/> okay erm</u>
<u n="380" who="S0179">that's perfect timing believe me as well</u>
<u n="381" who="S0058" trans="overlap">didn't think about that <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0179">ah <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="383" who="S0058">ah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0179">where?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0058">no you said ah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0179">the road at the back of Anne's might do it</u>
<u n="387" who="S0058">interesting</u>
<u n="388" who="S0179">it's gonna be open</u>
<u n="389" who="S0058">Cos not many people know about it <pause dur="short"/> or live in Anne's</u>
<u n="390" who="S0179">yeah but we don't wanna get blocked in there</u>
<u n="391" who="S0058">no true</u>
<u n="392" who="S0179"></u>
<u n="393" who="S0058">no but they would let you out <pause dur="short"/> like there's never not gonna be porters there but maybe a little bit risky</u>
<u n="394" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah but it excuse me sir what are you doing parked in there?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe a little bit pushing it <pause dur="short"/> mm right okay so erm <pause dur="short"/> I mean a few options we can either just try one of the roads round here</u>
<u n="396" who="S0179">no that's not gonna work <pause dur="short"/> can't risk it</u>
<u n="397" who="S0058">well that explains the horrendous traffic anyway</u>
<u n="398" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0058">well it means in future we can predict it basically</u>
<u n="400" who="S0179">well I did have one idea <pause dur="short"/> what we could just do is go in front of those garages</u>
<u n="401" who="S0058">I don't know what they're used for</u>
<u n="402" who="S0179" trans="overlap">think open</u>
<u n="403" who="S0058">I assume they're not used for anything</u>
<u n="404" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah open</u>
<u n="405" who="S0058">there's there's no no parking laws or anything <pause dur="short"/> ah it's erm what's his face</u>
<u n="406" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0058"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0179">oh <pause dur="short"/> small <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="409" who="S0058"><trunc>S</trunc> yeah small erm <unclear/> president <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0179">oh right</u>
<u n="411" who="S0058">is there any along here?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0179">no there weren't be <pause dur="short"/> ooh no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> so we'll just go into centre <unclear/> See <pause dur="short"/> see just one of these? Oh no it's the double yellow lines down here</u>
<u n="413" who="S0058">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="414" who="S0179">see the annoying thing is there used to be a good parking space</u>
<u n="415" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> classically <pause dur="short"/> I was gonna say it will be be full today anyway</u>
<u n="416" who="S0179">okay so where are we gonna go?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0058">so we can either erm</u>
<u n="418" who="S0179">just keep cruising</u>
<u n="419" who="S0058">we could try the one in Newnham</u>
<u n="420" who="S0179">I'm not confident</u>
<u n="421" who="S0058">A trek yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm <anon type="place"/> is probably full</u>
<u n="422" who="S0179">oh <pause dur="short"/> damn our trump card</u>
<u n="423" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0179">I can try down there but I don't I'm not er</u>
<u n="425" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how far the you know but you you know there might be spaces a little further up but it's hard to know erm</u>
<u n="426" who="S0179">well alternative is we go out <pause dur="short"/> we go down <pause dur="short"/> go out and come into a road on the other side of where er that footpath comes out</u>
<u n="427" who="S0058">I think yeah we can just park on one of the roads round here <pause dur="short"/> the they they can't all be full with parents</u>
<u n="428" who="S0179">did you understand where I meant?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0058">so so down there</u>
<u n="430" who="S0179">no you know where the footpath at the end of this road?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0179">that goes through into a housing estate</u>
<u n="433" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0179">park in that housing estate</u>
<u n="435" who="S0058">ah <pause dur="short"/> and footpath it back through</u>
<u n="436" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="437" who="S0058">seems like a good idea yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos that one that's so far away <pause dur="short"/> but I'm just meaning like a little bit further down there's the roads</u>
<u n="438" who="S0179">I'm just gonna move forwards now cos there's some <trunc>g</trunc> someone coming up behind us <pause dur="short"/> what I should probably just get out of the way <pause dur="short"/> I don't think we're gonna find a space here anyway</u>
<u n="439" who="S0058">no I and these people aren't gonna move them quickly as well <pause dur="short"/> it's the same  so</u>
<u n="440" who="S0179">yep can do</u>
<u n="441" who="S0058">erm so</u>
<u n="442" who="S0179">ah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0058">do you see what I mean? We could turn left and go just down one of those streets but it's hard</u>
<u n="444" who="S0179" trans="overlap">we might just have been able to get in there but that's probably pushing it <pause dur="short"/> what street? Oh right</u>
<u n="445" who="S0058">do you know what I mean? Just a street <pause dur="short"/> erm a little bit further away from any of the colleges</u>
<u n="446" who="S0179">I'm not sure that we'd find any round there</u>
<u n="447" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> possibly not <pause dur="short"/> I I don't know how big they are with just residents</u>
<u n="448" who="S0179">probably fairly <pause dur="short"/> what about <anon type="place"/>? <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0058" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> what that way you mean?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that yeah it might work <pause dur="short"/> probably a bit quieter <pause dur="short"/> as in I think there's lots of flats and stuff round there which <pause dur="short"/> do you wanna try that?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0058">I mean it might be a little bit <trunc>furth</trunc> a little bit closer than driving round to that housing estate <pause dur="short"/> it's a fair step to get back</u>
<u n="454" who="S0179">Christ this is crazy</u>
<u n="455" who="S0058">it's insane isn't it? Huh</u>
<u n="456" who="S0179">there's just one space in there</u>
<u n="457" who="S0058">is there? Ah right</u>
<u n="458" who="S0179">I think <pause dur="short"/> let's just see if we can get in</u>
<u n="459" who="S0058">haha</u>
<u n="460" who="S0179">I've got a nagging feeling there might be just the one <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="461" who="S0058">oh <pause dur="short"/> nicely done</u>
<u n="462" who="S0179">alright</u>
<u n="463" who="S0058">and they're not you know it's a good weekend to park here cos they're not gonna be questioning the fact that there's cars everywhere <pause dur="short"/> we could even walk through <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0179">I fully intend to <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna take some shuffling to get in there but we can do it with a bit of creativity <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> what would be very useful if you could just watch out for pedestrians for me</u>
<u n="465" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's never mind</u>
<u n="466" who="S0179">ah sweet <pause dur="short"/> well done me</u>
<u n="467" who="S0058" trans="overlap">that's good <pause dur="short"/> yeah nicely spotted <pause dur="short"/> cool well done</u>
</body>
</text>
