<text id="SH9T">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:14:43</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-11-10</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0324 S0325</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's home, Linton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>School, The school orchestra (wind-band), Our English test, English lessons, Art lessons, French lessons, People at school</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about school</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, announcing, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T06</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0324">
				<exactage>14</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>14</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0325">
				<exactage>13</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>9</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Japanese -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0324">what did I miss at wind band last week?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0325">well we did the he got out the booklet you know the Christmas booklet and it has like Once in Royal David City</u>
<u n="3" who="S0324">oh yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0325">yes and we did that and it was really bad and um me and me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we had it and we were playing what were we playing we were playing some random song and there's a little extra bit on the end <vocal desc="laugh"/> and we looked back over this little bit and we were playing a completely different song it was really funny and the but we didn't really play that much</u>
<u n="5" who="S0324">oh that sounds</u>
<u n="6" who="S0325" trans="overlap">we played Let It Be the one that you told me Mr <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you really like</u>
<u n="7" who="S0324" trans="overlap">oh Let There Be Peace <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0325">Let There Be Peace and that was the worst one in the whole world I can't</u>
<u n="9" who="S0324">yeah that was really awkward yeah oh are are we bringing our green T-shirts next week?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0325">yeah yeah he said because</u>
<u n="11" who="S0324">er this week Thursday</u>
<u n="12" who="S0325">yeah yeah because erm he said he had spare time after that going to the dentist</u>
<u n="13" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0325">but erm I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> might have brought it this week last week but she forgot about it sort of thing</u>
<u n="15" who="S0324">oh</u>
<u n="16" who="S0325">so not really sure</u>
<u n="17" who="S0324"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh sounds great I'm not looking forward to the photo</u>
<u n="18" who="S0325"><trunc>phot</trunc> oh I hate those photos because you're like</u>
<u n="19" who="S0324">why do you have to play your instrument?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0325">yeah well we yeah you have to pretend you're playing it so like</u>
<u n="21" who="S0324">and then it looks like you're</u>
<u n="22" who="S0325">cheeks are all puffed</u>
<u n="23" who="S0324" trans="overlap">like you're a hamster stuffing the cheeks</u>
<u n="24" who="S0325" trans="overlap">yeah and I don't oh oh yeah have we got English tomorrow? we finishing off that English assessment?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0324">er yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0325">no we don't do we? it's week one I don't know I don't know the timetable you wrote loads you wrote like two pages no you wrote three pages</u>
<u n="27" who="S0324" trans="overlap">I'm on my third page</u>
<u n="28" who="S0325">yeah you're about halfway through that aren't you?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0324">mm maybe</u>
<u n="30" who="S0325">I'm on my first page but third page but I I've literally written a line</u>
<u n="31" who="S0324">so haven't exactly written more than you then</u>
<u n="32" who="S0325">you wrote a whole page for the second question</u>
<u n="33" who="S0324">the third question <pause dur="short"/> no the second one the one about structure</u>
<u n="34" who="S0325" trans="overlap">the second one <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I wrote about half a page because I couldn't I couldn't think of anything else to write and I was writing really small</u>
<u n="35" who="S0324">what was the second question?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0325">erm the author the writer structures the text</u>
<u n="37" who="S0324">no erm <pause dur="short"/> wasn't it how <unclear/> use language</u>
<u n="38" who="S0325" trans="overlap">oh erm how does the author use language to create a sense of the weather or something like that</u>
<u n="39" who="S0324" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0325">what did you put for that? I put <pause dur="short"/> that he used because there was something about the bus erm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0324">shaking like a drunken man</u>
<u n="42" who="S0325">yeah did that and I did the wind sometimes <pause dur="short"/> grabbed it or something and then like</u>
<u n="43" who="S0324" trans="overlap">yeah with it round a corner or</u>
<u n="44" who="S0325">no no it was it was I well I did it and then I said it sort of the but the wind was grabbing it and shaking it around and then what was the third one? the structure</u>
<u n="45" who="S0324">the structure how does the author structure the text to interest to <unclear/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0325">I didn't like that one</u>
<u n="47" who="S0324">what did you put for that?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0325">I put erm <pause dur="short"/> something about <pause dur="short"/> erm the way it came in closer to that to the girl</u>
<u n="49" who="S0324">oh yeah what I <unclear>did from</unclear> I basically copied the thing we did from <unclear/></u>
<u n="50" who="S0325">but I just sort of rambled I rambled too much</u>
<u n="51" who="S0324" trans="overlap">yeah so did I I rambled</u>
<u n="52" who="S0325">and so I kept just talking about it was zooming in on this and on that and in on that and was so I'm gonna read it through tomorrow or whenever else when we have English</u>
<u n="53" who="S0324">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0325">and then I'm going to be like oh that take didn't go very well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0324">what did you do for the four things erm the erm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0325" trans="overlap">oh yeah the weather?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0324">yeah the four things about the weather or something the first question</u>
<u n="58" who="S0325">I did it was cold and grey um misty <pause dur="short"/> clammy cold</u>
<u n="59" who="S0324" trans="overlap">cold</u>
<u n="60" who="S0325">clammy cold and like something rain I can't remember <unclear/> was</u>
<u n="61" who="S0324" trans="overlap">oh yeah it's like <trunc>mizz</trunc></u>
<u n="62" who="S0325" trans="overlap">mizzling rain yeah I did that I don't know what mizzling means</u>
<u n="63" who="S0324">neither do I</u>
<u n="64" who="S0325">yeah and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was asking about erm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0324">oh yeah something to do with metaphor and</u>
<u n="66" who="S0325">yeah something that word <trunc>alu</trunc> <trunc>alo</trunc></u>
<u n="67" who="S0324" trans="overlap"><trunc>all</trunc>allergy</u>
<u n="68" who="S0325">analogy</u>
<u n="69" who="S0324">oh yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0325">that's it yeah but erm I don't know what that means either</u>
<u n="71" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0324">neither do I <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> knows</u>
<u n="73" who="S0325">so many words</u>
<u n="74" who="S0324" trans="overlap">so many words like I bet she she understood everything like if you gave her this text with like</u>
<u n="75" who="S0325">I dunno a nineteen fifteen novel</u>
<u n="76" who="S0324">yeah just with random words she'd know what all of them were</u>
<u n="77" who="S0325">yeah she'd know like whenever we did the definitions on the board she always knows what they are Miss <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is like</u>
<u n="78" who="S0324" trans="overlap">oh does anyone know they</u>
<u n="79" who="S0325">anyone know what they are? and she's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s like yeah me me I know what they are</u>
<u n="80" who="S0324">and then whenever you ask her she won't explain it she's actually quite nice she's not that bad</u>
<u n="81" who="S0325">she's nice yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0324">because she does explain things to you and stuff</u>
<u n="83" who="S0325"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I feel really I feel really stupid sitting next to her though because she knows all these words and I'm like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is this a metaphor? no this is a simile because it's it uses like a noun but I do know what a metaphor is I was just</u>
<u n="84" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0324">like if you ask her like what does this random word mean? she'd know exactly what it meant and explain it <pause dur="short"/> quite well</u>
<u n="86" who="S0325" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I I think erm me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> today in art were failing so bad and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she you know because the thigh to the knee is meant to have two heads</u>
<u n="87" who="S0324">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0325">she only put one and I was like no no no no down to the down to the foot and I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's wrong because you have to put another head and she was like <trunc>sh</trunc> but Miss got really angry because everyone was talking yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0324">I was yeah erm and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is really good at drawing what she can see but not as good as at like the head like proportion</u>
<u n="90" who="S0325" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0324">she never really measures it</u>
<u n="92" who="S0325" trans="overlap">follows it she's more good at observation</u>
<u n="93" who="S0324">yeah like when she's drawing that face she didn't like you know erm Miss <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was telling us how the nose was like one eye or something</u>
<u n="94" who="S0325">yeah and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> still looks good cos she doesn't have the motivation but I'm not like good with that I like to know</u>
<u n="95" who="S0324" trans="overlap">and she can kind of make it look right without doing <unclear/> little stuff</u>
<u n="96" who="S0325" trans="overlap">just by treasuring little stuff yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0324">yeah it's like whenever I draw a face I have to do like the cross thing so I know where the eyes are <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0325" trans="overlap">yeah same <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah and do halfway and then halfway down that</u>
<u n="99" who="S0324">I start with the face cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> starts with the eyes</u>
<u n="100" who="S0325">yeah I start with the eyes</u>
<u n="101" who="S0324">I do the face shape and cross and then I start with the eyes</u>
<u n="102" who="S0325">I used to do that but then Miss <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> said it's better to do the face first then draw the shape of the face</u>
<u n="103" who="S0324">yeah she said that to us but I didn't do it</u>
<u n="104" who="S0325">oh</u>
<u n="105" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0324">yeah but you can't do it when you're doing the thing because you need to have the head size to be able to measure out the proportion</u>
<u n="107" who="S0325" trans="overlap">yeah but I think <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I think what she means is the shape of the head</u>
<u n="108" who="S0324">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0325">because I I find that quite hard and I can't do the I'm not very good at the erm eyes and the mouth and nose and stuff</u>
<u n="110" who="S0324">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0325">I asked her</u>
<u n="112" who="S0324" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0325">what was I going to say?</u>
<u n="114" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0325">have you have you looked at the French thing? have you done that?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0324">which one what</u>
<u n="117" who="S0325">the paragraphs that we have to do do we not have to learn that?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0324">well well we don't because they're not going to see us because they're just gonna see this thing so it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="119" who="S0325" trans="overlap"><unclear/> dull</u>
<u n="120" who="S0324">yeah so it doesn't matter if <unclear/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0325" trans="overlap"><unclear/> remember to get some Blu-Tack</u>
<u n="122" who="S0324">oh yeah I don't have any</u>
<u n="123" who="S0325">and you have to neither do I <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0324">we can get some <unclear/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0325">and I need to remember to bring my Iphone on that day to record but I don't have Imovie on my Iphone</u>
<u n="126" who="S0324">yeah well then you can send your clips to me I can get it on the Mac and then</u>
<u n="127" who="S0325" trans="overlap">I've got it I've got Imovie on my Ipad</u>
<u n="128" who="S0324">oh yeah well it is better on the Mac cos then we can do it easier and you can come round and we can do it</u>
<u n="129" who="S0325" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0324">and if I realised if the sound isn't very good so if you just hear like background noise you can always use this microphone and just record our voices again</u>
<u n="131" who="S0325">oh yeah and just have the <pause dur="short"/> the person</u>
<u n="132" who="S0324" trans="overlap">just have the picture and record like a track over the top</u>
<u n="133" who="S0325">and mute that one</u>
<u n="134" who="S0324">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0325">I was with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I saw millions of pictures on her Snapchat of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s party I think</u>
<u n="136" who="S0324">oh yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0325">there there was <pause dur="short"/> I think there were quite a few people there but compared to erm that girl from <anon type="place"/> her party</u>
<u n="138" who="S0324" trans="overlap">oh yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? something like that</u>
<u n="139" who="S0325" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but everyone seems to know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm not sure who <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is but</u>
<u n="140" who="S0324" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah she</u>
<u n="141" who="S0325">she's friends with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0324">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0325">she's not actually pretty</u>
<u n="144" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0324">everyone says she's pretty</u>
<u n="146" who="S0325">I've only like seen her once and like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> photo on Instagram or something but I thought she was in the year above us and</u>
<u n="147" who="S0324" trans="overlap"><unclear/> in our <pause dur="short"/> year looks so much older</u>
<u n="148" who="S0325">yeah but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in her Instagram photos looked about fifty</u>
<u n="149" who="S0324"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah because she does it like black and white and she puts so much makeup on you can't see it very clear so it's just like yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0325" trans="overlap">makeup on <pause dur="short"/> I don't know it's all I don't know what she's taking next year for her options? like dance and does she no she doesn't take dance does she?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0324">no she doesn't take dance</u>
<u n="152" who="S0325"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> choosing dance as her first option</u>
<u n="153" who="S0324">her first <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0325">her first option then art then</u>
<u n="155" who="S0324" trans="overlap">but when's she actually gonna use dance though?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0325">and if you wanna be a dancer you have to go to stage school and</u>
<u n="157" who="S0324">yeah you have to</u>
<u n="158" who="S0325">and you have do proper training having a a dance GCSE isn't really going to be a dance teacher</u>
<u n="159" who="S0324">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0325">it doesn't really help anything but she's taking she's taking dance art philosophy and ethics and</u>
<u n="161" who="S0324" trans="overlap">yeah why does she want to do</u>
<u n="162" who="S0325">and like French or something I <pause dur="short"/> but philosophy and ethics doesn't count as a humanities so if you're gonna take philosophy and ethics you might as well take history instead and get the English baccalaureate <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>bac</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0324">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0325">because I don't know</u>
<u n="165" who="S0324" trans="overlap">well she likes philosophy and ethics I don't oh</u>
<u n="166" who="S0325">Miss <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> Miss <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> have her next year as well which is going to be fun and then I don't understand why in year eleven because we don't have philosophy and ethics any more we have to have like what is it citizenship or something?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0324">oh yeah something like that</u>
<u n="168" who="S0325">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0324">like PSHE day</u>
<u n="170" who="S0325">yeah twice every two weeks why should be doing something a bit more important like maths</u>
<u n="171" who="S0324">yeah why don't we just</u>
<u n="172" who="S0325">or English</u>
<u n="173" who="S0324">or get that time to work on triple science or something</u>
<u n="174" who="S0325">yeah or something a bit more important</u>
<u n="175" who="S0324">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0325">get the time to revise or I don't know go and talk to teachers about it</u>
<u n="177" who="S0324">mm yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0325">instead of doing random and it's not even like we're taking a GCSEs <vocal desc="laugh"/> so why should we waste our especially PE as well why do we have to do what is it three lessons a week three lessons every two weeks the same as we have now</u>
<u n="179" who="S0324">erm <pause dur="short"/> no we have two four lessons every two weeks</u>
<u n="180" who="S0325">four lessons every two weeks I think it's the same or five five I think every two weeks for PE</u>
<u n="181" who="S0324">at the moment we have four</u>
<u n="182" who="S0325">yeah but I think next year we have five that's what they said but I don't understand why unless you're taking GCSE PE</u>
<u n="183" who="S0324" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0325"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will take GCSE PE</u>
<u n="185" who="S0324">I bet</u>
<u n="186" who="S0325">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will probably take GCSE PE because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s taking GCSE PE</u>
<u n="187" who="S0324">yeah before <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was gonna take like before she left she was going to take art music</u>
<u n="188" who="S0325">food tech</u>
<u n="189" who="S0324">was she going to take food tech? I didn't think she was going to</u>
<u n="190" who="S0325">I think she was I think she was going to take art music food tech and business and business was going to be her first choice</u>
<u n="191" who="S0324">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0325">and something what's she taking now?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0324">oh she's I don't think she's taking art is she?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0325" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I don't think so no</u>
<u n="195" who="S0324">is she in your art?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0325">no</u>
<u n="197" who="S0324">yeah so she isn't taking art anymore I didn't think she was going to take food tech but if she was then I guess that's also one</u>
<u n="198" who="S0325">she'll be taking exactly the same as <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0324">yeah she will cos she just follows her around</u>
<u n="200" who="S0325"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0324">and <pause dur="short"/> oh it's fourteen minutes now</u>
<u n="202" who="S0325">okay</u>
<u n="203" who="S0324">shall we stop it?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0325">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0324">bye</u>
<u n="206" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0324">oh slide to unlock okay</u>
<u n="208" who="S0325"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
