<text id="SHBJ">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:31:31</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-23</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0070 S0180 S0183</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's home, London</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Health, education, babies, alcohol, New Zealand, Lovefilm, ethnicity</topics>
		<activity>A Chat with ANON at Bentley Court </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, requesting, inviting, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0070">
				<exactage>44</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bath, Somerset</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Bit West country</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Italian -- Beginner; Korean -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0180">
				<exactage>37</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kingston-upon-Hull, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>31</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Researcher</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Kiswahili -- Advanced; French -- Intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0183">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace></birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Hong Kong</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Accountant</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2>Cantonese</l2>
				<fls>Hakka -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0070">next time we're in Oxford Street <pause dur="short"/> did you see on the thing on the news last night about the Selfridges and their raw cow milk?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0180">yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0070">hmm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0180">it's illegal to sell <trunc>pa</trunc> unpasteurized <pause dur="short"/> have they agreed that?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0070">yeah they are apparently? I only thought it was illegal you know <pause dur="short"/> that was not</u>
<u n="6" who="S0180">how why? How were they're saying it? Out out <unclear/> in the bottle</u>
<u n="7" who="S0070">yeah <trunc>the</trunc> they showed it <pause dur="short"/> people going in filling up their own bottles</u>
<u n="8" who="S0183">really?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0070">whether you can buy it already bottled and then you fill up again</u>
<u n="10" who="S0180">so are they saying this is from our farm?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0070">no some geezer sells it to some farmer sells it to them and then they sell it on</u>
<u n="12" who="S0180">honestly</u>
<u n="13" who="S0070">but it's weird cos we used to get it when we were young</u>
<u n="14" who="S0180">unpasteurised milk yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0070">yeah and it's delicious</u>
<u n="16" who="S0180">that's the thing isn't it? It's been fetched from a farm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0070">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0180">so you know the farm or whatever <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it it well it can upset your stomach</u>
<u n="19" who="S0070">well I mean</u>
<u n="20" who="S0180">it won't kill you though</u>
<u n="21" who="S0070">we <pause dur="short"/> well I was always told yeah that that that you know it's dangerous because it hadn't been pasteurised <pause dur="short"/> but what they were saying yesterday is that there's actually healthy bacteria in the</u>
<u n="22" who="S0180">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I remember seeing a programme about it</u>
<u n="23" who="S0070">I don't know much about it I just know that it tastes amazing</u>
<u n="24" who="S0180">mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0070">so next time I'm out there I think I'll get me a bottle</u>
<u n="26" who="S0180">interesting</u>
<u n="27" who="S0070">hmm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0180">but they have to stop selling it now?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0070">well yeah I suppose apparently and it seems <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="30" who="S0180">hmm <pause dur="short"/> I bought some genuine Dead Sea bath salts</u>
<u n="31" who="S0070">did you?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0180">apparently they're good for you</u>
<u n="33" who="S0070">do you have a bath?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0180">I can't fit in it <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can fit in it <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was a small man</u>
<u n="35" who="S0070">was he?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0180">is a small man</u>
<u n="37" who="S0070">I thought he was German? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0180">yeah he is  he is  a small German but <pause dur="short"/> yeah he's from Bavaria maybe <pause dur="short"/> maybe they're smaller down there <pause dur="short"/> but um well the thing is uh the only bathtub I could lie in was in a home in <anon type="place"/> that's big</u>
<u n="39" who="S0070">uh huh</u>
<u n="40" who="S0180">do you have a <trunc>bath</trunc> in the bathroom? Shower?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0070">no <pause dur="short"/> shower</u>
<u n="42" who="S0180">A shower</u>
<u n="43" who="S0070">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm not really a bath man <pause dur="short"/> I get  I get  restless with baths <pause dur="short"/> gerry likes to bath <pause dur="short"/> but I get a bit you know</u>
<u n="44" who="S0180">I I like it <pause dur="short"/> put the radio on</u>
<u n="45" who="S0070">okay</u>
<u n="46" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0070">I get a bit restless with the radio I need a radio television and computer on <pause dur="short"/> to be comfortable occupied</u>
<u n="48" who="S0180">you're like a little dog with ADH</u>
<u n="49" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="50" who="S0070">yeah <pause dur="short"/> with attention deficit</u>
<u n="51" who="S0180">ADDH</u>
<u n="52" who="S0070">know your acronyms <pause dur="short"/> aDHD</u>
<u n="53" who="S0180">attention Deficit Disorder ADD</u>
<u n="54" who="S0070">I think I am though</u>
<u n="55" who="S0180">ooh</u>
<u n="56" who="S0070">and now I've got to wear glasses</u>
<u n="57" who="S0180">have you?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0070">are you a bit <unclear/> really?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0070">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0180">you know when you get floaters you get floaters in your eyes?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0070">no</u>
<u n="62" who="S0180">bit frustrating</u>
<u n="63" who="S0070">no <pause dur="short"/> I've just been noticing over the last only a couple of months that when I read <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit blurred</u>
<u n="64" who="S0180">you can't see near <pause dur="short"/> I've got the opposite <pause dur="short"/> I can read with them off</u>
<u n="65" who="S0070">can you?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0180">I can  I can  read now <pause dur="short"/> half a metre I can read it</u>
<u n="67" who="S0070">okay</u>
<u n="68" who="S0180">without my glasses <pause dur="short"/> so you've got you are long-sighted</u>
<u n="69" who="S0070">well apparently also I've got astigmatism</u>
<u n="70" who="S0180">really?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0070">so so I've got some problem with they reckon <pause dur="short"/> I disagree with them <pause dur="short"/> cos you get so I went down to for an eye test and she said <trunc>y</trunc> yeah <trunc>you</trunc> the problem is we're so you need glasses the short eh up close</u>
<u n="72" who="S0180">it's all the reading you've been doing for the MA in <unclear/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0070">well maybe <pause dur="short"/> cos and I just thought over the last little while it's cos I've been a bit tired or you know when you're tired it gets a bit but apparently not <pause dur="short"/> apparently I need</u>
<u n="74" who="S0180">oh no</u>
<u n="75" who="S0070">and she said so so I've got varifocals</u>
<u n="76" who="S0180">are these the ones you can just go into Boots and buy off the shelf?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0070">well</u>
<u n="78" who="S0180">Reading glasses or you have to go in for a prescription?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0070">no because because she said there's some problem also with my right eye I think with distance</u>
<u n="80" who="S0180">oh</u>
<u n="81" who="S0070">she said do you have problems reading road signs? I said no not at all <pause dur="short"/> and I don't think I have when she put up her her chart up there and I read it quite well <pause dur="short"/> I thought there was nothing wrong with that <pause dur="short"/> anyway so I got varifocals <pause dur="short"/> so apparently yeah you can't  you can't  get them off the peg can you? So</u>
<u n="82" who="S0180">no</u>
<u n="83" who="S0070">and um two hundred and sixty <unclear/> pounds</u>
<u n="84" who="S0180">two hundred and sixty? Yeah I expected that</u>
<u n="85" who="S0070">I had no idea</u>
<u n="86" who="S0180">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0070">Cos I went in there and I thought that you know well as a student your eyesight is free <trunc>t</trunc> test is free <pause dur="short"/> no it's not it's twenty-eight pounds and then</u>
<u n="88" who="S0180">you got a student card?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0070" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it's not <pause dur="short"/> you don't get any discount <pause dur="short"/> I said do you get discounts? He said yeah if you're an old age pensioner or a <unclear/> for glasses <unclear/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0180">yeah <pause dur="short"/>  for the test you get a discount?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0070">no</u>
<u n="92" who="S0180">really?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0070">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> some places do but not but I went to Vision Express</u>
<u n="94" who="S0180"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> gets it free for the first year if it's a <unclear/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0070">oh really? Oh</u>
<u n="96" who="S0180"><unclear/> And teeth as well apparently</u>
<u n="97" who="S0070">and then  and then and then  they said lenses start from eighty pound and I said well</u>
<u n="98" who="S0180">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0070">it's not gonna be eighty pound it would probably be like a hundred pounds or something <pause dur="short"/> so I saw a pair of <unclear/> frames and I thought oh okay it's gonna cost like two hundred quid altogether isn't it? Two hundred and sixty pound just for the lenses right <pause dur="short"/> I couldn't believe it</u>
<u n="100" who="S0180">and the frames?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0070">well I had to reselect another pair I've gotta go back tomorrow and have a look</u>
<u n="102" who="S0180">it's ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> but if you only use them for reading just use a cheaper pair of frames <pause dur="short"/> but the lenses the cheapest are just two hundred and sixty?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0070">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0180">these might be especially varifocal</u>
<u n="105" who="S0070" trans="overlap">Cos he started off with vary varifocal <pause dur="short"/> and then he said okay so we've got four ones <pause dur="short"/> the first ones which are excellent he said and of course I didn't know any prices at this point I was still on eighty pounds <pause dur="short"/> he said they were excellent they're scratch resistant de de de de <pause dur="short"/> three hundred and sixty pounds and I just I didn't know what to say <pause dur="short"/> I didn't <pause dur="short"/> and I said you know I can't</u>
<u n="106" who="S0180">it's scary <pause dur="short"/> but you can imagine if they  if they  privatise the NHS this what it will be like <pause dur="short"/> it's like there are four ways to chop off your leg</u>
<u n="107" who="S0070">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0180">the first way is a bit more painful</u>
<u n="109" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0070">for the <unclear/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0180">it's cheap though</u>
<u n="112" who="S0070">the second one is you saw it off with a knife</u>
<u n="113" who="S0180">no exactly</u>
<u n="114" who="S0070">no but that's what it would be</u>
<u n="115" who="S0180">for eighty pound more you can get an anaesthetic <pause dur="short"/> and fifty pound you get a pillow</u>
<u n="116" who="S0070">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0070">you can imagine it can't you?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0180">that's what I call suspicious of the Conservatives because like my mum worked in NHS yes they do need reform you do see there's a lot of waste there going on</u>
<u n="119" who="S0070">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0180">but that that's different from saying that's different from privatising it</u>
<u n="121" who="S0070">from privatising it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0180">you can reform something without privatising it in the way they might want to</u>
<u n="123" who="S0070">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0180">along American lines</u>
<u n="125" who="S0070">yeah local subsidies</u>
<u n="126" who="S0180">yeah it would be very I don't think people would accept that though <pause dur="short"/> but they know surely they know that most people wouldn't accept that</u>
<u n="127" who="S0070">but then you know how would we not accept it? How would we you know</u>
<u n="128" who="S0180">people would <unclear/> get angry because they I think <pause dur="short"/> no I can't see it <pause dur="short"/> if that's privatised then hmm there's there's no no hope Britain would be privatise it the NHS</u>
<u n="129" who="S0070"><unclear/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> is that <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0180">hmm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0070">no there isn't any hope but <pause dur="short"/> no it would be be shocking wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0180">it would be it'd just be impossible wouldn't it? What would happen if we did have what it would be the school systems like that <pause dur="short"/> the school system is not <pause dur="short"/> I think if they  if they  make the school system like NHS it would have been good but you know there's still in UK a lot of private schools <pause dur="short"/> from the fifties onwards they've given they still let a lot of private schools get away with being quite elitist</u>
<u n="133" who="S0070">right</u>
<u n="134" who="S0180">and you still got and in the UK now you've got</u>
<u n="135" who="S0070">well and then the school I well the school I went to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I maintain I didn't have a secondary education</u>
<u n="136" who="S0180">really?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0070">it was  it was  a church school that that my parents paid for <pause dur="short"/> I mean we didn't do <unclear/> we didn't do anything</u>
<u n="138" who="S0180">and they paid for it?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0070">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean cos I suppose my parents sort of thought oh we'll send them to private school that would be good for them</u>
<u n="140" who="S0180">ooh</u>
<u n="141" who="S0070">but my brother  my brother  was a pain in the ass and an asshole and a trouble maker <pause dur="short"/> so they didn't want him going to the local comprehensive school because he was a</u>
<u n="142" who="S0180">A tearaway</u>
<u n="143" who="S0070">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so he they sent him into a school in <anon type="place"/> and and because because you know I suppose he was my older brother and I wanted to go to in the same school as he did so they sent me there <pause dur="short"/> but it was <unclear/> it was absolutely crap <pause dur="short"/> we didn't do anything <pause dur="short"/> like it was the kind of thing there were a few students who did who were kind of quite motivated and and engaged with the classes and I suppose came from families who who had some knowledge of education <pause dur="short"/> my parents didn't have any sort of real knowledge of education <pause dur="short"/> so you know when they came up done your homework? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> Okay <pause dur="short"/> mm go out and play <pause dur="short"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> yipee <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> so so we didn't  we didn't  do anything <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and and you know <trunc>t</trunc> the the where were <trunc>certa</trunc> there was no certain <trunc>standardisa</trunc> you know there was no Ofsted then <pause dur="short"/> so you paid the money and that's it <pause dur="short"/> went in hung around came back again <pause dur="short"/> it's funny <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying about in Zambia cos I suppose again there you pay for education worth in Africa because it's</u>
<u n="144" who="S0180">yeah you pay for everything</u>
<u n="145" who="S0070">you pay for everything</u>
<u n="146" who="S0180">water</u>
<u n="147" who="S0070">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0180">like at the <unclear/> even if they now</u>
<u n="149" who="S0070" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and so so you then have cos she said she went to a school once and the teacher was laying down at the front of the class</u>
<u n="150" who="S0180">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0070">you know and these are kids in front of a class of kids and he was paid to go there and I suppose they'd only paid a little bit <pause dur="short"/> if they paid a bit more he might have sat up <pause dur="short"/> if they paid a bit more he might have stood up <pause dur="short"/> paid a bit more he might have taught them something</u>
<u n="152" who="S0180"><unclear/> about this all across the developing world</u>
<u n="153" who="S0070">ah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0180">you get a system like that there</u>
<u n="155" who="S0070">what you pay for is what you get <pause dur="short"/> they don't get pens or pencils or paper <pause dur="short"/> they've got to bring their own paper</u>
<u n="156" who="S0180">paper</u>
<u n="157" who="S0070">and yeah yeah you can understand <pause dur="short"/> you know they're not you know but it's open to corruption then isn't it? You know cos you pay a little bit you know well you can come and sit on a chair and you're not going to get taught anything</u>
<u n="158" who="S0180">so my my cousin's daughter in Kenya goes to a school where some of the kids don't have enough to eat in the morning</u>
<u n="159" who="S0070">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0180">so my aunt from Australia who's going to Kenya to do some charity work like has organised a kitchen <pause dur="short"/> so they can come and have breakfast and lunch</u>
<u n="161" who="S0070">hmm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0180">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was helping her do that and I was shocked and thought hmm? Even the school that my cousin's daughter is going some kids are really quite poor <pause dur="short"/> you know she was saying we need to go and do some voluntary work</u>
<u n="163" who="S0070">hmm</u>
<u n="164" who="S0180">because um to provide breakfast and lunch for these kids</u>
<u n="165" who="S0070">hmm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0180">get them in school</u>
<u n="167" who="S0070">uh hmm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0180">but they have like a huge gap between the elite schools which are like you know have a dash of <unclear/> or whatever <pause dur="short"/> and then you have the opposite extreme it's an even bigger gap in those countries</u>
<u n="169" who="S0183">can you hold him?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0070">yes</u>
<u n="171" who="S0183">so I can get on with some stuff</u>
<u n="172" who="S0180">aw is he sleeping now?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0183">I washed his clothes</u>
<u n="174" who="S0180">aw <pause dur="short"/> he make little noises <pause dur="short"/> try and take him out every day though cos fresh air's good for him and it just sort of sleeps more more <pause dur="short"/> he's warm now <pause dur="short"/> ah he's so cute <pause dur="short"/> I would say that wouldn't I?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0070">I suppose so</u>
<u n="176" who="S0180">aw he he sleeps very well after feeding <pause dur="short"/> he's sleeps like that he's like conked out</u>
<u n="177" who="S0070">yeah it's nice isn't it?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0180">mummy will wrap him up and <pause dur="short"/> I could just sit on the street and <trunc>t</trunc> twiddle his dummy</u>
<u n="179" who="S0070">well people would give you money <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> there you go <pause dur="short"/> have some money you say yeah I can't afford to feed the baby <pause dur="short"/> down on the <anon type="place"/> high street</u>
<u n="180" who="S0180">I'll tell you what is so funny about people you know there's a wonderful old statue temperance you know the temperance statue? They get well you know they had alcohol problems this year that they put these free water fountains they were talking about</u>
<u n="181" who="S0070">I didn't know</u>
<u n="182" who="S0180">so there's one in you know the church on <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0070">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0180">and it's the only spot where all the winos hang up and the fountains of this <trunc>te</trunc> the temperance fountains don't work <pause dur="short"/> it's ironic isn't it they built that to give people water so they wouldn't drink so much gin and beer in the Victorian times and drunk and stuff and um now you just see all the drunks sitting around it drinking beer cans and none of the fountains work <pause dur="short"/> just that whole I want to take a photo one day <pause dur="short"/> that's so ironic that scene</u>
<u n="185" who="S0070">it is isn't it? The fountains stopped working long ago but the drunks are still here</u>
<u n="186" who="S0180">but they sell those big beer cans for a pound</u>
<u n="187" who="S0070">that is shocking like shocking I've I've often thought about that you know go past an off-licence</u>
<u n="188" who="S0180">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0070">and <trunc>a</trunc> all those things are only designed by alcoholics aren't they?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0180">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> well a newsagent down here on <anon type="place"/> Road</u>
<u n="191" who="S0070">hmm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0180">every time I go in there for my morning paper on Saturday or Sunday there's a you know there's an old drunk guy in there buying four for six cans of Tenants <unclear/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0070">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> you get drunk for a pound</u>
<u n="194" who="S0180">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and he's always having some sort of drunken conversation with the poor woman behind the counter</u>
<u n="195" who="S0070">yeah it's just mad and then you get those litres and white lightening cider <pause dur="short"/> I like a glass of cider but who else apart from</u>
<u n="196" who="S0180">type of people who buy that?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0070">buy that <pause dur="short"/> and obviously it doesn't taste like cider but it tastes like <trunc>app</trunc> like rocket fuel cos for <unclear/></u>
<u n="198" who="S0180">the stigma <pause dur="short"/> but they they make it for the people</u>
<u n="199" who="S0070">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and all that that like range of litter bottles that you get you know those little you know</u>
<u n="200" who="S0180">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0180">whiskeys <trunc>a</trunc>and you know <trunc>w</trunc> what's that for then? What's that one for or that one for or that one for?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0180">just for show you know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0070">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know and then all of those you know the cheap end of the whiskey you know your White Stags your Bells and Teachers you know it's not you know sit at home and savour the taste of like <pause dur="short"/> it must be pretty weird to savour the taste of the whiskey anyway <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="204" who="S0180">it is a weird the situation isn't it? You can see a big bogey up there</u>
<u n="205" who="S0070">you can suck it out <pause dur="short"/> put your mouth over it and suck it out <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yum yum <pause dur="short"/> baby bogey</u>
<u n="206" who="S0180">are we recording still? Ah <pause dur="short"/> twelve more minutes <pause dur="short"/> twelve more minutes to make half an hour</u>
<u n="207" who="S0070">half an hour</u>
<u n="208" who="S0180">but we shouldn't say that on the tape</u>
<u n="209" who="S0070">I suppose not but it's an extra conversation</u>
<u n="210" who="S0180">yeah he's put on about a kilo and a half since he's been born so em</u>
<u n="211" who="S0070">how long when was he born nearly a month ago?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0180">five weeks ago</u>
<u n="213" who="S0070">five weeks</u>
<u n="214" who="S0180">eh five weeks on Sunday about four and a half weeks ago <pause dur="short"/> he's one month <pause dur="short"/> but he he can sleep through it's amazing how they can sleep through conversations cos <pause dur="short"/> I can have  I can have  the radio on and Wendy might be hoovering and he'll still be sleeping <pause dur="short"/> because they they have a way of shutting off</u>
<u n="215" who="S0070">I was going to say what do they have what do they hear you know do they?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0180">well they</u>
<u n="217" who="S0070">what goes on in their heads?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0180">most things of noise but they can if they need to sleep they can just shut it all out and sleep</u>
<u n="219" who="S0183">well that's cos when they're in the womb they hear it already so they just get used to  used  to it</u>
<u n="220" who="S0070">mm mm</u>
<u n="221" who="S0180">nothing new it's just less muffled</u>
<u n="222" who="S0183">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0180">what's funny though is like when you after he's fed</u>
<u n="224" who="S0070">oh they do smell yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0180">they smell buttery</u>
<u n="226" who="S0070">well apparently we smell buttery anyway don't we? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0180">but it with the breast milk he does <pause dur="short"/> it's like smelling it's like he's eaten some you know anchor butter or something</u>
<u n="228" who="S0070">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0180">it's just a lovely rick <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't smell so much now but <pause dur="short"/> well he's got a <unclear/> in his mouth that's why <pause dur="short"/> it's going to be very weird and corny <pause dur="short"/> no but it's true it's nice <pause dur="short"/> it's a lovely sort of buttery creamy</u>
<u n="230" who="S0070">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0180">you could eat him</u>
<u n="232" who="S0070"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah so yeah let's get some of that <trunc>pas</trunc> unpasteurised milk when we're in Oxford street next and you can sit at home and sniff it</u>
<u n="233" who="S0180">I give him a Maori greeting look</u>
<u n="234" who="S0070">ah <pause dur="short"/> sweet</u>
<u n="235" who="S0180">do you know I'm sort of when I was there in New Zealand</u>
<u n="236" who="S0070">did you notice many Maori people?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0070">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0180">but a lot of them are mixed as well</u>
<u n="239" who="S0070">yeah yeah and there's a lot of Pacific islanders <pause dur="short"/> that was quiet interesting isn't it?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0180">so they tend to be poorer or more working class cos there are ghettos up and Auckland and</u>
<u n="241" who="S0070">yeah and apparently they there's there are sort of drug problems</u>
<u n="242" who="S0180">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0070">which they kind of</u>
<u n="244" who="S0180">have you seen that film Once We Were Warriors</u>
<u n="245" who="S0070">no</u>
<u n="246" who="S0180">with Tamerero Morrison <pause dur="short"/> he's a Maori actor <pause dur="short"/> he was  He was  in Star Wars</u>
<u n="247" who="S0070">oh right</u>
<u n="248" who="S0180">but he's a really really good actor that was about the Maori communities in Auckland</u>
<u n="249" who="S0070"><unclear/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0180">yeah and it's about eh it was actually about child abuse within the family there for</u>
<u n="251" who="S0070">okay</u>
<u n="252" who="S0180">but it was a very interesting film <pause dur="short"/> but quite violent</u>
<u n="253" who="S0070">was it</u>
<u n="254" who="S0180">it was set <pause dur="short"/> it's a really famous em</u>
<u n="255" who="S0070">once We Were Warriors</u>
<u n="256" who="S0180">yeah it's really famous <pause dur="short"/> that and Whale Rider <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0070">I've seen Whale Rider yeah yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0180"><unclear/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0070">hmm <pause dur="short"/> but my mind's made up <pause dur="short"/> I've got a <unclear/> for a <unclear/> you know that</u>
<u n="260" who="S0180">those are two well most well-known Kiwi films</u>
<u n="261" who="S0070">actually I that reminds me I've got a thing for Love Film you know that <pause dur="short"/> and it's a free cos I joined it but someone came round to the house before Christmas and said did you go to da da da da da sign here <pause dur="short"/> so I signed here to get rid of them and it turned out I was you know wrong</u>
<u n="262" who="S0180">oh no <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> you might have been signed up to the Mormons</u>
<u n="263" who="S0070">well mm I probably have as well <pause dur="short"/> so they give me a free card that I can give to someone so you if I give it to then you can have free membership</u>
<u n="264" who="S0180">oh is that online where you order online?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0070">yeah you order online they send them to you send them through you get um you can watch them send them back <pause dur="short"/> they are quite convenient</u>
<u n="266" who="S0180">I might have a look at that <pause dur="short"/> what's it called? The company?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0070">love Film <pause dur="short"/> but I've got a a card which I can give to you</u>
<u n="268" who="S0180">you've never used it <pause dur="short"/> they <unclear/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0070">no I've got <pause dur="short"/> I'm a member</u>
<u n="270" who="S0180">oh so you can recommend someone</u>
<u n="271" who="S0070">I can recommend someone and you you get like a month two months free</u>
<u n="272" who="S0180" trans="overlap">yeah do that yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I don't often watch films but I would be interested in doing that</u>
<u n="273" who="S0070">well things like this you know so you get the obscure ones aren't like you know on television you can get hold of</u>
<u n="274" who="S0180">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that would be good actually I'd like to do that</u>
<u n="275" who="S0070">I keep forgetting every time I see you to bring it  bring it  over</u>
<u n="276" who="S0180">yeah no no do that <pause dur="short"/> no I I will send you this <unclear/> because that was very sweet for to get that flight <trunc>d</trunc> for some reason</u>
<u n="277" who="S0070">but this one particular guy <pause dur="short"/> we were we went to a pub quiz one night</u>
<u n="278" who="S0180">hmm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0070">my friend's girlfriend was doing it <pause dur="short"/> she she does stuff in nutrition and she was doing a a seminar we thought oh god let not sit through that <pause dur="short"/> so we nipped off to the pub and got involved in a pub quiz <pause dur="short"/> and the guy who was doing it he was a Maori</u>
<u n="280" who="S0180">oh?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0070">but he was obviously gay</u>
<u n="282" who="S0180">hmm</u>
<u n="283" who="S0070">and I thought it thought mm</u>
<u n="284" who="S0180">be it might be true it might in this in</u>
<u n="285" who="S0070">well it might not be yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0180">in other cultures it's not <unclear/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0070">I mean I don't know it was <trunc>al</trunc> all that I found interesting was travel all over to the other side of the world and camp people sound</u>
<u n="288" who="S0180">yeah yeah they do</u>
<u n="289" who="S0070">must be a <unclear/> <unclear/> Phonetic eh</u>
<u n="290" who="S0180">was he really?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0070">the phonetics of camp was he</u>
<u n="292" who="S0180"><trunc>Ul</trunc> ultra camp was he?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0070">not too <trunc>u</trunc> not sort of you know not annoyingly camp but you know just the way the sort of</u>
<u n="294" who="S0180">how funny</u>
<u n="295" who="S0070">yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean there's a kind of there's a  there's a  voice isn't there? Sometimes</u>
<u n="296" who="S0180">and the <unclear/> funny isn't it?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0070">it is yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0180">faster than me I used to do a teacher's cup there used to be a teacher couple of teachers in the town I was teaching in in China and I had a really strong New Zealand accent <pause dur="short"/> and they'd say crash crash and jumps</u>
<u n="299" who="S0070">yeah and they actually write it now in some places I suppose cos they go and</u>
<u n="300" who="S0180">no they don't</u>
<u n="301" who="S0070">yeah when they're emphasising that <unclear/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0180">oh really the combination ah right</u>
<u n="303" who="S0070">I think they realised that's its <pause dur="short"/> yeah so we say we sell fish and chips <pause dur="short"/> fish and chips</u>
<u n="304" who="S0180">all all our sports teachers at school in London were itinerant Australians and Kiwis <pause dur="short"/> they came to London for a couple of years and then went went back in</u>
<u n="305" who="S0070">they're mad on outside things aren't they?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0180">we had a lot of them</u>
<u n="307" who="S0070">I suppose you would be I mean</u>
<u n="308" who="S0180">we had a lot of <trunc>antipido</trunc> <trunc>antipido</trunc> <trunc>anti</trunc></u>
<u n="309" who="S0070"> tipodean</u>
<u n="310" who="S0180">antipodeans <pause dur="short"/> one of my main memory was the big  at the end of the sports session <pause dur="short"/> okay now guys put the cups in bag</u>
<u n="311" who="S0070">cats <trunc>c</trunc> <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="312" who="S0180"><unclear/> Put the cups  put the cups  in the bag now people</u>
<u n="313" who="S0070">are South Africans are they considered as antipodeans?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0180">I think they are because it's a similar accent <pause dur="short"/> do you think it has something to do with the um?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0070">I thought it meant a place</u>
<u n="316" who="S0180">I don't know I think it means southern hemisphere? But that it's interesting that it's a similar accent isn't it the?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0070">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0180">is it to do with the magnetic magnetism of the southern pole?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0070">yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0180">does that affect the voice?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0070">I don't know <unclear/></u>
<u n="322" who="S0180">because why is it the South African accent so similar and why is American not like that?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0070">you know do you think it's to do with the <trunc>em</trunc> <trunc>em</trunc> em eh <unclear/></u>
<u n="324" who="S0180">Cos a lot of Irish went to Australia</u>
<u n="325" who="S0070">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0180">so why isn't the Australian accent similar to the American which it does sound very Irish <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0070"><unclear/>? mm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0180">these these are the really interesting things about linguistics aren't they?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0070">mm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0180">and socially but but <pause dur="short"/> again you don't see that</u>
<u n="331" who="S0070">no I've not heard any</u>
<u n="332" who="S0180">and it's nice isn't it?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0070">well I suppose you got to be careful where you start doing things like that because people sort of accuse you of all kind of</u>
<u n="334" who="S0180">well</u>
<u n="335" who="S0070"></u>
<u n="336" who="S0180">well <unclear/> be damned</u>
<u n="337" who="S0070">I would <pause dur="short"/> do and be damned yes <pause dur="short"/> I was in London Met the other day filling in a form and it came across ethnicity</u>
<u n="338" who="S0180">really?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0070">and it was weird because there was a box with nothing in it was it wasn't a tick box <pause dur="short"/> and I thought how strange? How would you describe yourself ethnically <pause dur="short"/> I would never do such a thing you know and I suppose there are certain people who would  who would  like want to say I am this I am that <pause dur="short"/> but I mean I would not know <pause dur="short"/> unless I'm given a tick box and forced</u>
<u n="340" who="S0180">what was your form for?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0070">I can't remember it was some to <trunc>ki</trunc> I was re-enrolling <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="342" who="S0180">but it's weird being <unclear/> I can I had one for like government cos they're obsessed with it aren't they in the UK</u>
<u n="343" who="S0070">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0180">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it's not accurate</u>
<u n="345" who="S0070">no it's not because you're either white British white Irish or go to bloody hell sort of thing</u>
<u n="346" who="S0180">and white white doesn't mean anything anyway</u>
<u n="347" who="S0070">White doesn't mean anything you know and and and and and but so so what I mean is if you're forced to tick a box you <trunc>ki</trunc> you kinda go okay you're white bloody British then <pause dur="short"/> but if you're asked what's your ethnicity I don't frigging know you know</u>
<u n="348" who="S0180">I always other or put mixed</u>
<u n="349" who="S0070">well you see I was actually thinking should I just write in the box other</u>
<u n="350" who="S0180">yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0070">you know <pause dur="short"/> cos like oh yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0180">I suppose <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="353" who="S0180">Cos how would you describe</u>
<u n="354" who="S0070">yeah <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> bit of Irish</u>
<u n="355" who="S0180">you got an Irish yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0070">yeah yeah I mean what what what I always put mixed other cos it's true <pause dur="short"/> yeah because how would you sort of describe British British <pause dur="short"/> asian British</u>
<u n="357" who="S0180">british those darn boxes I don't know but it's not</u>
<u n="358" who="S0070">but they're they're not</u>
<u n="359" who="S0180">and I'm not Anglo-Indian cos my mum's not completely Indian</u>
<u n="360" who="S0070">right <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="361" who="S0180">her mum was not Indian</u>
<u n="362" who="S0070">well there you go she was born in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0180"><anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0070"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0180">but <trunc>e</trunc> even ethnically adapted <unclear/> but her mum didn't <pause dur="short"/> her mum was <anon type="place"/> and they well they're quite mixed themselves</u>
<u n="366" who="S0070">oh</u>
<u n="367" who="S0180">I wouldn't  I wouldn't  even say she was ever Indian</u>
<u n="368" who="S0070">we should start writing a <unclear/> Well actually</u>
<u n="369" who="S0180">okay if they wanna know</u>
<u n="370" who="S0070">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> if you're really that interested which you're not</u>
<u n="371" who="S0180">so what was interesting is that when we were in Brixton in em Costa Coffee which is very nice new Costa Coffee they've built under the railway arches <pause dur="short"/> and there was a mother there next to us who was promoting these <trunc>na</trunc> these nappies that you eh <trunc>dis</trunc> not disposable what's the opposite reuseable nappies <pause dur="short"/> and they're launching them at the <anon type="place"/> cinema where they have a mother baby parent baby afternoon from twelve till two and they're gonna a free demonstration of how to use them <pause dur="short"/> it looks really good <pause dur="short"/> but she handed us a leaflet if you're interested fill this in and we'll send you some more information <pause dur="short"/> and one of the lines was ethnicity</u>
<u n="372" who="S0070">yeah why?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0180">what's ethnicity? Are they gonna see ooh you know en Anglo-Saxons signing up for our <pause dur="short"/> are they <pause dur="short"/> are only ethnicities interested in doing the dishes</u>
<u n="374" who="S0070">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0180">I mean what will they do with that information? It's totally irrelevant in that context so I mean you know the government's is obsessed with it <pause dur="short"/> cos they put it on their form cos they want</u>
<u n="376" who="S0070">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0180">okay they want to know if discrimination is happening or or they want to know if certain ethnicities lives in a particular area</u>
<u n="378" who="S0070">right</u>
<u n="379" who="S0180">so it can provide I don't know language service <pause dur="short"/> but then even if you it doesn't tell you anything it doesn't tell you what language you speak</u>
<u n="380" who="S0070">yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0180">it doesn't tell you um <pause dur="short"/> you know it's really misleading <pause dur="short"/> but it's it's a legacy of the past really isn't it?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0070">it is really <pause dur="short"/> yeah it is</u>
<u n="383" who="S0180">obsessed was that</u>
<u n="384" who="S0070">so that was a box ticking thing or or a space left?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0180">no it's a space left cos you've got to bloody</u>
<u n="386" who="S0070">that's what I mean it's impossible to do it really? If you're  if you're  a living conscious being</u>
<u n="387" who="S0180">yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0070">if you're a philistine and you think ah I want to be Black Caribbean then it's you know easy to fill in isn't it? And I want to be white British <pause dur="short"/> wey</u>
<u n="389" who="S0180">yes</u>
<u n="390" who="S0070">you know it's easy but if you actually think well hang on a minute</u>
<u n="391" who="S0180">that's the thing isn't it?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0070">I'm not in the National Front</u>
<u n="393" who="S0180">that's the thing with research isn't it?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0070">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0180">you've got <pause dur="short"/> you if you were designing a survey or questionnaire</u>
<u n="396" who="S0070">quite <pause dur="short"/> would you do such a silly thing?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0180">didn't we have this discussion with <unclear/> where is it what is it open or closed research questions?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0183">open</u>
<u n="399" who="S0180">yeah and then what would you do with that? Cos <trunc>i</trunc> is that quantifiable data? Well I suppose not</u>
<u n="400" who="S0070">well I suppose this is it it's not isn't it it's put a <trunc>quanti</trunc> <trunc>quala</trunc> quantity in in boxes</u>
<u n="401" who="S0180" trans="overlap">it it it it yeah <pause dur="short"/> it would</u>
<u n="402" who="S0180" trans="overlap">so you could divide the box somehow <unclear/> quantify it can you?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0070">yeah but if they wanted to  what would they say? Oh we got a lot of others</u>
<u n="404" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="405" who="S0070">ooh we're all others <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to start ticking other <pause dur="short"/> cos what would they say if you did tick</u>
<u n="406" who="S0180">start a campaign <pause dur="short"/> everybody tick other</u>
<u n="407" who="S0070">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> what's that <unclear/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0180">none of the above</u>
<u n="409" who="S0070">none of the above</u>
<u n="410" who="S0180">oh yeah did you see that? It's a great film isn't it? I love that  I love that film</u>
<u n="411" who="S0070" trans="overlap">it's brilliant <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0180">and he was  And John Candy</u>
<u n="413" who="S0070">yes</u>
<u n="414" who="S0180">yes they worked well together didn't they? Cos he was just such a nut case in that film <pause dur="short"/> which it <unclear/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0070">yeah brilliant</u>
<u n="416" who="S0180">I love the bit when eh what is it? They go they get into the hotel and the top floor's already taken <pause dur="short"/> how much are they paying? And the they find out oh we'll pay double <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> It's a film about madness of the eighties isn't it?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0070">yeah and it's into <pause dur="short"/> no we don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0180">it's it's it's a remake of an original</u>
<u n="419" who="S0070">oh is it?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0180">the original was made in the fifties or something</u>
<u n="421" who="S0070">ah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0180">and in the end he just makes it and he has to spend thirty thousand in <unclear/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0180">and he buys that stamp and sends it</u>
<u n="424" who="S0183">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0180">em cos it's postmarked is it not <unclear/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0070">oh yeah it's not worth anything</u>
<u n="427" who="S0180">Great isn't it?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0070">no it's a good film</u>
<u n="429" who="S0180">yeah well well none of the above</u>
<u n="430" who="S0070">well quite yeah because how would that  how would that  fit you know do you have to then explain if you tick other do you have to explain what other is?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0180">well that's the thing you don't sometimes <pause dur="short"/> so that renders their surveys a bit useless doesn't</u>
<u n="432" who="S0070">but would you cos you know when you  when you  fill in a landing card and it says nationality as stated on your passport so that you don't start saying you know</u>
<u n="433" who="S0180">Cos your nationality doesn't mean ethnicity</u>
<u n="434" who="S0070">no exactly yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0180">but some people take it to mean nationality</u>
<u n="436" who="S0070">and I was thinking the other day about racism <pause dur="short"/> isn't that a bit of an outdated a term really? Cos we don't sort of talk about it races anymore do we? We call it like ethniscicism</u>
<u n="437" who="S0180">yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0070">I don't like your ethnic group</u>
<u n="439" who="S0180">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and ethnic group can mean you have the same ancestry but different religion <pause dur="short"/> cos they've started saying you know if you're Jewish ethnicity or if you're eh</u>
<u n="440" who="S0070">yeah <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> or like an India northern Indian</u>
<u n="441" who="S0180">or Muslim ethnicity</u>
<u n="442" who="S0070">A Muslim or</u>
<u n="443" who="S0180">but that's not <trunc>ethni</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> people get very confused isn't it because Muslim is not an ethnicity it's a religion</u>
<u n="444" who="S0070">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="445" who="S0180">but you'd be surprised if you asked people even university professors</u>
<u n="446" who="S0070">right</u>
<u n="447" who="S0180">some people take ethnicity not to mean genetic ancestry but they mean religion</u>
<u n="448" who="S0070">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0180">belief</u>
<u n="450" who="S0070">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0180">but that's totally fluid isn't it?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0070">hmm</u>
<u n="453" who="S0180">it's all just confused <pause dur="short"/> basically</u>
<u n="454" who="S0070">thank goodness for cake really</u>
<u n="455" who="S0180">yes</u>
<u n="456" who="S0070">ooh that's nice that drink</u>
<u n="457" who="S0180">ooh <pause dur="short"/> put the <unclear/> back in there if you</u>
<u n="458" who="S0070">go on have some more  have some more  ice</u>
<u n="459" who="S0180">have some more <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0070">I'm okay for now I'm a bit full actually Roy</u>
<u n="461" who="S0180">well that's good <pause dur="short"/> we only have a few minutes</u>
<u n="462" who="S0070">have we? It's good though isn't it?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0180">I can splice though <pause dur="short"/> I can cut off</u>
<u n="464" who="S0070">can you?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0070">the first few minutes if they were rude and then continue</u>
<u n="466" who="S0070">are we going out in the garden?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0180">yeah we can do? Cos we could do another one out there</u>
<u n="468" who="S0070">yeah <pause dur="short"/> bit nicer</u>
<u n="469" who="S0180">I'll just get the mat so you can sit down on it</u>
<u n="470" who="S0070">okay <pause dur="short"/> cos we may  we may  as well</u>
<u n="471" who="S0180" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0070">shall we stop it now?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0180">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0070">yeah cos we can still carry on nattering</u>
<u n="475" who="S0180">I could take  out there</u>
<u n="476" who="S0070">well yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0180">Wendy I'm taking the  out</u>
<u n="478" who="S0070">we're going <unclear/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0180"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="480" who="S0070">she's doing something on her computer</u>
<u n="481" who="S0180">no don't cry</u>
<u n="482" who="S0070"><shift new="singing"/> Don't cry for me <trunc>Argenti</trunc> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="483" who="S0180">when I kiss him he starts crying</u>
<u n="484" who="S0070">well I'm not surprised</u>
<u n="485" who="S0180">Don't</u>
<u n="486" who="S0183">it's alright he just needs</u>
<u n="487" who="S0070">he just gets a little shock <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="488" who="S0180">ah <pause dur="short"/> I'm sorry baby</u>
<u n="489" who="S0070">look at all his stubble</u>
<u n="490" who="S0180">I'll give you a Maori kiss instead <pause dur="short"/> ah that's great like to see a Maori kiss</u>
<u n="491" who="S0183"><unclear/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0180">so cute</u>
<u n="493" who="S0070">does he wake up in the night? At this stage?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0180">he he does yeah <pause dur="short"/> but only if if he's uncomfortable and he needs a nappy change it's different from his hunger cry <pause dur="short"/> if he's uncomfortable he starts going uh uh uh uh uh <pause dur="short"/> if he's hungry he goes waaa waaa waaa</u>
<u n="495" who="S0070">oh no <pause dur="short"/> sounds pretty serious when he's hungry then</u>
<u n="496" who="S0183">yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0070">kind of a bit like you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when you're hungry</u>
<u n="498" who="S0183">huh?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0070">A bit like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when he's hungry</u>
<u n="500" who="S0180">I won't take him out like this cos it's not going to be hot</u>
<u n="501" who="S0183">hmm <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="502" who="S0180">he's he's got two blankets around him and it's nineteen outside</u>
<u n="503" who="S0070"><trunc>N</trunc> <trunc>n</trunc> <trunc>n</trunc> nineteen</u>
<u n="504" who="S0180">it's probably warmer outside than it is in here</u>
<u n="505" who="S0070">and he doesn't need the bathing suit</u>
<u n="506" who="S0180">I'm sure we'll just put his hat on <pause dur="short"/> just give me his hat and his baby suit and <pause dur="short"/> I wanna <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'll commandeer you to take the seating mat</u>
<u n="507" who="S0070">seating mat</u>
<u n="508" who="S0180">let's have look</u>
<u n="509" who="S0183">you want to take a suit</u>
<u n="510" who="S0070">picnic mat <pause dur="short"/> yeah we'll take a baby suit cos it's always um <pause dur="short"/> can you get the picnic stacked out for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to take down?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0183">yeah mm hm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0180">we'll go to sit outside</u>
<u n="513" who="S0070">I'd like to <unclear/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0180">yeah? <unclear/> scarf he already wearing one scarf</u>
<u n="515" who="S0070">well just just cos it might still be a bit you know <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to catch a chill <pause dur="short"/> I'm a bit of a poofter</u>
<u n="516" who="S0180">get two <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="517" who="S0183">no one's enough</u>
<u n="518" who="S0180">no no cos we can lie out or? Sit <pause dur="short"/> scare <pause dur="short"/> two one's not big enough really <pause dur="short"/> do you want this?</u>
<u n="519" who="S0183">no I'm okay <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm a bit full</u>
<u n="520" who="S0180"><unclear/> we'll leave it for now <pause dur="short"/> fruit? I will have a banana of you like</u>
<u n="521" who="S0070">I might when I come back cos they were very tasty</u>
<u n="522" who="S0180">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0070">to fire me up for the road</u>
<u n="524" who="S0180">we'll go sit sit outside</u>
<u n="525" who="S0183">you going to cover him?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0180">I will cover him don't worry <pause dur="short"/> he's gonna be okay with his papa</u>
<u n="527" who="S0070">get your sunglasses as well?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0180">I can shade him with the big umbrella</u>
<u n="529" who="S0183"><unclear/>?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0180">yes <pause dur="short"/> I've got my phone as well <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> send me the big umbrella it can be a sun shade</u>
<u n="531" who="S0183"><unclear/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0180">Cos it could be a sun shade for him <pause dur="short"/> have you got a lightly coloured umbrella?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0070">oi</u>
<u n="534" who="S0070">Cos doesn't black absorbs heat</u>
<u n="535" who="S0183">I do <pause dur="short"/> apart from it's a bit smaller</u>
<u n="536" who="S0180">see I'm thinking <unclear/> liberty <pause dur="short"/> no it won't be too small because <pause dur="short"/> you'll see <pause dur="short"/> alright this is my</u>
<u n="537" who="S0070">have you made a dog pool what's going on here?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0180">I found that in the garden</u>
<u n="539" who="S0070">you liar</u>
<u n="540" who="S0180">I did <pause dur="short"/> I would never say <pause dur="short"/> I would never be seen being a glory supporter <pause dur="short"/> that's so you can hit hit their logo</u>
</body>
</text>
