<text id="SHBY">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:12:59</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-07-22</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0421 S0423</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Manchester</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Where to put belongings, holidays, routines/ chores, cinema, returning product, Oldham, camera battery, card reader, shops, directions, weather, illnesses, university. </topics>
		<activity>Father and daughter converse on the way to the shops</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0421">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lytham St Annes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2>Hungarian</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0423">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bolton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Manchester, England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mossley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Customer Services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0421">I don't have much stuff</u>
<u n="2" who="S0423">I think the children must be breaking up from school</u>
<u n="3" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0423"><unclear>bit early</unclear></u>
<u n="5" who="S0421">I just have the necessities it's just I don't know where to put it</u>
<u n="6" who="S0423">maybe you need more cupboards</u>
<u n="7" who="S0421">I've got no room <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's like stuff that I like need but I'm like I just like I couldn't throw it out <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I just don't know how where to put it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0423">have you not got an attic of a good size?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0421">we've loads of stuff in the attic already</u>
<u n="10" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="long"/> it's half two already</u>
<u n="11" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>really gone quick</unclear></u>
<u n="13" who="S0421" trans="overlap">what have you done today?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0423">well it's my first day off so</u>
<u n="15" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh is it? oh</u>
<u n="16" who="S0423">I've been getting up early for work up to now so I've erm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0421">were you not off erm</u>
<u n="18" who="S0423">had a bit of a lie in got up</u>
<u n="19" who="S0421" trans="overlap">Sunday?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0423" trans="overlap">about nine no</u>
<u n="21" who="S0421">you know are going to <trunc>wor</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh no well <trunc>w</trunc>well no we come back Saturday</u>
<u n="23" who="S0421">yeah so were you off?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I was off Sunday</u>
<u n="25" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I was in Monday and Tuesday</u>
<u n="27" who="S0421">oh right</u>
<u n="28" who="S0423">so it's quite good really cos I <trunc>wa</trunc> I was only two days in work and then</u>
<u n="29" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0423">got my day off today</u>
<u n="31" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0423">cos I was so tired going back to work yeah I was off Sunday so I went over to see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> so I was in work early <trunc>s</trunc> early Monday morning early Tuesday <pause dur="short"/> so I got up about half eight quarter to nine this morning bit of had some breakfast did a bit of tidying up <pause dur="short"/> well I've not really I've still got to sort everything out you know since I come back I've gotta do the washing</u>
<u n="33" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0423" trans="overlap">wash my clothes and put bags away and stuff so I wanna <unclear>plan for</unclear> so get that done today and tomorrow could do with giving the place a bit of a clean have to get out and do some shopping get some food in <pause dur="long"/> so yeah I thought I'll have a look at what's on at the cinema in case you wanted to go out but I <trunc>wou</trunc> don't really have any money till I get paid next</u>
<u n="35" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0423">after going on holiday I don't think there's much on at the minute anyway</u>
<u n="37" who="S0421">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't think so <pause dur="long"/> yeah I mean it's only one ninety-nine this thing that I'm returning but I might as well return it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0423">well yeah why give the shop the money if it isn't working?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know if it's not working</u>
<u n="40" who="S0423">maybe you you'll have to <pause dur="short"/> dunno cos it's been a while you've had it</u>
<u n="41" who="S0421">no it's still</u>
<u n="42" who="S0423" trans="overlap">if you're gonna</u>
<u n="43" who="S0421">I can still return it</u>
<u n="44" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="45" who="S0421">I have about a week left</u>
<u n="46" who="S0423">oh right <pause dur="short"/> so you don't really have to explain or anything to say it's not never worked since you got it?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's still in its packaging so it's obvious I've not used it</u>
<u n="48" who="S0423">well how do you know it's worked or not then?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0421">cos you just</u>
<u n="50" who="S0423" trans="overlap">is there a button on it?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0423">through the packet yeah?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="55" who="S0421">you wouldn't be able to return it if you'd taken it out of the packaging I don't think</u>
<u n="56" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know maybe I guess</u>
<u n="58" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah well if you took it out and it wasn't working</u>
<u n="59" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but like you say well it's not worked so</u>
<u n="61" who="S0421">yeah I guess so</u>
<u n="62" who="S0423"><unclear/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well sometimes they're a bit funny once it's been opened</u>
<u n="64" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0421">I suppose cos it is a device that doesn't work I suppose they won't mind <pause dur="short"/> but yeah it is in its packaging so they can't say no</u>
<u n="66" who="S0423">well yeah <pause dur="long"/> have you oh we were in er I was gonna say have you been into <anon type="place"/> since you moved here but we were in TK Maxx</u>
<u n="67" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0423">to get this weren't we in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/> yeah I plugged your computer in your camera into my computer</u>
<u n="70" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="71" who="S0421">and er I was like it wouldn't do it because there's no battery in your camera and I was like oh</u>
<u n="72" who="S0423">well I do it on mine</u>
<u n="73" who="S0421" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="74" who="S0423">without the battery</u>
<u n="75" who="S0421">really? it wouldn't show up on mine you have to turn it on</u>
<u n="76" who="S0423">is the battery not back in it? what have you done with the battery then?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0421">no the battery is there's like the charge</u>
<u n="78" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh no power?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0423">oh right well yeah normally when I plug in the computer it you go to the back of the camera I should have said and it says PC or what you're doing and you click okay on it</u>
<u n="81" who="S0421">what even when it's not on?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0423">yeah cos it's getting power from your computer</u>
<u n="83" who="S0421">cos it it just wouldn't do any it just said no battery and it just went black</u>
<u n="84" who="S0423">what on</u>
<u n="85" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="86" who="S0423" trans="overlap">on the camera? did you look on the camera screen?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah on the screen yeah it was just black</u>
<u n="88" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="89" who="S0421">maybe it's not compatible with my well anyway we have a card reader so <pause dur="short"/> that's how I got them</u>
<u n="90" who="S0423">oh did the card go in it?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0421">well I took the card out and put it in my card reader after the</u>
<u n="92" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what's a card reader?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0421">it's like a machine</u>
<u n="94" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0421">where you take the card out of your camera</u>
<u n="96" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0421">and you plug it in and it</u>
<u n="98" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="99" who="S0421">reads it so you can put it the pictures on your computer</u>
<u n="100" who="S0423">so then you've plugged that machine in the</u>
<u n="101" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0423">right</u>
<u n="103" who="S0421">cos it <trunc>co</trunc></u>
<u n="104" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos some cards will go straight into the computer won't they?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah but yours is funny so you need a card reader</u>
<u n="106" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well yeah it won't go in mine no</u>
<u n="107" who="S0421" trans="overlap">but we are er he's got like four different slots on it</u>
<u n="108" who="S0423">right</u>
<u n="109" who="S0421">like it's got SD as well like sometimes we use it for our SD ones cos sometimes if you plug it straight into the computer it doesn't work even with an SD</u>
<u n="110" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="111" who="S0421">so the card reader usually always works</u>
<u n="112" who="S0423">mm mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="113" who="S0421">have you got to get anything from the shop?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0423">no I suppose I could do with getting some food but I've got some for tonight</u>
<u n="115" who="S0421">oh right</u>
<u n="116" who="S0423">I thought I'd do that I don't know what I want so I don't think I'll start shopping for food now</u>
<u n="117" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="118" who="S0423">I don't really have anything in mind I mean I've got <pause dur="short"/> all the dry stuff I need and what have you so it's just fresh stuff I could do with topping up on</u>
<u n="119" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0423">getting some fruits and veg maybe stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> got plenty of rice and pasta and <unclear>of course</unclear> there's still quite a bit of that left from holiday <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0421">is this <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0423">yeah we're coming into <anon type="place"/> now</u>
<u n="123" who="S0421">not far is it?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's changed a bit I know you're getting close to it and it's changed a bit since having the tram put in <pause dur="long"/> might have been better off going over to the right there <pause dur="short"/> not sure of the best way into <trunc>Sains</trunc> but or TK Maxx and Sainsbury's is it to the right there? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0421">oh I dunno</u>
<u n="126" who="S0423">I can't see it oh here it is to the right here so if we maybe take a left here and then turn around and go down that way I think <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="long"/> not that familiar I don't really often come into <anon type="place"/> myself really and I <pause dur="long"/> the sky's looking a bit black side looks like</u>
<u n="127" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0423" trans="overlap">we might get a bit of heavy rain soon</u>
<u n="129" who="S0421">yeah I think it's supposed to rain today</u>
<u n="130" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0421">is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not working today then?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0423">he's off sick at the minute</u>
<u n="133" who="S0421">oh is he?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0423" trans="overlap">he's got a kidney problem which</u>
<u n="135" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="136" who="S0423" trans="overlap">is what your grandad has isn't it?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0423" trans="overlap">but it's I think this is slightly different</u>
<u n="139" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and he's got a kidney infection</u>
<u n="141" who="S0421">they're supposed to be painful aren't they anything to do with kidneys?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's</u>
<u n="143" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like kidney stones are painful aren't they?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so he's <pause dur="short"/> he's gonna be off work for the rest of the week at least why has she's just gone through a red light</u>
<u n="145" who="S0421">how did he get that?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0423">who?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0421"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0423">well he had it a few years ago and it's just one of those things isn't it?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so I'm not sure what causes it</u>
<u n="151" who="S0421" trans="overlap">you can't catch it can you?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0423">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's not contagious I wouldn't be bringing you if it was contagious I probably wouldn't be going myself</u>
<u n="153" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> I have a fear of medical problems <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0423">well I think everybody does really though don't they?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like mine's quite severe though <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's why I'm always on oh that Rook just ate a worm</u>
<u n="156" who="S0423">what?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0421">that Rook over there</u>
<u n="158" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="159" who="S0421">just ate a worm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0423">yeah?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0421">yeah that's why I'm always online like <vocal desc="laugh"/> what's wrong with me? I hope nothing's wrong with me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's the worst thing you can do is to go online</u>
<u n="163" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0423">no wonder you have a fear of it if you read the stuff that's online</u>
<u n="165" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and it's like go to the hospital and I'm like no</u>
<u n="166" who="S0423">well yeah some of the stuff says you will die immediately and and</u>
<u n="167" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0423"><unclear/> you symptoms</u>
<u n="169" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0423">ridiculous the stuff you get online <pause dur="short"/> you're a a young healthy <pause dur="short"/> girl I dunno why you're looking at that stuff</u>
<u n="171" who="S0421">oh so is that what I have to worry about when I'm old? I'm gonna be like what's wrong with me? <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'll be at the doctor every week like I hope nothing's wrong with me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0423">if you look after yourself there's no reason why you want to be worrying about when you're older either</u>
<u n="173" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0423">so it's er you take care of yourself don't you?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0421">but some things it's like yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well some things you <unclear>just get</unclear></u>
<u n="177" who="S0421" trans="overlap">there's no explanation you can just get it and I'll be like <vocal desc="misc"/> like cos then like if there's something</u>
<u n="178" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well if you have a proper illness you'll know about it</u>
<u n="179" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0423">you don't wanna go looking online for it</u>
<u n="181" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0423">I mean</u>
<u n="183" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because</u>
<u n="184" who="S0423" trans="overlap">your body'll tell you you're not well</u>
<u n="185" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos some stuff it's like oh to avoid getting this make sure you eat vegetables and I'm like okay I'll eat vegetables but there's some stuff is like you can't prevent this and I'll be like <vocal desc="misc"/> and then it's like is it what oh oh? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0423">well yeah I mean some stuff you if if you get it you get it but you know the general advice is to keep healthy is you exercise and eat healthily isn't it?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0423">so if you follow that advice then it it helps and if you still get something there's nothing you could have done about it anyway</u>
<u n="189" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="190" who="S0423">if you get something you do but <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0421"><shift new="singing"/> do do do TK Maxx <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0423">generally if you you shouldn't expect to be getting anything</u>
<u n="193" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="194" who="S0423">especially as you're so young and everything and healthy</u>
<u n="195" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0423">you just need to <pause dur="short"/> you need to look at yourself when at university eat properly and <pause dur="short"/> don't overwork and things like that</u>
<u n="197" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I need to have my meal times</u>
<u n="198" who="S0423">you know try to rest yourself when you're tired and things</u>
<u n="199" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0423">don't go out partying all the time</u>
<u n="201" who="S0421">oh because that's</u>
<u n="202" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos it's gonna tire you</u>
<u n="203" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because that's what I was gonna do more likely don't stay up all night in the library that's twenty-four hour <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
