<text id="SHHG">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:47:08</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-10-03</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0439 S0444</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Greens Café - Cambourne</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>food, friends, catch-up, ex-boyfriends, family, work, health, future plans</topics>
		<activity>Catch-up with friend from Oxford</activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, announcing, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0439">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern - Non-accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0444">
				<exactage>25</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace></birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Oxford, UK</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 10 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Pearson marketing executive</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0439">I do love this place it's so nice it's just like it's a nice cheap little café really it's good</u>
<u n="2" who="S0444">nothing wrong with that</u>
<u n="3" who="S0439" trans="overlap">what is that?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0444">er</u>
<u n="5" who="S0439">oh that's that I know</u>
<u n="6" who="S0444">my drugs</u>
<u n="7" who="S0439">oh your drugs? you pharmaceutical company</u>
<u n="8" who="S0444">very <unclear/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0439">dunno why I want lemonade I just really want lemonade</u>
<u n="10" who="S0444">go for it</u>
<u n="11" who="S0439">okay so tell me all about you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> how are you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doing?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0444">mm <pause dur="short"/> good it was really good to go away and to have some time and some space that wasn't in <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0444" trans="overlap">that was nice cos we we'd only really been seen each other maybe and we did manage to <unclear/> it might have been once a week but it was only like one day</u>
<u n="15" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0444">so there's that kind of you know but yeah no everything's good things are good like his family are now giving me books to read</u>
<u n="17" who="S0439">oh wow</u>
<u n="18" who="S0444" trans="overlap">which is always good</u>
<u n="19" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0444" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="21" who="S0439">get er get in there with the family</u>
<u n="22" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> so they're all just lovely so</u>
<u n="23" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0444">yeah no like we're just mooching along not really like making any big decisions like moving in with each other or anything like that things like that but</u>
<u n="25" who="S0439">oh food</u>
<u n="26" who="S0444">erm</u>
<u n="27" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/>?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0439">thank you</u>
<u n="29" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">there you are enjoy</u>
<u n="30" who="S0444">thanks</u>
<u n="31" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0444">awesome I'm intrigued by the <trunc>Giuse</trunc>Giuseppe dressing that they have</u>
<u n="33" who="S0439">oh do you want some?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0444">erm no I think this is the Giuseppe dressing</u>
<u n="35" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh oh nice so have you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm done the deed?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0444">yes all good</u>
<u n="37" who="S0439">all good</u>
<u n="38" who="S0444">yeah what about you?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0439"><trunc>wha</trunc> me? me and my love life?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0439">no boys in my love life at the moment erm <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> so obviously I was seeing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0439">and then I ended that</u>
<u n="44" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0439">erm I've er yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> broke up with his girlfriend</u>
<u n="46" who="S0444">oh did he now?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0444">how did you hear?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0439">he told me</u>
<u n="50" who="S0444">why should you be bothered?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0439"><trunc>don</trunc> yeah don't ask erm he moved in with her</u>
<u n="52" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0439">in July</u>
<u n="54" who="S0444">oh god</u>
<u n="55" who="S0439">and then broke up with her two weeks ago</u>
<u n="56" who="S0444">oh dear</u>
<u n="57" who="S0439">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0444">did he do the breaking up?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0439">he did he dumped her he told her he didn't love her anymore and didn't wanna be with her</u>
<u n="60" who="S0444">wow</u>
<u n="61" who="S0439">I know despite the fact that she was like come from Australia to be with him and and they'd just moved in together and <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> bit messy</u>
<u n="62" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0439">erm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0444">so what was the message? hey I've broken up with my girlfriend just thought you should know?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0439">mm <pause dur="long"/> well no not well kind of <pause dur="short"/> like me and him like obviously we talk like we're friends and then</u>
<u n="66" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="67" who="S0439">like before my birthday the week before my birthday we had a conversation cos I went out and got absolutely hammered by accident ended up on my own on the floor outside HSBC throwing my guts out</u>
<u n="68" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> how come?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I don't even know</u>
<u n="70" who="S0444" trans="overlap">what happened?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0439">I dunno I don't know</u>
<u n="72" who="S0444">were you just out and it was <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah I was fine and then suddenly it just hit me and I don't actually know how I even got home I don't know very much really erm but I called everybody like I was calling my <trunc>par</trunc> like I called everybody on my phone and I called him by accident and he must have picked up so I'm like he like and then the next day <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sent me a message like oh he was really worried about you like and I was like shit sorry I I don't remember I I called everybody I my phone it's ridiculous I had messages from everybody being like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> where are you? are you in hospital? like please get <trunc>i</trunc> please contact us like it was horrendous and he's like</u>
<u n="74" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I didn't get anything</u>
<u n="75" who="S0439">oh sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0444">I feel left out but</u>
<u n="77" who="S0439">erm and he was like well it's fine but my girlfriend didn't think it was very appropriate and I was like no I completely understand that's perfectly fine</u>
<u n="78" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0439">like having your ex girlfriend call you at like two in the morning hung drunk is not I I completely get that and he was like and it's <trunc>rea</trunc> and I was like but no offence don't tell me that my me calling you was inappropriate compared to some of the messages</u>
<u n="80" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0439">you've been sending me</u>
<u n="82" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0439">thank you very much and he was like yeah okay I get that erm <pause dur="short"/> and then <pause dur="short"/> and he said well she just doesn't really want us to talk very much anymore and I was like okay that's fine you know <pause dur="short"/> she's <trunc>compl</trunc> she's come over from Australia to be with you I don't wanna ruin that you know if she's if she doesn't like me talking to you let's just you know stop talking then so that carried on and then a week later on my birthday he sent me a message at half past ten at night er you know I'd just got back from Barcelona I was really happy got a message from him saying erm happy birthday I hope you had the most amazing day just wanted to message you even though we're not supposed to be talking but I just want you to know that I still really care and I was like oh great thanks just ruined my <trunc>bir</trunc> and then the cheek of it the end of it was like please don't reply to this message</u>
<u n="84" who="S0444">what?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0444">right</u>
<u n="87" who="S0439">so</u>
<u n="88" who="S0444"><unclear/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah so I didn't reply</u>
<u n="90" who="S0444">yeah of course</u>
<u n="91" who="S0439">I was like</u>
<u n="92" who="S0444" trans="overlap">of course you aren't</u>
<u n="93" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no like first I'm not gonna reply not cos you told me not to reply but I'm just not gonna reply and erm <pause dur="short"/> and then I went up to erm Newcastle</u>
<u n="94" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0439">for the run <pause dur="short"/> and he sent me messages being like I'm so proud of you you know this is amazing you've done something incredible you know like words can't describe how much I care for you and how important you are to me and I was like</u>
<u n="96" who="S0444" trans="overlap">shut up</u>
<u n="97" who="S0439">yeah I was like dude no offence but you shouldn't be saying but you have a girlfriend and l and he was like I've made so many mistakes in my life I'm like no offence if you think your girlfriend is a mistake break up with her like it's not fair on her if you're acting like she's a mistake and he was like you will always be my Eskimo I'm like I'm not your Eskimo like we haven't been together for two years</u>
<u n="98" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0439">what are you on about boy? he was just like oh okay and then a few days later he <trunc>mess</trunc> he I heard like nothing from him and then I just got a message from him on erm Hangout on Google Hangout saying erm yeah I can't text you cos I <trunc>sai</trunc> I broke up with my girlfriend and she keeps trying to contact me and I was like okay what do you want me to say to that? he says <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> it's just been a bit ridiculous with him</u>
<u n="100" who="S0444">you're the one that got away obviously</u>
<u n="101" who="S0439">I think so yeah and like he wants to meet up and <trunc>stu</trunc> not like</u>
<u n="102" who="S0444">no like</u>
<u n="103" who="S0439" trans="overlap">not like in like a</u>
<u n="104" who="S0444" trans="overlap">chat like</u>
<u n="105" who="S0439" trans="overlap">flirty way</u>
<u n="106" who="S0444" trans="overlap">but yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0439" trans="overlap">but he needs to chat to meet up</u>
<u n="108" who="S0444">but</u>
<u n="109" who="S0439">and he wants to get together and <pause dur="short"/> it's just manic it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="110" who="S0444">what's he doing at the moment?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0439">mm <pause dur="long"/> he's doing an Open University course so he can go back to uni and be a physiotherapist</u>
<u n="112" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0439">erm <pause dur="short"/> while working for the Daily erm not the Daily Mail the Royal Mail</u>
<u n="114" who="S0444">okay that's cool</u>
<u n="115" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but yeah so it's the same old story with him</u>
<u n="116" who="S0444">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh well</u>
<u n="117" who="S0439">I know how long did this been going on for? like two years now? <pause dur="short"/> like on November the second</u>
<u n="118" who="S0444" trans="overlap">the second yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0439">yeah on November the second I will be single for two years <pause dur="short"/> like and he's still round every corner <pause dur="long"/> so</u>
<u n="120" who="S0444">it's like I've always said you know if you are happy with the level of it and you can handle it it's fine but when it gets to the time when it's just like dude shut up right</u>
<u n="121" who="S0439">yeah no</u>
<u n="122" who="S0444">I mean would any part of you ever wanna get back with him?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0439">I think maybe in a few years</u>
<u n="124" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0439">maybe in the future but not now I like I I still really care about him</u>
<u n="126" who="S0444">well no of course like</u>
<u n="127" who="S0439">and I he means he means a lot to me</u>
<u n="128" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I'm not saying that it's just that</u>
<u n="129" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="130" who="S0444" trans="overlap">kind of thing that <pause dur="short"/> I'm only kind of projecting personal experience with the boy</u>
<u n="131" who="S0439">oh yeah no no</u>
<u n="132" who="S0444" trans="overlap">when it was like you know <trunc>i</trunc>it's that kind of thing you keep talking to them and then you meet up with them and then it's like oh it's quite nice to hang out with them and that's how it often is</u>
<u n="133" who="S0439">mm no yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0444">I know that you're much stronger than that but I'm just saying I'm just like mm okay</u>
<u n="135" who="S0439">oh no no no</u>
<u n="136" who="S0444" trans="overlap">unless you decide not to</u>
<u n="137" who="S0439">yeah like <pause dur="short"/> I think we're more than just friends</u>
<u n="138" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="139" who="S0439">but I don't wanna be with him and I know that I don't wanna be with him</u>
<u n="140" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and you're always gonna be more than just friends because of what you were like</u>
<u n="141" who="S0439">yeah but I know that in this moment in time in my life I don't wanna be with him <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but I haven't really met anybody that I wanna be with at the moment so</u>
<u n="142" who="S0444">could be but not for me yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0439">oh Justin Bieber so he could be the love of my life</u>
<u n="144" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/> or <unclear>Alejandro</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> from Boyce Avenue</u>
<u n="145" who="S0439">oh yes Boyce Avenue yes we should get tickets probably the London one is easier for you is it? or <pause dur="long"/> they're so good like Boyce Avenue they're just they're just so relaxing to listen to</u>
<u n="146" who="S0444">they are <pause dur="short"/> my mum was really annoying me because we've always wanted to go to Salzburg you know blah blah blah blah blah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0439">to where?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0444"><trunc>Sal</trunc>Salzburg</u>
<u n="149" who="S0439">oh yeah Salzburg yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0444">and erm she was you know so I said look I'm gonna book something for the BA sale but it's in September but we're really gonna</u>
<u n="151" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0444">like that I kept telling you about erm <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="long"/> she was like <pause dur="long"/> she was like no no no I can't afford to go I can't afford to go and I was like that's not a good enough reason to not we could go like</u>
<u n="153" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0444">she could afford it she just feels bad to go</u>
<u n="155" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0444">so like screw it it's your fiftieth birthday this year</u>
<u n="157" who="S0439">so are you taking her or?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I'm taking her</u>
<u n="159" who="S0439">ah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0444" trans="overlap">so I've paid for her <trunc>t</trunc> well I'm paying for her to go but we're going the week before the well the week that they're kind of touring but I'm back on the sixteenth? so that's how I was like seventeenth eighteenth nineteenth twentieth I can do</u>
<u n="161" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="162" who="S0444">I don't think the thing is that if it was <pause dur="short"/> was it Nottingham or some ridiculous?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0439" trans="overlap">they had a Nottingham tour yeah or Nottingham Space</u>
<u n="164" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I don't think like I'd get to like erm so so I was like well if I come up and see you and I was like how do I get to mine from here?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0444">then that would be fair enough cos it would turn out well one of them was on a Friday I think and that was the Nottingham one and one of them was on a Sunday and I was like is it gonna be tricky for both of us</u>
<u n="167" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0444">to get back on a Sunday night? like do you know that kind of way? I was a bit like if it starts at half seven it won't finish until nine ten</u>
<u n="169" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0444">it's alright on the <anon type="place"/> tube but you're still pushing it to get back the last one and I have no idea</u>
<u n="171" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0444">what it's like to <anon type="place"/> so I was just like mm that was my only thing where I was like that's why I was like</u>
<u n="173" who="S0439" trans="overlap">so we could do the Nottingham the Nottingham is fine for me</u>
<u n="174" who="S0444" trans="overlap">that's why I was like well in Cardiff we could always do like a mini <trunc>weeke</trunc> like a</u>
<u n="175" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mini little trip like out there like cos Cardiff I really like Cardiff as a place so I was like we could always just like go</u>
<u n="177" who="S0439">I haven't been to Cardiff</u>
<u n="178" who="S0444" trans="overlap">go on a Saturday and then like</u>
<u n="179" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0444">hang out there for the day go to the gig</u>
<u n="181" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0444" trans="overlap">have a few drinks and then mooch around on the Sunday like</u>
<u n="183" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0444">if you want and I don't know what it's like getting there from <anon type="place"/> might be a bit of a pain but</u>
<u n="185" who="S0439"><anon type="place"/> to Cardiff is hard but</u>
<u n="186" who="S0444">come to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0439">yeah come to <anon type="place"/> first</u>
<u n="188" who="S0444">if you came to <anon type="place"/> on that Friday <pause dur="short"/> right if you chill in <anon type="place"/> on the Friday</u>
<u n="189" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0444">go to Cardiff on the Saturday</u>
<u n="191" who="S0439">so when is that next March?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0444">yeah so it's</u>
<u n="193" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0444" trans="overlap">not for a while</u>
<u n="195" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0444">so we we have time so I was just like are you gonna be in the country by that point or is it June? I can't remember</u>
<u n="197" who="S0439">I am gonna be in the country in March I think if I go to Oz it'll be in June</u>
<u n="198" who="S0444">cool</u>
<u n="199" who="S0439">the decision is either to go to Oz for a year</u>
<u n="200" who="S0444">right</u>
<u n="201" who="S0439">or to go for <trunc>O</trunc> to Oz for three months and then go to university</u>
<u n="202" who="S0444">to do psychology?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0439">exactly to do psychology</u>
<u n="204" who="S0444">how long will it take full time a year?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0439">a year to do the psychology conversion and then a year to do the next masters <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0444">I like the idea of three months just not because it means that you're here for longer but it's just that kind of thing where it gives you enough of a break from work</u>
<u n="207" who="S0439">exactly it means I can</u>
<u n="208" who="S0444">to then start</u>
<u n="209" who="S0439" trans="overlap">get yeah start again exactly</u>
<u n="210" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and then if you wanted to go back to Australia afterwards you'd have a trade in which to go back</u>
<u n="211" who="S0439" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="212" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and get work visa</u>
<u n="213" who="S0439">that's what I think <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0444">I'm really excited you're definitely gonna go though like</u>
<u n="215" who="S0439">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's really exciting</u>
<u n="217" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I'm gonna <unclear/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I have like June as like an end date in my head</u>
<u n="218" who="S0444">yeah well so I'll move to <anon type="place"/> and you'll have <trunc>g</trunc>gone for like <unclear/> where where are you thinking about for the uni from like your research last year that you did?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0439">erm <anon type="place"/> probably still <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0444">maybe it will be your student discount</u>
<u n="221" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0444">instead of being me</u>
<u n="223" who="S0439">it'll go into <anon type="place"/> I think <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="place"/> is more expensive</u>
<u n="224" who="S0444">oh is it? by a lot is it?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0439">no not in the grand scheme of things it's erm <pause dur="short"/> it's about a grand more expensive</u>
<u n="226" who="S0444">right</u>
<u n="227" who="S0439">so not in the end in the grand scheme of things it's not a lot more but</u>
<u n="228" who="S0444" trans="overlap">but it</u>
<u n="229" who="S0439">still a grand yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0444">would you wanna move there and be?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0439">no I think if I went to <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> I'd commute on the days I had to</u>
<u n="232" who="S0444">this is where my geography doesn't come into er</u>
<u n="233" who="S0439">so where my parents live it's about by train it's about like an hour and a hour from <anon type="place"/> and it's about an hour from <anon type="place"/> driving</u>
<u n="234" who="S0444" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="235" who="S0439">so it's not actually that bad like I could commute it especially if I was only on campus two days a week</u>
<u n="236" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0439">and the only issue is now my mother's been made redundant <pause dur="short"/> yeah from the school</u>
<u n="238" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> just like</u>
<u n="239" who="S0439">erm the school she worked at got overtaken by an academy and so therefore money is important and therefore they have literally made I think about twenty people redundant mostly admin staff erm er so I don't know where they're what they're gonna be doing anymore like mum like dad still he <trunc>h</trunc>has he has his</u>
<u n="240" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0439">job and he his job and his salary is good enough to support them</u>
<u n="242" who="S0444">okay <unclear/> of them yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0439">but mum can't just sit at home all day <trunc>sh</trunc> like dad'll go crazy so</u>
<u n="244" who="S0444" trans="overlap">that's the thing like how is your mum feeling like?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0439">erm she I think she's actually okay with it I mean she's not</u>
<u n="246" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0439" trans="overlap">doing too badly</u>
<u n="248" who="S0444">I suppose if it's like I know it sounds awful but if it's a group of people if it's</u>
<u n="249" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="250" who="S0444" trans="overlap">gonna be made redundant it doesn't make it any easier but it does make you feel like it wasn't just you know</u>
<u n="251" who="S0439">you yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0444">cos I think the weird thing you know at <anon type="place"/> where it was like individual people</u>
<u n="253" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0444"><unclear/> but</u>
<u n="255" who="S0439">how is everything with <anon type="place"/> though?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0439">so like <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0444">I think it's better than it was but from my department but there's been a restructure where editor and <unclear/> aren't editors and <unclear/> anymore they are content and learning specialists so they have the same job title yeah it's all a bit weird I don't I don't know much about it cos it only just got announced but basically they're kind of aligning everything</u>
<u n="259" who="S0439">god</u>
<u n="260" who="S0444"><unclear>but we're just</unclear> gonna be managing everyone everyone and ETLs are gonna become scrum masters matters but we're not quite sure what they're doing</u>
<u n="261" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah I saw that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has become a scrum master on Linkedin</u>
<u n="262" who="S0444">so yeah so <pause dur="short"/> I don't know much about it cos obviously <pause dur="short"/> there's an effect at primary or secondary I felt really sorry <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos obviously she'd worked so hard to be an editor and now <unclear/> a load of specialists and she's like where what does that what does that even mean? I don't know</u>
<u n="263" who="S0439">so maybe she's still doing the same editorial role basically?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh yeah they just don't call it that</u>
<u n="265" who="S0439" trans="overlap">they just call it something different yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0444">exactly so it's kind of like well it's like product management which has some weight in other industries <pause dur="short"/> content and learning specialist?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0444" trans="overlap">that <unclear/> in any industry apparently they spent a year and half trying to figure out that <pause dur="short"/> but yeah so I think everybody <pause dur="long"/> everybody in those camps are kind of like you know they've just taken that on board erm I think some of the reactions have been positive I know that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0444"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="271" who="S0439">who? oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sorry yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0444">cos it's just been real they've just got all the pressure on them at the moment over this <unclear/> erm and there's a lot of tension between editors and <unclear/> it's been like well some of you aren't pulling your weight cos you're not doing more than the nine to five kind of thing it's like <unclear/> er</u>
<u n="273" who="S0439">god</u>
<u n="274" who="S0444" trans="overlap">you know yeah but erm I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was in a really difficult position cos they were like arguing about the schedules and <unclear/> leeway but we couldn't have leeway and so yeah but I helped make the <trunc>sched</trunc> she didn't say it but she was like I helped make those schedules I know why they're that way from a positive perspective I can see where the publishers are coming from and it's like</u>
<u n="275" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0444">but erm like marketing is better now that the restructure has actually been announced it's a bit</u>
<u n="277" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well the thing is they started restructuring when I was there</u>
<u n="278" who="S0444" trans="overlap">when we were <unclear/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0439" trans="overlap">like</u>
<u n="280" who="S0444">and er it was basically it was on my birthday my first year right? so we'd not even been there a year it was my birthday it was July that they first announced the restructure <pause dur="short"/> and it's only just been <unclear/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah it feels like they've been restructuring for years</u>
<u n="282" who="S0444">yeah and I mean yeah okay transformation takes time but I think there is I think just it's better in marketing than it was but it's quite dependent they've got quite a lot of more senior roles going at the moment but like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> etcetera are all gonna go <unclear>first</unclear> so it depends whether they hire internal or externally <unclear>cos</unclear> that's gonna be like <unclear/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0439" trans="overlap">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are both gonna go for the same job? or?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0444">oh yeah everyone's going for the same job <unclear/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0439">shit that's a bit dangerous isn't it?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0444" trans="overlap">but they've been doing that all the time like</u>
<u n="287" who="S0439">oh okay</u>
<u n="288" who="S0444">so <pause dur="short"/> so I think it's fine but I think there will be some backlash if internal people don't get it like</u>
<u n="289" who="S0439">yeah can imagine if like especially like people like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who's been in the company for a long time if he didn't get the job that'd be really bad</u>
<u n="290" who="S0444">yeah well obviously I mean like everybody's kind of like yeah same old same old <unclear/> <unclear>like and</unclear> it's new initiative after new initiative but <unclear>if it's</unclear> better than it was in terms of people <unclear>being</unclear> like fight over</u>
<u n="291" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0444"><unclear/> you know that was just a bit sorry for me it's just I feel a lot better doing the job that I'm doing <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0444">I loved the job that I was doing before with science in terms of the people that I was working with</u>
<u n="295" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0444">that was awesome the kind of work that we were being asked to do was just like <unclear>it's not</unclear></u>
<u n="297" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="298" who="S0444"><unclear>that's just</unclear> not good erm and with history I know more about it which is good and I have a bit more control over what I'm doing and you know and they seem to really like the stuff that I'm doing so far like within the first few weeks for the first week I'd been given like a brochure and it was like oh yeah it it it just needs updating so <pause dur="short"/> I've already er got all the copy together you just need to put it <unclear>into the</unclear> <unclear/> this was from somebody who was kind of just looking after me for a little while I looked at it and went no that's shite that is a load of shite rewrote it within the first <unclear>couple of days</unclear> like <vocal desc="laugh"/> the head of like <unclear/> project management going to the science team going gosh I know you told me that she was good but I didn't know she was quite this good</u>
<u n="299" who="S0439">ah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0444">you know <unclear>so sad</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/> and the science team was just like we hate this come back please we miss you</u>
<u n="301" who="S0439" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0444">like</u>
<u n="303" who="S0439" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0444">but you know I think that's the thing if I'd had a job where I was working with people I think I'd be alright like</u>
<u n="305" who="S0439" trans="overlap">so are you not working with people? are you just?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0444">yeah I'm working with people but it's more like I know that <pause dur="short"/> that's er jobs that involve that or good ones</u>
<u n="307" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="308" who="S0444"><unclear/> <unclear>you know</unclear> I don't mind doing the odd <unclear>Excel</unclear> task and whatever but you know it's engaging with people that</u>
<u n="309" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I really like but it's kind of like well yeah what jobs let you do? cos it is that standard thing where they're not gonna like oh <pause dur="long"/> like I've probably said to you before they're kind of like well you've got a choice to make you either you know you're bright you either go for a job that uses your talents but it will make you poorly or you go for a less intellectually demanding job which won't be as intellectually stimulating but it means that you can be healthier</u>
<u n="311" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0444">and it's I'm still kind of weighing up but it's difficult cos it's like if I had I dunno if my family were closer or if I was living with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or if I were living with a really close friend that like you know saw er day in day out and had to deal with it and other people were really impacted by it</u>
<u n="313" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0444">as in any of the choices that I made I would choose to do a less demanding job</u>
<u n="315" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0444" trans="overlap">because I don't want there to be an effect you know I don't want to be impacted but at the moment when it's just not just me but when it's pretty much confined to me and</u>
<u n="317" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0444">my lovely friend that <unclear>happens to</unclear> support me but it's pretty much me who's impacted then I'm always gonna be like oh I'll do the intellectual job cos that's what I wanna do</u>
<u n="319" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and it's like I'm not ready to make those kind of choices yet</u>
<u n="321" who="S0439">no no</u>
<u n="322" who="S0444">so I just need to like see what I can do and see what's possible not on full hours yet at all I'm on seven</u>
<u n="323" who="S0439" trans="overlap">what hours are you doing?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0444">seven</u>
<u n="325" who="S0439">seven <trunc>hou</trunc></u>
<u n="326" who="S0444" trans="overlap">so I'm nearly there</u>
<u n="327" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh so you're nearly back up</u>
<u n="328" who="S0444">but I am finding it quite hard now like before I went to <anon type="place"/> I was like I need I need to go and take a break like <unclear/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0444">it's all about getting the balance isn't it?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0439">oh yeah definitely</u>
<u n="332" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> balance</u>
<u n="333" who="S0439">you need a work life balance</u>
<u n="334" who="S0444">and it's not even work anymore it's just like it's like oh I'm tired <unclear/> but <pause dur="short"/> it's just like it sounds ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> haven't been allowed to go to the gym since June</u>
<u n="335" who="S0439">you haven't been able to go to the gym? god</u>
<u n="336" who="S0444">I've not been allowed to go cos <unclear/> well if you're doing exercise like that's a massive thing out of your day</u>
<u n="337" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <trunc>y</trunc> cos they're counter intuitive</u>
<u n="338" who="S0444" trans="overlap">on top of doing work yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0444">I'm just like I just like but I ended up doing so much walking in Dublin like</u>
<u n="341" who="S0439">yeah so things did work out for you</u>
<u n="342" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's like it's like Berlin and like and it's like Berlin and it's kind of like we just ended up walking</u>
<u n="343" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0444" trans="overlap">we didn't deliberately go out to do masses of walking we just did</u>
<u n="345" who="S0439" trans="overlap">same with Barcelona we did just <trunc>s</trunc> too much walking</u>
<u n="346" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0439" trans="overlap">we did so much walking in Barcelona</u>
<u n="348" who="S0444" trans="overlap">did you? I was gonna ask about the big Barcelona episode but I was like <pause dur="short"/> so photos do you have them at home so we can go through them?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0444">or is it just the ones that you have on Facebook? cos</u>
<u n="351" who="S0439">it's <trunc>proba</trunc> most of them are just the ones I have on Facebook actually</u>
<u n="352" who="S0444" trans="overlap">they were lovely</u>
<u n="353" who="S0439">it was you've yeah you went to Barcelona didn't you?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0444" trans="overlap">awesome it's such a cool place</u>
<u n="355" who="S0439">very beautiful place <pause dur="short"/> did like it a lot <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah sorry carry on with what you were saying</u>
<u n="356" who="S0444">no <unclear/> that much but erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah so like going to the gym I'm like right I'm I just I just you know it's that kind of it's like you know <unclear/> to make someone feel better and it's all about that payoff and it's like</u>
<u n="357" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah you get endorphins</u>
<u n="358" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's like we were saying too it's like I was saying to you like earlier but it was that the mind set <unclear/> a bit weird but it's like a lot of the stuff that they've been <unclear/> at the hospital is kind of like <pause dur="short"/> stuff that saps you of energy but also gives you energy at the same time? so it's like seeing a friend</u>
<u n="359" who="S0439">yeah seeing friends saps your</u>
<u n="360" who="S0444" trans="overlap">can drain energy</u>
<u n="361" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0444">but seeing them being normal and being like happy and having a great time</u>
<u n="363" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0444">it's giving you an energy boost</u>
<u n="365" who="S0439">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0444" trans="overlap">so it's that kind of and it's that kind of thing where I was like you know like you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> okay like how are you feeling like you know I don't know you what are you thinking I'm like no I I can do this</u>
<u n="367" who="S0439">good yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0444">I can do this I just need to <vocal desc="laugh"/> it might just be er a little bit more chilled with no going out we'll take like</u>
<u n="369" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh it's fine</u>
<u n="370" who="S0444">I was just like</u>
<u n="371" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I'm old I don't go out very much</u>
<u n="372" who="S0444" trans="overlap">dude like I'll just chill I'll just chill and listen to cheesy music and do what we do <unclear/> though</u>
<u n="373" who="S0439" trans="overlap">exactly I don't do</u>
<u n="374" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and it was like</u>
<u n="375" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I don't go out very much <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0444">and it's a bit like just whatever you do please don't make me go into a situation where I have to meet all your lovely friends cos I'm like if I'm tired</u>
<u n="377" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh my god no</u>
<u n="378" who="S0444" trans="overlap">if I'm tired by then I was like I've got to meet some of them <vocal desc="laugh"/> but but <unclear/></u>
<u n="379" who="S0439" trans="overlap">maybe <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> tomorrow but</u>
<u n="380" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s in Australia anyway so and</u>
<u n="382" who="S0444" trans="overlap">is she? has she gone back for a bit?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0439">well she's gone back for a wedding <pause dur="short"/> and it was really weird oh it was so good she left last weekend no she didn't she left last Tuesday</u>
<u n="384" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0439">but it was her it's her birthday this Wednesday</u>
<u n="386" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0439">so on the Friday night I arranged a meal for her at <anon type="place"/> er <anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0444" trans="overlap">lovely yeah it's really nice there</u>
<u n="389" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and they have like a pre seven o'clock eleven</u>
<u n="390" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0439" trans="overlap">ninety meal so</u>
<u n="392" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0439">yeah so she was like erm it was a surprise for her and</u>
<u n="394" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="395" who="S0439" trans="overlap">like like the whole week she would be like <pause dur="short"/> she was like oh yeah so we're having a movie night on Friday? cos I said let's have a movie night and she was <trunc>li</trunc> she was like yeah yeah and I'll invite <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm like yeah yeah that's fine I'd already told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that we're going for dinner so she was like messaging them being like erm oh yeah so you know are you coming round on Friday? I'm looking forward to seeing you</u>
<u n="396" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh bless her</u>
<u n="397" who="S0439" trans="overlap">bring loads of snacks like</u>
<u n="398" who="S0444" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0439" trans="overlap">sending loads of messages</u>
<u n="400" who="S0444" trans="overlap">what a sweetie</u>
<u n="401" who="S0439">and then she was like but then she sent me a message like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you can come round earlier and then we can have dinner and we'll catch up and then not that we need to catch up but</u>
<u n="402" who="S0444" trans="overlap">but generally yeah just come round and</u>
<u n="403" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah and then we'll go then they can come round for snacks it's like yeah yeah that sounds really good really good and erm she was like well I've got to go for a run I was like okay then I'll come down at about quarter to six and let you have a shower I was like</u>
<u n="404" who="S0444">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0439" trans="overlap">please have a shower</u>
<u n="406" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0439">so I</u>
<u n="408" who="S0444" trans="overlap">good</u>
<u n="409" who="S0439">yeah so I turned up at erm twenty to six and she was like there she opened the door and she goes hi I'm like you're in your gym clothes aren't you? she was like yeah sorry I haven't showered yet I smell I'm like no no no I'm more worried that you have twenty minutes to get ready and she's like what? I was like we're going out <vocal desc="laugh"/> and she was like oh shit</u>
<u n="410" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0439">so I drove her into town and she's like where are we going? why are we going into a carpark? I was like</u>
<u n="412" who="S0444">ah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0439">mm and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> turned up and she goes oh you sneaky bitch</u>
<u n="414" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0439">and then and then I <trunc>st</trunc>stayed round on the Friday night</u>
<u n="416" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0439">and she was like now you know there's no surprises are there? there's no more surprises? I like no don't worry that's it and then we woke up on Saturday morning and went into her bedroom at nine o'clock and I was like you have an hour to get ready before we go to the train station and she was like oh my god what have you done? so we took her to London to see The Book of Mormon</u>
<u n="418" who="S0444">ah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and she didn't know and she was like we're going to London why are we going to London what's happening? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0444">ah bless</u>
<u n="421" who="S0439">and the whole thing was a complete surprise then after that</u>
<u n="422" who="S0444" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I was like that is it there's no more surprises <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="424" who="S0444">she must have loved it</u>
<u n="425" who="S0439">she did she really liked it like I I've wanted to see The Book of Mormon for ages</u>
<u n="426" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0439"><trunc>lo</trunc> it's hilarious</u>
<u n="428" who="S0444" trans="overlap">is it good?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0439">so politically incorrect if you have like a high moral sense of humour you will not like it</u>
<u n="430" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0439">if you're <trunc>gr</trunc> disgusting like I am it was hilarious <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="432" who="S0444">I was looking at it cos they had like er a load of like last minute dot com like theatre deals</u>
<u n="433" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0444" trans="overlap">like they had a whole like fortnight of it</u>
<u n="435" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0444">so I ended up getting really cheap tickets for The Commitments</u>
<u n="437" who="S0439">oh cool</u>
<u n="438" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and for Riverdance <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="439" who="S0439">oh you and your dancing</u>
<u n="440" who="S0444">I'm such a geek</u>
<u n="441" who="S0439" trans="overlap">Riverdance no you're</u>
<u n="442" who="S0444" trans="overlap">such a geek</u>
<u n="443" who="S0439" trans="overlap">a geek</u>
<u n="444" who="S0444">I went with I went with other people this time not just myself</u>
<u n="445" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="446" who="S0444">so you know it was okay but erm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0439" trans="overlap">who did you go with?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0444">I went with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="449" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0444" trans="overlap">London <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then one of her friends from work was like please can I come along?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0444">and I was like yeah sure erm so yeah though it was it was it was really good fun but <unclear/> was part of that</u>
<u n="453" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0444">but it was felt like I had to</u>
<u n="455" who="S0439" trans="overlap">they were so expensive though</u>
<u n="456" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah it was just still the kind of thing where it's like it's still a bit too expensive</u>
<u n="457" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it was so expensive like we got to be fair our our seats were okay they were near the they were very much near the back</u>
<u n="458" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0439">but they were still fifty-nine pounds <pause dur="short"/> and like</u>
<u n="460" who="S0444">how many of you went?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0439">three and me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> bought <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s ticket for her so we</u>
<u n="462" who="S0444" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0439">paid ninety each but</u>
<u n="464" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0439">we wanted to see it and like</u>
<u n="466" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and there's no point not going erm</u>
<u n="468" who="S0444">oh no</u>
<u n="469" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would never have been able to afford it she</u>
<u n="470" who="S0444">no</u>
<u n="471" who="S0439" trans="overlap">she's a social worker she doesn't earn enough erm</u>
<u n="472" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0439">so we just took her and it was just a lovely day out and the weather was</u>
<u n="474" who="S0444" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0439">lovely and it was just <pause dur="short"/> really good</u>
<u n="476" who="S0444">so how long did she come back for the wedding?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0439">just for three weeks</u>
<u n="478" who="S0444">oh okay</u>
<u n="479" who="S0439">she's coming back from the fifteenth</u>
<u n="480" who="S0444">ah</u>
<u n="481" who="S0439">and then we have erm inverted commas a surprise birthday party for her <vocal desc="laugh"/> well she was like I really want a house party will you organise me a house party? it's like okay she goes well I know it's supposed to be a surprise and you can have everybody jump out and shout surprise but please organise me a house party I was like</u>
<u n="482" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="483" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="484" who="S0444" trans="overlap">does she know what date it's gonna be on?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> she knows pretty much exactly when it is</u>
<u n="486" who="S0444" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="487" who="S0439">so I messaged <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this week and I was like erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants a house party and you have to organise it but I'll help you if you want and he's like oh good god okay thank you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like</u>
<u n="490" who="S0444" trans="overlap">was that erm her housemate or</u>
<u n="491" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s her housemate <pause dur="short"/> the Australian</u>
<u n="492" who="S0444">oh <trunc>righ</trunc> was <unclear>she</unclear> the one that went to Barcelona with her?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0439">yeah he went to Barcelona</u>
<u n="494" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0439">with us yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0444" trans="overlap">of course and yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0444">it makes more sense now all fitting together</u>
<u n="499" who="S0439">he went to Barcelona <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah so she's back in a few weeks</u>
<u n="500" who="S0444">ah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0439">I dunno she hates Australia like she doesn't wanna be there</u>
<u n="502" who="S0444">really?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0444">why?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0439">she just hates it she hates the heat she hates the people she just hates it she's like I wanna be back in England I'm like I'll swap with you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="506" who="S0444">yeah trade?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0439">trade yeah <pause dur="short"/> dunno so oh what else is <trunc>go</trunc> there was so much going on what else is happening? so <pause dur="short"/> so well yeah went to Barcelona <pause dur="short"/> that was really really good it was so hot it was thirty-five degrees it was so hot erm did the La Sagrada Familia all of that</u>
<u n="508" who="S0444" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="509" who="S0439">went to the magic fountain show in the evening</u>
<u n="510" who="S0444" trans="overlap">lovely it's amazing</u>
<u n="511" who="S0439">it's so beautiful and we ran all the way up to the top to the museum</u>
<u n="512" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0439" trans="overlap">at the top and that was so pretty <pause dur="short"/> er <unclear/> was okay it was nice</u>
<u n="514" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah it's nice</u>
<u n="515" who="S0439">it was really cheap it was just an Airbnb thing and then we went to Paris for the weekend</u>
<u n="516" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah cool</u>
<u n="517" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="518" who="S0444">that looks awesome</u>
<u n="519" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="520" who="S0444" trans="overlap">did you stay there? oh oh I remember the fallout you were mentioning</u>
<u n="521" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0444" trans="overlap">that was the fallout but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> being like you were more friends <unclear/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="524" who="S0444">you're not hanging out with yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0439">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> er <unclear/> on a bit but we sorted that out I spoke to her and</u>
<u n="526" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0439">I was like you can't behave like that <pause dur="short"/> which she was fine with</u>
<u n="528" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0439">so</u>
<u n="530" who="S0444">I think they're like they're alright now aren't they?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0439" trans="overlap">they're okay now they're not and then</u>
<u n="532" who="S0444" trans="overlap">what they were but</u>
<u n="533" who="S0439" trans="overlap">they're not the same as they were I don't think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't make as much effort with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> anymore</u>
<u n="534" who="S0444">okay</u>
<u n="535" who="S0439">erm but they're still fine erm <pause dur="short"/> and then I went to Newcastle and then last weekend <pause dur="short"/> what did I do last weekend? I did something last week oh last weekend was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s surprise birthday this weekend you're here next weekend I'm home weekend after that I'm going to London on the Saturday to go to some talks and then I'm going to the Yorkshire Sculpture Park on the eighteenth</u>
<u n="536" who="S0444">I've never</u>
<u n="537" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I've never been and I really wanna go cos they have the poppy exhibition and obviously I went to the first poppy exhibition but I wanna go to this like erm</u>
<u n="538" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="539" who="S0439">I wanted to really see it erm</u>
<u n="540" who="S0444">it's a shame it's not the week after cos I was gonna be up in Bradford then</u>
<u n="541" who="S0439">oh are you? oh</u>
<u n="542" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0439">no I'm in London that on the twenty-fourth</u>
<u n="544" who="S0444">oh</u>
<u n="545" who="S0439">weekend after that is rugby world cup final and I'm going to Manchester to go to a snowboard and ski show exhibition</u>
<u n="546" who="S0444">as you do</u>
<u n="547" who="S0439">as you do weekend after that we're in Bratislava</u>
<u n="548" who="S0444">woohoo</u>
<u n="549" who="S0439">the weekend after that is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s engagement party</u>
<u n="550" who="S0444">ah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0439">weekend after that I think I'm actually free</u>
<u n="552" who="S0444">don't do anything</u>
<u n="553" who="S0439">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> weekend after that we're in Naples</u>
<u n="554" who="S0444">yay</u>
<u n="555" who="S0439">and then weekend after that is the first weekend of December</u>
<u n="556" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="557" who="S0439">what the fuck I that's two months of my life</u>
<u n="558" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="559" who="S0439">just</u>
<u n="560" who="S0444">just gone</u>
<u n="561" who="S0439">flown</u>
<u n="562" who="S0444">just gone</u>
<u n="563" who="S0439">just gone</u>
<u n="564" who="S0444">I was kind of saying to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I was like you won't be seeing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> until January unless you see her at home like</u>
<u n="565" who="S0439">bit manic everything is just a bit manic at the moment so</u>
<u n="566" who="S0444" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="567" who="S0439" trans="overlap">how is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? how's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doing bless her?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0444">really well <pause dur="short"/> really well</u>
<u n="569" who="S0439" trans="overlap">is she happy?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0444">settled into their house fine the house is like <anon type="place"/> getting on</u>
<u n="571" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0444">you know she's got a really good group of people in primary she's been really sociable doing lots and lots of things</u>
<u n="573" who="S0439">that's good</u>
<u n="574" who="S0444">so yeah</u>
<u n="575" who="S0439">did anything happen with that boy she was messaging no?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0444">no it kind of fizzled out er</u>
<u n="577" who="S0439" trans="overlap">not that I Facebook stalked him and he wasn't very good looking</u>
<u n="578" who="S0444">was he not?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0439">no he wasn't bless him</u>
<u n="580" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh er I I saw him I was there at the house party but I obviously I didn't pay any I was paying enough attention to be like oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> seems to be getting on with that guy and there was like you know casually looking over to that is she alright? but no I just well I though oh okay then just erm</u>
<u n="581" who="S0439">yeah he was not a fitty</u>
<u n="582" who="S0444">was an Oxford graduate though</u>
<u n="583" who="S0439">he was an Oxford graduate that is true</u>
<u n="584" who="S0444">which you know we decided that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants an Oxford graduate</u>
<u n="585" who="S0439">oh I see</u>
<u n="586" who="S0444" trans="overlap">so you know you know we were we were we were we were narrowing down the criteria this time</u>
<u n="587" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="588" who="S0444" trans="overlap">bless</u>
<u n="589" who="S0439" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="590" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah so yeah yeah it was quite funny so</u>
<u n="591" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that's good I'm glad that she's happy though</u>
<u n="592" who="S0444">yeah she is</u>
<u n="593" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I'm glad that she's enjoying it yeah cos I haven't seen you since your birthday</u>
<u n="594" who="S0444">I know</u>
<u n="595" who="S0439"><unclear/></u>
<u n="596" who="S0444"><unclear/> no not this weekend no you can't do that weekend</u>
<u n="597" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="598" who="S0444">you can't do this weekend I can't do that weekend ah well</u>
<u n="599" who="S0439">yeah I haven't seen you since your birthday since your</u>
<u n="600" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="601" who="S0439" trans="overlap">cos I met your dad I love your dad your your parents are amazing</u>
<u n="602" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="603" who="S0439">loved bonding with your dad <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="604" who="S0444" trans="overlap">in <trunc>fa</trunc> everybody found it so good so like where's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? yeah she's hanging out with my dad they're like why is she hanging out with your dad? I was like cos he is awesome</u>
<u n="605" who="S0439">cos I love your dad <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0444">I got it's really funny <pause dur="short"/> I I would play you the kind of message the voicemail that I got this morning cos my mum has finally invested in a smartphone</u>
<u n="607" who="S0439">okay yeah</u>
<u n="608" who="S0444"><unclear/> and she actually turns it on</u>
<u n="609" who="S0439">oh oh she can turn it on a smartphone that is impressive</u>
<u n="610" who="S0444">erm as well as that she keeps it switched on with a <unclear/></u>
<u n="611" who="S0439">oh I see yeah fair enough</u>
<u n="612" who="S0444">yeah she she was on pay as you go and ten quid lasted her for a year</u>
<u n="613" who="S0439">oh wow</u>
<u n="614" who="S0444">and she never used her phone</u>
<u n="615" who="S0439">oh god okay yeah</u>
<u n="616" who="S0444">so yeah so she kind of messaged me be like oh you know we've driven out to this random town hall in the middle of nowhere somewhere but it's really pretty here and you know and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and dad were talking and they were saying oh you know more and I was saying you know and who has the better deal with it <pause dur="short"/> me or dad? and she went you do dad's hard done by cos we're gonna drive here</u>
<u n="617" who="S0439">ah your dad gets dragged around bless him</u>
<u n="618" who="S0444">and then he was like and then <vocal desc="laugh"/> then she was like I need you here cos you know you'd be alright with it I need you to balance it out and I was like yeah but dad might have bribed me too you don't know I might say that as well and she was like you know she's like oh they're both taking the mick now they're both taking the mick now I was like <pause dur="short"/> bribe them with food and</u>
<u n="619" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="620" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and so like <vocal desc="laugh"/> I got a voicemail message <vocal desc="laugh"/> and it's like them all talking just over each other in the car</u>
<u n="621" who="S0439">oh good god</u>
<u n="622" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's really funny they were like we're not backing down we're not backing down we're not <vocal desc="laugh"/> gonna stand for this type of thing and I was like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="623" who="S0439" trans="overlap">what they're not gonna stand for?</u>
<u n="624" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I don't know</u>
<u n="625" who="S0439">going to like</u>
<u n="626" who="S0444" trans="overlap">like yeah yeah random places</u>
<u n="627" who="S0439">random places</u>
<u n="628" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and they were only like joking like</u>
<u n="629" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="630" who="S0444">and then she's like yeah and then you texted me saying I should bribe them with food and then dad was like we're not backing down <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we're not backing down and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes I could do with some chips</u>
<u n="631" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="632" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="633" who="S0439">and that's how your sister was bought by chips</u>
<u n="634" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's like</u>
<u n="635" who="S0439" trans="overlap">love it</u>
<u n="636" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's <unclear/> oh bless him but <trunc>th</trunc>they're they're good they er</u>
<u n="637" who="S0439">ah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="639" who="S0439">that's good</u>
<u n="640" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah and their head teachers has changed in the school where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> works</u>
<u n="641" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="642" who="S0444">and I'm really hoping that head is erm supportive of her being there</u>
<u n="643" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah hopefully he will be</u>
<u n="644" who="S0444">but she's still doing her maths and her English so you know <pause dur="short"/> it's alright</u>
<u n="645" who="S0439">that's good</u>
<u n="646" who="S0444" trans="overlap">hasn't got many friends but</u>
<u n="647" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she'll make some friends I'm sure she will</u>
<u n="648" who="S0444">she will I mean she's got like a lot of friends a <unclear/> but just hard like</u>
<u n="649" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="650" who="S0444">just being like I think that she's so <pause dur="short"/> far away from her friends like with the just the different everybody that lives there <unclear/> really inaccessible part of the <unclear/></u>
<u n="651" who="S0439">oh really?</u>
<u n="652" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's hard to get to and it's quite <unclear/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and she doesn't drive does she?</u>
<u n="654" who="S0444">no and she <trunc>d</trunc> she'd be alright at driving I think erm yeah no I think and do her maths and everything which is giving her loads of confidence</u>
<u n="655" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="656" who="S0444">so and it was well great to see her with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and like on our birthday cos I was a bit like</u>
<u n="657" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0444">I was you know like I was saying to her oh I don't want her to think that it's all about me and I kind of want it <unclear/> and give her her presents and <trunc>stu</trunc> like that and what have you</u>
<u n="659" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="660" who="S0444">but it's like well no I'm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just like you know hey now</u>
<u n="661" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh that's good</u>
<u n="662" who="S0444"><unclear/> cos she's we've not seen her be like that</u>
<u n="663" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="664" who="S0444">so it was really nice <unclear/></u>
<u n="665" who="S0439" trans="overlap">so she was befriending <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's good isn't it?</u>
<u n="666" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah and like <unclear/> and joining in</u>
<u n="667" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0444">and you know all that yeah</u>
<u n="669" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah sorry I had to run off</u>
<u n="670" who="S0444">ah no you're fine I was I was just so happy that they all see you friends like <unclear/></u>
<u n="671" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="672" who="S0444">so like</u>
<u n="673" who="S0439">it was really nice and the concert was really good</u>
<u n="674" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="675" who="S0439">I enjoyed it</u>
<u n="676" who="S0444">no I'm not just saying that er means <unclear/></u>
<u n="677" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh you're oh good oh okay</u>
<u n="678" who="S0444" trans="overlap">well compared to the normal</u>
<u n="679" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="680" who="S0444">Christmas is much better</u>
<u n="681" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0444" trans="overlap">you would be <unclear>invited though</unclear> but I think you're probably not actually around</u>
<u n="683" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="684" who="S0444">by the twelfth of December so that might <unclear/> she might have gone to Lapland <unclear/> to go to Lapland so</u>
<u n="685" who="S0439" trans="overlap">going to Lapland on the twenty-second</u>
<u n="686" who="S0444">yeah <unclear/> save some money and some energy and not <unclear/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0439">yeah er it's it is manic</u>
<u n="688" who="S0444" trans="overlap">Christmas parties and <unclear/></u>
<u n="689" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah it'll be nice to see like I haven't seen <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in <trunc>age</trunc> well I saw <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I caught up with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when he came to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="690" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="691" who="S0439" trans="overlap">the other time and I saw <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> briefly at your birthday and stuff</u>
<u n="692" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="693" who="S0439">so</u>
<u n="694" who="S0444">yeah like I think yeah I think I think I haven't really seen him cos he's been on holiday and like he's been in London a lot so</u>
<u n="695" who="S0439" trans="overlap">is he still with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="696" who="S0444">still with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they've moved in</u>
<u n="697" who="S0439">oh they've moved in together that's</u>
<u n="698" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="699" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that's good</u>
<u n="700" who="S0444">in er <anon type="place"/> so yeah I think I think that's all going well and probably</u>
<u n="701" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that's good</u>
<u n="702" who="S0444" trans="overlap">catch up with them in afterwards it's that kind of thing where everybody's starting to move out a little bit further so it's quite you know</u>
<u n="703" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="704" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's <unclear/> like get everyone going <unclear/> but it's lovely having like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <unclear/></u>
<u n="705" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="706" who="S0444"><unclear/> always with me</u>
<u n="707" who="S0439" trans="overlap">ah that's <pause dur="short"/> gosh</u>
<u n="708" who="S0444">so</u>
<u n="709" who="S0439">that's nice</u>
<u n="710" who="S0444">it is really nice and you know cos it had been like I was having like complete post holiday blues on like Thursday and I was like there was some reason where I just I just wasn't feeling right</u>
<u n="711" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="712" who="S0444" trans="overlap">about going back home and being on my own and</u>
<u n="713" who="S0439">yeah yeah no I get that yeah</u>
<u n="714" who="S0444" trans="overlap">going back to <unclear/> you know <pause dur="short"/> and erm</u>
<u n="715" who="S0439">so you get to hang out with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a bit</u>
<u n="716" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I ended up having no I ended up having dinner by myself in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="717" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="718" who="S0444">and I felt better cos I was outside and I just</u>
<u n="719" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="720" who="S0444">I think I just needed a bit of time</u>
<u n="721" who="S0439" trans="overlap">do you know I I have dinner on my own sometimes</u>
<u n="722" who="S0444" trans="overlap">a bit of <unclear/> I've never had it like</u>
<u n="723" who="S0439">really?</u>
<u n="724" who="S0444" trans="overlap">at a restaurant before I was like I'm gonna do this</u>
<u n="725" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0444">I'm gonna do this and er that was fine then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like cos I'd messaged <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but it had gone very quickly off <unclear/></u>
<u n="727" who="S0439" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="728" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh she must not be feeling well cos she's not been feeling brilliant</u>
<u n="729" who="S0439">oh okay</u>
<u n="730" who="S0444" trans="overlap">er erm</u>
<u n="731" who="S0439">what just like an illness or?</u>
<u n="732" who="S0444">I think she is thinks it's like a virus or something and it's lingering or hasn't</u>
<u n="733" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="734" who="S0444" trans="overlap">manifested she's been feeling very tired and she's very very overworked</u>
<u n="735" who="S0439">oh is she? bless her</u>
<u n="736" who="S0444">if you know like sixteen books to manage or something</u>
<u n="737" who="S0439">yeah wow</u>
<u n="738" who="S0444">and they keep piling more and more and more on her</u>
<u n="739" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="740" who="S0444" trans="overlap">so she's you know erm so I think she ended up in tears with one of her managers</u>
<u n="741" who="S0439">oh bless her</u>
<u n="742" who="S0444" trans="overlap">like with her manager being like mm</u>
<u n="743" who="S0439" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="744" who="S0444">you know <pause dur="short"/> but I think this by my standards I was like dude <unclear/></u>
<u n="745" who="S0439"><unclear/></u>
<u n="746" who="S0444">I was like dude they're giving you too much to do</u>
<u n="747" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="748" who="S0444">you know I don't know what's going on in primary so you know you I can't really comment so you know hopefully it'll get getting a bit better yeah</u>
<u n="749" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="750" who="S0444">yeah but she it's so <unclear>nice</unclear> she's feeling completely <unclear/> shattered and like you know doing stuff like little walks round the canal and she's like oh we can go blackberry picking next week if the weather's nice</u>
<u n="751" who="S0439" trans="overlap">ah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is so sweet she's such a lovely girl</u>
<u n="752" who="S0444">she's really gotten in with like a good like not just coming along sort of <trunc>r</trunc>really instigating a lot of stuff now so</u>
<u n="753" who="S0439">that's good</u>
<u n="754" who="S0444" trans="overlap">as regards like <unclear/> weekend yeah I'm just like cos we were talking about it last night on the way home it's like and er she was and she was saying you know is that <trunc>h</trunc> I don't I just I'm darn well gonna have a good year I'm gonna be sociable I'm gonna be happy and you know I'm gonna make the most of it and I was like yeah</u>
<u n="755" who="S0439">you've got to</u>
<u n="756" who="S0444">go for it</u>
<u n="757" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you've got to do that</u>
<u n="758" who="S0444">and she was like yeah yeah cos I was saying that like all the like like er you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> me <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we we all try and do well apart from <unclear/> we all try to do as much as possible <unclear/> so probably maybe spreading ourselves slightly too thin but doing lots and lots and lots</u>
<u n="759" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="760" who="S0444" trans="overlap">because that's what we get enjoyment out of but yeah yeah and she's like yeah yeah but you're more sociable than me and I'm like I don't I don't think so</u>
<u n="761" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="762" who="S0444">everyone else is and I'm like that's the thing which is difficult for me is not being able to do thing after thing after thing</u>
<u n="763" who="S0439">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="764" who="S0444" trans="overlap">but er you know it's life it'll get better you know give it <unclear>couple of years</unclear></u>
<u n="765" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="766" who="S0444">so</u>
<u n="767" who="S0439">you'll recover you'll get there</u>
<u n="768" who="S0444">it's getting there so I'm not</u>
<u n="769" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="770" who="S0444">I'm not too but</u>
<u n="771" who="S0439" trans="overlap">has <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> been able to still be sociable since moving out?</u>
<u n="772" who="S0444">yeah I think I think she was just trying to get that balance really like she's wanting to still commit to doing the social things</u>
<u n="773" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="774" who="S0444" trans="overlap">but she's kind of like yeah but how are you gonna get back after eleven? and she's like oh I'm tired and you know you know so it's</u>
<u n="775" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="776" who="S0444" trans="overlap">she'll be really grumpy or <unclear/> like she lost all her work on Word and</u>
<u n="777" who="S0439">shit okay</u>
<u n="778" who="S0444" trans="overlap">that she'd been working on all afternoon and like you know had to</u>
<u n="779" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="780" who="S0444" trans="overlap">stay until like she's been doing like nearly twelve hour days like like and she says that I'm almost like sleeping working and worrying</u>
<u n="781" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no one should be doing twelve hour days</u>
<u n="782" who="S0444" trans="overlap">so she's like I just need to <unclear/> so I'm hoping that like over like the weekend with <unclear/> she just needs like some headspace</u>
<u n="783" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="784" who="S0444">I think I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> being there at the weekend I think it's really nice I actually met him</u>
<u n="785" who="S0439">oh wow</u>
<u n="786" who="S0444">like when they had like an open doors weekend like in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="787" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="788" who="S0444" trans="overlap">with er all the <unclear/> three of us just went round</u>
<u n="789" who="S0439">that's cool</u>
<u n="790" who="S0444">so it was really sweet cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were just talking football it was like yeah we'll just leave you guys to it me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="791" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="792" who="S0444" trans="overlap">will just natter</u>
<u n="793" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s nice</u>
<u n="794" who="S0444">I liked him erm and er yeah no so that was that was really really nice and er</u>
<u n="795" who="S0439">uhu</u>
<u n="796" who="S0444">I was like I've finally met you only took us three three</u>
<u n="797" who="S0439">three three years yeah</u>
<u n="798" who="S0444">mm</u>
<u n="799" who="S0439">no I did like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when I met him</u>
<u n="800" who="S0444">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah so all should be going well I'm just trying to think of any <pause dur="short"/> there's not really any interesting</u>
<u n="801" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0444" trans="overlap">anything <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is pregnant again</u>
<u n="803" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s pregnant again? oh I bet everybody knows about that hasn't she just come back?</u>
<u n="804" who="S0444">I think she came back in like spring of this year or something like</u>
<u n="805" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="806" who="S0444" trans="overlap">or maybe January so and she's going off on maternity leave in December</u>
<u n="807" who="S0439">christ</u>
<u n="808" who="S0444">I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s pregnant</u>
<u n="809" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in marketing?</u>
<u n="810" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="811" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="812" who="S0444">so apart from that oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yeah but <unclear/></u>
<u n="813" who="S0439" trans="overlap">er?</u>
<u n="814" who="S0444"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="816" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="817" who="S0439">is she pregnant?</u>
<u n="818" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="819" who="S0439">okay that's cool</u>
<u n="820" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="821" who="S0439" trans="overlap">when's she going off?</u>
<u n="822" who="S0444">soon I think</u>
<u n="823" who="S0439">so she won't complete the maths project?</u>
<u n="824" who="S0444">I don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="825" who="S0439">or would she?</u>
<u n="826" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I think she's got maths at <unclear/></u>
<u n="827" who="S0439">oh has she?</u>
<u n="828" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">guys do you want me to get you <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="829" who="S0439">oh yeah thank you</u>
<u n="830" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah thank you very much</u>
<u n="831" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">you're welcome was it alright for you?</u>
<u n="832" who="S0444">oh it was lovely very</u>
<u n="833" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it was really nice thank you it was really good</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="834" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh</u>
<event desc="sound of cutlery"/>
<u n="835" who="S0439">oh you alright?</u>
<u n="836" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">sorry yeah I knew that would happen</u>
<u n="837" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="838" who="S0444">of I've got a message</u>
<u n="839" who="S0439">you've got a message?</u>
<u n="840" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="841" who="S0439">thank you do you want anything sweet or do you want another drink?</u>
<u n="842" who="S0444">er I'm alright <pause dur="short"/> alright actually erm I don't know do you want? I'm I'm willing to share something sweet should you be inclined so</u>
<u n="843" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well we can always get something to have something sweet later it's not like we have to like stuff our faces now we can just stuff our faces later</u>
<u n="844" who="S0444">we could just stuff our faces all the time</u>
<u n="845" who="S0439">we can stuff our faces all the time</u>
<u n="846" who="S0444">well I am very much at your command and leisure bearing in mind I have no geographical grasp of like</u>
<u n="847" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="848" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> so</u>
<u n="849" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well do you want to want to go to the <anon type="place"/> shop?</u>
<u n="850" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="851" who="S0439">let's go to the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="852" who="S0444" trans="overlap">and eat chocolate and I can add it to your present bag <pause dur="short"/> I've been</u>
<u n="853" who="S0439" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="854" who="S0444">it was actually just I think it looks a bit like you with the box</u>
<u n="855" who="S0439">I just love the box</u>
<u n="856" who="S0444" trans="overlap">just being slightly <unclear>humorous</unclear></u>
<u n="857" who="S0439">sorry</u>
<u n="858" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear>fun</unclear> being like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="859" who="S0439" trans="overlap">sorry I didn't mean to go OTT with the box</u>
<u n="860" who="S0444" trans="overlap">no no no I loved it I loved it I was like best thing that I</u>
<u n="861" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="862" who="S0444" trans="overlap">anybody's ever done for me I was like</u>
<u n="863" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I just got so into it</u>
<u n="864" who="S0444">I know that's the thing I kept buying stuff and I was like oh</u>
<u n="865" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="866" who="S0444" trans="overlap">you'll see why it is around a certain theme but I think I'm gonna have to explain a huge bit</u>
<u n="867" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="868" who="S0444">and be like</u>
<u n="869" who="S0439">we'll go through it tonight I think though for this afternoon we'll go to the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="870" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="871" who="S0439">we'll go and get chocolate</u>
<u n="872" who="S0444">uhu</u>
<u n="873" who="S0439">there is a cinema there so we can check what's on</u>
<u n="874" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="875" who="S0439" trans="overlap">if we wanna go to the cinema we can go to the cinema</u>
<u n="876" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear>that's well cool</unclear></u>
<u n="877" who="S0439">there are restaurants there are stuff like that there erm <anon type="place"/> is not much more than that so</u>
<u n="878" who="S0444">er</u>
<u n="879" who="S0439">then I think</u>
<u n="880" who="S0444" trans="overlap">that's the kind of place that I'm kind of like if there's any</u>
<u n="881" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="882" who="S0444" trans="overlap">if we do <anon type="place"/> tomorrow</u>
<u n="883" who="S0439">yeah so we can</u>
<u n="884" who="S0444" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="885" who="S0439" trans="overlap">chill tonight</u>
<u n="886" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="887" who="S0439" trans="overlap">we can like I said earlier we can have takeaway we can go cook something we could go out for dinner</u>
<u n="888" who="S0444">yeah yeah whichever</u>
<u n="889" who="S0439" trans="overlap">erm we could watch period drama we can</u>
<u n="890" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>are you feeling a period drama mood?</unclear></u>
<u n="891" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well I always know</u>
<u n="892" who="S0444" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="893" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that we like period drama</u>
<u n="894" who="S0444"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="895" who="S0439">we can watch the rugby for a bit just to see the score</u>
<u n="896" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah yeah sure</u>
<u n="897" who="S0439">I've got Netflix so obviously we can</u>
<u n="898" who="S0444">yeah well I'm happy to</u>
<u n="899" who="S0439" trans="overlap">rummage through that</u>
<u n="900" who="S0439" trans="overlap">see the rugby like</u>
<u n="901" who="S0439">uhu</u>
<u n="902" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I mean if you wanna meet up with your friends</u>
<u n="903" who="S0439">no no no</u>
<u n="904" who="S0444" trans="overlap">that is fine</u>
<u n="905" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no I called</u>
<u n="906" who="S0444" trans="overlap">it's just if there's a massive group of them</u>
<u n="907" who="S0439" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="908" who="S0444">I might be <unclear/></u>
<u n="909" who="S0439" trans="overlap">let me explain this to you basically the the group of friends we only know because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes to <anon type="place"/> which is</u>
<u n="910" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="911" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="912" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I remember you like yeah</u>
<u n="913" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and they're all like they're nice but they're all a little bit weird you know like</u>
<u n="914" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="915" who="S0439" trans="overlap">there's just something weird about them all so <vocal desc="laugh"/> so no it's fine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="916" who="S0444">okay then well cos I was like I don't really wanna deprive you of doing anything too sociable like</u>
<u n="917" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no no no don't worry</u>
<u n="918" who="S0444">more than happy to er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like</u>
<u n="919" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="920" who="S0444" trans="overlap">tomorrow</u>
<u n="921" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="922" who="S0444" trans="overlap">that's totally cool</u>
<u n="923" who="S0439" trans="overlap">so I'll message <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> tonight and we can like go somewhere for breakfast in town or something?</u>
<u n="924" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah sounds good</u>
<u n="925" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and then we can go to the colleges have a wander round look at the market you can see</u>
<u n="926" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="927" who="S0439">the beautifulness that's <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="928" who="S0444">oh I know it's beautiful I'm just like oh god</u>
<u n="929" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I can show you <anon type="place"/> where I work</u>
<u n="930" who="S0444">yeah</u>
<u n="931" who="S0439" trans="overlap">erm and that'll be</u>
<u n="932" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I just want the abbey tour of <anon type="place"/> really</u>
<u n="933" who="S0439" trans="overlap">the abbey tour of <anon type="place"/> okay</u>
<u n="934" who="S0444">do you mind if you drive <unclear/> or is there a bus from <anon type="place"/> like?</u>
<u n="935" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no no oh no no that's fine I can drive to <unclear/></u>
<u n="936" who="S0444" trans="overlap">cos I could do it with</u>
<u n="937" who="S0439" trans="overlap">cos I've got to come back to go to <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> anyway</u>
<u n="938" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="939" who="S0439">to go home so it's only like</u>
<u n="940" who="S0444">oh are you going home tomorrow?</u>
<u n="941" who="S0439">no no no like I've got to go like</u>
<u n="942" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="943" who="S0439">to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="944" who="S0444">oh</u>
<u n="945" who="S0439">so</u>
<u n="946" who="S0444">oh ah</u>
<u n="947" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's only like an extra twenty minutes the other way so that's fine don't worry about it erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah so that's about it but I don't <trunc>h</trunc> it's not</u>
<u n="948" who="S0444" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="949" who="S0439">not like lots and lots planned but just hanging out with my</u>
<u n="950" who="S0444" trans="overlap">yeah we can have <unclear/></u>
<u n="951" who="S0439">exactly sounds good brilliant</u>
<u n="952" who="S0444">ah</u>
<u n="953" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="954" who="S0444">awesome</u>
<u n="955" who="S0439">so all I've got to do is I've got to get the bill</u>
<u n="956" who="S0444">are you sure?</u>
<u n="957" who="S0439">oh my god it's fine you came here to see me so yes</u>
<u n="958" who="S0444" trans="overlap">I know but <unclear/></u>
<u n="959" who="S0439">no shut up girlie it's not gonna be</u>
<u n="960" who="S0444" trans="overlap">alright I'm shutting up and I'll be</u>
<u n="961" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="962" who="S0444">I'm sociable now</u>
<u n="963" who="S0439">good</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
