<text id="SHHX">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:56:13</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-06-11</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0679 S0680</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s living room, Leeds </rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Orchids, Birthday cakes, School dinners, Other stuff about our senior school, Shopping in East Kent, Shopping in Cambridge, Cambridge University, Plans for the afternoon</topics>
		<activity>Chatting with sister, Saturday afternoon</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0679">
				<exactage>54</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kent, Margate</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None/Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>31 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired (University manager)</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0680">
				<exactage>64</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Margate, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Mostly Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, West Yorks.</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>42 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- School</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0679"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I had a look at your two orchid plants in the erm in I suppose what you'd call your pantry isn't it?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0680">my under stairs in the kitchen</u>
<u n="3" who="S0679">yeah yeah erm neither look in the best of health <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ha</trunc> did one of them get a bit cold in the winter?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0680">well they were over at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house <pause dur="short"/> erm so they were in a <pause dur="short"/> a really a mainly sort of unheated kitchen and they were quite near the window</u>
<u n="5" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0680">but I did pull them back and put them down on the draining board so they weren't fully next to the window and erm I think they did get a bit cold cos as you can see one of the leaves has gone a bit funny in the middle <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0679">yeah I've got a problem like that with one of my leaves and I know exactly how it happened it was in the bathroom and it put its leaf well its leaf went against the window and it was a bit condensated I think it didn't exactly freeze on the window but I think it got very cold in the end of the leaf</u>
<u n="8" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0679">and then I turned it round to try and help it and I think it may have inadvertently stuck its other leaf don't know quite what happened to the other leaf but something happened to it I reckon because it's got a similar mark on it like it's in the <trunc>m</trunc> in the middle of the leaf like on yours</u>
<u n="10" who="S0680">yes <pause dur="short"/> well mine my leaves wouldn't have been touching anything cold</u>
<u n="11" who="S0679">no but it would been jolly chilly in there wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0680">yes but I mean it didn't touch against anything</u>
<u n="13" who="S0679">no no</u>
<u n="14" who="S0680" trans="overlap">so it's not the end so</u>
<u n="15" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="16" who="S0680">it must be mine must be the cold atmosphere because</u>
<u n="17" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="18" who="S0680">er it's in you couldn't possibly have it touching anything</u>
<u n="19" who="S0679">the roots look</u>
<u n="20" who="S0680" trans="overlap">for that</u>
<u n="21" who="S0679">okay on that one though</u>
<u n="22" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="23" who="S0679">so if it probably could do with upping the watering a bit and give it a nice biggish drink and then see by tomorrow how much it actually wants then you may have to</u>
<u n="24" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0679">if er then you <trunc>cou</trunc> you know could discard the water out</u>
<u n="26" who="S0680">well I have been giving it half a cup er well half of that little container while it's been resting <pause dur="short"/> erm because it was still in well it was sort of resting I I ended up cutting off the long flower stalk but the flowers were on it for ages and ages</u>
<u n="27" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0680">in fact its flowers were still on when it shouldn't have had flowers <pause dur="short"/> erm so it may just be confused</u>
<u n="29" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0680">I don't know but I put it in that under cupboard because there's a window in there and it's er although it's south-facing it gets shaded by that er a bit shaded by that shrub outside and I don't really have any erm being a terraced house I either have north or south I don't have any <pause dur="short"/> east or west was it east the chap we saw?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0679">I don't know but at at erm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0680">it was a side wasn't it that I don't have?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0679" trans="overlap">in the bathroom where I keep mine that's</u>
<u n="34" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0679">west actually</u>
<u n="36" who="S0680">oh it might be west but that man we erm had a er went to the talk from</u>
<u n="37" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0680">he was saying <pause dur="short"/> he thought preferably the type of windowsills I don't have available</u>
<u n="39" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0680">well at least you're not in a back-to-back that'd give</u>
<u n="41" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no that would give you fewer options</u>
<u n="42" who="S0680">even fewer options but erm I wouldn't necessarily have bought one of those myself but as they were bought for me</u>
<u n="43" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0680">erm you know can't really say I oh I can't have one of those I don't have the right window for it</u>
<u n="45" who="S0679">especially the one that erm er lived in your neighbour's house for a while before he remembered to give it to you</u>
<u n="46" who="S0680">oh yes that's may not have helped helped its early progress</u>
<u n="47" who="S0679">erm I think there's a problem with the two that erm well it was three and it's now two that er we were given at the botanic gardens last year</u>
<u n="48" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="49" who="S0679">they look awfully sickly and they've got some really dodgy brown marks on the leaves which I don't think are intended</u>
<u n="50" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="51" who="S0679"><vocal desc="cough"/> excuse me</u>
<u n="52" who="S0680">yes well well those er my two one of them seems to have a little leaf starting to grow</u>
<u n="53" who="S0679">that's a good sign</u>
<u n="54" who="S0680">in the middle but it looks a bit well it doesn't look like it's dried but it is a much darker colour but that that's maybe how they are but the other one is er only got a dried bit in the middle really it hasn't sort of brought up a new shoot</u>
<u n="55" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0680">so er it's got some new roots cos I thought the knobbly things might turn into something else but they they're roots</u>
<u n="57" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0680">so I'm not quite sure <pause dur="short"/> about those we'll have to er see how they get on really</u>
<u n="59" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0680">mm I have got some little cuttings in the bathroom of a well there's an aluminium plant <pause dur="short"/> erm in some water er</u>
<u n="61" who="S0679" trans="overlap">they seem far less common than they used to be</u>
<u n="62" who="S0680">no you can't get that so I was trying to keep that one on because it is <pause dur="short"/> I I ought to cut the tops off and do them again because they're getting very tall and thin but I'm worried about losing them completely cos I haven't really seen any about</u>
<u n="63" who="S0679">no</u>
<u n="64" who="S0680">er so and they do seem to like being in water so that's why I've left them like that erm and next to it in another little pot there's some Philodendron I believe it is sweetheart <pause dur="short"/> vine plant which erm has heart-shaped leaves for its name and that likes being in water so I've left those cuttings in water for quite a time and I noticed the other day <pause dur="short"/> that it's very cheeky one of them erm has put out a a shoot which they do and they <trunc>ca</trunc> you can root from those shoots and it's stretched across and stuck its new roots in the other one's water</u>
<u n="65" who="S0679">ah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0680">so they're like in a chain which reminded me of your orchid</u>
<u n="67" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0680" trans="overlap">that was in the next pot to another orchid in your bathroom and it and it put its roots in its neighbour's pot</u>
<u n="69" who="S0679">and that might be the same one that er put its root on your flannel</u>
<u n="70" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh yes and that's right cos I'd forgotten that yes cos when I was there and the flannel was hanging on the hook a little further down it it seemed to be progressing its root and its root was resting on my flannel</u>
<u n="71" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="72" who="S0680">so er</u>
<u n="73" who="S0679" trans="overlap">very <unclear/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0680">it's a different way of getting your flannel dry having an orchid drink the water off it but er</u>
<u n="75" who="S0679">you know the spiky plants at your house that no sorry not at your house at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house</u>
<u n="76" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="77" who="S0679">that came from <anon type="address"/> probably originally?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="79" who="S0679">there's about half a dozen of them just sitting in water</u>
<u n="80" who="S0680">oh well <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> er some are in water and some are in little tiny pots</u>
<u n="81" who="S0679">oh well I think most of them are in water</u>
<u n="82" who="S0680">but they may have got too cold as well</u>
<u n="83" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="84" who="S0680">although they normally live in my north face they seem to like it in my north-facing sticky out window</u>
<u n="85" who="S0679">I think they look quite poorly sitting in water I'm thinking about taking them into productive protective custody</u>
<u n="86" who="S0680">you think I should have them taken from me?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0679">well I don't know until you can you know and and I can</u>
<u n="88" who="S0680" trans="overlap">until I'm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0679">until your certified as er somebody who is</u>
<u n="90" who="S0680" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> when I'm a <trunc>ca</trunc> a capable plant mother</u>
<u n="91" who="S0679">well I don't know</u>
<u n="92" who="S0680">yeah yes</u>
<u n="93" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I think they don't look very well at the moment</u>
<u n="94" who="S0680">no but I think they belong to the one upstairs possibly</u>
<u n="95" who="S0679">mm I'm having some problems with those myself actually although I have got a lovely tub</u>
<u n="96" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0679">and oh the thing I didn't tell you is that I just stuck some in this pot from I had one oh I dunno last <trunc>ye</trunc> couldn't have been last year cos last year so little got done the year before last planted it up and it was quite poorly but it it it came on nicely and this year it's put up three of those you know those flowers that shoot on long stems?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0680">oh right really nice substantial ones?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0680">oh good</u>
<u n="101" who="S0679" trans="overlap">erm and it hasn't done anything silly like that pheasant's breast plant</u>
<u n="102" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="103" who="S0679">which erm keeps putting flowers out stalks out and they seem to go at funny angles</u>
<u n="104" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="105" who="S0679">these are I don't know I'm they may have happened by now but they were growing up quite slowly</u>
<u n="106" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="107" who="S0679">erm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0680">well that one in the bathroom usually has flowers</u>
<u n="109" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="110" who="S0680">but it hasn't had any</u>
<u n="111" who="S0679">well I've had it years and years and it's never done anything but erm it looks as though you know it it it's</u>
<u n="112" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0679">it's coming on but then I took two babies off when I repotted it and they they look quite sickly</u>
<u n="114" who="S0680">oh</u>
<u n="115" who="S0679">but so I replanted them up again er and so I was just wondering whether I ought to take the other ones or at least I think you should give them some soil I think they've got they caught chlorosis</u>
<u n="116" who="S0680">what's that?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0679">it's when they lose their their chlorofilm <trunc>chlor</trunc></u>
<u n="118" who="S0680">oh yes they they do look a bit insipid on the other hand they can go red cos they get too cold</u>
<u n="119" who="S0679" trans="overlap">chlorophyll not chloroform yes</u>
<u n="120" who="S0680">chlorofilm? <trunc>chloro</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0679"><trunc>chlor</trunc></u>
<u n="122" who="S0680" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> chloroform</u>
<u n="123" who="S0679"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they might not be allowed as erm houseplants if they had chloroform in them</u>
<u n="125" who="S0679">no no don't sort of put them and <unclear/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0680" trans="overlap">you don't go sniffing them</u>
<u n="127" who="S0679">no</u>
<u n="128" who="S0680" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yes yes chlorophyll yes I was wondering if I should know <vocal desc="laugh"/> what substances they had in them yes</u>
<u n="129" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0680">but the erm what do you call them? I think mum used to call them a she called them a money plant the ones with the sort of <trunc>su</trunc> the succulents with the round fleshy leaves</u>
<u n="131" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="132" who="S0680">erm there's a bit of an old it may have been the original sort of one I had cos it's a very old woody root that was on its side and it had started to grow some little bits now that's in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s bathroom</u>
<u n="133" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0680">and that's look gone lovely</u>
<u n="135" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0680">that's that's enjoying itself in there it's it looks much better and I should make some little plants out of those</u>
<u n="137" who="S0679">mm got you've got a few other things on at the moment</u>
<u n="138" who="S0680">I know that's why things have got haven't got erm</u>
<u n="139" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0680">done</u>
<u n="141" who="S0679">now thinking about important things well this is probably only of theoretical important thing because we know what you're doing about your birthday cake but if you were going to choose what birthday cake you wanted and this isn't the birthday cake you're going to get</u>
<u n="142" who="S0680">oh this is a</u>
<u n="143" who="S0679" trans="overlap">because</u>
<u n="144" who="S0680">fantasy birthday cake?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0680">is it yes</u>
<u n="147" who="S0679" trans="overlap">if you could <trunc>choo</trunc> because we've got the blackcurrant sundaes as your birthday cake</u>
<u n="148" who="S0680" trans="overlap">we have blackcurrants yes</u>
<u n="149" who="S0679">erm in cake in the inverted commas but if you were starting from you know level playing field</u>
<u n="150" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="151" who="S0679">and you could choose what kind of cake you would have</u>
<u n="152" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="153" who="S0679">for your birthday</u>
<u n="154" who="S0680">oh yes</u>
<u n="155" who="S0679">which predominantly to feed yourself you know not trying to work out what what other people would want what what what would you what would you erm choose?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know really</u>
<u n="157" who="S0679" trans="overlap">overwhelmed</u>
<u n="158" who="S0680"><trunc>wha</trunc>what are you suggesting?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0679">well I don't know I mean I don't know I mean if it were me I might I quite like lemon lemon cake er</u>
<u n="160" who="S0680">drizzle for me</u>
<u n="161" who="S0679">er well some drizzle some drizzle <unclear>in it</unclear></u>
<u n="162" who="S0680" trans="overlap"><unclear/> lemon <trunc>dr</trunc>drizzle</u>
<u n="163" who="S0679">could be</u>
<u n="164" who="S0680">or lemon</u>
<u n="165" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well <trunc>le</trunc> well <unclear/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0680" trans="overlap">ice</u>
<u n="167" who="S0679">got a flavour yes I mean possibilities coffee and walnut is nice</u>
<u n="168" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="169" who="S0679" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0680">coffee and walnut is very nice</u>
<u n="171" who="S0679" trans="overlap">erm I I I made er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a a a sort of light sponge cake which isn't always my favourite but you know with the cream and the gooseberry and with the elderflower in</u>
<u n="172" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh yes that was very nice</u>
<u n="173" who="S0679" trans="overlap">which I bought you</u>
<u n="174" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="175" who="S0679">at a teashop on your sixtieth birthday</u>
<u n="176" who="S0680" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> tearooms</u>
<u n="177" who="S0679">yes I don't know what what was your favourite?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0680"><anon type="place"/> tearooms? in somewhere</u>
<u n="179" who="S0679"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0680" trans="overlap">in <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/> that was a very nice tearoom yes</u>
<u n="181" who="S0679">yes so what would you have?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes and you made me a very nice cake with that mousseline</u>
<u n="183" who="S0679">that would be coffee</u>
<u n="184" who="S0680">coffee mousseline</u>
<u n="185" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0680">that was a very nice cake</u>
<u n="187" who="S0679">there's lots of cakes what what</u>
<u n="188" who="S0680" trans="overlap">you were saying it didn't have it might just be for me so it could be like a sort of</u>
<u n="189" who="S0679">well you know</u>
<u n="190" who="S0680">small shop-bought</u>
<u n="191" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I was saying not not trying to be cos</u>
<u n="192" who="S0680" trans="overlap">well <unclear>not</unclear></u>
<u n="193" who="S0679" trans="overlap">er sometimes when you're trying to work out what birthday cake to have if you've got people who have particular likes and dislikes you try and go for a middle-of-the-road cake</u>
<u n="194" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="195" who="S0679">although <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to try and get round <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s difficulty just made him some span spane plain sponge cake</u>
<u n="196" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes</u>
<u n="197" who="S0679">and made us coffee or something</u>
<u n="198" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="199" who="S0679">erm but you know so</u>
<u n="200" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah well I like coffee cake I like chocolate cake as well with a nice well not you know er something coffee's probably better erm coffee and walnut but quite like lemon drizzle but you get a lot of it your carrot cake's very nice</u>
<u n="201" who="S0679"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you get a lot of it depending on how big you've cut the slice probably</u>
<u n="202" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no I mean it is commonly available but not all of it is of very good erm standing erm your erm carrot cake's a very fine one</u>
<u n="203" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0680"><trunc>espe</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0679" trans="overlap">which would you which <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="206" who="S0680" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> especially when it has carrots in it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I've only on one occasion left the carrots out</u>
<u n="208" who="S0680">but that was alright actually it <trunc>wa</trunc></u>
<u n="209" who="S0679" trans="overlap">ordinarily it would have carrots in</u>
<u n="210" who="S0680" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well it er carrots <trunc>w</trunc> carrot cake without the carrots was quite nice actually wasn't it? it was just a different experience</u>
<u n="211" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah but nicer than one might expect it didn't have</u>
<u n="212" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="213" who="S0679" trans="overlap">lots of holes in it where the carrots were meant to be</u>
<u n="214" who="S0680" trans="overlap">no no no but had I mean that</u>
<u n="215" who="S0679" trans="overlap">only a few things in it</u>
<u n="216" who="S0680">erm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0679">it's</u>
<u n="218" who="S0680" trans="overlap">carrot carrot-free carrot cake</u>
<u n="219" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="220" who="S0680">as they say there</u>
<u n="221" who="S0679" trans="overlap">for people who don't like carrots</u>
<u n="222" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/> for people who don't like carrots well at school they used to do erm what did they used to do? they used you used to be able to get erm curry you'd have curry or you could have erm curry without the curry powder in it</u>
<u n="223" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0680">curry <trunc>wa</trunc> er was a non-curry which was basically mince</u>
<u n="225" who="S0679">oh right</u>
<u n="226" who="S0680" trans="overlap">that they er <trunc>ha</trunc> had they bought yes you you there was curry or curry or there was erm <pause dur="short"/> curry without curry powder in it or something they used to call it</u>
<u n="227" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="228" who="S0680">which is sort of thinking well that's mince isn't it? so it's mince or curry plain mince or curry whatever</u>
<u n="229" who="S0679">I don't remember er now you haven't told me what birthday cake you would like</u>
<u n="230" who="S0680">oh sorry I was</u>
<u n="231" who="S0679" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="232" who="S0680" trans="overlap">avoiding the issue</u>
<u n="233" who="S0679" trans="overlap">you can make you can make the decision just now and you're not committed to staying with it but if you at this very moment a cup of a pot of Earl Grey tea was going to come in</u>
<u n="234" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="235" who="S0679">and a birthday cake was going to come in what flavour would you like that cake to be?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0680">well there's so</u>
<u n="237" who="S0679" trans="overlap"><trunc>wha</trunc> what kind?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0680" trans="overlap">there's so many oh so many nice ones but now you remind me of that gooseberry one that was particularly fine</u>
<u n="239" who="S0679">so it would be the gooseberry the sponge cake the or the</u>
<u n="240" who="S0680" trans="overlap">so the</u>
<u n="241" who="S0679" trans="overlap">the lighter the Victoria sponge with cream in it and gooseberry cooked with some elderflower</u>
<u n="242" who="S0680">yes well it's like a</u>
<u n="243" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well it's <trunc>elder</trunc></u>
<u n="244" who="S0680" trans="overlap">puree</u>
<u n="245" who="S0679">I think it's <trunc>elder</trunc> and gooseberryflower gooseberryflower?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0679">gooseberry and elderflower</u>
<u n="248" who="S0680" trans="overlap">flower</u>
<u n="249" who="S0679">cake probably it's called</u>
<u n="250" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/> gooseberryflower might be nice</u>
<u n="251" who="S0679" trans="overlap">okay so today that's the cake you would have?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0680">yes well it it's cos it's got sort of erm it's got bits of gooseberry in</u>
<u n="253" who="S0679">no it hasn't</u>
<u n="254" who="S0680">hasn't it got bits of slightly it well it's it or it's puree it's sort of it's erm</u>
<u n="255" who="S0679">what you mean</u>
<u n="256" who="S0680" trans="overlap">well it's in that cake</u>
<u n="257" who="S0679">in the cake? no <trunc>n</trunc> it's just sponge cake</u>
<u n="258" who="S0680">I no in the the filling</u>
<u n="259" who="S0679">oh in the filling</u>
<u n="260" who="S0680">the filling isn't</u>
<u n="261" who="S0679" trans="overlap"><trunc>ye</trunc> the filling is real gooseberries yes</u>
<u n="262" who="S0680">it's real gooseberries but</u>
<u n="263" who="S0679" trans="overlap">but <unclear/> have bits of them in</u>
<u n="264" who="S0680">no it's <trunc>rea</trunc></u>
<u n="265" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well it doesn't have the end bits obviously</u>
<u n="266" who="S0680" trans="overlap">real gooseberries but it wasn't all pippy and pippy and watery it was a bit sort of</u>
<u n="267" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0680">I think they might have pureed a little bit to give it</u>
<u n="269" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="270" who="S0680">some thickness</u>
<u n="271" who="S0679">when I did it I jammed it with elderflower</u>
<u n="272" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh you jammed it yes well I mean it's got to have</u>
<u n="273" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm well I don't <trunc>kn</trunc> I mean</u>
<u n="274" who="S0680" trans="overlap">something done to it yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I put it in a pan and erm</u>
<u n="276" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="277" who="S0679">put elderflower syrup in</u>
<u n="278" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="279" who="S0679">and made a sort of jam out of it</u>
<u n="280" who="S0680">oh that sounds very nice yes</u>
<u n="281" who="S0679">well I thought there's no point putting some</u>
<u n="282" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="283" who="S0679">elderflower and some sugar cos you get less elderflower then</u>
<u n="284" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="285" who="S0679">I'm not <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I may also when I it I may I I had some caster sugar I think</u>
<u n="286" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="287" who="S0679" trans="overlap">and I stuck elderflower</u>
<u n="288" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="289" who="S0679">flowers in</u>
<u n="290" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="291" who="S0679">elderflowers I suppose you can call them can't you? erm</u>
<u n="292" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="293" who="S0679">and erm <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>u</trunc> may have used that in the cake</u>
<u n="294" who="S0680">mm but you've got to have make your filling sort of stay within the bounds of your cake <unclear/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well I make it quite thick yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes it's got to be quite a thick</u>
<u n="297" who="S0679" trans="overlap">cos erm I mean</u>
<u n="298" who="S0680" trans="overlap">consistency</u>
<u n="299" who="S0679">you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is able to make jam that you can't get out of the jam jar so <unclear/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes</u>
<u n="301" who="S0679">oh I probably put a little bit of lemon juice actually in it too</u>
<u n="302" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/> gravity-resistant jam yes</u>
<u n="303" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0680">did you find a commercial industrial use for it?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no no no he managed to get it out</u>
<u n="306" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="307" who="S0679">you could if you were concerted you could get it out and he he recooked it with more fruit</u>
<u n="308" who="S0680">oh right</u>
<u n="309" who="S0679">and made a very nice he made the best it was the best jam he ever had</u>
<u n="310" who="S0680">and was he alright afterwards? it didn't cos you wouldn't want it to sort of solidify <vocal desc="laugh"/> in you tummy would you?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh no it was just the erm</u>
<u n="312" who="S0680" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="313" who="S0679">it was the angle the knife the amount of leverage you could actually get in the top of the jam jar</u>
<u n="314" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh right I see yes</u>
<u n="315" who="S0679">erm but</u>
<u n="316" who="S0680" trans="overlap">that's why Bonne Maman jam jars are good cos</u>
<u n="317" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes absolutely</u>
<u n="318" who="S0680" trans="overlap">they don't have any resistance</u>
<u n="319" who="S0679">erm</u>
<u n="320" who="S0680" trans="overlap">at all</u>
<u n="321" who="S0679">you were talking about school dinners</u>
<u n="322" who="S0680">oh yes</u>
<u n="323" who="S0679">and the only school dinner I remember as in school dinner pudding is</u>
<u n="324" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0679">really actually this isn't true but at the time it was true when I <trunc>s</trunc> I I thought of it the other day was gypsy tarts</u>
<u n="326" who="S0680">gypsy tarts yes</u>
<u n="327" who="S0679">now how would you make the gypsy?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0680">well</u>
<u n="329" who="S0679">do you think it was politically correct to say gypsy tart now?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0680" trans="overlap">it's probably it's probably erm</u>
<u n="331" who="S0679">travellers' tart</u>
<u n="332" who="S0680" trans="overlap">travellers' tart now I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/> er gypsy tarts well it's er condensed milk I believe it's condensed milk and possibly brown sugar to give the</u>
<u n="333" who="S0679" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="334" who="S0680" trans="overlap">colour maybe</u>
<u n="335" who="S0679">so it's like a</u>
<u n="336" who="S0680" trans="overlap">because it's instant straight through your enamel and make your teeth drop out sort of stuff</u>
<u n="337" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0680">and then it's kind of whisked <trunc>w</trunc>whisked up a bit <trunc>s</trunc> and so it's sets I mean er whether they put egg or something in it to make it set</u>
<u n="339" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I <unclear/> mm</u>
<u n="340" who="S0680">but it is like a it's it is like a sort of mousse isn't it? <event desc="sound of phone"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0680">oh I don't know who that can be it is like a mousse</u>
<u n="342" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="343" who="S0680">kind of a set mousse isn't it? it's not <event desc="sound of phone"/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0680">as I recall it's a bit more it's not just like a blancmange <pause dur="short"/> it's not like a custard</u>
<u n="345" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="346" who="S0680">it's more of a erm <pause dur="short"/> well mousse is the nearest thing I can think of not too <unclear>holey</unclear></u>
<u n="347" who="S0679" trans="overlap">it doesn't it doesn't <trunc>c</trunc> it doesn't flow out of the pastry case?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0680">no no it sits</u>
<u n="349" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="350" who="S0680">but you know but it's not like making a chocolate blancmange and</u>
<u n="351" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0680">setting it in a pastry</u>
<u n="353" who="S0679">I was trying to describe it this was at that party on</u>
<u n="354" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="355" who="S0679"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s family party</u>
<u n="356" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="357" who="S0679">and I was talking to his <pause dur="short"/> sister-in-law</u>
<u n="358" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="359" who="S0679" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="361" who="S0679">and erm she said how she liked school dinners and I said I wasn't sure I really liked school dinners very much I I quite liked gypsy tart</u>
<u n="362" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="363" who="S0679">and I said but I think they only have it in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0680">well I'm wondering that</u>
<u n="365" who="S0679">I think it's I think it's a <anon type="place"/> food I think I've seen it written somewhere anyway it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0680" trans="overlap">because erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> knew about gypsy tart he was sort of <anon type="place"/> almost well he was at school in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="368" who="S0680">even though he lived in <anon type="place"/> I mean he was born in <anon type="place"/> but they lived in <anon type="place"/> when</u>
<u n="369" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="370" who="S0680">by the time he was at in school age</u>
<u n="371" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="372" who="S0680">so he <trunc>re</trunc> er well admittedly he's only just in <anon type="place"/> but he</u>
<u n="373" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0680" trans="overlap">remembered gypsy tart well but other people nobody round in Yorkshire</u>
<u n="375" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="376" who="S0680">seemed to know they'd have curd tart in Yorkshire but they didn't know about gypsy tart</u>
<u n="377" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="378" who="S0680">so I think it might be a</u>
<u n="379" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="380" who="S0680">a southern thing</u>
<u n="381" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm cos I described it it was somebody as like banoffee pie without banana in</u>
<u n="382" who="S0680">and that's probably why</u>
<u n="383" who="S0679" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="384" who="S0680" trans="overlap">I liked it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0679">I wasn't I wasn't very far off then was I?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="387" who="S0679">because that's condensed milk and erm sugar I'm fairly sure</u>
<u n="388" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes cos I think it's got should be condensed milk for the er thickness of it</u>
<u n="389" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0680">as well rather <trunc>tha</trunc> and <trunc>eva</trunc> evaporated</u>
<u n="391" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="392" who="S0680">cos don't you make fudge or something with <pause dur="short"/> condensed or can you make fudge with condensed?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0679" trans="overlap">with <unclear/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0680" trans="overlap">I've never made it</u>
<u n="395" who="S0679">cut out a recipe out of the Waitrose magazine for tablet which is</u>
<u n="396" who="S0680">oh yes that's Scottish isn't it?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0679" trans="overlap">Scottish tablet</u>
<u n="398" who="S0680">extremely sweet</u>
<u n="399" who="S0679">which is a simple kind of fudge apparently</u>
<u n="400" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes but it's well it's extremely sweet <event desc="sound of phone"/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0680">I'm sorry about this</u>
<u n="402" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="403" who="S0680">I don't know is it's all these er it's all these they've got my email mixed er my er they've got my phone mixed up with the queen and her ninetieth I think</u>
<u n="404" who="S0679">I don't want to go on about school dinners but erm what was your favourite then?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0680">I can't recall having a favourite I mean you just had them</u>
<u n="406" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="407" who="S0680">my view rather some bits were better than others they did pretty good roast potatoes <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was always the one for roast potatoes cos she was little and</u>
<u n="408" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0680">she was <trunc>li</trunc>little and blonde</u>
<u n="410" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="411" who="S0680">and er you know sort of quite cute she was <trunc>al</trunc> my friend she was always the one who got er picked early on in the when we were in the first year to give present bouquets and things to visiting dignitaries and er she always managed to get seconds at least on roast potatoes</u>
<u n="412" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0680">don't know whether the dinner ladies thought it might make her grow a bit more but er</u>
<u n="414" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="415" who="S0680">but she was quite small and thin but er she could eat like a horse</u>
<u n="416" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="417" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0679">we didn't have strapping boys to give the meat the the potatoes to</u>
<u n="419" who="S0680">no no this is true not at that time no it was just us and er <pause dur="short"/> yes but and then when when it was sixth form did you have tables erm separate tables?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0679">we were allowed tables</u>
<u n="421" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0679">chairs and tables knives and forks and water cups</u>
<u n="423" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="424" who="S0679">from the first year actually</u>
<u n="425" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so were we but when you were in the sixth form up to the sixth form you you queued up in your years and got your plate and went and sat down at a table</u>
<u n="426" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="427" who="S0680">once you've got your dinner</u>
<u n="428" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="429" who="S0680">past the servery hatch</u>
<u n="430" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="431" who="S0680">but when you were in the sixth form they had erm tables of about six eight six or eight those <trunc>l</trunc>longer sort of tables and erm <pause dur="short"/> I think we had we sat at those somehow I have a feeling that you we had heated containers that you had your dinner out of or else they they put these on the table for the eight to kind of help themselves I suppose it was encouraging table manners</u>
<u n="432" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="433" who="S0680">I don't know cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was always er keen to finish off the the tray</u>
<u n="434" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="435" who="S0680">the allocated tray of potatoes if</u>
<u n="436" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="437" who="S0680">everybody didn't want them and</u>
<u n="438" who="S0679">no we didn't have anything</u>
<u n="439" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="440" who="S0679">we we always just had an ordinary table</u>
<u n="441" who="S0680">yes I'm sure we had some I can't remember</u>
<u n="442" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="443" who="S0680">the exact arrangement now because those tables were at <trunc>s</trunc> er not you know where you went through to the stage? there used to <trunc>b</trunc> you used to be able to walk behind the</u>
<u n="444" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="445" who="S0680">the stage?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0679">mm the the <trunc>p</trunc> to the PE area?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0680">yes erm the pudding used to be there served up just in that entrance there</u>
<u n="448" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="449" who="S0680">there used to be ladies with the big vats of custard</u>
<u n="450" who="S0679">mm yes</u>
<u n="451" who="S0680">and the</u>
<u n="452" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes yes yes</u>
<u n="453" who="S0680" trans="overlap">slices with the tray tarts and things</u>
<u n="454" who="S0679" trans="overlap">in the hall but would be the other side of the door</u>
<u n="455" who="S0680" trans="overlap">on the on the</u>
<u n="456" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="457" who="S0680">side of the</u>
<u n="458" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="459" who="S0680">in the wings of the stage really</u>
<u n="460" who="S0679">oh no</u>
<u n="461" who="S0680" trans="overlap">area</u>
<u n="462" who="S0679" trans="overlap">this this was just done in the hall erm outside the you know in the further up in the same entrance hall</u>
<u n="463" who="S0680" trans="overlap">cos the servery was in the servery bit</u>
<u n="464" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="465" who="S0680">and er but and there's that narrow bit of hall beyond those going through to the passageway at the side of the going through to the other block there was a narrow bit and then there was the main</u>
<u n="466" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="467" who="S0680">dining hall</u>
<u n="468" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0680">well the sixth form tables used to be in that narrow bit</u>
<u n="470" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="471" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="472" who="S0679">oh I think people who had sandwich lunches ate them there</u>
<u n="473" who="S0680">yes I don't know whether had one had sandwich lunches I think they got put in some classroom</u>
<u n="474" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="475" who="S0680">or somewhere I don't think sandwich packed lunches were</u>
<u n="476" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="477" who="S0680">encouraged</u>
<u n="478" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="479" who="S0680">really yes but we used to have water on the table and</u>
<u n="480" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="481" who="S0680">that sort of thing as well</u>
<u n="482" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0680">and at Christmas if you got a sixpence in your pudding</u>
<u n="484" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0680">which health and safety probably wouldn't allow these days</u>
<u n="486" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no I'm sure not</u>
<u n="487" who="S0680">er if you got a sixpence you were supposed to hold it up and stand on your chair</u>
<u n="488" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="489" who="S0680">and everybody would clap</u>
<u n="490" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="491" who="S0680">did you do anything like that?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0679">no</u>
<u n="493" who="S0680">well you were ten years behind me so</u>
<u n="494" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0680">so er perhaps it was considered the done thing</u>
<u n="496" who="S0679">no probably not</u>
<u n="497" who="S0680">no did you used to have to queue up did you queue up at the side in a medical room opposite</u>
<u n="498" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0680" trans="overlap">those girls' toilets there?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah yes</u>
<u n="501" who="S0680">come in that way</u>
<u n="502" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="503" who="S0680" trans="overlap">and down the side</u>
<u n="504" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="505" who="S0680">and round to the surgery</u>
<u n="506" who="S0679">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="507" who="S0680">oh right</u>
<u n="508" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="509" who="S0680">I'm not quite sure where the staff used to sit or if they used to take theirs up to the staff some of the staff used to have dinners</u>
<u n="510" who="S0679">I don't know <unclear/> the staff had dinners</u>
<u n="511" who="S0680">and before you got into that bit by the medical room you used to queue up outside in the</u>
<u n="512" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="513" who="S0680">exterior</u>
<u n="514" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0680">hold <vocal desc="laugh"/> to come in those doors</u>
<u n="516" who="S0679">I don't remember queuing in cos I was in the boys' school for the first three years were in the boys' school</u>
<u n="517" who="S0680">oh I didn't realise you were</u>
<u n="518" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="519" who="S0680">in the or that one</u>
<u n="520" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well that the boys' the junior school was in the boys' school</u>
<u n="521" who="S0680">oh right</u>
<u n="522" who="S0679">and then the O level classes and sixth form some of the sixth form anyway were in the erm the girls' school</u>
<u n="523" who="S0680">oh cos you were <unclear/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0679" trans="overlap">but I don't</u>
<u n="525" who="S0680" trans="overlap">weren't you?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0679">I I <trunc>hardl</trunc> I I do remember yes it was the same I can remember queuing up for the the meals but then I remember you you did as a prefect right you know a sixth former you could do dinner duty</u>
<u n="527" who="S0680">oh so you you were in mixed?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0679">yes all the time</u>
<u n="529" who="S0680">you were in mixed and did you have your dinners in the boys' school hall?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0679">well only when I was er in the junior school</u>
<u n="531" who="S0680">in the junior school oh right</u>
<u n="532" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="533" who="S0680">I see I didn't realise you'd had your dinners there but always had mine in the</u>
<u n="534" who="S0679">well you'd have them in your own school wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0680" trans="overlap">in my school <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0679">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="537" who="S0680" trans="overlap">with the blue <trunc>p</trunc> with the mosaic pillar in the middle</u>
<u n="538" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm did I tell you I went back to <anon type="place"/> the last time I went down to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0680">oh right</u>
<u n="540" who="S0679" trans="overlap">and erm I they had a they had the farmers' market they used to have them in one of the there's an academy somewhere around there</u>
<u n="541" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="542" who="S0679">erm but they don't</u>
<u n="543" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh it's er yes I know I can't think which school it used to be</u>
<u n="544" who="S0679">er it's on the <anon type="place"/> road</u>
<u n="545" who="S0680">erm <pause dur="short"/> oh there was a <anon type="place"/> was it?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="547" who="S0680">no it's one of the other ones</u>
<u n="548" who="S0679" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> is near just next door</u>
<u n="549" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes next door it's the other way I can't think of I</u>
<u n="550" who="S0679" trans="overlap">anyway</u>
<u n="551" who="S0680" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0679" trans="overlap">it's something something academy</u>
<u n="553" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes yes it used to be somebody else's</u>
<u n="554" who="S0679" trans="overlap">and so I'd been to the farmers' market there so I went to the farmers' market at <anon type="place"/> cos I thought well it's an excuse to have a look and see what</u>
<u n="555" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="556" who="S0679">they've done but it's erm <pause dur="short"/> it it's a completely cos they've knocked down the boys' school</u>
<u n="557" who="S0680">oh</u>
<u n="558" who="S0679" trans="overlap">and they've built it where the boys' school was cos you remember we went back to <anon type="place"/> just before they started building?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="560" who="S0679">cos they've kept some of the girls' school and the boys' school's gone</u>
<u n="561" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="562" who="S0679">but they've put a sort of a sixth form I think it's the sixth form studies building</u>
<u n="563" who="S0680">yes oh</u>
<u n="564" who="S0679" trans="overlap">there</u>
<u n="565" who="S0680">right so they are they are they still <anon type="place"/> or are they an academy?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0679">no they're <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="567" who="S0680">oh</u>
<u n="568" who="S0679">well I think they're haven't they all got to become academies now or did that get thrown out?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0680" trans="overlap">no I think it got I think it I think er there was a U-turn on that</u>
<u n="570" who="S0679">mm well they're er they are they're <anon type="place"/> grammar school but they're in a a school group with <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0680">oh yes I know they are but they haven't <unclear/> added academy <unclear/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I don't think so but they're a language they're a language</u>
<u n="573" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0679">specialist school or something</u>
<u n="575" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes yeah oh right</u>
<u n="576" who="S0679">but going back going back and like</u>
<u n="577" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="578" who="S0679">you know this isn't my school</u>
<u n="579" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="580" who="S0679">er I have no</u>
<u n="581" who="S0680" trans="overlap">well not <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="582" who="S0679" trans="overlap">connections no interest</u>
<u n="583" who="S0680" trans="overlap">not <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="584" who="S0679">in going back</u>
<u n="585" who="S0680">not not <vocal desc="laugh"/> if it's been flattened but we went er a few years back we went and we we met that very nice man who showed us round</u>
<u n="586" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="587" who="S0680" trans="overlap">didn't we?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0679">yes that was just before they took</u>
<u n="589" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="590" who="S0679">the building down</u>
<u n="591" who="S0680">because erm it was interesting walking round the girls' school because erm although they've changed some of it there were odd bits of the girls' school sort of poking out here and there like</u>
<u n="592" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0680">the odd bit of staircase you remember</u>
<u n="594" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I remember that</u>
<u n="595" who="S0680" trans="overlap">with the original erm rails or or the odd erm well some of some of the views had changed cos they'd built things here and and also erm when I was at school you weren't allowed to go across the joining erm sort of erm er what would you call it? not exactly a bridge cos it was over a corridor but the bit the walkway that was on top of the corridor joining erm the bit erm from the dining hall where the passage went across to the rest of the classrooms with our music in erm you you weren't allowed to go across that because one end was the staff room and the other end was <trunc>che</trunc> near the chemistry lab or something</u>
<u n="596" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="597" who="S0680" trans="overlap">but we we actually we actually walked quite near there or over there</u>
<u n="598" who="S0679">oh yes</u>
<u n="599" who="S0680">somehow</u>
<u n="600" who="S0679">yes cos</u>
<u n="601" who="S0680" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="602" who="S0679">yes it was</u>
<u n="603" who="S0680" trans="overlap">you know the</u>
<u n="604" who="S0679">biology that was where biology was</u>
<u n="605" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="606" who="S0679">er chemistry on one side biology on the other and it was like the tech room in the middle</u>
<u n="607" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="608" who="S0679">that was the tech room and then I don't know that I don't the staffroom wouldn't have been the other end in my day</u>
<u n="609" who="S0680">no the staff you know the open well the initially open-plan nineteen fifties sixties whatever it was erm you know fifties probably early sixties open-plan stairs they had in the</u>
<u n="610" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="611" who="S0680">entrance hall?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="613" who="S0680">which was a dining hall</u>
<u n="614" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="615" who="S0680">erm or it when you went up there there was the open-plan ones which I didn't like and then they went to normal stairs and as you went round the first classroom of that landing was French and the room behind it was the staffroom</u>
<u n="616" who="S0679">mm well the staffroom moved into the old library when I was there</u>
<u n="617" who="S0680">oh the library upstairs?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="619" who="S0680">was that the <trunc>libr</trunc> like the library used to be a classroom cos we had I had the library as a classroom and then there was a little room you came from that staircase you went into the library and if you went out the library the other end there was a little room that if you walked through it it was a classroom but</u>
<u n="620" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="621" who="S0680" trans="overlap">if you walked through it you ended up on the top of the other staircase</u>
<u n="622" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="623" who="S0680">where needlework and geography I oh it's</u>
<u n="624" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0680" trans="overlap">on that floor geography</u>
<u n="626" who="S0679" trans="overlap">probably</u>
<u n="627" who="S0680">was on the floor and then if you went down a floor it was needlework</u>
<u n="628" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="629" who="S0680">erm because you couldn't use it <trunc>wha</trunc> you weren't supposed to use that as a through route because it was a classroom</u>
<u n="630" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="631" who="S0680">erm it I think it was an English classroom</u>
<u n="632" who="S0679">fairly sure you can go through it in my day</u>
<u n="633" who="S0680">erm or am I or was that right? or was it that little joining place you weren't supposed to through? was it off the commerce room was like that cos the commerce room was below the library I'm just trying to think <trunc>h</trunc> what happened to the commerce room</u>
<u n="634" who="S0679">in my day you went to the boys' school</u>
<u n="635" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="636" who="S0679">cos I'm I first saw erm rows of people sitting behind typewriters</u>
<u n="637" who="S0680">ah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0679">cos I think I my first year erm my form room was the on the floor above in the junior school in the first year I think that was the year where the school leaving age increased from</u>
<u n="639" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="640" who="S0679">fifteen to sixteen</u>
<u n="641" who="S0680">no I think I can remember that <unclear/> and I think perhaps you could go in the library both ends but you couldn't go in the commerce room maybe that was it</u>
<u n="642" who="S0679">it would be quite handy for the staffroom to be able to get into both ends wouldn't it? it would save somebody having to all the way down and all the way up</u>
<u n="643" who="S0680">yes yes well that's it they could cut across that link from the</u>
<u n="644" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="645" who="S0680">the art and music <pause dur="short"/> down near the bicycle sheds end of things of the girls' school</u>
<u n="646" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="647" who="S0680">to the main hall end because otherwise erm otherwise you've got to go erm you've got to go down and round through the hall and along that passage to get</u>
<u n="648" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="649" who="S0680">so it's quite a long way whereas you can just nip out the back door of the staffroom cos the teachers used to sunbathe up there on that <trunc>pat</trunc> thing</u>
<u n="650" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="651" who="S0680"><unclear/> cos nobody else was you know the lunchtime had their sandwiches or you know whatever they were doing erm up there yes <pause dur="short"/> well that's interesting</u>
<u n="652" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="653" who="S0680">but it has all changed rather a lot round there with that <anon type="place"/> retail park not far away and things</u>
<u n="654" who="S0679">yeah I mean obviously they've got a lot of shops down there now haven't they?</u>
<u n="655" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="656" who="S0679">in that area because you know the bit I dunno <anon type="place"/> it's</u>
<u n="657" who="S0680" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> retail park or something</u>
<u n="658" who="S0679">is that is that <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="659" who="S0680"><anon type="place"/> is east yes <anon type="place"/> is <anon type="place"/> retail park</u>
<u n="660" who="S0679">oh is it?</u>
<u n="661" who="S0680">something I think</u>
<u n="662" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="663" who="S0680">yeah so I think I've seen that as a name or it it's that kind of <trunc>a</trunc>area</u>
<u n="664" who="S0679">well there's <anon type="place"/> and then if you go on a bit you get to Tesco which isn't quite joined then there's Asda isn't there?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0680">yes well I think the whole thing</u>
<u n="666" who="S0679" trans="overlap">we've got a heck of a lot of shops</u>
<u n="667" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="668" who="S0679">you can see why the er high street in <anon type="place"/>'s died</u>
<u n="669" who="S0680">is struggling yes</u>
<u n="670" who="S0679">because</u>
<u n="671" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="672" who="S0679">unless there's a lot more people down and they need a lot more things cos afterwards when I left <anon type="place"/> when I went to the farmers' market I thought I might pick up a little something for lunch</u>
<u n="673" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="674" who="S0679">and there wasn't really anything that looked really tasty</u>
<u n="675" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="676" who="S0679">so I thought I'd pop into Marks and Spencer's cos remember there's that big Marks and Spencer's Food?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0680">near the Travelodge?</u>
<u n="678" who="S0679">yeah yeah on that <trunc>b</trunc> and I thought well I'll pick up erm what I'd had previously was these little box salads er</u>
<u n="679" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh yes?</u>
<u n="680" who="S0679">not not <trunc>l</trunc>leaves erm but erm couscous and roast vegetables and</u>
<u n="681" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="682" who="S0679">you know those prepared salads?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0680" trans="overlap">prepared yes yes</u>
<u n="684" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I suppose you'd call them so I thought oh I'll get another one of those well in fact I got two and had half of two</u>
<u n="685" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="686" who="S0679">and erm and I thought gosh you know there's every shop unlike <anon type="place"/> it seems where you have to go to different bits if you were going to go in town for shopping or</u>
<u n="687" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="688" who="S0679">you know you have to go right up <anon type="place"/> road to get a range of shops all the shops they're they're all kind of around there they're all within not exactly walking distance because you're not meant to walk around there really</u>
<u n="689" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="690" who="S0679">but there's a lot more choice of shops than when we were there</u>
<u n="691" who="S0680">well they were different as well we when we there were when I when I was when I was there to start with the supermarkets had only started to arrive when I was little</u>
<u n="692" who="S0679">yes yes but I'm not I'm but if you wanted to buy anything you sort of had to go to <anon type="place"/> didn't you?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0680">well the very big shops were at <anon type="place"/> I mean our Marks and Spencer's is a reasonable size</u>
<u n="694" who="S0679">but you either went into</u>
<u n="695" who="S0680" trans="overlap">or or people went to Oxford Street you used to <trunc>g</trunc>go on a shopping trip to London people did</u>
<u n="696" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes but all the sort of the shops you'd go to <anon type="place"/> for say when I was there in eighty <pause dur="short"/> I suppose perhaps <anon type="place"/> high street had started dying in the eighties but in the eighties like <anon type="place"/> had all the</u>
<u n="697" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="698" who="S0679">the names you know</u>
<u n="699" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="700" who="S0679">I'm talking about <anon type="place"/> and posh department stores but you know the sort of shops</u>
<u n="701" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="702" who="S0679">that you'd get in every high street you had to go to <anon type="place"/> to find one but</u>
<u n="703" who="S0680" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="704" who="S0679">they're all at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="705" who="S0680">yes well I know there used to be erm a Dolcis in <anon type="place"/> and well there used to be a Dolcis on <anon type="place"/> high street was it a Dolcis or was it a Saxo?</u>
<u n="706" who="S0679">no</u>
<u n="707" who="S0680" trans="overlap">they had one almost both of them opposite each other didn't they?</u>
<u n="708" who="S0679">no well Freeman Hardy Willis and Dolcis</u>
<u n="709" who="S0680" trans="overlap">there was Freeman Hardy Willis but I know <anon type="place"/> had one</u>
<u n="710" who="S0679" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> was it?</u>
<u n="711" who="S0680">erm I don't no I think it was Dolcis er it's in <anon type="place"/> maybe</u>
<u n="712" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="713" who="S0680">they didn't have a branch at <anon type="place"/> at the time cos it's I didn't really remember it opposite anyway we if you wanted to see all those sorts of shoe shops you you had to really go to <anon type="place"/> if you wanted to see the full</u>
<u n="714" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="715" who="S0680">range although we got quite a few of them you know if you didn't want to go to erm the Clarks or the er ones in <anon type="place"/> so er and er <pause dur="short"/> well we had <anon type="place"/>'s got in your have you was <anon type="place"/>'s still there?</u>
<u n="716" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="717" who="S0680">cos <anon type="place"/>'s</u>
<u n="718" who="S0679" trans="overlap">used to have those little machines that shot money round the roof didn't it?</u>
<u n="719" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm yes er <anon type="place"/>'s was alright I mean that had materials and things but there were more fabric shops in <anon type="place"/> because it was a a bigger place but you could you could get what you wanted <trunc>r</trunc> more or less</u>
<u n="720" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="721" who="S0680">erm thinking about it and there were quite a few electrical shops and things but the trouble is if you haven't got a car <pause dur="short"/> you can go on the bus to <anon type="place"/> but erm <pause dur="short"/> as you say if you're a pedestrian it's a lot of walking</u>
<u n="722" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="723" who="S0680">you know if you're an older person it's a</u>
<u n="724" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="725" who="S0680" trans="overlap">you might <trunc>fi</trunc> they might have what you want but you've if you haven't got a car to go in or you haven't got a car to drive round all the different bits of it</u>
<u n="726" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="727" who="S0680">erm it's a lot of walking</u>
<u n="728" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="729" who="S0680">and the road scheme doesn't seem to be terribly sensible</u>
<u n="730" who="S0679">but I was just amazed how much they had there</u>
<u n="731" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="732" who="S0679">erm and I thought gosh I suppose</u>
<u n="733" who="S0680" trans="overlap">all this</u>
<u n="734" who="S0679">it serves all the</u>
<u n="735" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="736" who="S0679">all the towns around</u>
<u n="737" who="S0680">yes well there's erm the sort of not DIY exactly what am I thinking of? erm</u>
<u n="738" who="S0679">well there's a whole lot load of those as well</u>
<u n="739" who="S0680">DIY and and erm <pause dur="short"/> furniture shop type places and things <pause dur="short"/> quite a few of those there are some <trunc>d</trunc> DIYs but it's not all clothes and food there's other carpets and</u>
<u n="740" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="741" who="S0680">stuff aren't there? quite a few different <pause dur="short"/> but er well I suppose because and also with <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> your shops in <anon type="place"/> have had to fit in with <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> because they couldn't just knock a great hole in the middle of</u>
<u n="742" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="743" who="S0680" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> and stick a shopping centre in</u>
<u n="744" who="S0679">well they did with the <anon type="place"/> centre</u>
<u n="745" who="S0680">they did with the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="746" who="S0679" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="747" who="S0680" trans="overlap">but I mean in</u>
<u n="748" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="749" who="S0680">in the er in the main bit</u>
<u n="750" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="751" who="S0680">erm you know they had more more restriction on that and it's it's a wealthier place than <anon type="place"/> cos you get more tourists sort of thing</u>
<u n="752" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="753" who="S0680">to come and look at everything I suppose the same with <anon type="place"/> that would be the the main <pause dur="short"/> historic centre</u>
<u n="754" who="S0679">mm but they've got a whole new shopping centre on the side of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="755" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="756" who="S0679">or it seemed to be</u>
<u n="757" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="758" who="S0679">as I'm not a big shopper it doesn't make too much difference to me really</u>
<u n="759" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="760" who="S0679">cos I rarely go into <anon type="place"/> to buy anything</u>
<u n="761" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="762" who="S0679">but I was just <trunc>am</trunc> I was just amazed cos I I popped in and I thought I'd buy a sandwich and I thought gosh there are all these shops here</u>
<u n="763" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="764" who="S0679">cos I I went and used erm <pause dur="short"/> a Wilko</u>
<u n="765" who="S0680">Wilkinson's?</u>
<u n="766" who="S0679">yes yes</u>
<u n="767" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="768" who="S0679">and there was something else there and I thought well I'm not gonna spend I could usually pick something up there because these things need a bit of planning</u>
<u n="769" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="770" who="S0679">erm</u>
<u n="771" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="772" who="S0679">normally because don't have the the the shops around</u>
<u n="773" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="774" who="S0679">erm <pause dur="short"/> and I suppose it's living out a bit anyway cos it's a bit of a drive to get not a drive to get into <anon type="place"/> but</u>
<u n="775" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="776" who="S0679">you know it's an effort to go into <anon type="place"/> in a way</u>
<u n="777" who="S0680" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> and also in <anon type="place"/> erm a lot of the land is controlled by the universities</u>
<u n="778" who="S0679">oh absolutely</u>
<u n="779" who="S0680">so</u>
<u n="780" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="781" who="S0680">there's er unless the university wants to sell off that land which they or use it themselves there's not <vocal desc="laugh"/> they're a bit like a a version of Tescos that used to wasn't it Tescos used to go around buying up things? well</u>
<u n="782" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="783" who="S0680">er <anon type="place"/> don't exactly go around buying up things but they've got so much <trunc>h</trunc> land from historic times and</u>
<u n="784" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="785" who="S0680">things they've been left and stuff that there's a lot of <anon type="place"/> you might not appreciate does actually belong to to various university groups</u>
<u n="786" who="S0679">oh absolutely I mean most of the centre belongs to <unclear>wherever</unclear> and it wasn't that long ago that they bought that erm the bit that's now <anon type="place"/> docks</u>
<u n="787" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="788" who="S0679">they they bought</u>
<u n="789" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh yes I mean but I mean within <anon type="place"/> but they</u>
<u n="790" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="791" who="S0680">they they've bought land in all sorts of odd places</u>
<u n="792" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="793" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="794" who="S0679" trans="overlap">but they've you know it was</u>
<u n="795" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="796" who="S0679" trans="overlap">it's it's one of the docks <unclear/></u>
<u n="797" who="S0680">is it <trunc>f</trunc> er <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0679"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="799" who="S0680"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="800" who="S0679" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="801" who="S0680"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="802" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="803" who="S0680" trans="overlap"><trunc>y</trunc><trunc>y</trunc>yes</u>
<u n="804" who="S0679">erm I think <anon type="place"/> er one of the colleges bought it</u>
<u n="805" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="806" who="S0679">erm because somebody the story goes that the bursar found out about it when everyone else was on holiday</u>
<u n="807" who="S0680">and he thought it was a bargain</u>
<u n="808" who="S0679" trans="overlap">and he had he <trunc>ha</trunc></u>
<u n="809" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="810" who="S0679">no he had to make a decision before he could get in touch with the master or whoever</u>
<u n="811" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="812" who="S0679">you know or</u>
<u n="813" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="814" who="S0679">the other senior people so he took a punt on it</u>
<u n="815" who="S0680">yes mm</u>
<u n="816" who="S0679">and it worked out very well and I don't there's two things he bought that and he bought something else at the same time</u>
<u n="817" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="818" who="S0679">and er he's made the college</u>
<u n="819" who="S0680">and they bequeathed with things</u>
<u n="820" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I can't think which college it is now is it <anon type="place"/>? one of the colleges</u>
<u n="821" who="S0680">don't know</u>
<u n="822" who="S0679" trans="overlap">whichever <unclear/> yes yes cos erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s daughter who's doing some fundraising and erm they were trying to raise something for their must be their four hundredth anniversary</u>
<u n="823" who="S0680">oh yes mm</u>
<u n="824" who="S0679">and they set two years or something</u>
<u n="825" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="826" who="S0679" trans="overlap">to get all these millions and they set off to do these well</u>
<u n="827" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="828" who="S0679">I don't think they personally were but they they were doing it's a worldwide sort of</u>
<u n="829" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="830" who="S0679" trans="overlap">appeal</u>
<u n="831" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="832" who="S0679">and they got at least as much money in a very short time</u>
<u n="833" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="834" who="S0679">so yes but people are you know successful and want to give money</u>
<u n="835" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="836" who="S0679">and then you get weird <trunc>peop</trunc> not weird people but <trunc>k</trunc> <trunc>un</trunc> there was the man er man who gave the <anon type="place"/> as in the <anon type="place"/> centre at <anon type="place"/> college</u>
<u n="837" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="838" who="S0679">you know as you drive out along the erm the road to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="839" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="840" who="S0679">there's a funny-shaped building</u>
<u n="841" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="842" who="S0679"><anon type="place"/> college</u>
<u n="843" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="844" who="S0679">and that was left by somebody who was erm apparently had no connections with the college but just thought it would be a good place to have his name remembered I suppose</u>
<u n="845" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="846" who="S0679">or wanted to do a good deed or</u>
<u n="847" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="848" who="S0679" trans="overlap">erm whatever</u>
<u n="849" who="S0680">that's right mm</u>
<u n="850" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="851" who="S0680">mm that's good</u>
<u n="852" who="S0679">oh I was going to tell you something and I just can't think what it is now we were talking about er <pause dur="short"/> land oh oh it's gone no it's gone completely it will come back <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> what are you hoping to get <pause dur="short"/> is there anything you you would really like to do this afternoon or you feel we ought to do this afternoon? cos it's nearly it's nearly the eve of your birthday</u>
<u n="853" who="S0680">it is</u>
<u n="854" who="S0679">and I know that you might there might be things in relation to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house that we need to sort out <pause dur="short"/> or you might want to go out now or</u>
<u n="855" who="S0680">well</u>
<u n="856" who="S0679" trans="overlap">or you might want to do anything</u>
<u n="857" who="S0680">it looks a bit well it's not actually raining now but it doesn't look very bright out there</u>
<u n="858" who="S0679">I'll take that as a kind of no then</u>
<u n="859" who="S0680">although the trees are looking extremely verdant but er <pause dur="short"/> I can't I mean it's it well I know it's I'm looking out of the north window but looking down there further it doesn't look that sunny on those house roofs that</u>
<u n="860" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="861" who="S0680">might have got some sunshine</u>
<u n="862" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="863" who="S0680">and there's a bit of a breeze blowing so perhaps we we could go for a little <pause dur="short"/> walk and go and nose at <anon type="place"/> park see what they're doing</u>
<u n="864" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes oh I'm not suggesting we trek as it were I just</u>
<u n="865" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="866" who="S0679">you know as in er here or</u>
<u n="867" who="S0680" trans="overlap">well we could</u>
<u n="868" who="S0679"><trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="869" who="S0680">well we'll we'll take a drive up to <anon type="place"/> park and just go and nose about and see what they're doing to set up for the triathlon</u>
<u n="870" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh yes okay</u>
<u n="871" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh in fact we could drive up there to find out how long it is and see if it's as far as you can walk</u>
<u n="872" who="S0679" trans="overlap">good plan mm</u>
<u n="873" who="S0680">erm</u>
<u n="874" who="S0679">you could make me walk and see where I stop</u>
<u n="875" who="S0680">you can run along behind the car and I'll tell you how far you've been</u>
<u n="876" who="S0679" trans="overlap">because it make me go set off and then I'll tell you I've got there or you come and pick me up but</u>
<u n="877" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="878" who="S0679">that might not be</u>
<u n="879" who="S0680">no so we we could have a a a test of how far it is because we won't be able to to go anywhere tomorrow because</u>
<u n="880" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="881" who="S0680">I can't go anywhere because the road is closed</u>
<u n="882" who="S0679">I can actually <trunc>l</trunc> always look it up on Google Maps but we could that</u>
<u n="883" who="S0680">oh yes I hadn't thought about that</u>
<u n="884" who="S0679">that is a possibility</u>
<u n="885" who="S0680">yes <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="886" who="S0679">do you want to go down to <anon type="place"/> and look at that shop entrance?</u>
<u n="887" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh not especially</u>
<u n="888" who="S0679">I can't remember exactly why I want to do it now but</u>
<u n="889" who="S0680">oh</u>
<u n="890" who="S0679">have we looked at it enough on Google Maps?</u>
<u n="891" who="S0680">you you've looked at it I just wanted to establish where it was because</u>
<u n="892" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="893" who="S0680">it's difficult with erm addresses that have got a hundred and something in them or five hundred and something as to which bit of a very long road it is erm and I thought it was on that bit yes</u>
<u n="894" who="S0679">now I haven't put those er</u>
<u n="895" who="S0680" trans="overlap">and you can't go and get your keys</u>
<u n="896" who="S0679" trans="overlap">sorry</u>
<u n="897" who="S0680" trans="overlap">cut in <anon type="place"/>'s yet so</u>
<u n="898" who="S0679" trans="overlap">cos I haven't got them</u>
<u n="899" who="S0680">you haven't got them so</u>
<u n="900" who="S0679" trans="overlap">where is that?</u>
<u n="901" who="S0680"><anon type="place"/>'s is along it's up <anon type="place"/> road almost to the school</u>
<u n="902" who="S0679">oh right okay erm the thing I haven't done also is I haven't put the reflector spotlights on Freecycle yet</u>
<u n="903" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="904" who="S0679">because possibly</u>
<u n="905" who="S0680">somebody needs to be there</u>
<u n="906" who="S0679">no no no</u>
<u n="907" who="S0680" trans="overlap">if anybody's interesting</u>
<u n="908" who="S0679">no no no they'll phone they'll get in touch in whatever way</u>
<u n="909" who="S0680">oh right</u>
<u n="910" who="S0679" trans="overlap">we ask them to</u>
<u n="911" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="912" who="S0679">cos you need to know when otherwise you're gonna you know don't just wait and see if anyone comes you arrange it with a particular individual</u>
<u n="913" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="914" who="S0679">but possibly I should have should measure the erm the width of the front of the lamp you know the top of the non-screwy end of the lights</u>
<u n="915" who="S0680">the glass bit?</u>
<u n="916" who="S0679">yes the width of it because looking at how they're sold</u>
<u n="917" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="918" who="S0679">they're sold in diameters</u>
<u n="919" who="S0680">not in wattage?</u>
<u n="920" who="S0679">well I guess wattage as well</u>
<u n="921" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="922" who="S0679">but they tend to be quite close-fitting don't they? they're not like a bulb which hangs in a space they tend to go into something don't they?</u>
<u n="923" who="S0680">er they do but a lot of those they as they were originally on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s disco they weren't necessarily inserted</u>
<u n="924" who="S0679">okay</u>
<u n="925" who="S0680">in <unclear/></u>
<u n="926" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well I'll try and I'll put them <unclear>advertise</unclear> but I just think it might be a question we'll get</u>
<u n="927" who="S0680">right</u>
<u n="928" who="S0679">but I can put them on</u>
<u n="929" who="S0680">yes and and the fact that <pause dur="short"/> presume they work</u>
<u n="930" who="S0679">well we can't</u>
<u n="931" who="S0680">well if they rattle they don't work and if they all rattle then there's no point</u>
<u n="932" who="S0679">we are selling them with <trunc>guarant</trunc> we're we're not selling er we aren't giving them away with the guarantee</u>
<u n="933" who="S0680">no <pause dur="short"/> but I mean we could just</u>
<u n="934" who="S0679">and some of them</u>
<u n="935" who="S0680" trans="overlap"><trunc>sh</trunc>shake a few</u>
<u n="936" who="S0679">yeah well I mean I went through them as much as I could bear</u>
<u n="937" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="938" who="S0679">and if you shake them too much I think you'll break them anyway</u>
<u n="939" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="940" who="S0679">so I mean it's a little self-defeating</u>
<u n="941" who="S0680" trans="overlap">they've got to stand a little bit of movement because of the er <pause dur="short"/> fact they're going to travel about</u>
<u n="942" who="S0679">are they?</u>
<u n="943" who="S0680">well somebody's gonna come and get them</u>
<u n="944" who="S0679">well yes yes but <unclear/> they're going to be yes once they've got them home and tested them they <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="945" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="946" who="S0679">may not travel</u>
<u n="947" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="948" who="S0679">so presumably if it's the same setup as <anon type="place"/> you put your ad up say this is what I've got I want it collected by X so I'll say Wednesday <pause dur="short"/> erm and</u>
<u n="949" who="S0680" trans="overlap"><trunc>s</trunc>so are they all erm white you know plain normal</u>
<u n="950" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="951" who="S0680">normal light</u>
<u n="952" who="S0679">about a third</u>
<u n="953" who="S0680" trans="overlap">reflectors? yes are they coloured reflectors?</u>
<u n="954" who="S0679">a few</u>
<u n="955" who="S0680" trans="overlap">or are they coloured light bulbs?</u>
<u n="956" who="S0679">er</u>
<u n="957" who="S0680">have you got some coloured light bulbs?</u>
<u n="958" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I've got four four sort of things but if we discount the</u>
<u n="959" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="960" who="S0679" trans="overlap">coloured light bulbs IE things</u>
<u n="961" who="S0680" trans="overlap">because I've got rid of quite a few er because er when I went to the tip last with you</u>
<u n="962" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="963" who="S0680">they hadn't emptied the light bulbs and there was</u>
<u n="964" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="965" who="S0680">erm an array of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="966" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="967" who="S0680">multicolour light bulbs</u>
<u n="968" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="969" who="S0680">erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> in on the end of the</u>
<u n="970" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="971" who="S0680">collection looking quite erm jolly</u>
<u n="972" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="973" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="974" who="S0679" trans="overlap">erm so discounting about half a dozen light bulbs which were coloured</u>
<u n="975" who="S0680" trans="overlap">right yes</u>
<u n="976" who="S0679" trans="overlap">which were in boxes that said reflectors largely</u>
<u n="977" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="978" who="S0679">apart from the ones that claim to be pearl light bulbs</u>
<u n="979" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="980" who="S0679">which obviously weren't</u>
<u n="981" who="S0680">you see the ones that</u>
<u n="982" who="S0679" trans="overlap">there's a there's three types there's coloured reflectors</u>
<u n="983" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="984" who="S0679">small white reflector small white reflector large</u>
<u n="985" who="S0680">yes because those light boxes that erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is going to take away</u>
<u n="986" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="987" who="S0680">have light bulbs in them which are light bulbs that would work</u>
<u n="988" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="989" who="S0680">but there's not a lot of point in taking them out unless somebody wants to stand and unscrew them all</u>
<u n="990" who="S0679">which are what are they? light large reflectors small reflectors?</u>
<u n="991" who="S0680">I would imagine they're probably ordinary light bulbs</u>
<u n="992" who="S0679">oh light bulbs okay well I think probably people <trunc>d</trunc> I don't know how much they use ordinary light bulbs</u>
<u n="993" who="S0680" trans="overlap">although they may have <trunc>alth</trunc> are all those are those reflectors all screw or</u>
<u n="994" who="S0679">I think they're all screw</u>
<u n="995" who="S0680" trans="overlap">bayonet?</u>
<u n="996" who="S0679">screw I think I don't think I found any bayonets</u>
<u n="997" who="S0680">right <pause dur="short"/> that cos that's another thing you need to put whether they're bayonet or screw</u>
<u n="998" who="S0679">yeah I think possibly they're always screw</u>
<u n="999" who="S0680">but the <pause dur="short"/> it's not something I use very much</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0679" trans="overlap">anyway if somebody's interested then we can have a more detailed conversation with them if necessary</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0680">yes what I mean is it's it's good deal to have actually have the answer</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0680">cos I hadn't thought about that</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0679">mm if we haven't got the answer we can find out</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0680">and we haven't got <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="1006" who="S0679" trans="overlap">it all seems a bit <trunc>lai</trunc> more laid-back than the erm <anon type="place"/> where you put an advert up and by the time you've sent it you've got three people</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0680">three phone calls</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0679" trans="overlap">phoning and saying</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0679">I'll come now or can I come now?</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0680">cos we might have to put some of those small speakers on on <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was gonna say on Freeview what am I talking about?</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0679">Freecycle</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0680" trans="overlap">Freecyle <vocal desc="laugh"/> yes</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0680">mm as well if nobody wants them</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0680">just to see if anybody wants to take them</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0679">have you got a phone number for that guy who's meant to be emailing us? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0680">he's the <anon type="place"/> branch</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah <trunc>ha</trunc> have you got his phone number?</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0680">I've got the <anon type="place"/> branch number</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well can you phone him up phone him up and ask if <trunc>h</trunc> if he received the email alright? and that'll remind him who you are and then you'll know if he's there or not and if he's got the email</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0680">right</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0679">cos we <trunc>mi</trunc> you'll until you know somebody's got an email you might be <trunc>w</trunc>waiting for a response for something that hasn't got to them</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0680">yes well that's what he told me to do to do er to get</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah but you know just contact him at</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0679">I can look the number up perhaps if you haven't got it</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0680">no I've got it on a piece of paper</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0679">yeah okay</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0680">on all of my lists over there</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0680">can't think of what else we might have been putting on Freecycle</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0679">well let's just let's just see how we go I don't know how dynamic it is here they seem to be going into quite a lot of detail with what's happened to things it's</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0680" trans="overlap">what they report do they?</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0679">well they they say when things are taken in a</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0680" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0679">like in <anon type="place"/> they just assume like just kind of assume I think</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0680">oh</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0679">you know so erm we'll see</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0680"><unclear>right</unclear></u>
<u n="1042" who="S0679">erm <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> you want to make some choices over the candles or do you want me to well you want to take out some candles and I'll take the rest to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0680">well I'll show you what there are just</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0679" trans="overlap">okay brilliant</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0680">cos erm cos they're like a plummy colour</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0680">or well whitey cream cream really I suppose</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0679">mm well you keep what you need for sure</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0680">well I haven't used any for years</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0679">mm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't like candles in his house so I don't tend to use them</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0679">but erm</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0680">well I don't</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0679">I might keep a couple of white ones because I have got actually got some <pause dur="short"/> I might you know I <trunc>m</trunc> life's been a bit difficult over the last few years so you know I haven't it's like I hadn't <vocal desc="laugh"/> gone round to finish my bag of radishes because</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0679">I hadn't got the like I was saying I haven't eaten any radishes and I haven't tended to bother with them because when I had got them I hadn't got them when I was at work I erm wasn't getting through you know I was</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0679">buying them and thinking I would eat them and being in too much hurry to do anything about them and then last year or the year I didn't think to ask anybody to put them in my shopping when I wasn't doing my own shopping</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0679">didn't think oh I fancy some radishes so there's things in life that I might quite like but have passed me by because either I was at work and hadn't got time to do it or was too poorly to be bothered with them I suppose</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0679" trans="overlap">or to think of them</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0679">but er I wouldn't mind some just white candles cos they can be quite nice</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0680">right well they're not white white cream</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0679">well I will review them <pause dur="short"/> but I'm trying not to collect too many things cos it's easy to think one would like things and then one finds life goes on perfectly well without them</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0680">yes I can't think of anything else that you were immediately going to <unclear/></u>
<u n="1068" who="S0679">okay well we can make a start on that and if you to perhaps get get hold of that chap see if he's around or his colleagues might know when he's <trunc>ne</trunc>next in work</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0680">well they said he was around for a fortnight</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0679">yes but he might not be even they might have let him have some days off</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0680">no but no I don't</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0680">he may</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0680">be going on holiday I don't know</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0680">it's all</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0679">and let me know if you want me to text actually not text I'm not good at texting if you want me to email <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for you</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0680">well I don't at the moment so I'll</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0679" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0680" trans="overlap">just send her a happy birthday</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0679">okay <pause dur="short"/> I'm just a bit worried if you send an email I mean there's pros and cons to it but</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0679">if you send an email she might email you back</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0680">I'll send an email</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0679" trans="overlap">which could encourage you to look at your email more but might not</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0680" trans="overlap">I've <trunc>sen</trunc> well I haven't had time to look at my email</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0679">no I know you've had a lot on</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0680">erm <pause dur="short"/> I shall <trunc>em</trunc> I <trunc>f</trunc> if I email her I can</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0680">write at the bottom <pause dur="short"/> to contact me via text or phone</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0680">which some of my neighbours know not to if they send me a text they if they send me an email they <trunc>s</trunc> usually tell me I've got one</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0680">text me to tell me to look at it now I did send <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> one a little while ago so whether she will now start emailing me I don't know</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0679">mm erm something to do later is look again at the email that came from that erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> chap</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0680"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> chap?</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0679">is it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0680"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0679">oh well anyway we'll sort it out later but</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0680"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1102" who="S0679" trans="overlap">the <trunc>o</trunc> thing we were talking about with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> those emails</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0680">oh right</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0679">yeah anyway</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes I don't think I've got all of those</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0679">no</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0680">but I <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="1108" who="S0679" trans="overlap">perhaps perhaps some came to me but anyway</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0680" trans="overlap">well no they wouldn't come <trunc>t</trunc></u>
<u n="1110" who="S0679" trans="overlap">we'll we'll look</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0680">no they wouldn't come to you unless they were talking about something in general the ones from him wouldn't have come to you</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0679">no no none of them came from him they always they all came via somebody else</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0679">but erm oh we need to look at the emails to be sure so erm <pause dur="short"/> do you want to give that person a ring in case they close early on Saturday?</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes well I can do some time</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0679">yeah okay <event desc="abrupt end"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
