<text id="SHK7">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:10:07</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-25</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0255 S0259</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's house</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Acquaintances</relationships>
		<topics>Spiders, mice, birds</topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0255">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Boston, Lincs</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Boston/London/Peterborough</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>account manager - sales</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0259">
				<exactage>42</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Peterborough</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Anglia</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>42</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Cleaner</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>7</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0255">you were saying what about spiders?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0259">oh yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0255">on the news</u>
<u n="4" who="S0259">yeah they were on the news yesterday I think it was yesterday or the day before about people taking photos of what they've found in their house</u>
<u n="5" who="S0255">oh right</u>
<u n="6" who="S0259">and some of em are like real big jet black ones</u>
<u n="7" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="8" who="S0259">and they were talking to the lady the weather lady and she was saying cos the weather's been so mild and not having a lot of rain</u>
<u n="9" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0259">they've been breeding and breeding and now it's getting cold</u>
<u n="11" who="S0255" trans="overlap">getting big er yeah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0259">they're looking for somewhere but she said they are</u>
<u n="13" who="S0255">big</u>
<u n="14" who="S0259">quite big</u>
<u n="15" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0255">and I know normally when they <trunc>cu</trunc></u>
<u n="18" who="S0259">horrible</u>
<u n="19" who="S0255">when they cut all the harvest ones you get all the ones</u>
<u n="20" who="S0259">mm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0255">that come in from there don't you?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0259">from the fields yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0255">all the all the big ones from there</u>
<u n="24" who="S0259">and mice <vocal desc="laugh"/> they start running about don't they?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0259">cos been living in there all year ain't they?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0255">yeah well we had erm it was a few weeks ago I I was just going to bed went in looked in the en suite bit and there was one almost as big as your hand and it was just it was big brown big thick brown legs and it it was just sat in the middle of the bathroom floor thing and I looked and I thought that's er</u>
<u n="28" who="S0259">what? in the bath? or?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0255">no no actually it was just on the floor and I thought</u>
<u n="30" who="S0259" trans="overlap">oh god no I would've died</u>
<u n="31" who="S0255">that that's a really big spider and I thought okay I'm gonna get it out and normally I'll just get a spider I'll just get it with my hand and take it outside</u>
<u n="32" who="S0259">oh no I can't do that</u>
<u n="33" who="S0255">and and put it <trunc>outs</trunc> doesn't normally bother me but one that big I thought yeah actually it <trunc>pr</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> it'll <trunc>pro</trunc></u>
<u n="34" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0255">I might be aware I'd got that in my hand so I just I thought I know I'm gonna get erm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0259">oh</u>
<u n="37" who="S0255">what shall I get? and I thought <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got a spider catcher thingy that er like you can get the handle</u>
<u n="38" who="S0259" trans="overlap">yeah but it's only little it's not a big one is it?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0255">oh it was</u>
<u n="40" who="S0259">it's a plastic thing is it?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0255">you you get this like a it's a long stick and you hold the handle it's like something that you use to pick stuff up with and so and</u>
<u n="42" who="S0259" trans="overlap">oh I've seen that in there</u>
<u n="43" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0259">yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0255">yeah and er and it's like erm wire nylony wire prongy things on the end</u>
<u n="46" who="S0259">and you just grab it?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0255">so yeah you just get hold and it just gets hold of it like that so</u>
<u n="48" who="S0259"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0255">I thought oh I'll go and say so I went through to her and said can I borrow your spider pick thingy? she said have you got a spider? I said yeah it's absolutely huge I said I just</u>
<u n="50" who="S0259"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0255">I just don't wanna pick it up I'm gonna get it with this <trunc>spi</trunc> so she told me where I was and as I was just walking back with it I thought I bet it's moved and I got back in it had gone <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="52" who="S0259">oh no so it's still in there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0255">yeah although it's probably gone under the bath or something cos that that panel's missing yeah so</u>
<u n="54" who="S0259" trans="overlap">yeah oh they do that don't they? oh it is ain't it?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0255">and er not seen it since I thought I should've put something over it</u>
<u n="56" who="S0259" trans="overlap"><unclear>well I ain't seen it</unclear> today</u>
<u n="57" who="S0255">oh no this was weeks ago this was weeks ago so I'm I'm sure it's probably quite happy living</u>
<u n="58" who="S0259" trans="overlap">oh I know I I had one like that in my bath the other day and I just took er put a conker in the plughole</u>
<u n="59" who="S0255">oh right</u>
<u n="60" who="S0259">cos they come they're coming up through the plugholes ain't they?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0259">up the drains I don't know how they get up there</u>
<u n="63" who="S0255">why don't you just put the plug in the plughole?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0259">well I do that but the boys have showers</u>
<u n="65" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0259">where they just and the shower's over the bath</u>
<u n="67" who="S0255">right</u>
<u n="68" who="S0259">so they just unplug it</u>
<u n="69" who="S0255">oh yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0259">and don't plug it back in</u>
<u n="71" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0259"><trunc>s</trunc>so my mum gave me a <vocal desc="laugh"/> load of conkers she said just <trunc>p</trunc> scatter them around the corners of your house which I have done cos they reckon that that's <trunc>chest</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc>something with the chestnut</u>
<u n="73" who="S0255">oh right</u>
<u n="74" who="S0259">keeps them away yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0255">does it?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0259">you can actually buy a chestnut spray like erm er</u>
<u n="77" who="S0255">really?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0259">yeah and you know and just go round like spray on your windows</u>
<u n="79" who="S0255">oh right</u>
<u n="80" who="S0259">so when you have em open in the summer and that</u>
<u n="81" who="S0255">and then don't come on</u>
<u n="82" who="S0259">spray them on your ledges and it keeps em away supposed to so I've done that</u>
<u n="83" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0259">and see if it works</u>
<u n="85" who="S0255">yeah you'll have to let me know</u>
<u n="86" who="S0259" trans="overlap"><unclear/> in the plughole yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0255">put one in the plughole <vocal desc="laugh"/> it'll er come up and go <vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0259">round the corners of the house cos my back door's constantly</u>
<u n="89" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0259">open and shutting</u>
<u n="91" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0259">because of the dog she likes to go in there</u>
<u n="93" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0259">through the summer it's just left open all the time up to about probably half past nine at night</u>
<u n="95" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0259">and then I think well I <trunc>s</trunc> I'd better shut that now</u>
<u n="97" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0259">do you know what I mean? so anything could've popped over <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0255">oh know when we</u>
<u n="100" who="S0259">so</u>
<u n="101" who="S0255">when we were building the extension we got we had mice when we were first building this bit</u>
<u n="102" who="S0259">mm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0255">on the back here and we just in the end we got overrun and we didn't know how they were getting in and they were just breeding and breeding and breeding</u>
<u n="104" who="S0259">oh god</u>
<u n="105" who="S0255">and we actually had them so they were running round the house and it was <trunc>r</trunc>it was ridiculous you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was there with a</u>
<u n="106" who="S0259" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="107" who="S0255">with a walking stick trying to get them and oh it was really funny</u>
<u n="108" who="S0259"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's like that's like pied piper <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0255">I know and it was it was because she was like <vocal desc="misc"/> you could hear it and it was just so every time you had to do anything any cooking or anything you had to like <trunc>wi</trunc> disinfect all the tops</u>
<u n="110" who="S0259">oh god</u>
<u n="111" who="S0255">and all the cooker and all the just <trunc>c</trunc> er</u>
<u n="112" who="S0259">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0255">it was absolutely ridiculous erm first of all we started off with the live traps cos we were all all being very good er we'll get the live traps</u>
<u n="114" who="S0259"><unclear/> yeah and chuck them back out</u>
<u n="115" who="S0255">so we'd be <trunc>c</trunc> we'd catch them and then chucking them out and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said but however they're getting in they're just coming back in</u>
<u n="116" who="S0259">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0255">so then we started we'd drive round round the corner to near where the electricity pylon bits are round near <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0259">oh right</u>
<u n="119" who="S0255">and we used to drive round there with all these traps with all the mice and let them all out and go go free little mice go free</u>
<u n="120" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0255">and after about another week or so we were just totally overrun <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was sort of okay we've given them a chance you know we've</u>
<u n="122" who="S0259">mm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0255">we've taken er so then we started putting traps down</u>
<u n="124" who="S0259">had to really yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0255">erm but even then we were just there were so many erm we actually found out it was when the extension was built the the the old gas pipe they'd put a new one in new gas pipe in</u>
<u n="126" who="S0259" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0255">and where the old gas pipe thing went out it was only a little tiny hole</u>
<u n="128" who="S0259" trans="overlap">but they were living in it</u>
<u n="129" who="S0255">but they hadn't yeah they hadn't actually erm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0259">oh sorry it's my phone</u>
<u n="131" who="S0255">hadn't actually blocked it up <pause dur="short"/> yeah so they hadn't blocked it up so they were coming in there so we just put a load of foam like you know the foamy stuff? that that</u>
<u n="132" who="S0259">oh right yeah blocked it up yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0255">yeah and did that and we never had er any more problems once we'd got rid of them all</u>
<u n="134" who="S0259">they get through the tiniest holes don't they?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0259">cos I used to live erm as you go where are we? yeah as you go towards the windmill just past the windmill</u>
<u n="137" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0259">on the same side as me I used to live in a house there that I used to rent</u>
<u n="139" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0259">and we used to have loads of em</u>
<u n="141" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0259">absolutely <trunc>m</trunc> the tops of my cupboards when I first moved in</u>
<u n="143" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0259">I thought right I'll go round and clean they were</u>
<u n="145" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="146" who="S0259">flooded with drops</u>
<u n="147" who="S0255">yeah?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0259">droppings from <trunc>w</trunc> you know and I'm like oh my god and like you know like where your pipes run through the floor?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0259">from your your radiators</u>
<u n="151" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0259">and you got like the bit that goes round the carpet?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah little gap yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0259">they were popping their heads through there and I'm like right they're under the floorboards</u>
<u n="155" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0259">how are they getting in there? and we sat there <trunc>w</trunc> and so I set traps and everything I got loads of em</u>
<u n="157" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0259">and er we sat there one night and we could hear this almighty running around and going what the hell is that?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0259">and it was a rat</u>
<u n="161" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0259">or maybe more than one that'd got under the floorboards and was running up between the walls</u>
<u n="163" who="S0255">oh my gosh</u>
<u n="164" who="S0259">yeah so I I called the landlord</u>
<u n="165" who="S0255">we used to hear them in the in the loft</u>
<u n="166" who="S0259">yeah horrible</u>
<u n="167" who="S0255"><vocal desc="misc"/> like that you could hear them</u>
<u n="168" who="S0259">I called the landlord</u>
<u n="169" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0259">he put traps down never caught anything</u>
<u n="171" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="172" who="S0259">and then I got <trunc>m</trunc>my Jack Russell</u>
<u n="173" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0259">and one night I was sitting there in the living room she was <unclear/> down the carpet</u>
<u n="175" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0259">and I'm going what's she doing?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0259">and she kept going cos I had a sliding patio door leading out to the garden</u>
<u n="179" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0259">in the living room she kept standing at the corner there and I'm like oh she may as well go outside</u>
<u n="181" who="S0255">yeah she <trunc>di</trunc></u>
<u n="182" who="S0259">but as jumped out</u>
<u n="183" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0259">she just used to <unclear>dig</unclear></u>
<u n="185" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0259"><trunc>scra</trunc> er like that</u>
<u n="187" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0259">right next to so one day I laid flat</u>
<u n="189" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0259">on the patio</u>
<u n="191" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0259">and looked underneath and there was a hole like that</u>
<u n="193" who="S0255">ah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0259">underneath the patio door it was about two brick thick</u>
<u n="195" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0259">and they were missing</u>
<u n="197" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0259">and <trunc>undernea</trunc> I got a <trunc>tor</trunc></u>
<u n="199" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0259">and you could see all the floorboards</u>
<u n="201" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0259">you could see where the rats had been going in and out where they'd been catching themselves</u>
<u n="203" who="S0255">oh my word</u>
<u n="204" who="S0259">cos there's like bits of fur</u>
<u n="205" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0259">and that's where they're all getting in</u>
<u n="207" who="S0255">goodness</u>
<u n="208" who="S0259">yeah and if it weren't from my dog</u>
<u n="209" who="S0255" trans="overlap">so did you did you block it up then?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0259">yeah blocked it up</u>
<u n="211" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0259">and never had no more problems</u>
<u n="213" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0259">and if it weren't for my little</u>
<u n="215" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0259">Jack Russell</u>
<u n="217" who="S0255">well yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0259">I'd probably never've found where they were getting in</u>
<u n="219" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="220" who="S0259">unbelievable</u>
<u n="221" who="S0255">no I I it's only only takes like two to get in and they breed don't they? so much</u>
<u n="222" who="S0259">oh that's it it's horrible it's <unclear>scary</unclear> listening to em it's <unclear>gross</unclear></u>
<u n="223" who="S0255" trans="overlap">well we started erm we were talking about what we were gonna put down and we were put we were on about putting the erm you know you can put the poison down?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0259">mm</u>
<u n="225" who="S0255">cos it <trunc>w</trunc>it was getting that bad we were thinking we're gonna have to do something but my brother was saying if you put the poison down they eat it and they tend then they go outside and then they die outside and birds eat the mice</u>
<u n="226" who="S0259">right</u>
<u n="227" who="S0255">and then the birds get poisoned because they've got the poison in the mice</u>
<u n="228" who="S0259" trans="overlap">oh that's no good</u>
<u n="229" who="S0255">so he said that's it's</u>
<u n="230" who="S0259">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0255">you know he he said he always says to people not to do that</u>
<u n="232" who="S0259">cos I used I used them little bait boxes</u>
<u n="233" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0259">with a little hole in and they used to go in em</u>
<u n="235" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0259">but they say then they go back to the nest</u>
<u n="237" who="S0255">to the nest yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0259">and feed their little ones</u>
<u n="239" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0259">and that's what kills em</u>
<u n="241" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0259">never think about birds <unclear/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0255">no well that's he said that because he's <trunc>re</trunc> I mean he's a huge huge carp fisherman</u>
<u n="244" who="S0259">that's not good is it? so</u>
<u n="245" who="S0255">he's been and he spends loads of time out by the lakes and he's really into all birds and trees and you know all that sort of stuff but he said people don't think you think oh yeah you just kill them off he said but actually he said quite a lot of them they'll be going in and out and doing other stuff</u>
<u n="246" who="S0259">oh <unclear/> yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0255">and then the bird catches them and yeah all</u>
<u n="248" who="S0259">that ain't no that good killing off birds <unclear/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no that that's it that's what he said so I thought oh</u>
<u n="250" who="S0259">don't see seem to see that many now do we?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="252" who="S0259">not the starlings and blackbirds but</u>
<u n="253" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0259">you don't get many of the others any more</u>
<u n="255" who="S0255">we found with with having that bird food all out there now cos I mean we're <trunc>s</trunc>we're sort of filling it up all the time now we get I mean the starlings come a couple of times a day the young ones they always come</u>
<u n="256" who="S0259">mm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0255">in fact the mums come with the baby starlings and actually feed them from it so then the baby starlings as they're getting bigger they all come on their own it's like the teenagers squabbling all over</u>
<u n="258" who="S0259" trans="overlap">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0255">so they come we get blackbirds erm er sparrows like there there's just the standard seed that we put</u>
<u n="260" who="S0259">mm</u>
<u n="261" who="S0255">the sparrows really like that and again the young ones come with the mums and then the they keep coming we get blue tits erm goldfinches chaffinches</u>
<u n="262" who="S0259">yeah <unclear>nice</unclear></u>
<u n="263" who="S0255">blue yeah blue tits I said blue tits which so we get er quite a little thing</u>
<u n="264" who="S0259">mm</u>
<u n="265" who="S0255">and some of the little finches as well a lot of em go into <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> next door she puts loads of different stuff out</u>
<u n="266" who="S0259">oh right</u>
<u n="267" who="S0255">always has done she gets all sorts of all sorts of ones there</u>
<u n="268" who="S0259" trans="overlap">when I when I used to live up there I used to have them all out in my garden</u>
<u n="269" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="270" who="S0259">cos the bloke I was with at the time he just loved to do mm <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>f</trunc> he was a fishing man</u>
<u n="271" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0259">so he set things up like that in the garden we used to get all sorts come in</u>
<u n="273" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0259">cos at the back of us it's just an empty field</u>
<u n="275" who="S0255">right</u>
<u n="276" who="S0259">but now they've built where they've built them houses now</u>
<u n="277" who="S0255">okay</u>
<u n="278" who="S0259">and it</u>
<u n="279" who="S0255">oh is that that college?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0259" trans="overlap">yeah what's it called? opposite the college</u>
<u n="281" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0259">yeah <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0255">okay</u>
<u n="284" who="S0259">and it used to be just open field</u>
<u n="285" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0259">and er</u>
<u n="287" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0259">cos my garden's quite long at the bottom it had a gate</u>
<u n="289" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="290" who="S0259">and if you left the gate open sometimes you used to get the odd muntjac deer</u>
<u n="291" who="S0255">oh really?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0259">pop in the garden</u>
<u n="293" who="S0255">oh that's lovely</u>
<u n="294" who="S0259">the boys used to sit at the bedroom window watching it</u>
<u n="295" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0259">but of course now they've built on there ain't they? so</u>
<u n="297" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="298" who="S0259">yeah it goes right back to Ikea</u>
<u n="299" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0259">where Ikea so it's just all</u>
<u n="301" who="S0255">yeah open and mm</u>
<u n="302" who="S0259">open field yeah so we just get all sorts coming in there <vocal desc="laugh"/> but er yeah as I say nice bit of land then they stick a house on it don't they?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0255">mm well that's what they always do though isn't it?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0259">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0255">so mm</u>
<u n="306" who="S0259">er</u>
<u n="307" who="S0255">okay</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
