<text id="SHSL">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:57:11</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-15</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0018 S0073</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Birmingham</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Flatmates, family, local areas, work, pubs, injuries and health, films, plans for the evening</topics>
		<activity>Friends having a cup of tea together.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, apologizing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0073">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Solihull, West Midlands</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Urdu -- Advanced; French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0018"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/> What is post codeism?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0018">post codeism is something that I read on a mate's website <pause dur="short"/> he does like anti youth violence and um we did a track once called you're bigger than your post code <pause dur="short"/> because it was all about</u>
<u n="4" who="S0073">was that the B side to Halal what is meat you're looking for?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0018" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> this is one before Halal <vocal desc="laugh"/> It was like um when we did all the anti war war and error stuff and post codeism is a word I read um a couple of weeks ago on this youth violence thing because it's basically I would imagine you know kind of relating specifically to your endz endz again</u>
<u n="6" who="S0073">uh huh</u>
<u n="7" who="S0018">E N D Z</u>
<u n="8" who="S0073">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0018">um and and having that as your manner <pause dur="short"/> it's that whole kind of you're territorialism</u>
<u n="10" who="S0073">okay</u>
<u n="11" who="S0018">kind of thing like the crypts and bloods and so on all in gangs and so on and its like you're not from around here are you bloke? And he's like</u>
<u n="12" who="S0073">are you local?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0018" trans="overlap">are you local? Yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> it's exactly the same thing <pause dur="short"/> are you local? You're not <trunc>lo</trunc> you're not from around here are you? <vocal desc="laugh"/> So it's basically what's happening in the ghetto's uh rather than in uh the countryside and farmers Cornwall <pause dur="short"/> so um people get beaten up for not being in the right area and that's why I think post codeism is or feeling as though you just exist within a certain area <pause dur="short"/> and if you try and go outside of it you're somehow you know you're under <trunc>thre</trunc> anyway it's all bullshit <pause dur="short"/> um so that's that was a new word that uh uh I don't know about any other words really <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> You can just talk I suppose <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0073">well I like this post code <pause dur="short"/> I'm enjoying living in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0018">yeah?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0073">it's great fun</u>
<u n="17" who="S0018">how's the house yeah?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0073">yeah super <pause dur="short"/> it's such a</u>
<u n="19" who="S0018">like Hollyoaks <pause dur="short"/> it's like Hollyoaks isn't it?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No actually <pause dur="short"/> I mean the only parts I really socialise with is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the house <pause dur="short"/> cos the boys are hardly ever there</u>
<u n="21" who="S0018">they're off biking</u>
<u n="22" who="S0073">and uh hmm biking and climbing and wooing ladies <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="23" who="S0018">Good luck with that <pause dur="short"/> that's both look like fucking <vocal desc="laugh"/> I shouldn't record this actually should I?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0073">mind your language <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0018">oh they're lovely <trunc>g</trunc> they're nice guys actually <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>da</trunc> I have to say this now <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are lovely guys <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um now I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been uh scopeing for a while</u>
<u n="26" who="S0073">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he went out on a date with a girl he met online the other night? And Friday night he did have</u>
<u n="27" who="S0018">I would imagine she would have to be online <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't imagine any other kind of spark really</u>
<u n="28" who="S0073">no but he <trunc>act</trunc></u>
<u n="29" who="S0018">does he switch off the lights when you go to work? I hope you do <pause dur="short"/> my name is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> by the way <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s a bit <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s just like you know oozing that upper class kind of uh you know South African kind of yeah yeah no I uh</u>
<u n="30" who="S0073">I'm chilled</u>
<u n="31" who="S0018"><trunc>Some</trunc> sometimes I have to go back to South Africa that's it <pause dur="short"/> that's where I live yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um</u>
<u n="32" who="S0073">Dan sent me a text message um he <trunc>do</trunc> he does bless him he's so anal <pause dur="short"/> he</u>
<u n="33" who="S0018">oh he's ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> but I <trunc>lo</trunc> I love him for it <pause dur="short"/> I think there's some bits where he's actually right</u>
<u n="34" who="S0073" trans="overlap">yeah true</u>
<u n="35" who="S0018">Cos uh <trunc>h</trunc> he <trunc>do</trunc> he doesn't just do it to piss people off he is actually right some of the time</u>
<u n="36" who="S0073">he sent me a message on the Sunday and it was actually the first week I'd moved in <pause dur="short"/> the first weekend and I thought oh no he <trunc>tra</trunc> he phoned <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to find out what my number was</u>
<u n="37" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh my god</u>
<u n="38" who="S0073">and I was really worried cos I was with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like <trunc>wh</trunc> what does he want my number for?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0018">what's he stalking me for?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0073">no <pause dur="short"/> no he's not stalking and I thought I'd set the house on fire or something or left the water running or something and um no he sent me a text message saying oh no it's just a reminder saying just to remind you I know I'll probably see you but can you leave five pounds out for the gardener on Wednesday? <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's like just <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0018">God</u>
<u n="42" who="S0073">there's forward planning for you</u>
<u n="43" who="S0018">why don't you just pay and I'll give you the five pounds back? <vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh no we've done that before <vocal desc="laugh"/> it all ends in tears</u>
<u n="44" who="S0073">it doesn't work</u>
<u n="45" who="S0018">look at all that dust</u>
<u n="46" who="S0073">yes</u>
<u n="47" who="S0018">that's disgusting isn't it?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0073">human skin apparently</u>
<u n="49" who="S0018">ah shit <vocal desc="laugh"/> How's uh big tits?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0073">ah you're evil <pause dur="short"/> how she is <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0018">that's what they are <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't think we should skate around the subject <vocal desc="laugh"/> They're cans <pause dur="short"/> they're hooters <pause dur="short"/> they're just jugs and they</u>
<u n="52" who="S0073">okay enough</u>
<u n="53" who="S0018">they're expanded jugs they're extended jugs</u>
<u n="54" who="S0073">yes <pause dur="short"/> um she's</u>
<u n="55" who="S0018">sorry I was just</u>
<u n="56" who="S0073" trans="overlap">she's</u>
<u n="57" who="S0018">trying to think of other words <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously we're doing the word thing <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> So we could do</u>
<u n="58" who="S0073">no no I think</u>
<u n="59" who="S0018">we could go and do loads</u>
<u n="60" who="S0073">I think that's</u>
<u n="61" who="S0018">no I think that's got to be enough</u>
<u n="62" who="S0073">I think we've got enough there</u>
<u n="63" who="S0018">you've got enough there</u>
<u n="64" who="S0073">to put in</u>
<u n="65" who="S0018">mummy <pause dur="short"/> no never mind</u>
<u n="66" who="S0073">she's fine <pause dur="short"/> she did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> tell you about her multiple men manipulation?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0018">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> well the thing is I really like um well what's his name? Well I used to really like what's his name? What's he's <trunc>g</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0073">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh my god</u>
<u n="69" who="S0018">Cos <trunc>y</trunc> cos I've got I got on quite well with him brother on <pause dur="short"/> cos basically we started we were in a pub and he's kinda I think he's half Turkish</u>
<u n="70" who="S0073">he <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0018">or half Indian or something</u>
<u n="72" who="S0073">I don't know whether it was he's half Irish half half Egyptian</u>
<u n="73" who="S0018">something ethnic</u>
<u n="74" who="S0073">egyptian</u>
<u n="75" who="S0018">something dirty brown and ethnic <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="76" who="S0073">you are such a <trunc>r</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> rude rude</u>
<u n="77" who="S0018">I'm Asian by the way whoever's listening to this I am so I can kind of get I don't know if I can <pause dur="short"/> uh um but let's just say I can <pause dur="short"/> um yeah because I met him at a pub and um he's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I'm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and we started talking about Chris Morris's four lions <pause dur="short"/> cos there's a brother <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and a brother <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0073">really?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0018">in four lions <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think brother <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> blows himself up and brother <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says he's gonna blow up the internet <pause dur="short"/> um but uh yeah so I thought he's alright <pause dur="short"/> but it sounds like he's a bit of a like <trunc>he</trunc> he's just after the shag isn't he really?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0073">he's a bad white boy</u>
<u n="81" who="S0018">I think all of it I think she's just like I think she just needs to stop being so um I don't know kinda uh of um</u>
<u n="82" who="S0073">well</u>
<u n="83" who="S0018">ditzy</u>
<u n="84" who="S0073">well Katie described her very well <trunc>sh</trunc> as wagish</u>
<u n="85" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0073">she's a wag</u>
<u n="87" who="S0018">she's a  wag <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>Sh</trunc> she actually needs to live in Solihul I think <vocal desc="laugh"/> which is actually where she's from</u>
<u n="88" who="S0073">she's from <anon type="place"/> which is even</u>
<u n="89" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0073">more sterile less society to come from</u>
<u n="91" who="S0018">completely so she <trunc>need</trunc> I think that she needs to uh</u>
<u n="92" who="S0073">populated by all the <trunc>fo</trunc> flashy footballers <pause dur="short"/> there you go a wag</u>
<u n="93" who="S0018">she needs to get yeah she does she needs to get back with the program <pause dur="short"/> it's <trunc>wei</trunc> it's weird  it's weird  people from <anon type="place"/> think that <anon type="place"/> is like Milan <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0073">no but wait there <pause dur="short"/> you're from <anon type="place"/> and I'm from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0018">I don't think that it's like Milan</u>
<u n="96" who="S0073">we both know the Welsh translation pig sty</u>
<u n="97" who="S0018">pig sty</u>
<u n="98" who="S0073">is more appropriate</u>
<u n="99" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's like New York Paris London <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="100" who="S0073">the costa del <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0018">God <pause dur="short"/> awful <pause dur="short"/> just thinking about it makes you <trunc>scr</trunc> I'm trying to get my mum and dad to move out but</u>
<u n="102" who="S0073">hmm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0018">they've been there all their lives and they've yeah there's no way there's going to leave it <pause dur="short"/> I don't think</u>
<u n="104" who="S0073">well I guess it must be nice to for their purposes</u>
<u n="105" who="S0018">no it's</u>
<u n="106" who="S0073">if you've got like a nice little middle class retirement</u>
<u n="107" who="S0018"><trunc>Y</trunc> Yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0073">it's quite</u>
<u n="109" who="S0018">yeah they no they've got a nice quite a large house that it's a <trunc>deta</trunc> it's a detached house so it's you know it's good for them and you know it's they've worked all their lives for it <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="110" who="S0073">yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0018"><unclear/> It's different for them for us for me it's different and I'm I'm middle class they're working class so it's uh <pause dur="short"/> well I'm working <trunc>mid</trunc> I'm working middle class <pause dur="short"/> I was working class now I am middle class and I'm aspiring to be a well you know aspiring to be <trunc>m</trunc> married you know someone in the royal family hopefully</u>
<u n="112" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Princess <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0018">princess <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> oh oh god exactly <pause dur="short"/> I mean I am already married to kind of like some kind of weird Solihillion mix <vocal desc="laugh"/> she she like kind of south <pause dur="short"/> ah I shouldn't say this she's from south <unclear/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0073">she's from <anon type="place"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0018">ooh yeah <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0073">is that the eh <trunc>Lo</trunc> London equivalent of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0018">I think it's the Asian equivalent of <anon type="place"/> probably <pause dur="short"/> it's the only kind of no they're other no there are no I think it is actually yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's probably the largest conurbation of middle class Asian people but having said you you've got Wembley and London is weird isn't it? You've got kind of bits of north London Wembley um I don't know <pause dur="short"/> you know it would be interesting to find out where the poshest Asian place is <pause dur="short"/> I don't think there are many <pause dur="short"/> I think there's just like kind of like you know <trunc>m</trunc> majority are ghettos</u>
<u n="118" who="S0073">have you</u>
<u n="119" who="S0018" trans="overlap">I don't think there'll be eh</u>
<u n="120" who="S0073">do you live in London?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0018">for on and off <pause dur="short"/> for about six months a year but that's cos my my girlfriend lived there after college but uh I can't do London after three <pause dur="short"/> I I I've tried convincing myself that it would be nice to make a move <pause dur="short"/> I need to get it out of my system <pause dur="short"/> probably will do it for a year at some point just just for a a laugh <vocal desc="laugh"/> But I I <trunc>c</trunc> can't see myself doing it for like uh for life</u>
<u n="122" who="S0073">hmm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0018">Cos <anon type="place"/> is the best place to be <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="124" who="S0073">do you really think so?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0018">I think so <pause dur="short"/> I've I've thought about it quite a lot <pause dur="short"/> I mean if I had the opportunity to live elsewhere I would take it but that's you know everyone says that <pause dur="short"/> but unfortunately that's down to economics</u>
<u n="126" who="S0073">uh hmm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0018">if you want to have a second home somewhere good luck cos you'll be working all your life doing it <pause dur="short"/> if you're a very rich person <vocal desc="cough"/> or you enjoy shit loads of money then you can uh you know I suppose you can afford to live anywhere and good luck to you <pause dur="short"/> but when you've got family responsibilities when you've got you know like me I've an ageing grandfather I've got an <trunc>ol</trunc> old getting old mum and dad I have a family business and the thing is that I I say that those things are are important <pause dur="short"/> they're also very practical as well</u>
<u n="128" who="S0073">hmm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0018">I mean I gain a lot of privilege from having family business <pause dur="short"/> uh they're a pain in the ass as well <vocal desc="laugh"/> But if yeah I mean potentially it would be nice just to do London for a bit <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/>'s great because it's got largest amounts of um uh I suppose Asian people black people within you know kind of the west midlands <pause dur="short"/> it's been home for my granddad my dad and me uh</u>
<u n="130" who="S0073">was your dad born in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> he came over when he was sixteen? Fifteen sixteen?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0073">oh <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="133" who="S0018">um so in that way it's kind of yeah and also Brum's home I suppose <pause dur="short"/> but don't get me wrong I mean if I  if I  had the moneys I I'd you know I'd go to Barcelona or Valencia at the drop of a hat</u>
<u n="134" who="S0073">hmm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0018">easily <pause dur="short"/> easily as you would probably you know</u>
<u n="136" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Definitely</u>
<u n="137" who="S0018">uh or or South of France or you know anything Mediterranean like I've got two friends now <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s in Valencia another friend is in Porto</u>
<u n="138" who="S0073">do you reckon <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is there to stay?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0018"><trunc>I</trunc> <trunc>y</trunc> the thing is you can't hold <trunc>Sh</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is a very strange boy he's not <trunc>ve</trunc> he's not all there really</u>
<u n="140" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You are so</u>
<u n="141" who="S0018">he's not all there <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't give much away and he doesn't tell many people much stuff but you know I I I don't at the moment I don't really think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I don't know his what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants so I think he's just trying to be happy and that's and he can afford it <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>h</trunc> he's got a good enough job to be able to do that <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't think he'll stay there forever uh</u>
<u n="142" who="S0073">how come he can do his job from Valencia?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0018">Cos I think a lot of the stuff that he does is correspondence and because he's learnt how to um take certain kind of classes or or teach certain excuse me certain classes to do with uh um you know <trunc>con</trunc> conflict resolution and and so on very kind of I think  I think  once you've  once you've  got kind of a model down for um you know what conflict resolution is or or what you know uh you know kind of uh poverty um uh global development or anti-poverty stuff <pause dur="short"/> once you've got those kind of things down you can just apply to you know a specific geography and go well right this country's got these problems so a person from whoever beware of this beware of that conflict resolution is about X Y and Z thank you very much <pause dur="short"/> I'll take three thousand pounds for that lesson</u>
<u n="144" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0018">or or whatever</u>
<u n="146" who="S0073">blimey is that <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> no I don't know no no no I don't want to cast aspersions cos I don't really know but I would imagine it's not a fucking peanuts <pause dur="short"/> I would imagine it's like fucking proper <vocal desc="laugh"/> Can I say fuck?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0073">mind your Ps and Qs</u>
<u n="149" who="S0018">sorry</u>
<u n="150" who="S0073">no you can't</u>
<u n="151" who="S0018">sorry person listening <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0073">well that kind of blimey no wonder you're going to live in Valencia</u>
<u n="153" who="S0018">I was going to swear then I won't but</u>
<u n="154" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/> There was me with my twenty euros an hour English teaching</u>
<u n="155" who="S0018">well the thing is you know what easy come easy go <pause dur="short"/> some people just you know some people are able to no matter what they do kind of wangle things</u>
<u n="156" who="S0073">hmm</u>
<u n="157" who="S0018">and it's normally people who are actually very very fucking cunning</u>
<u n="158" who="S0073">uh hmm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0018">who are able to do that <pause dur="short"/> uh I don't mind saying that about any of my mate <pause dur="short"/> I have to be cunning now and again <pause dur="short"/> we all have to be cunning but I think it's always the ones who are slightly you know kind of a bit more uh you know a bit more cunning <trunc>wh</trunc> who end up warning the mullah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0073">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0018">it's about training yourself I suppose to be able to to have that <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit of an unsaid rule isn't it? No one likes talking about it but it's true for the wankers who kind of real like real fucking wankers who make shit loads of fucking cash</u>
<u n="162" who="S0073"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0018">oh shit</u>
<u n="164" who="S0073">mind your language</u>
<u n="165" who="S0018">language <vocal desc="laugh"/> Sorry again <pause dur="short"/> oi slang is part of</u>
<u n="166" who="S0073">true <pause dur="short"/> true true true</u>
<u n="167" who="S0018">language you know um</u>
<u n="168" who="S0073">but it's not just slang it's uh expletive</u>
<u n="169" who="S0018">expletives</u>
<u n="170" who="S0073">slang</u>
<u n="171" who="S0018">it is nonetheless</u>
<u n="172" who="S0073">rude boy</u>
<u n="173" who="S0018">that's very bad</u>
<u n="174" who="S0073">you're a rude boy</u>
<u n="175" who="S0018">that's very bad</u>
<u n="176" who="S0073">so how's the family business going? Is are you pretty much?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0018">it's good touch wood <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0073">are you pretty much taking over?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I'm step back</u>
<u n="180" who="S0073">hmm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0018">I've taken that's why I take two days off now a week <pause dur="short"/> because it's just been exasperating just kind of trying to get through like the last four five years it's just like I literally had to get away because psychologically it was just doing me damage</u>
<u n="182" who="S0073">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0018">because it's just too much it's like every fucking <pause dur="short"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> every day coming in you know same old you know kind of <trunc>li</trunc> I didn't have a job description <pause dur="short"/> it's basically like you know you come in and you do what I say</u>
<u n="184" who="S0073">hmm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0018">and living like that <pause dur="short"/> working like that is not <pause dur="short"/> it's actually you know de educated me <pause dur="short"/> is that a word? Uneducated me through a period of time because I've learned all of these different kinds of structures and you know kind of how to work within management structure work within an environment</u>
<u n="186" who="S0073">uh hmm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0018">then you <trunc>w</trunc> worked walk into a family business and it's</u>
<u n="188" who="S0073">chaos</u>
<u n="189" who="S0018">perhaps with the chaos it's like you will do what I say when I say it</u>
<u n="190" who="S0073">is it your dad?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0073">in control</u>
<u n="193" who="S0018">that's your job and um and even though he <trunc>doe</trunc> I think he doesn't know about management <pause dur="short"/> he's never worked in a management structure he's a <trunc>sa</trunc> you know he's a <trunc>we</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> he's a self-made man <pause dur="short"/> so I've kind of tried to instil it but I've with the four years I've tried to do it I've just given up <pause dur="short"/> I just thought right when you're ready or when you're older and I can overpower you <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'll wait until then <pause dur="short"/> until then I'm gonna bugger off air and just do my own thing <pause dur="short"/> so uh yeah I'm doing two days a week and just doing my own like you know just bits of music we're doing a hopefully soon uh me and eh Toff on <trunc>in</trunc> inter-generational eh relationships within the South Asian diaspora of the west midlands</u>
<u n="194" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Sounds very serious</u>
<u n="195" who="S0018">it is</u>
<u n="196" who="S0073">I'm sure the project isn't going to be that <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure you're going to pepper it with uh expletives</u>
<u n="197" who="S0018">oh no no</u>
<u n="198" who="S0073">and silliness and funnyness</u>
<u n="199" who="S0018">I'm sure that I'm sure there'll be plenty of expletives</u>
<u n="200" who="S0073">so</u>
<u n="201" who="S0018">but we</u>
<u n="202" who="S0073">so what are you going to do? Is it music?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0018">we're gonna record um the oral histories of father grandfather fathers and sons</u>
<u n="204" who="S0073">uh huh</u>
<u n="205" who="S0018">compare them uh over pivotal <trunc>part</trunc> points in their lives</u>
<u n="206" who="S0073">ah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0018">pivotal religious social political points <pause dur="short"/> and try and make up a little map of I suppose uh what it is to be part of the South Asian diaspora within <anon type="place"/> and also where there are parallels and differences between those generations</u>
<u n="208" who="S0073">oh wow</u>
<u n="209" who="S0018">because there seems  there seems  to be a lot</u>
<u n="210" who="S0073">uh hmm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0018">uh people don't you know that closeness that our fathers had when they were uh you know kind of <trunc>f</trunc> wherever they were from Africa Pakistan Sri <trunc>Lan</trunc> wherever <pause dur="short"/> there was a you know the the family unit was slightly different <pause dur="short"/> so we want to see how British society has affected that in a way</u>
<u n="212" who="S0073">fantastic <pause dur="short"/> sounds like PhD material</u>
<u n="213" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I hope hope a lot of good stuff comes out of it</u>
<u n="214" who="S0073"><trunc>Act</trunc></u>
<u n="215" who="S0018">I hope that it's positive not you know kind of negative really</u>
<u n="216" who="S0073">is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> em <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s girlfriend? No <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0018"><trunc>M</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0073"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> ah of course</u>
<u n="219" who="S0018">but he's <trunc>in</trunc> he's involved a little bit <pause dur="short"/> he's gonna  he's gonna  help us kinda direct the project a little bit</u>
<u n="220" who="S0073">hmm</u>
<u n="221" who="S0018">Cos he's</u>
<u n="222" who="S0073">oh no yeah I bumped into <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and his wife and his baby in the supermarket the other day</u>
<u n="223" who="S0018">oh alright okay</u>
<u n="224" who="S0073">I just get their names mixed up</u>
<u n="225" who="S0018">oh right okay did you called him <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/>?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0073">no I didn't thankfully</u>
<u n="227" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0073">I didn't say anything I said hi</u>
<u n="229" who="S0018">oh alright <pause dur="short"/> no he's he's cool he's um yeah he's got the little one so I um I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I think something just snapped like in September October November actually last year <pause dur="short"/> cos me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had been talking about our relationships with our fathers just when we got together for a beer cos it was always something that was grinding my gears <pause dur="short"/> uh and always something that kind of um he he lost his father awhile ago a few  a few  years ago and became like you know ultimately the head of the family or something and he had to take on a lot of responsibilities <pause dur="short"/> so we had a lot of stuff to talk about in terms of you know father figures and so on <pause dur="short"/> and um and I just November last year it was dreary horrible outside I just said why the fuck are we <trunc>talki</trunc> why do we talk about interesting things and not fucking do it? There are so many cunts</u>
<u n="230" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Fezel <pause dur="short"/> there are so many evil</u>
<u n="231" who="S0018">there are so many evil people</u>
<u n="232" who="S0073">people</u>
<u n="233" who="S0018">out there who manipulate funding in the system to do things that are essentially very you know  you know  <trunc>non</trunc> nonsensical <pause dur="short"/> why don't we put our heads together and actually do something positive? Um and and and not just earn money ourselves but put something back and um he said well okay let's let's start something up <pause dur="short"/> and there's something called the community interest company that you'd now make rather than being uh an out and out imperial capitalistic whore <vocal desc="laugh"/> you can actually do something where you incorporate a company and all of the assets and everything that the all the profits of that company</u>
<u n="234" who="S0073">uh hmm</u>
<u n="235" who="S0018">itself or or or or a <trunc>commun</trunc> or or the specific role that that company is</u>
<u n="236" who="S0073">oh it's like a little NGO?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0018">similar to like an NGO <pause dur="short"/> yeah but it's it's it's it still allows you to be able to earn a wage and it also allows you to be able to do positive pivotal things for a community</u>
<u n="238" who="S0073">hmm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0018">or the community <pause dur="short"/> so we've just set one up <pause dur="short"/> well we've just set the paper off yesterday to companies now so hopefully um hopefully that will  that will  come off <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>we</trunc> we've called ourselves True Form Development</u>
<u n="240" who="S0073">ooh</u>
<u n="241" who="S0018">which is hmm yes which is  which is  which I think was was good <pause dur="short"/> we took <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s name and my name and we just tried to uh come up with words that uh</u>
<u n="242" who="S0073">had the same letter in?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0018" trans="overlap">had the same letters in <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0073">ah cunning way to choose a name</u>
<u n="245" who="S0018">initially we were going to call ourselves TFMD which is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> Make Dollars <vocal desc="laugh"/> After EPMD but we thought that that would be not not in uh not in keeping <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="246" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/> The philosophy of the</u>
<u n="247" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0073">philanthropy</u>
<u n="249" who="S0018">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="250" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0018">so um</u>
<u n="252" who="S0073">so what would be the end objective to I mean cos I imagine you do the research and that <trunc>y</trunc> you do it</u>
<u n="253" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0073">but then what would you do with it when you've compiled it all and?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0018">hmm <pause dur="short"/> well they'll be a couple of things <pause dur="short"/> they'll be a maybe a short doc film thing <pause dur="short"/> we'll have an exhibition or an event</u>
<u n="256" who="S0073">hmm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0018">um we'll be putting all of our findings online as a kind of online archive</u>
<u n="258" who="S0073">hmm</u>
<u n="259" who="S0018">we will then look to probably get our stuff put into archive at <anon type="place"/> at <anon type="place"/> uh Library and then off the basis of those four five outputs we'll we'll see I mean potentially there's part two and part three to this project next year or the year after <pause dur="short"/> but we'll have to see if it if it's  if it's  if it creates a buzz within the community if it's something worthwhile otherwise we'll go under and uh  and uh and uh  yeah <pause dur="short"/> but potentially yeah we we we're going to maybe do a few bits of music um taking the kind of the bits of um music that an older generation the younger generation like and fusing it together</u>
<u n="260" who="S0073">oh cool</u>
<u n="261" who="S0018">uh we'll be doing a number of video diaries you know just to kind of in terms of um <trunc>wh</trunc> what it's like for um a normal day for a young person and a <trunc>you</trunc> a normal day for a a person who's slightly older</u>
<u n="262" who="S0073">uh hmm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0018"><trunc>F</trunc> from that community and what else? There's just a load of material we're gonna have to trawl as long as people are up for us</u>
<u n="264" who="S0073">uh hmm</u>
<u n="265" who="S0018">going through the you know underwear drawers</u>
<u n="266" who="S0073">and how are you going to source the the participants?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0018">well we're looking to source <trunc>d</trunc> we're going to do a big troll of about a hundred two hundred specific people um because it the community's just too huge <pause dur="short"/> we're going to have to poster campaign and so on</u>
<u n="268" who="S0073">uh hmm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0018">with a number and that people can contact <pause dur="short"/> but um I mean even if we can find between ten fifteen people essentially that should be enough for the project</u>
<u n="270" who="S0073">hmm</u>
<u n="271" who="S0018">to be able to I think show effective what the project is set out to do <pause dur="short"/> and I'm quite confident we'll get  we'll get  that <pause dur="short"/> but let's let's just hope that people are kind of open um to it <pause dur="short"/> so um</u>
<u n="272" who="S0073">I'm sure they would be <pause dur="short"/> people love speaking about themselves</u>
<u n="273" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0073">don't they?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm hoping so <pause dur="short"/> cos uh you know it's also  it's also  kind of nice because um in previous projects it's just been like oh yeah we're doing project blah blah <pause dur="short"/> but now because of the family aspect because he's got a little one uh and also because of the fact that um you know wanting to do a lot more of my own stuff away from the family business we've kind of come together at exactly the right it feels like the right time like hungry to do something <pause dur="short"/> so so yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0073">hmm</u>
<u n="277" who="S0018">hopefully it will be a good  a good  one</u>
<u n="278" who="S0073">sounds very interesting</u>
<u n="279" who="S0018">hopefully it will be a good one <pause dur="short"/> yeah I <trunc>mak</trunc> can I make you a cup of tea actually? Do you want a tea?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0073">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'd love one <pause dur="short"/> thank you <pause dur="short"/> I'll just put this on <trunc>reco</trunc> uh pause</u>
<u n="281" who="S0018"><event desc="recording skips"/> Previously living in Mosel it was just like what are you doing? Nothing <pause dur="short"/> should we have pint? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> end up having four pints each fucking night whatever you <trunc>kn</trunc> every other night</u>
<u n="282" who="S0073">but that's</u>
<u n="283" who="S0018">and it's just ridiculous</u>
<u n="284" who="S0073">I know it seems to be that that's all a lot of British people do for for their leisure time is let's go to the pub and I just get so bored of just going to the bloody pub <pause dur="short"/> we're going bell ringing tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0018">I <pause dur="short"/> I got bored of going to the pubs so I went bell ringing <vocal desc="laugh"/> life's death</u>
<u n="286" who="S0073">ding dong ding dong</u>
<u n="287" who="S0018">in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0073">in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? How could you forget <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0018">yeah babe</u>
<u n="290" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah babe? Um her neighbour does bell ringing at one of the churches there and he's invited us along <pause dur="short"/> hmm <pause dur="short"/> hmm <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> Ring my bell <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0073">that will be fun fun fun <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I know what you mean about the pub thing and the drinking thing</u>
<u n="293" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0073">Cos once you're in a pub it's it's not normal to drink something that's non alcoholic either is it?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0018">but I've also seen the <trunc>eff</trunc> I've seen the effect on me of booze <pause dur="short"/> I've seen the effect on people around me <pause dur="short"/> I've seen the effect of good friends of mine <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> good friends of mine <pause dur="short"/> mutual friends on booze um I've actually had to step in on a couple of occasions on like like not just  not just  people like who who are very close to me but even like  even like  friends of friends and I feel as though I have the fucking authority now to be able to go I think you've had too much <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0073">yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0018">when it gets to the evening and you know like at some point in the evening like I've had it here a couple of times where like a mate of a mate has come over and is just talking utter fucking drivel and because everyone is just a bit too civil they'll just go oh that's the end of the night  the end of the night  is gonna be me listening to this cock and I'm not gonna be able to do anything about it <pause dur="short"/> and I've just started going you know what? You've had enough swing your hook or you've had enough shut up and listen to the people who are funny or who can still put two syllables together</u>
<u n="298" who="S0073" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> drunk people they feel that they have to monologue</u>
<u n="299" who="S0018">well which is  which is  fine <pause dur="short"/> I mean I've done that but I just  I just  kind of I I I enjoy the fact that there is someone at least a little bit more compos mentis who's able to say you know something a little bit more interesting <pause dur="short"/> but the worst thing is when you have you know two or three people who are completely pissed which can be funny but when they are either arguing against each other or talking utter nonsense it's a bit problematic <pause dur="short"/> uh for instance last week I was in London um went to Kentish Town to meet an old friend of mine</u>
<u n="300" who="S0073">oh <pause dur="short"/> is that where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to live?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0018">yeah she said yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> um so we went to this <trunc>pu</trunc> I was I always said this didn't I? The whole race issue and uh he he was like kinda you know after after a meal and you've had a bit of few whiskeys and so on <pause dur="short"/> he tried convincing me that racism came from chimps</u>
<u n="302" who="S0073">that's right</u>
<u n="303" who="S0018">and I was</u>
<u n="304" who="S0073">it's not right but I remember you saying</u>
<u n="305" who="S0018">and I was  and I was  just like uh we've known each other for ages and and I just maybe I don't really know you you know and my my brother is his son's godfather <pause dur="short"/> which is very strange for a Muslim man <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="306" who="S0073">but was it actually that much of a contentious</u>
<u n="307" who="S0018" trans="overlap">well yeah it was cos</u>
<u n="308" who="S0073">statement?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0018">yeah because it kinda well because of the fact that we were actually where it led from was Empire and we started</u>
<u n="310" who="S0073">oh okay</u>
<u n="311" who="S0018">then we started talking about racism and what he tried and did was to try and shift the subject of the conversation to being you know kind of something that <trunc>g</trunc> genealogical? Genealogy?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0073">genealogical?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0018"><trunc>Genealo</trunc> genealogical</u>
<u n="314" who="S0073">let's make up a new word</u>
<u n="315" who="S0018">let's make it up <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure  I'm sure  the person listening to this will be able to tell us <pause dur="short"/> is that right? We'll join you in a few minutes <pause dur="short"/> uh um after these words <pause dur="short"/> um so um so yeah it it was kind of him trying to change into a kind of um a biological argument and a sociological argument without looking at the history of racism but trying to jump back you know to the beginnings of time which unfortunately a lot of people tend to do when it comes to either religious racial or ethnic based argument it comes back to either the big bang or measuring skulls and I just found that just a bit fucking obtuse <pause dur="short"/> um but anyway regardless um yeah the point is that you know it's important I suppose just to be able to keep uh track of what you're saying <pause dur="short"/> not get completely so wankered that you're actually dribbling <vocal desc="laugh"/> in someone's face</u>
<u n="316" who="S0073">yes there are the fair few dribblers</u>
<u n="317" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0073">straggling down the high street at half past eleven in Moseley</u>
<u n="319" who="S0018">it's like that comedian Richard Herring said once in this video he's getting heckled by someone <pause dur="short"/> by this drunk dude and he the drunk dude just won't let him get on with his stand-up routine <pause dur="short"/> so he just rips the shit out of him basically <pause dur="short"/> he just kill annihilates him and one of the things he said is look don't come to a comedy club get so drunk that you can't think <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah? You're gonna end in it's gonna end in tears <pause dur="short"/> so that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> I think you can't get that drunk till you can't think <pause dur="short"/> I think that's uh something for British society to maybe think about</u>
<u n="320" who="S0073">pause for thought</u>
<u n="321" who="S0018">pause pause for thought</u>
<event desc="phone rings"/>
<u n="322" who="S0073">oh what's that?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0018">what's that? Oh who's that? It's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just bumped into <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at the mailbox <pause dur="short"/> aside from being shocked that he actually can speak he told <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's the head of factual for ooh</u>
<u n="324" who="S0073">oh it's all happening <pause dur="short"/> is that a letter box?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0018">just some leaflet twat <vocal desc="cough"/> He's the head of factual for childrens based in Salford <pause dur="short"/> what the fuck? Hey that's nice</u>
<u n="326" who="S0073">is that a nugget of</u>
<u n="327" who="S0018">it's a nugget of</u>
<u n="328" who="S0073">beeb gossip?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yes you were telling me about how difficult political pawn situation <pause dur="short"/> pawn as in chess not as in hmm</u>
<u n="331" who="S0018">fucking</u>
<u n="332" who="S0073" trans="overlap">stop it <pause dur="short"/> rude boy</u>
<u n="333" who="S0018">that's that's what porn is <vocal desc="laugh"/> the person who is listening to this tape would know that <pause dur="short"/> don't you know that?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0073">stop it <pause dur="short"/> you're so cheeky</u>
<u n="335" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0073">actually maybe they'll they'll appreciate a bit of comic relief</u>
<u n="337" who="S0018">I'm sure they would</u>
<u n="338" who="S0073">actually I don't know if it's a computer program listening</u>
<u n="339" who="S0018">comic relief <pause dur="short"/> is that like uh a a comedian wanking someone off?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0073">oh stop it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0018">sorry <pause dur="short"/> sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> I just thought  I just thought  of that <pause dur="short"/> god imagine what Islamic relief is? Anyway let's not talk about that <pause dur="short"/> em <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0073">so how's your finger?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0018">it's</u>
<u n="344" who="S0073">I see you've been itching it that means it's healing <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna start calling you slash</u>
<u n="345" who="S0018">it is <trunc>r</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh don't call me slash <vocal desc="laugh"/> fucking hell</u>
<u n="346" who="S0073">oh</u>
<u n="347" who="S0018">I mean bloody hell</u>
<u n="348" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Uh when are you having the stitches taken out?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0018">actually it should be today <pause dur="short"/> cos he <trunc>sa</trunc> I'm sure he said I can't remember whether he said a week or two weeks? But it is itching <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="350" who="S0073">have you taken that off? And</u>
<u n="351" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh no I've replaced it like every day</u>
<u n="352" who="S0073">uh-huh</u>
<u n="353" who="S0018">replaced it yesterday so</u>
<u n="354" who="S0073">is it scabbing over quite well?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0018">there's no scabs on it</u>
<u n="356" who="S0073">really?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="358" who="S0073">but can you see that the two sides of the cut have fused?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0073">oh</u>
<u n="361" who="S0018">so it could be worth taking it to the nurse nursey nurse <pause dur="short"/> maybe I should text the nursey nurse actually today</u>
<u n="362" who="S0073">how many stitches were there?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0018">five? Six? Not that many <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>f</trunc> four five</u>
<u n="364" who="S0073">mm</u>
<u n="365" who="S0018">it's such an idiotic injury</u>
<u n="366" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0018">the thing is I've bumped into like two or three friends who've got exactly the same injuries <pause dur="short"/> the in fact the doctor himself I think had an injury just a little one just there from putting his hand in a cut glass or just a chipped glass <vocal desc="cough"/> and then another mate who I met the day after who like had it in there <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="368" who="S0073">ow</u>
<u n="369" who="S0018">so yeah you gotta be</u>
<u n="370" who="S0073">washing up <pause dur="short"/> government warning <pause dur="short"/> health and safety <pause dur="short"/> washing up can be bad for your the beautiful unblemishedness quality of your hands</u>
<u n="371" who="S0018">well the boys at Kung Fu were taking the piss at me yesterday <pause dur="short"/> I can't lie to them <vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't lie to them really <pause dur="short"/> they're like how do you do that? In a fight Did you? What was the fight? Okay I did it whilst washing up</u>
<u n="372" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I had a fight with a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0018">God</u>
<u n="374" who="S0073">cafe coffee cup</u>
<u n="375" who="S0018">I should call them <pause dur="short"/> I should call <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and try and get some free shit <trunc>a</trunc> some free stuff from them <pause dur="short"/> stuff</u>
<u n="376" who="S0073">that's a bit they're making their glasses a bit delicate <pause dur="short"/> then again were you washing up very aggressively?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0018">very aggressive washing</u>
<u n="378" who="S0073">were you washing that man right out of your cups?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0018">completely <pause dur="short"/> it's just uh washing up just pisses me annoys me <pause dur="short"/> so uh I'm gonna have to get a dishwasher I think</u>
<u n="380" who="S0073">I think</u>
<u n="381" who="S0018">not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0073">I think it might be time if you gonna</u>
<u n="383" who="S0018">it might be time</u>
<u n="384" who="S0073">if you're gonna slash yourself</u>
<u n="385" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but no it's healing up alright just need to try and uh stay safe  stay safe  kids don't do any washing up</u>
<u n="386" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think it yeah two weeks sounds like a more realistic</u>
<u n="387" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0073">time for healing <pause dur="short"/> I remember when I slashed my leg <pause dur="short"/> I told you about that didn't I? No? I was grape picking in France</u>
<u n="389" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0073">and I saw a spider on my leg and I had secateurs on my hand and I went to get the spider away and I slashed my leg <pause dur="short"/> opened it up about five inches and that was twenty I can't remember how many exactly</u>
<u n="391" who="S0018">how deep was that?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0073">twenty stitches <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> How deep was your <trunc>gla</trunc> slash?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> how deep is</u>
<u n="394" who="S0073"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> Your gash <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0018">oh my god <pause dur="short"/> steph</u>
<u n="396" who="S0073">how deep was it? Em</u>
<u n="397" who="S0018"><vocal desc="cough"/> Sorry</u>
<u n="398" who="S0073">em</u>
<u n="399" who="S0018">person listening</u>
<u n="400" who="S0073">it it kind of I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it</u>
<u n="401" who="S0018">must have been deep to get stitches</u>
<u n="402" who="S0073">went into like an elliptical shape</u>
<u n="403" who="S0018">oh shit</u>
<u n="404" who="S0073">and I could see the flesh the the fatty you know you can see all the different layers of skin and</u>
<u n="405" who="S0018">okay <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="406" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0018">oh man</u>
<u n="408" who="S0073">it didn't bleed too badly actually <pause dur="short"/> but yeah it was quite urgh I had to hold it together</u>
<u n="409" who="S0018">did you keep bleeding?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0073" trans="overlap">from two sides</u>
<u n="411" who="S0018">did you keep bleeding? Keep keep bleeding  Did you keep bleeding?  Did you keep bleeding? <vocal desc="laugh"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> Keep keep bleeding <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> That's the worst thing you can actually listen to to the in the A and E couldn't you? <vocal desc="laugh"/> Someone should make a mixed tape of that <vocal desc="laugh"/> you keep bleeding <pause dur="short"/> dying <trunc>fo</trunc> no no that's bad <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's bad that's getting a bit sick</u>
<u n="412" who="S0073">in the haemophiliac ward <vocal desc="laugh"/> Anyway</u>
<u n="413" who="S0018">anyway</u>
<u n="414" who="S0073">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I had to hold it together the two sides of it together while they took me to hospital because had I not it just would have brrr ah spread urgh horrible horrible <pause dur="short"/> but no it was em I think it was two weeks before I had the stitches out <pause dur="short"/> but there's a good it's alright cos there's a lot more flesh on that part of your body <pause dur="short"/> I mean when you do it on your knuckle ah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0018">there's not much there <pause dur="short"/> just blood bloody blood</u>
<u n="416" who="S0073">urgh</u>
<u n="417" who="S0018">the whole fucking just all of that was just covered cos I was I'd stupidly invited the one of the ginger knobs in one of the I've got a pair of ginger knobs outside that I don't know their names I just call them the ginger knobs <pause dur="short"/> two ginger cats they're like twins <vocal desc="laugh"/> Who kinda come round and defecate in my garden and eat my left over chicken and I'd <trunc>invite</trunc> I'd invited one of them in cos they were just meowing pathetically outside <pause dur="short"/> so I thought alright the cat's in I may as well you know do some washing <pause dur="short"/> so I ended up kinda bleeding half over this cat god knows what the fucking what the owner would have thought when the cat got home</u>
<u n="418" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh no</u>
<u n="419" who="S0018">Cos it I had a few drops of blood on the tail</u>
<u n="420" who="S0073">really?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0018">Cos it was just there meowing for food while I was washing <pause dur="short"/> so I cut myself</u>
<u n="422" who="S0073">he wasn't he was laughing at you</u>
<u n="423" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I tried to press it back together the thing for some reason I just tried to push it back together like it would stick back on?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0073">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0018">and kept doing it</u>
<u n="426" who="S0073">there is that just kind of suspended moment of reality where you just in disbelief completely yeah oh no I'll just pop it back together</u>
<u n="427" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0018">and I just ended up <pause dur="short"/> I didn't have any kitchen roll <pause dur="short"/> I ended bleeding over the office oh over the office? Over the kitchen <pause dur="short"/> I said right what I'm I going to have to do? Cos this is not a plaster <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> so I'm gonna have to take it somewhere <pause dur="short"/> uh so I drove <pause dur="short"/> I put then got into the car bleeding all over the car took it to took myself to the em surgery over the road and I said I'm bleeding everywhere can someone please help me? Can you get me a nurse? And the nurse isn't here <pause dur="short"/> I was like what <trunc>wh</trunc> where she's out? I was like the nurse is? Okay fine <pause dur="short"/> can I see a doctor? Saw a doctor quite a fit doctor actually called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who I think is gonna become my new doctor very immanently <pause dur="short"/> em and she said no I'm not trained you're gonna have to get yourself to A and E</u>
<u n="429" who="S0073">I'm not trained?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0018">I'm not trained to do that or something like that and I was like oh right <pause dur="short"/> then took myself to uh</u>
<u n="431" who="S0073">that's slightly worrying</u>
<u n="432" who="S0018">isn't it?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0073">that your doctor isn't trained to perform a bit of first aid?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0018">and then got to Queen Elizabeth and almost got clamped <pause dur="short"/> cos it was in I was like it's an emergency man <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="435" who="S0073">that's just adding insult to injury</u>
<u n="436" who="S0018">I was like sorry mate you're gonna have to uh you're gonna have to move your car <pause dur="short"/> I was like uh oh dear what a long day</u>
<u n="437" who="S0073">aw</u>
<u n="438" who="S0018">but uh yeah <pause dur="short"/> so hopefully in a couple of weeks should have a good war scar there and uh will carry on telling the people that obviously it was someone who got on the wrong side of me</u>
<u n="439" who="S0073">A bit of shrapnel from the war</u>
<u n="440" who="S0018">from the war <pause dur="short"/> the war <pause dur="short"/> but no it's it's cool <pause dur="short"/> it's nice having two days just to get on with stuff doing this kind of stuff it's nice</u>
<u n="441" who="S0073">so what's the plan tonight?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0018">this evening I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying that uh em we're gonna go for food somewhere? I think Pangea which is over the road on <anon type="place"/> opposite Spice Merchant?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0073">uh-huh</u>
<u n="444" who="S0018">uh with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> uh em that way</u>
<u n="445" who="S0073">that way</u>
<u n="446" who="S0018"><vocal desc="cough"/> And em</u>
<u n="447" who="S0073">is that a new restaurant?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> it's been there for years  it's been there for years  but em never gone there cos it's just it always just seems like like too you know kind of contrived but em I'll check it out <pause dur="short"/> there's only so many things you can do in the bubble <vocal desc="laugh"/> that is <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> em and then maybe a beer and then hopefully an earlyish night <pause dur="short"/> uh and then work tomorrow and then I've got to sort out my curtain rail I've got to sort out my car <pause dur="short"/> I've got a dent on my car I need to take out and what else? Maybe a bit gardening if it's nice</u>
<u n="449" who="S0073">I haven't seen your garden cos I always come round when it's dark</u>
<u n="450" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's just like a little square pitch of earth at the back but I need to just kind of it looks a bit</u>
<u n="451" who="S0073">you can get some vegetables in there</u>
<u n="452" who="S0018" trans="overlap">needs needs a bit of flattening or may put some more  some more  grass down seed</u>
<u n="453" who="S0073">it looks well fertilised by your ginger knobs</u>
<u n="454" who="S0018">ah bloody hell <pause dur="short"/> it's such well the thing is not just them too <vocal desc="cough"/> who's next door? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> next door she's got two kittens as well</u>
<u n="455" who="S0073">aww</u>
<u n="456" who="S0018">that are kind of around <pause dur="short"/> so they they are they come around and then there's another <trunc>tab</trunc> there's a tabbie from somewhere with a bell who kind of comes down now and again when there's some chicken out <pause dur="short"/> but in the summer it's really cool cos basically all five of them if we're sitting outside drinking wine <trunc>y</trunc> you you'll come over in the summer when it's really like nice and hot and we just put the music outside em and just have like a little fire get drunk until <trunc>in</trunc> into the evening <pause dur="short"/> it's just like reminding us it's just trying to remind me myself of Spain really</u>
<u n="457" who="S0073">aw</u>
<u n="458" who="S0018">and just kind of yeah and the cats really just laze around just like you know waiting for you know bits of barbeque or whatever so</u>
<u n="459" who="S0073">I think I might come round and be one of your cats <pause dur="short"/> I'll just laze around</u>
<u n="460" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="461" who="S0073">stretch out on the lawn wait to be chucked things off the barbeque <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="462" who="S0018">what I do want to do what I didn't do last summer is the film screening <pause dur="short"/> as soon as it gets hot</u>
<u n="463" who="S0073">oh <pause dur="short"/> brilliant</u>
<u n="464" who="S0018">I <trunc>re</trunc> I've been saying it for like a year and a half two years <pause dur="short"/> now I've got  I've got  Shiv's projector here <pause dur="short"/> he's left it here</u>
<u n="465" who="S0073">cool</u>
<u n="466" who="S0018">so I'm going to hook it up and will do like a you know</u>
<u n="467" who="S0073">excellent</u>
<u n="468" who="S0018">we'll do I'll just email you know whoever and every other week it will be someone else's turn they can just choose the film and we'll just run it on and watch it</u>
<u n="469" who="S0073">brilliant</u>
<u n="470" who="S0018">and and you know</u>
<u n="471" who="S0073">my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had this beautiful country house in <trunc>V</trunc> just outside of Valencia and it was kind of a painted a duck egg blue but very pale pale pale blue <pause dur="short"/> em it was beautiful shapes <pause dur="short"/> it was like shaped like of the roof was shaped like a wave and on the <trunc>pat</trunc> one of the patios in front there was uh like a perfect screening venue to put chairs and tables and chill out and uh he projected films onto the side of the house in the summer <pause dur="short"/> it was brilliant</u>
<u n="472" who="S0018">that's the vibe</u>
<u n="473" who="S0073">I know</u>
<u n="474" who="S0018">that's the <trunc>v</trunc> well I mean it's not a big house but we can get you know <trunc>t</trunc> ten people</u>
<u n="475" who="S0073">where are you going to project onto?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0018">there's a white wall right at the back outside</u>
<u n="477" who="S0073">ah</u>
<u n="478" who="S0018">so what I'll do is I'll paint over uh and if I can I may  I may  like buy a a thingy screen uh a proper projection screen or or maybe just a sheet that is like tensioned</u>
<u n="479" who="S0073">uh-huh</u>
<u n="480" who="S0018">you can get like I think you can get like it's not silk <pause dur="short"/> it's similar to silk</u>
<u n="481" who="S0073">mm hm</u>
<u n="482" who="S0018">but it's it's it's it's kind of like that material and you just basically I'll pin it up and we'll just you know put the projector on top of the toilet you know get a <trunc>gener</trunc> get a general extension wire wind me the end</u>
<u n="483" who="S0073">oh it's that back wall you're talking about? The back wall garden</u>
<u n="484" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so we just sit in the back garden and we just watch the back wall</u>
<u n="485" who="S0073">yay</u>
<u n="486" who="S0018">and we'll hook up like uh you know like a bit of a sound system to it and get the full surround sound <pause dur="short"/> it will be great</u>
<u n="487" who="S0073">Fezel's driving</u>
<u n="488" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely and people can bring their films or you know it's just a DVD player isn't it? Just wing it on</u>
<u n="489" who="S0073">do they allow outside film projections in <anon type="place"/>? Cos that's the one good thing about living in a country where people are used to good weather <pause dur="short"/> there's so much more things happen outside</u>
<u n="490" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I think this is why they stopped because it's just the danger of</u>
<u n="491" who="S0073">mm</u>
<u n="492" who="S0018">the rain but also because of just red tape <pause dur="short"/> there's so much involved in trying to get the process actually done then and kind of provisionally put in <pause dur="short"/> because they used to do it at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> em in fact that's a brilliant idea we should do that <trunc>y</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> cos they they did like back in the day they did like a classical movie but I can't remember what it was <pause dur="short"/> they did like a really old black and white movie <pause dur="short"/> I'm not they should do that again <pause dur="short"/> they should start screening that shit</u>
<u n="493" who="S0073">they did something in the uh what's it called? The <trunc>Sain</trunc> Paul's Church in Birmingham? Just before Christmas they uh projected Alfred Hitchcock's The Bird's onto the wall</u>
<u n="494" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0073">inside</u>
<u n="496" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0073">and that you got bats in the belfry and everything and all the bats were flying around with the birds</u>
<u n="498" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0018">who did you go to that with?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0073">oh no I didn't go <pause dur="short"/> I found out about it after the fact</u>
<u n="502" who="S0018">I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was telling me about it</u>
<u n="503" who="S0073">did he?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0018">cronism</u>
<u n="505" who="S0073">cronism <pause dur="short"/> we're getting quite a lot of isms into this conversation</u>
<u n="506" who="S0018">cronism from Indie <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will ring you when he's done four PM ish <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0073">oh</u>
<u n="508" who="S0018">oh that's going to be a pain in my ass</u>
<u n="509" who="S0073">why? Was that siesta time?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0018">it is siesta time <pause dur="short"/> it will be chill out time <pause dur="short"/> it will be the kind of time where I'm winding down and going right <pause dur="short"/> enough today <pause dur="short"/> having said that it is twelve and I've done absolutely fuck all <pause dur="short"/> I mean nothing <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's hard not swearing you know</u>
<u n="511" who="S0073">is it?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0018">it is <pause dur="short"/> it's hard</u>
<u n="513" who="S0073">you should wash your mouth with soap and water young lad</u>
<u n="514" who="S0018">bad</u>
<u n="515" who="S0073"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I guess it makes you realise how much you swear</u>
<u n="516" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0073">it's funny though that I've noticed that you swear like before</u>
<u n="518" who="S0018"><trunc>W</trunc> I think it's because of the fact I know I'm being recorded and I'm kind of subconsciously making the effort to swear actually because I know someone else is gonna have to listen to me swearing and it's a bit naughty</u>
<u n="519" who="S0073">your inner rebel coming out</u>
<u n="520" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0073">so what is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doing today? Why is?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0018">he's here for a job interview I think</u>
<u n="523" who="S0073">oh okay</u>
<u n="524" who="S0018">I think em they're looking to hopefully move back to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> so they want to em yeah just find you know kind of bits and bobs of work really</u>
<u n="525" who="S0073">oh is he the guy that did the masters in what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> works in?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0018"><trunc>Y</trunc> Yes <pause dur="short"/> northern</u>
<u n="527" who="S0073">conflict</u>
<u n="528" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0073">resolution?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0018">I think he did I don't know if it was in conflict resolution or whether it was in something else <pause dur="short"/> but em yeah he's uh yeah he's a I <trunc>me</trunc> he's a really nice guy from Scarborough and em he worked for I think  I think  he worked in procurement for a bit or something like that <pause dur="short"/> em but <trunc>h</trunc> he he's just looking to get he's you know he's just looking to get out of the house <pause dur="short"/> he's he they've been living back at home with his parents and being kind of like you know a couple it's it's a bit difficult really so they just want to come and come out and have their own you know lives I suppose <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="531" who="S0073">what does she do?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0018">she's a doctor</u>
<u n="533" who="S0073">oh right</u>
<u n="534" who="S0018">so em I mean I think she earns <trunc>a</trunc> an alright amount but I think if if one only one person is earning it's really difficult isn't it?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0073">mm</u>
<u n="536" who="S0018">em so yeah</u>
<u n="537" who="S0073">so are people flocking to <anon type="place"/> cos of the low house prices and the?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0018">I don't know  I don't know  I think I mean we were talking last night to oh cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and em <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came over to uh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s and they texted me so I kind of popped by after after Wing Chun and they were saying that</u>
<u n="539" who="S0073">after what?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0018">wing Chun</u>
<u n="541" who="S0073">what's that?</u>
<u n="542" who="S0018">win Chun is uh em like a primary form of Kung Fu</u>
<u n="543" who="S0073">oh Judo <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="544" who="S0018">it's basically where Kung Fu <trunc>origina</trunc> Wing Chun Kung Fu is a I think the original form of Kung Fu</u>
<u n="545" who="S0073">oh okay</u>
<u n="546" who="S0018">and uh I went there afterwards and they were kind of just saying yeah we've been looking but there's just nothing for sale around here or if it  it if  is it's inflated <pause dur="short"/> and if it is it's not particularly nice and it goes very quickly</u>
<u n="547" who="S0073">mm</u>
<u n="548" who="S0018">Cos there's such a high uh rental uh em turnover <pause dur="short"/> so people just buy houses and rent them out <pause dur="short"/> em so uh so  that's the  that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> I was kinda lucky getting this actually all those years ago I made the right decision early</u>
<u n="549" who="S0073">how many years ago did you get it?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0018">two thousand and four five?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0073">mm</u>
<u n="552" who="S0018">no <trunc>la</trunc> later?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0073">five or six years</u>
<u n="554" who="S0018">five or six <pause dur="short"/> yeah something like that <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0073">I thought they were quite a few <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were looking before Christmas and when they were visiting like two or three a week weren't they?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> em well <trunc>accor</trunc> yeah I mean I don't  I don't  know really I haven't been paying that much attention <pause dur="short"/> all I know is that they were looking to buy but they they just can't find anywhere em you know kind of decent</u>
<u n="557" who="S0073">mm</u>
<u n="558" who="S0018">em the majority of houses on this road are go for between a hundred and sixty upwards which is expensive for a first house for any you know for anyone <pause dur="short"/> so it's you know I wouldn't have been able to afford it if I hadn't have left you know kind of if I hadn't worked for my  for my  dad and just done a boring business job</u>
<u n="559" who="S0073">mm hm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0018">so em yeah it's it's a weird one <vocal desc="cough"/> but I'm getting a bit bored of this place now</u>
<u n="561" who="S0073">really?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0073">why didn't you sell it onto them?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0018">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I think I mean</u>
<u n="565" who="S0073">go and live in a canal barge or something</u>
<u n="566" who="S0018">I mean if when I get married I'll probably sell it <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I wanna live in here married <pause dur="short"/> well I mean even though I could I just kind of don't know <pause dur="short"/> it would be nice to be somewhere different <pause dur="short"/> somewhere slightly bigger <pause dur="short"/> it's quite slim a slim house</u>
<u n="567" who="S0073">slim? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="568" who="S0018">quite narrow</u>
<u n="569" who="S0073">it is <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> they all tend to be around here don't they?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0018">it's just you know it's just</u>
<u n="571" who="S0073">typical</u>
<u n="572" who="S0018">four five metres wide</u>
<u n="573" who="S0073">victorian type houses all around <anon type="place"/> </u>
<u n="574" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="575" who="S0073">so you mentioned the marriage word <pause dur="short"/> have you been uh inspired by <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> getting engaged?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> long way to go yet  long way to go yet  But having said that I am thirty-five this year</u>
<u n="577" who="S0073">are you?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0018">that's so that's five years from forty still unmarried <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="579" who="S0073">happily unmarried</u>
<u n="580" who="S0018">happily unmarried but I think the parents are kind of uh getting on now</u>
<u n="581" who="S0073">oh do you get a lot of pressure?</u>
<u n="582" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean they're <vocal desc="yawn"/> coming on to their sixties and I think they just want to have grandchildren and you know play with them and be happy and</u>
<u n="583" who="S0073">what about?</u>
<u n="584" who="S0018">have someone to spoil</u>
<u n="585" who="S0073">what about your brother? Is he  is he  single?</u>
<u n="586" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0073">is he  is he  not bearing half the brunt of the we want <trunc>ch</trunc> grandchildren</u>
<u n="588" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="589" who="S0073">you must</u>
</body>
</text>
