<text id="SHT2">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:20:01</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-02</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0251 S0252</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Living room in Malton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Internet Shopping, Ebay and Amazon</topics>
		<activity>Internet shopping</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0251">
				<exactage>52</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>North Ferriby, East Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>23</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>GCSE Maths Examiner</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0252">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>York</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0251">what are you doing there <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0252">I'm I'm ah listing eh a some of my old textbooks on Ebay</u>
<u n="3" who="S0251">oh <trunc>tha</trunc>that's a good idea you can get so many free listings a month now can't you?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0252">yeah it's a I think it's a twenty free listings which can be either an auction or a buy it now</u>
<u n="5" who="S0251">oh right which do you normally prefer?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0252">it <unclear/> with both really I think one good thing about buy it now is that you can guarantee a price</u>
<u n="7" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="8" who="S0252">erm but I don't think erm if it's a more popular item that it ah you might have it for a long time whereas with <trunc>a</trunc>an auction</u>
<u n="9" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="10" who="S0252">you do hopefully sell it before a set date</u>
<u n="11" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="12" who="S0252">whereas that it's not going to with a a buy it now</u>
<u n="13" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no although sometimes people can give you a best offer can't they?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0252">they can yes but I think my only concern with that is if there is the best offer option I feel as though I'm giving them an invitation to offer less than what I want</u>
<u n="15" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0252">whereas if I just <trunc>a</trunc>ask the price I want I'll get the price I want</u>
<u n="17" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes mm</u>
<u n="18" who="S0252">I don't particularly really want to start negotiating a price once I've decided <unclear/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no although if you're buying something if you want to buy something have you ever had any success on negotiating a slightly better deal?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0252">erm I have had some limited successes I have had probably one very good success where I managed to get something for half the amount</u>
<u n="21" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm wow</u>
<u n="22" who="S0252">but it's usually at best within five to twelve percent</u>
<u n="23" who="S0251">yeah just a pound or two</u>
<u n="24" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="25" who="S0251">which do you think is best for erm selling something? Ebay or Amazon?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0252">again there's for and against with both erm I think the eh Amazon platform is a little bit easier to work with</u>
<u n="27" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="28" who="S0252">that you don't have to take a picture</u>
<u n="29" who="S0251">true</u>
<u n="30" who="S0252">the description's already there</u>
<u n="31" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="32" who="S0252">basically you just have to give a condition <unclear/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0251">so it's quicker to do isn't it really?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0252">mm hm and also I think the erm products usually realise a higher price on Amazon than on Ebay which obviously is a good thing if you are buying</u>
<u n="35" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="36" who="S0252">erm <pause dur="short"/> but erm if you are selling you really want to go for Amazon</u>
<u n="37" who="S0251" trans="overlap">if you want to sell yes but it really offers you a huge market if you've got something to sell doesn't it?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0252">yes it does and also there's more flexible for erm offering services to European countries and worldwide countries we have had a erm a couple of sales for things <unclear/> Portugal and Denmark as well</u>
<u n="39" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes it's great isn't it? although you got to be careful with the postage there because that can be quite pricey can't it?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes yes I think it's erm relatively expensive just to post them in the UK so</u>
<u n="41" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="42" who="S0252">it <trunc>re</trunc> probably it's all been <unclear/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0251"><unclear/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0252" trans="overlap">much further oh aye</u>
<u n="45" who="S0251">and it's also good say if you're looking for a book that's out of print in the past if you went to all the second-hand bookshops in your area and you hadn't found it you pretty much couldn't have it</u>
<u n="46" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="47" who="S0251">but with the internet you can look at all the second-hand bookshops that have got books available on the internet</u>
<u n="48" who="S0252">you can <pause dur="short"/> within the UK and the world</u>
<u n="49" who="S0251">yeah so you stand a good chance of finding it</u>
<u n="50" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="51" who="S0251">if it is for sale somewhere that you</u>
<u n="52" who="S0252" trans="overlap">I'm hooked with the <unclear/> so you can get it at a price that ah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes or in best condition</u>
<u n="54" who="S0252">mm yes</u>
<u n="55" who="S0251">because the emails have reduced the amount of letter post I would say because people ermerm are sending more emails but fewer letters but I think it's probably increased the amount of parcel post</u>
<u n="56" who="S0252">it has</u>
<u n="57" who="S0251">that's sent</u>
<u n="58" who="S0252">it has</u>
<u n="59" who="S0251">with all these things that are put for sale people buying and selling well all kinds of commodities really</u>
<u n="60" who="S0252">absolutely I think erm from the Royal Mail's point of view it it shouldn't make a lot of difference because obviously parcels realise a higher price at least a few pounds to send</u>
<u n="61" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="62" who="S0252">whereas erm a small letter is maybe fifty-sixty pence</u>
<u n="63" who="S0251">yeah although there's a lot more competition now isn't there?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0252">there is</u>
<u n="65" who="S0251">for the erm parcel post side of the business</u>
<u n="66" who="S0252">ah to be honest they're not the most competitive for any parcel that is larger than a kilogram or erm that doesn't fit through the slots that are put in place</u>
<u n="67" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="68" who="S0252">erm other couriers tend to be ah a bit more generous on dimensions</u>
<u n="69" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0252">and it's really more or less just priced by weight</u>
<u n="71" who="S0251">yes and ah is it Hermes where you can print off the erm postal stamp on the computer?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0252" trans="overlap">stamp yes</u>
<u n="73" who="S0251">on your printer and then you take it to the ah local corner shop don't you?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0252">you do yes I think that erm follows a a German model where when the <foreign lang="ger">Deutsch</foreign> post was charging too much</u>
<u n="75" who="S0251">oh right</u>
<u n="76" who="S0252">erm they started popping up in erm corner shops</u>
<u n="77" who="S0251">mm hm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0252">erm that's now started to happen in this country as well</u>
<u n="79" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0252">but I think for erm larger parcels they are definitely a lot more competitive than Royal Mail</u>
<u n="81" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="82" who="S0252">and then but then that's erm if you're sending an item between twenty and fifty pounds worth of value except erm Royal Mail only goes up to twenty pounds on the second erm first class ah packages whereas erm Hermes can go up to fifty pounds</u>
<u n="83" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yep yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0252">ah but then that price so it just offers a little bit more protection without an additional fee</u>
<u n="85" who="S0251">but are some of the other companies that do parcel deliveries more for commercial <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0252" trans="overlap">I think so really I think one of the main downsides is that they would have to come up to the house to pick the parcel up</u>
<u n="87" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="88" who="S0252">which would mean that you would be in all day waiting for them to collect it whereas <unclear/> you can just drop it off at a corner shop you can do that when you want to really</u>
<u n="89" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm yeerm that's right but some of the post boxes in our area are having fewer collections now aren't they?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0252">they are which is a bit of a disappointment I think really when you think that our post really comes at well I don't know but sometimes one to two o'clock</u>
<u n="91" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="92" who="S0252">really that is the time when the boxes tend to be collected but I think really they're just using nine AM because erm they don't really want to give a specific time which is really more or less when it suits them</u>
<u n="93" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> that's right because in the past the post used to come in the morning ah certainly before perhaps about nine o'clock sort of time</u>
<u n="94" who="S0252">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0251">but now it seems to be coming after lunch regularly now and it has been a lot later than that in some instances</u>
<u n="96" who="S0252" trans="overlap">it does it does sometimes up to six PM</u>
<u n="97" who="S0251">I know I think that's dreadful <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0252">I know it almost <trunc>d</trunc>means that you receive the parcel the next day because you're not really able to act on it within that day any more</u>
<u n="99" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no that's right yes</u>
<u n="100" who="S0252">but erm it is surprising how the erm dot com revolution has changed erm even the post network</u>
<u n="101" who="S0251">yes it has hasn't it?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0252">do you think that erm we use the postal service a bit more with me erm putting books for sale?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0251">yes I think we do I think we've certainly bought a lot more online erm in the past few years and I think we've bought a wider range of goods online</u>
<u n="104" who="S0252">mm yes</u>
<u n="105" who="S0251">more recently erm books and sometimes clothes erm what else have we bought online?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0252">oh fridge freezer unit</u>
<u n="107" who="S0251">really? I think we did didn't we?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0252">we did</u>
<u n="109" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="110" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="111" who="S0251" trans="overlap">that was a very big item <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0252">it was and er</u>
<u n="113" who="S0251">I think that was the biggest item we've bought online <unclear/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0252">yes and holidays</u>
<u n="115" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="116" who="S0252">well I suppose they're technically bigger in terms of value</u>
<u n="117" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="118" who="S0252">yes car insurances home insurances erm well even to things erm like a tin of paint and er a pen er</u>
<u n="119" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes yes yep yes all kinds of things so</u>
<u n="120" who="S0252">yes I think one thing is it can be quite hard to erm find the things that you want with the local shops they might not necessarily have it in stock or the size or the colour</u>
<u n="121" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no that's right</u>
<u n="122" who="S0252">and I think sometimes they can even charge a bit too much</u>
<u n="123" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0252">I think one good thing about the internet is you can compare all the different prices before you purchase</u>
<u n="125" who="S0251">that's right</u>
<u n="126" who="S0252">so it should enable that you get at least a competitive price if not the best price available</u>
<u n="127" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yeah that's right one good thing about John Lewis though is that if you do find it elsewhere cheaper and it's exactly the same</u>
<u n="128" who="S0252">yes and in a shop</u>
<u n="129" who="S0251">and in a shop they will do a price match won't they?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0252" trans="overlap">I know it's very good that really</u>
<u n="131" who="S0251">so</u>
<u n="132" who="S0252">it does there are some items we've price matched that there was been er been no way that we'd've been able to buy it from that shop really</u>
<u n="133" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no that's right because it was too far away or something</u>
<u n="134" who="S0252">yes I mean for example the spade</u>
<u n="135" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="136" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="137" who="S0251">yeah and the postage would've been a lot on that presumably? cos <unclear>they're</unclear> quite heavy and a bulky object</u>
<u n="138" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes they are yes er one thing that retailers seem to be doing now is erm like er a click and collect service that you order it online and pick it up in store</u>
<u n="139" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="140" who="S0252">usually at a cheaper price or in some cases free</u>
<u n="141" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0252">do you think that has caught on or?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0251">ah well when we have done <trunc>cick</trunc>click and collect there's always been one or two people collecting things hasn't there?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="145" who="S0251">and then it saves you having to pay the postage</u>
<u n="146" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="147" who="S0251">although obviously you'd have to pay petrol</u>
<u n="148" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="149" who="S0251">to take your car there to go and collect the item don't you?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0252">you do that's but I suppose that aspect really you just ermerm in some ways reserving the item so you can pick it up and don't have to look for it or</u>
<u n="151" who="S0251">no</u>
<u n="152" who="S0252">risk someone else taking it or</u>
<u n="153" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="154" who="S0252">but having said that I think some companies actually use their erm online warehouse to <unclear/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes that's right</u>
<u n="156" who="S0252">to be honest I don't think it really benefits the store in that respect unless impulse buying encourages the purchase</u>
<u n="157" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0252">do you think erm purchasing things online will change even further some people have thought of erm having a digital streams in tube stations for people to <trunc>o</trunc>order their groceries online</u>
<u n="159" who="S0251" trans="overlap">really? while you're waiting for your train?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="161" who="S0251">yes well not a bad idea good use of time isn't it <unclear/> productive <unclear/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0252">yes all different Amazon's sort of teleport flying device to drop off parcels in people's gardens will catch on?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0251" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm not sure about that what do you think?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0252">I think the erm American government have banned those because I think they're worried about security risk</u>
<u n="165" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0252">in regards to those devices</u>
<u n="167" who="S0251">yes it all sounds a bit strange</u>
<u n="168" who="S0252">that's have you heard of any other ways that you think erm online shopping may evolve?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0251">eh I can't think of anything at the moment</u>
<u n="170" who="S0252">but erm even erm grocery shopping has changed as well</u>
<u n="171" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes I know</u>
<u n="172" who="S0252">but in some ways it's a bit like what it was before because erm people used to erm go into the shop with a list and then have it delivered by bicycle or van or</u>
<u n="173" who="S0251" trans="overlap">that's right the eh errands boy would bring it round for you</u>
<u n="174" who="S0252">yeah so in some ways it's reverted back to the past</u>
<u n="175" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes it's back to that yeah yes</u>
<u n="176" who="S0252">erm <unclear/> erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0251">yes because I didn't really feel attracted to having the groceries delivered at first</u>
<u n="178" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="179" who="S0251">and then now I've tried it I've got really used to it and I've found it much more convenient and then during the week I just do little bits of shopping extra that I might need like extra fresh vegetables or milk and things to top up as I go along but most of the shop I now get erm delivered from the online service</u>
<u n="180" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="181" who="S0251">I've really got to like it more than I imagined</u>
<u n="182" who="S0252">yes I think one of the the best things about it is that you can just stay in the comfort of your own home when you order it and when you receive it that you don't have to go into a supermarket which can be quite noisy stressful parking space you've got to load everything up and put it on the counter <unclear/> stand and then bag it up and then move it to the car and get out it's a try to time-consuming and unpleasant</u>
<u n="183" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm that's right yes yes that's right <pause dur="short"/> yes it's very laborious it can be yes</u>
<u n="184" who="S0252"><unclear/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0251">and usually all the checkouts have got queues on you're wandering up and down looking for the shortest queue and realise they're all busy so you've just got to grin and bear it</u>
<u n="186" who="S0252">yes probably bump into somebody that you were hoping to avoid or</u>
<u n="187" who="S0251" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well possible</u>
<u n="188" who="S0252">take up a bit of time</u>
<u n="189" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="190" who="S0252"><trunc>a</trunc>also I think erm it substitutes erm can be good at times it means that you can sometimes just a better product without eh paying extra</u>
<u n="191" who="S0251">yes occasionally it works in your favour but sometimes you don't get things that you were really hoping for</u>
<u n="192" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes I know best one we've had was two Alaskan ah salmon ah fillets ah which was swapped for erm four salmon Scottish fillets</u>
<u n="193" who="S0251" trans="overlap"><unclear/> what was the worked in our favour that time didn't it?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0252">it certainly did</u>
<u n="195" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0252">that's erm I I don't think that will happen too frequently</u>
<u n="197" who="S0251">no no I don't think that was just a one-off don't you? because they'd run out of the packets of two</u>
<u n="198" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="199" who="S0251">we've still got some good offers haven't we?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="201" who="S0251">we can still do eh all the special offers that are available the two for ones and that sort of thing</u>
<u n="202" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="203" who="S0251">you can still view those</u>
<u n="204" who="S0252">I think it enables you to look at offers better actually because I think when you're in the store with the shelving units being very high I imagine it's probably quite easy to miss offers out which obviously might be rather disappointing at times</u>
<u n="205" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes mm yes</u>
<u n="206" who="S0252">having said that though erm we have seen things on the websites you know being in store to pick it up but eh they haven't changed the label or erm the the offer doesn't seem to be applicable in that store so</u>
<u n="207" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes yes so you might not be aware of it</u>
<u n="208" who="S0252">in some ways you might actually miss out on the offers by not shopping online</u>
<u n="209" who="S0251">yes</u>
<u n="210" who="S0252">but the only downside is you can't make use of say reduced items with short dates</u>
<u n="211" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no no and another thing is if you have vouchers that you've printed off online</u>
<u n="212" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="213" who="S0251">you can't use them on an online shop can you?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0252">no</u>
<u n="215" who="S0251">at the moment</u>
<u n="216" who="S0252" trans="overlap"><trunc>o</trunc>only in very rare cases</u>
<u n="217" who="S0251">but I think the technology is going to be improved isn't it to incorporate that I don't know how long that's likely to take</u>
<u n="218" who="S0252" trans="overlap">yes yes well I think one awkward aspect is the fact that we've got at least sort of four five different retailers doing online deliveries that and had have had to work it means you're going to have to try have some kind of system that overlaps with that and</u>
<u n="219" who="S0251">mm in common</u>
<u n="220" who="S0252">I don't think that would work terribly well considering how erm competitive and volatile the erm supermarket industry is</u>
<u n="221" who="S0251">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0252">but obviously it will be nice when that time comes</u>
<u n="223" who="S0251">yes yes</u>
<u n="224" who="S0252">I must admit I don't think we get offers really frequently but when you do get them it is nice to use it</u>
<u n="225" who="S0251" trans="overlap">mm yeah yeah I think it be especially good as it gets nearer Christmas and the shops get really busy</u>
<u n="226" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="227" who="S0251">I think it's nice to go and look around and see what there is and then it gives you a bit of an idea but I like the shopping online now</u>
<u n="228" who="S0252">yes</u>
<u n="229" who="S0251">also you can try clothes on at home which is a bit more satisfactory</u>
<u n="230" who="S0252">yes also you can erm try and match it with existing clothes <unclear/> as well</u>
<u n="231" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes that's a good point</u>
<u n="232" who="S0252">which obviously you can't take the whole wardrobe to the the shop</u>
<u n="233" who="S0251" trans="overlap">no to see whether it matches what you've already got that's true</u>
<u n="234" who="S0252">but erm I think there are increasing number <unclear/> purchased online</u>
<u n="235" who="S0251">yes yes it has</u>
<u n="236" who="S0252"><unclear/> good selection of most types of clothing really</u>
<u n="237" who="S0251">yes some things you couldn't like shoes for instance</u>
<u n="238" who="S0252">I can get away with shoes</u>
<u n="239" who="S0251" trans="overlap">I wouldn't really like to buy shoes online because it's ah tricky to fit aren't they?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0252">they are I must admit they have generally been alright</u>
<u n="241" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="242" who="S0252">with</u>
<u n="243" who="S0251">but you just stick to the same make don't you?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0252">I do</u>
<u n="245" who="S0251" trans="overlap">the same brand</u>
<u n="246" who="S0252">preferably the same type of shoe but maybe just in a different colour</u>
<u n="247" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="248" who="S0252">I think that makes it a bit easier</u>
<u n="249" who="S0251">mm</u>
<u n="250" who="S0252">but obviously if you're a bit more adventurous you're taking a risk that you might have to send it back which can be a bit of a nuisance having to take it up and erm take it to the post office</u>
<u n="251" who="S0251" trans="overlap">yes yes yes that's right</u>
<u n="252" who="S0252">and some cases we've had it the parcels been lost and that turns into a bit of a tricky situation</u>
<u n="253" who="S0251">it does indeed <pause dur="short"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
