<text id="SHXF">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:27</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-04</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0018 S0138</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A café in a tennis club, Solihull</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Acquaintances</relationships>
		<topics>Weather and seasons, work, books, education, cities, language learning, coaching techniques</topics>
		<activity>Acquaintances chatting after an exercise class.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising,  anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T14</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0138">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Leeds, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Liverpool, Merseyside</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>12 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Area manager for a chain of gyms</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0018">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> no I'm gonna <vocal desc="laugh"/> Should be alright I don't know why we've got feedback though <pause dur="short"/> maybe this yeah that's it <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="2" who="S0138">is it that?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0018">no I think it's at the I put the recording volume button up by mistake <pause dur="short"/> aagh anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah well last week I was out there interview I was interviewing em <trunc>Jak</trunc> em Jacob Jacob Jake Whites</u>
<u n="4" who="S0138" trans="overlap">Jake Whites?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah and we were doing it out in the sun and I got sunburnt and everything <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0138" trans="overlap">it's bit different isn't it? Just a wee bit different</u>
<u n="7" who="S0018">then woke up this morning opened the curtains and it was snow <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0138">it's not just snow is it? It it's freezing it's perishing isn't it <pause dur="short"/> freezing</u>
<u n="9" who="S0018">I hate it ah <pause dur="short"/> I was thinking last week wow March England I'm catching the sun I've got a suntan how can this be true</u>
<u n="10" who="S0138">yeah well ah it's good that you were thinking that way round rather than I mean she's bad isn't it cos unfortunately this is it this is  this is  the norm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah no Well I yes unfortunately <pause dur="short"/> well I got back I moved back from the Mediterranean last summer</u>
<u n="12" who="S0138">which bit of the Mediterranean?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0018">I was living in Spain in South East Spain</u>
<u n="14" who="S0138">oh right</u>
<u n="15" who="S0018">and uh yes so I thought oh gosh this winter's going to be a nightmare it's going to be awful and I got to about halfway through December and I started thinking oh I can do this you know I'm quite I'm getting quite good at surviving in these climes so I started bragging about it by going oh I can actually survive British winters oh and then everyone was like no this is not a British winter this is mild</u>
<u n="16" who="S0138" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="17" who="S0018">started feeling a bit oh dear yes how am I going to manage</u>
<u n="18" who="S0138">that's where  that's where  two sets of clothes come out</u>
<u n="19" who="S0018">exactly <pause dur="short"/> it's the old adage you can never have uh there's never there's <trunc>nev</trunc> there's <trunc>no</trunc> not a thing as a very low temperature it's just ah inadequate clothing</u>
<u n="20" who="S0138">erm uh but the actual problem is that the most countries not just this country they never get their weather forecast right so you got out wearing one thing right by the  by the  time you're out you're you end up with a car full of stuff just in case or I do anyway with a daughter and a dog</u>
<u n="21" who="S0018" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Four changes of clothes one for each season and another one for rolling down a hill in a muddy puddle</u>
<u n="22" who="S0138" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you've got it <pause dur="short"/> you must have done it</u>
<u n="23" who="S0018">no I just can't get the whole you know seasons</u>
<u n="24" who="S0138">mhm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0018">you're used to like you're used to the sun coming up and going down and you're body's used to it and you relay on it in a way but for me seasons usually I don't know follow a pattern but that's the problem here in Britain it's</u>
<u n="26" who="S0138" trans="overlap">is there a season now? Haven't got any anymore</u>
<u n="27" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="28" who="S0138">and that's why the the the flowers the animals everything is just confused</u>
<u n="29" who="S0018">ah what are we doing living here? <vocal desc="laugh"/> Have you never thought of uh maybe managing David Lloyd's abroad?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0138" trans="overlap">living? I've only worked for the business for two years</u>
<u n="31" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="32" who="S0138">so em just like if someone said we've got something in Australia em we'd like you to go and look at them <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'd probably say I'm your man</u>
<u n="33" who="S0018" trans="overlap">aha <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0138">I'd say yeah I would do</u>
<u n="35" who="S0018">and what what were you working in before or was it?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0138">in the holiday park industry <pause dur="short"/> so have you heard of well there was a company called Park Resorts</u>
<u n="37" who="S0018">aha</u>
<u n="38" who="S0138">haven? Have you heard of Haven? They're the biggest one in this country <pause dur="short"/> park Resorts were second to it so I looked after all the holiday home sales for thirty-seven parks round the country</u>
<u n="39" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh wow</u>
<u n="40" who="S0138">which if <pause dur="short"/> holiday parks are peculiar places because so you don't realise when you go on them for holidays cos you're on holiday is that it's full of people that are that work there for in my view peculiar reasons</u>
<u n="41" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0138">well they're right on the edge of the country</u>
<u n="43" who="S0018">aha</u>
<u n="44" who="S0138">and they always have this feel that says that they're  that they're  <trunc>kin</trunc> kinda trying to get away from something and that's as far as they can get away without leaving the country</u>
<u n="45" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> they're trying to marginalise themselves</u>
<u n="46" who="S0138">they've all got stories to tell <pause dur="short"/> they're they're all honestly seriously holiday homes salespeople are a breed amongst themselves</u>
<u n="47" who="S0018">really what are they like ex-convicts and? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0138" trans="overlap">no they've just got issues <pause dur="short"/> they they're uh they're not particularly ex-convicts but but there's potential convicts in future that kind of thing</u>
<u n="49" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="50" who="S0138">they've just got issues</u>
<u n="51" who="S0018">bizarre <pause dur="short"/> maybe that's</u>
<u n="52" who="S0138" trans="overlap">and the but the only trouble with the the holiday park industry is that em whereas we're right next to a motorway and the <anon type="place"/> one is right next to a motorway <anon type="place"/> right on a dual carriageway holiday parks are a are down a B road somewhere so so we used to have four of them in Norfolk and em they were forty miles away from each other and I don't mean forty miles then forty miles then forty miles they were all in a forty miles radius</u>
<u n="53" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh radius yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0138" trans="overlap">it'd take three hours to get from one to the other just just because it was holiday season you'd be stuck behind a tractor or stuck behind a caravan somewhere and uh just a nightmare getting anywhere</u>
<u n="55" who="S0018">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0138">Don't get me wrong lovely industry to be in because I used to stay in the lodges</u>
<u n="57" who="S0018">aha oh nice</u>
<u n="58" who="S0138">and um and then I'd eh get up go down for a run down the beach before I'd end up going to work <pause dur="short"/> so so and and because and the other side of it is it's a bit like</u>
<u n="59" who="S0018" trans="overlap">lovely <pause dur="short"/> and did you live up there were where you living?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0138">I was living in <anon type="place"/> at the time but I I worked away again all week I just worked away in different places all week then</u>
<u n="61" who="S0018" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> okay right</u>
<u n="62" who="S0138">but em the I suppose the nice thing about the holiday park industry is it's a bit like this <pause dur="short"/> is that <trunc>be</trunc> because they come here as their chill out time and their relax time generally speaking people are in a decent mood <pause dur="short"/> because of that <pause dur="short"/> because of that sense of holiday you you when people going on holiday they they kinda um they forgive certain things which they shouldn't to be fair but they give forgive the certain things because they're on a holiday yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yep <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Mhm <pause dur="short"/> oh I'd have thought they'd maybe of it would have been the opposite that</u>
<u n="64" who="S0138">no no some people there's some people decide I've paid for these two weeks if it isn't absolutely bang on then I'm gonna get really upset but generally speaking people are quite chilled so it's it's a nice industry to be in because of that as well <pause dur="short"/> em as opposed to walking working in a supermarket where people are not so chilled <pause dur="short"/> it might that might be my view cause I'm never chilled in a supermarket</u>
<u n="65" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Me neither I hate the places <pause dur="short"/> and so now you're you happy working here in?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0138" trans="overlap">yeah well em I left Park Resorts I'm actually finding this quite difficult because em I'm I'm I'm quite used to opening uh asking lots of open questions</u>
<u n="67" who="S0018">oh right oh</u>
<u n="68" who="S0138">and getting people to feed things back to me</u>
<u n="69" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="70" who="S0138">so I must be quite I'm uh finding it quite difficult to expand on my answers rather than stop and ask you a question and let you talk rather than me</u>
<u n="71" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Okay that's fine as well</u>
<u n="72" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0138">well not really otherwise you won't get enough of me</u>
<u n="74" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh no no that's fine too I mean I'm I use British speech so I'm I'm a guinea pig as well as a recorder</u>
<u n="75" who="S0138" trans="overlap">yeah but you can't be a guinea pig on every one can you? Em but em forgotten what I was saying there the aw yeah whether I like it <pause dur="short"/> I uh em the uh the Park Resorts stuff <pause dur="short"/> the CEO left and he was employed <unclear/> and that finished which is fine</u>
<u n="76" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0138">em and I sat down with the wife one day and I'd been a member of David Lloyd for about ten years</u>
<u n="78" who="S0018">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0138">and and she simply said well you spend all of your non working life at David Lloyd's why don't you go work for them? And and that's how it happened</u>
<u n="80" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh fantastic</u>
<u n="81" who="S0138" trans="overlap">I em it took me about seven months <pause dur="short"/> I applied uh for on a number of <trunc>occas</trunc> it's quite a I know most industries are but this is quite a village of an industry they all know each other <pause dur="short"/> so so nobody knew me so nobody was kinda everybody was kinda seeing my C <pause dur="short"/>V <pause dur="short"/> then saying I'll come back to you and then when they came back to me it was because they'd gone round asking everybody who's this big Roberts kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> nobody knew me <pause dur="short"/> anyway so so I treated getting the job a bit like a new business venture so I started courting people took a couple of people to lunch so they got to know me so yada yada da and then got a a job as a general manager in <anon type="place"/> which is a great club fabulous club worked there for twelve months but</u>
<u n="82" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> aha <pause dur="short"/> where is <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0138"><anon type="place"/> if you  if you  look on a map you know where Manchester is?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="85" who="S0138">well you know if you looked on a map the bit this way round if you were looking really at the bit <anon type="place"/> Manchester Leeds</u>
<u n="86" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="87" who="S0138">well Manchester in the middle above Manchester is Bolton and above Bolton is <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="89" who="S0138">yep okay <pause dur="short"/> em so I worked there for twelve months and I commuted backwards and forwards from <anon type="place"/> on a daily basis that was fine uh then moved down here last July em and it's just far easier to rent a place down here <pause dur="short"/> far far easier <pause dur="short"/> em but love it  but love it  the it's it's got its usual commercial pressures but em <trunc>we</trunc> when you  when you  find yourself absorbed in something it it's not pressure is it? It's more just a em a hoop to jump through rather than pressure</u>
<u n="90" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> fantastic</u>
<u n="91" who="S0138">eh <trunc>wh</trunc> Winston Churchill said that he said em make your hobby your job and you'll never work again the rest of your life and I absolutely concur with that <pause dur="short"/> concur on that totally</u>
<u n="92" who="S0018" trans="overlap">there you go you absolutely took me to the letter on that <pause dur="short"/> em do you credit your wife with the idea or did you?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0138">I will I did due just then so</u>
<u n="94" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's true</u>
<u n="95" who="S0138">I must <trunc>du</trunc> I must do that naturally all the time so</u>
<u n="96" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's a very good example of thinking out of the box wasn't it?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0138">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0018">no I went to em to see a kind of life coach cos I've just found myself in the position where I'm trying to get a new career and <vocal desc="cough"/> and she yeah she said the problem is a lot of people don't think out of the box they think in a very uh led way about what career choices they should make and just sit here now and try and make a list of things that you know  you know  you wouldn't be able to do like uh personal secretary to George Clooney or something but just write write a list of your dream jobs that even if they're not realistic that you know just write a list of them and it it's true it starts  it starts  you the process</u>
<u n="99" who="S0138" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> great <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> is that you having a thing about George Clooney? You couldn't help it</u>
<u n="100" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No that was just a random example</u>
<u n="101" who="S0138">well nothing about him's normally random but</u>
<u n="102" who="S0018" trans="overlap">could have said Harrison Ford <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0138">did well did this this funnily enough I've I've got a life coaching quality</u>
<u n="104" who="S0018">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0138">but em there's a book that you'd probably be interested in which is called Stop Talking Start Doing and it takes you through that sort of process</u>
<u n="106" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="107" who="S0138">it's very very good and it's really a really easy read</u>
<u n="108" who="S0018">aha <pause dur="short"/> what's it called again? Stop Talking?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0138" trans="overlap">stop Talking Start Doing</u>
<u n="110" who="S0018" trans="overlap">start Doing <pause dur="short"/> mhm <pause dur="short"/> very interesting</u>
<u n="111" who="S0138">and em and there's <trunc>sim</trunc> similar to what you just said there's an exercise in it where you you start thinking through the things that you like but <trunc>t</trunc> <trunc>t</trunc> to guide you down these not the things that you do at work the things that you don't do <pause dur="short"/> so the things that mentally em you have to physically em it's quite hard to think it through because em when your mind drifts off stop those moments and say what's it drifting off to? What is happening at that point? What do you find yourself leaning towards when you're driving home? Eh if you're not going to go home and you decide to do something else what do you go and do? That kind of thing</u>
<u n="112" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0138">so it very similar to what you just said</u>
<u n="114" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0138">so what was the outcome of all this for you?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="cough"/> well the outcome really was that I was going to uh drop the PGCE course that I was doing and suffering from <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0138">suffering from?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0018">oh yes</u>
<u n="119" who="S0138">okay</u>
<u n="120" who="S0018">and um take a chance on trying to get into English language teaching publishing</u>
<u n="121" who="S0138">right okay</u>
<u n="122" who="S0018">because eh one of my</u>
<u n="123" who="S0138" trans="overlap">and that's how this came about or?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0018" trans="overlap">no this is just a freelance stop gap just to have a little project while I'm sending off job applications and hopefully getting interviews but em no it's because I was ranting and raving about how I really <pause dur="short"/> she said why why don't you like educationists? It's happening in your life now while you're doing the PGCE compared to what was it before and my biggest bug bear was that you know there was no a teacher is only as good as the resources that they are using <pause dur="short"/> the educational resources that they were using em okay you can teach a whole class without any resources from time to time but</u>
<u n="125" who="S0138" trans="overlap">but but can can I ask you a question?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0018">yeah sure</u>
<u n="127" who="S0138">you used a specific word there <pause dur="short"/> she said you said she asked you why?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0138">did she use that word why? Just from a coaching point of view why is deemed as quite critical question</u>
<u n="130" who="S0018">aha <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="131" who="S0138">just cos it it it's kinda saying to it it it's almost saying to somebody why did you make that choice? So so you probably say what was it about that that stopped?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah I think she probably did I don't remember exactly <pause dur="short"/> but she's into NLP</u>
<u n="133" who="S0138">oh right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0018" trans="overlap">Neuro Linguistic <trunc>Process</trunc> Programming <pause dur="short"/> process? Programming</u>
<u n="135" who="S0138" trans="overlap">processing <pause dur="short"/> processing</u>
<u n="136" who="S0018">processing <pause dur="short"/> oh is it aha</u>
<u n="137" who="S0138" trans="overlap">em well actually both <pause dur="short"/> it's both of them</u>
<u n="138" who="S0018">it is?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0138">but you can  you can  have both of them <pause dur="short"/> eh great subject</u>
<u n="140" who="S0018">yeah no I I'd find it extremely interesting but I'm sure she's a she's like a</u>
<u n="141" who="S0138">Brewer</u>
<u n="142" who="S0018">visionary in that field so she's ah probably got her question words right it was me that was probably reporting them to be wrong</u>
<u n="143" who="S0138" trans="overlap"><trunc>Tha</trunc> <trunc>tha</trunc> <trunc>tha</trunc> that's why I thought it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that might have said it sorry</u>
<u n="144" who="S0018">no it was probably s <trunc>roc</trunc> it was probably to try and get me to specify what it was that I didn't like whereas all my life I've enjoyed being a teacher I've loved it and then that specific situation I just completely <event desc="sound of being strangled"/> turned against the idea of it</u>
<u n="145" who="S0138" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mhm <pause dur="short"/> and what was the idea what was it?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0018">the the fact that a teacher a as a teacher you need to be able to lay the foundations of a good class by planning it well and making sure that your resources are quality resources that are going to aid the learning process <pause dur="short"/> em and then once you've got that in place you can then focus on your teaching to help <trunc>lea</trunc> um students learn um that what is in front of them or what task that they have been asked to do <pause dur="short"/> so you can kind of free up your own time</u>
<u n="147" who="S0138" trans="overlap">mhm <pause dur="short"/> mhm yep</u>
<u n="148" who="S0018">by making sure that the materials are quality and reliable</u>
<u n="149" who="S0138">mhm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0018">and except in the PGCE and and the classes and the schools I observed and taught in there was no reliance on quality published materials <pause dur="short"/> it was all random bits and bats of powerpoint presentations that people got off the</u>
<u n="151" who="S0138">oh wow</u>
<u n="152" who="S0018">times Educational Supplement em and <trunc>s</trunc> online</u>
<u n="153" who="S0138">so did they have consistency?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0018">no there was no consistency these kids didn't have a class book <pause dur="short"/> so so they could see some kind of follow through of what they'd done and what they had done two weeks ago and maybe oh yeah remember how we did that two weeks ago look at that page cause that's gonna help you now now close your books and we'll do an activity <pause dur="short"/> no it was all like scrappy bits of paper printed out or photocopied and they didn't actually have pride</u>
<u n="155" who="S0138" trans="overlap">mm mm mm <pause dur="short"/> cos kids like structure don't they?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yes exactly <pause dur="short"/> and colour and you know attractive images and</u>
<u n="157" who="S0138" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> an association more than anything else it I'm doing ah something over here that actually links in to what I was talking about last week</u>
<u n="158" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yep yep <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0138">that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="160" who="S0018">definitely and I think eighty percent of language learners have a visual memory so the visuals are extremely important in language learning it helps you makes associations as you say but it also helps as a memory hook for you know you need a huge amount of new memory capacity to learn a language anything visual that can act as a hook to help you remember is is fantastic</u>
<u n="161" who="S0138" trans="overlap">yep yep <pause dur="short"/> of course <pause dur="short"/> mhm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0018">but you know those these kids were coming to class without any kind of books <pause dur="short"/> they had a text eh a class book that they'd leave in the classroom cos they couldn't be bothered to take it home cos it wasn't cool to take carry a big bag around with them <pause dur="short"/> and so they had no record bar a few scrappy bits of A4 that had been hurriedly folded and glued into their class books that they never looked at anyway <pause dur="short"/> yeah they had no reference of what they'd done how they'd progressed and also in the the you know the spontaneous moment of the learning nothing really that that em backed that up</u>
<u n="163" who="S0138" trans="overlap">so how  so how  how did you then assess them?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0018">oh well it was all done on the basis of em assessment booklets every half term <pause dur="short"/> that tested their <trunc>speak</trunc> em listening skills writing skills reading skills and then they had to do a peer to peer speaking assessment</u>
<u n="165" who="S0138">right <pause dur="short"/> I mean at parents evenings did they have parents evenings?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0018">yeah yeah they do</u>
<u n="167" who="S0138">I mean what did you show the parents?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0018">well the education nowadays is all about meeting targets and assigning levels to students so on the basis of the assessment you write down okay this kid is at level three A in their reading skills four B in their foreign language listening skills</u>
<u n="169" who="S0138">and that's all you tell them?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0018">and that's <trunc>us</trunc> what you show the parents <pause dur="short"/> the progression of marks</u>
<u n="171" who="S0138" trans="overlap">oh right I guess I guess what I meant by that was I've got a seven year old or we've we've got a seven year old</u>
<u n="172" who="S0018">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0138">uh and em when we go to em the school nights then outside the classroom for structure we got all our little times where they go in but outside the class is all of the kids' workbooks</u>
<u n="174" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="175" who="S0138">so that you you sit and read all you get there twenty minutes early so you can sit and read all them workbooks done that term</u>
<u n="176" who="S0018" trans="overlap">fantastic</u>
<u n="177" who="S0138">so that then you can either em pick up on anything that's in that workbook and talk to them about it or literally just see if that workbook corresponds with what they're saying to you and what that workbook corresponds with work you're doing with them at home <pause dur="short"/> that kind of that's what I meant by that</u>
<u n="178" who="S0018" trans="overlap">brilliant <pause dur="short"/> so that's a primary school is it?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0138" trans="overlap">yeah and then  and then  you go in and then they do the bit that you're talking about here which is should be  she should  she should be up to a C level and she's actually now at a B level great news da da da <pause dur="short"/> they do that bit but they allow you to talk things through in the first instance <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="180" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> fantastic that's a great idea <pause dur="short"/> well I guess secondary education is different in <trunc>nat</trunc> by nature because you haven't just just got one the one teacher who knows about the whole child's development</u>
<u n="181" who="S0138">which is yeah fair enough</u>
<u n="182" who="S0018">across all the subjects I think yeah maybe</u>
<u n="183" who="S0138">of course it's secondary isn't it?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0018">yeah secondary you've got a teacher for every subject but then still there's no reason why you shouldn't kids shouldn't be taking pride in creating an exercise book in class of the work that they've done or taking care of a classbook</u>
<u n="185" who="S0138" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yep</u>
<u n="186" who="S0018">A course book a text book that kinda lays it down for them in a very nice visual way and you know engages them <pause dur="short"/> it no I think I get the feeling</u>
<u n="187" who="S0138">so they didn't get into that at all?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0018">no and so what I said to this life coach was that that is one of the main reasons that I don't I'm not gelling with this teaching methodology because <pause dur="short"/> I think it's one of the most important things to engage students and to motivate them and to give them interesting visually attractive materials that are going to help them take it step by step and achieve the learning objectives of the class and without that I was lost <pause dur="short"/> cos the onus was too much on me whereas the onus should have been on them cos they're they're the ones learning I'm just like the director of the film</u>
<u n="189" who="S0138" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mhm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0018">so I said that and she said Well could you get into maybe have you though about getting into a career whereby you make these materials and I'd always kind of known that that existed but then I thought Aww yeah okay and so off that I've been very interested</u>
<u n="191" who="S0138" trans="overlap">and and and where and and where does that type of career live geographically? Is it all over the place or the the?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0018" trans="overlap">em well the the biggest  the biggest  companies are companies like Pearson Longman and uh Oxford University Press Cambridge University Press so in the big university towns</u>
<u n="193" who="S0138" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> right okay</u>
<u n="194" who="S0018">big publishing</u>
<u n="195" who="S0138">and you'd be happy to live anywhere in the U <pause dur="short"/>K</u>
<u n="196" who="S0018">not anywhere <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't particularly fancy going to London for example but yeah I'm geographically mobile <pause dur="short"/> it's not a prerequisite that it be in Solihull or Birmingham <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0138">and and are you saying you're not London cos you've been there before and didn't like it or?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0018">no well I have I lived in London for about six months <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0138" trans="overlap"><unclear/> bottom three in the championship</u>
<u n="200" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I lived in London for about six months and didn't like how vast it was</u>
<u n="201" who="S0138" trans="overlap">how old where you? Was that a long time or was?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0018" trans="overlap">ah it was  it was  when I was eighteen sorry eighteen years ago</u>
<u n="203" who="S0138">it's interesting cos I eh I used to work for <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0018">aha</u>
<u n="205" who="S0138">A long time ago <pause dur="short"/> em and I worked at their <anon type="place"/> for bout six months actually <pause dur="short"/> and I hated London</u>
<u n="206" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0138">with a passion <pause dur="short"/> think it's just dirty em I think it's em it's it's the loneliest place on the planet where so many people seem to be around</u>
<u n="208" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0138">em eh the the whole element of eh you you're never out of your work clothes for for no other reason then you you may as well stay in them and have a pint or go for a meal because it'll take you three hours to get home if you do it any other way</u>
<u n="210" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah that's exactly what was going on for me</u>
<u n="211" who="S0138" trans="overlap">all that kind of thing</u>
<u n="212" who="S0018">I lived in <anon type="place"/> and a <trunc>fr</trunc> my best friend lived in <anon type="place"/> and it would take me less time to come up to Birmingham than it would to get over to see her yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0138" trans="overlap">yeah it would to get across yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="214" who="S0018">and it was em I mean back then I'd just finished university and I was just getting you know paid by the hour jobs just to keep myself going till I went to Spain <pause dur="short"/> but yeah you you you'd spend one hour of pay on transport another hour of pay on a beer after</u>
<u n="215" who="S0138">do you coach him?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0018">no I'm a he's been talking here as well <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0138" trans="overlap">oh talking to you</u>
<u n="218" who="S0018">yeah so no so that's why I didn't like it <pause dur="short"/> and I lived in Paris as well and I had the same feeling there it was just too big and</u>
<u n="219" who="S0138">now you see I this is going to make it sound as though I'm a gipsy but em I used to work for <unclear/> cos before the leisure industry I worked for the drinks industry and <unclear/> is obviously one of their offices in <unclear/> just outside Paris <pause dur="short"/> and em I lived in em <unclear/> past four months and still can't really speak a word of French <pause dur="short"/> I get <trunc>dre</trunc> dreadful at it as I say I'm dreadful with languages <pause dur="short"/> which which is sometimes get quite annoyed about em because I'm quite a structured person so I'm going to say all this and really I'm not interested enough cos I haven't done anything about it but I've I've always been interested in structure of Latin on the basis that that's the structure of most languages and I've always though if I could get to grips with the structure of that then I could link off that and be really interested in it <pause dur="short"/> never done anything about it like but I've always thought</u>
<u n="220" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> aww <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0138">em but em <pause dur="short"/> I can I honestly I can go away on holiday and forget the town that I'm staying in <pause dur="short"/> literally <pause dur="short"/> within days of being on holiday <pause dur="short"/> because I can't remember I I don't I seem to associate <trunc>wi</trunc> different sounding</u>
<u n="222" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="223" who="S0138">things <pause dur="short"/> people's names so so people from ethnic minorities or not particular ethnic minorities but with non-British names</u>
<u n="224" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="225" who="S0138">that that so for instance when I saw your ah email actually I would tend to say to myself em Stephanie just say to myself <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I would automatically do that in my head</u>
<u n="226" who="S0018">aha</u>
<u n="227" who="S0138">I could do that with an ethnic name em or a non British name and within seconds of doing it</u>
<u n="228" who="S0018">you'll have forgotten it</u>
<u n="229" who="S0138">it'll have gone away</u>
<u n="230" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0138">and it just eh I just really really difficult for me</u>
<u n="232" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> is it because you're  is it because you're  saying it to yourself does it happen to you when you write it down? mm?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0138">em it it's the only way I've been able to learn any kind of foreign language is through play with my daughter</u>
<u n="234" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="235" who="S0138">em my daughter's school is is a school of excellence in Spanish</u>
<u n="236" who="S0018">oh oh <foreign lang="spa"/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0138">as it happens <pause dur="short"/> so she em she started speaking when she em she's seven and she started speaking it when she was literally <trunc>fi</trunc> in reception area when they first started doing it</u>
<u n="238" who="S0018">mhm super</u>
<u n="239" who="S0138" trans="overlap">so we do all all of the em the Christmas in Spanish we do em we do em animals when we're playing in Spanish</u>
<u n="240" who="S0018">aha</u>
<u n="241" who="S0138">but even now I can't remember but as soon as she started if she started doing them and playing them I'd then start getting into it more</u>
<u n="242" who="S0018">right <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="243" who="S0138">so so even to the point where I think these you you can learn some of the languages by em on a  on a on a  CD that's got all animals on it for kids</u>
<u n="244" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0138">I've actually thought I need that really <pause dur="short"/> cos cos I've I've got I've wasted so much money on Linguaphone</u>
<u n="246" who="S0018" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="247" who="S0138">Cos as a job in the past I've spent a lot of time in the car getting from A to B</u>
<u n="248" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh huh <pause dur="short"/> oh right so you've taken a</u>
<u n="249" who="S0138" trans="overlap">I've always had em in the car <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> honestly <pause dur="short"/> waste of money</u>
<u n="250" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0138">and I  and I  persevered with them I mean I I bet I've had uh weeks of hours worth of listening to this <pause dur="short"/> weeks</u>
<u n="252" who="S0018" trans="overlap">really? So it's not the repetition thing it's not the visual thing or the aural thing it's just</u>
<u n="253" who="S0138" trans="overlap">the playing thing it helps</u>
<u n="254" who="S0018">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that that may be helped maybe that helps more because it's meaningful it's making it meaningful for you <pause dur="short"/> it's not just a random nonsense syllable string</u>
<u n="255" who="S0138" trans="overlap">could be <pause dur="short"/> yeah could be</u>
<u n="256" who="S0018">maybe you should watch Dora the Explorer in Spanish</u>
<u n="257" who="S0138" trans="overlap">I do <pause dur="short"/> oh in Spanish</u>
<u n="258" who="S0018" trans="overlap">with your  with your with your  daughter <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0138">she's too old for Dora the Explorer</u>
<u n="260" who="S0018"><vocal desc="cough"/> Is she?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0138" trans="overlap">now she is yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0018" trans="overlap">aww what a shame <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="263" who="S0138" trans="overlap">yeah unfortunately even at seven years old <pause dur="short"/> yeah she's too old which is ridiculous</u>
<u n="264" who="S0018" trans="overlap">they grow up quickly don't they <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0138" trans="overlap">ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> she em she now watches eh Witches of Waverly Place which is an American thing</u>
<u n="266" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="267" who="S0138">and then she gets an attitude from it as well</u>
<u n="268" who="S0018">oh really?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0138">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0018">oh no <pause dur="short"/> you're like please go back to Dora the Explorer</u>
<u n="271" who="S0138">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> I can always remember em ah it's terrible but em when I was watching Noddy with her years ago</u>
<u n="272" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0138">em we we did quite a lot of coaching in this environment em and so my background is to do with that and when when we talk about coaching I always talk about this thing that I saw on Noddy <pause dur="short"/> with Big Ears</u>
<u n="274" who="S0018" trans="overlap">aha</u>
<u n="275" who="S0138">I don't know if they did it on purpose but it it it was perfect example of a coaching process</u>
<u n="276" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0138">this em Noddy goes up to Big Ears' house and he goes one day and goes Noddy I've got a kite can you help me put it together so he helps him put it together <pause dur="short"/> goes in couple of days later eh and this is in the Spanish <unclear/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0138">goes in a couple of days later with his bike my my bike's broken Noddy can you help me or Big Ears can you help me with this yeah course I can da da da <pause dur="short"/> so he walks out one day and em Big Ears is saying to himself Noddy's always asking for my help he doesn't seem to be able to do anything for himself I must help him</u>
<u n="280" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0138">so Noddy goes up to his house one day and Big Ears and he knocks on the door and nobody answers and Big Ears in a  in a  beard goes behind him and um says can I help you? He says I'm looking for Big Ears my friend <pause dur="short"/> Says Don't think he's in today and said em so he says em eh Aw dear <pause dur="short"/> Why what's the matter? So Noddy says I've got this this this shelf that I need to put together before I put up and I don't know how to do it <pause dur="short"/> He went oh so why'd you come to Big Ears? So Big Ears'd know how to do it <pause dur="short"/> so he said well em okay <pause dur="short"/> what would Big Ears tell you to do with it? S says Well he'd tell me to take it out of the box <pause dur="short"/> Okay what would Big Ears tell you to do with it then?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0138" trans="overlap">real classic all the way down the line <pause dur="short"/> I was sat watching it thinking they should put that on corporate stuff <pause dur="short"/> it a mind for a four year old at that time <pause dur="short"/> great <pause dur="short"/> great</u>
<u n="284" who="S0018">well maybe they should put it in a corporate thing in Spanish <pause dur="short"/> that would learn <trunc>lang</trunc></u>
<u n="285" who="S0138" trans="overlap">yeah well yeah then I'd learn two things</u>
<u n="286" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Fantastic</u>
<u n="287" who="S0138">from a  from a  coaching point of view I can remember one guy he he said something to me that was really pertinent <pause dur="short"/> em and he was coaching me and he asked me a question and I went I don't know <pause dur="short"/> and all he said to me was well pretend you do <pause dur="short"/> that's all he said <pause dur="short"/> So what would you do if you did know <pause dur="short"/> pretend you do know <pause dur="short"/> what would you do?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0138">and he kept saying this what would you do <pause dur="short"/> if you did know <pause dur="short"/> I know you don't know but pretend you do what would you do?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0138">and you follow down these routes and you find an answer</u>
<u n="292" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0138">but yeah really eh it was really</u>
<u n="294" who="S0018">that's really interesting <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0138">powerful stuff</u>
<u n="296" who="S0018">yeah I remember the um it was in a textbook actually a a a reading about um creativity</u>
<u n="297" who="S0138">mhm</u>
<u n="298" who="S0018">and one way to increase your creativity <pause dur="short"/> for example there was a journalist who'd run out of ideas of what to write about and so the her coach said okay now write about write a list of everything you wouldn't want to write about would be completely wrong and from that she started developing because she was thinking about things that wouldn't be interesting she suddenly got all these ideas about what what would be interesting</u>
<u n="299" who="S0138" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> eh well it <pause dur="short"/> you can do that as a problem solving exercise</u>
<u n="300" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="301" who="S0138">is that if you've got a em let's say you've got a customer service issue you need to get customer services rights</u>
<u n="302" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="303" who="S0138">the the best way of getting it right is to get hold of people say I'll tell you what let's do it this way</u>
<u n="304" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="305" who="S0138">the objective is to have the worst customer service in this business</u>
<u n="306" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0138">tell me all the things that you'd do to create the worst customer service</u>
<u n="308" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0138">you'd do all those things and then just flip them on the head</u>
<u n="310" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0138">em <pause dur="short"/> and then exaggerate that flip</u>
<u n="312" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0138">and it's a really good way to do stuff like that</u>
<u n="314" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah that is a good way yeah yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0138">em <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm gonna have to</u>
<u n="316" who="S0018">no problem</u>
<u n="317" who="S0138">do you mind me calling you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? You don't mind me</u>
<u n="318" who="S0018" trans="overlap">no no not at all <pause dur="short"/> thank you so much</u>
<u n="319" who="S0138">it was a pleasure</u>
<u n="320" who="S0018">for your time <pause dur="short"/> and are you working late tonight?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0138">I'm going to <anon type="place"/> now</u>
<u n="322" who="S0018">are you?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0138" trans="overlap">yeah I've got to go up to the other club</u>
<u n="324" who="S0018" trans="overlap">to the other centre</u>
<u n="325" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
</body>
</text>
