<text id="SHXX">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:47:40</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-01-31</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0187 S0386</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Home  </rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Recent transactions, Sport, Experiences, Celebrities, Work, Other family members</topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining </conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0187">
				<exactage>21</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lincoln</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Fishponds</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2.5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>e_midlands</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0386">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>Unknown</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>Barbadian</nat>
				<birthplace>Barbados</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Barbados</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig></lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>none</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Grantham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0187">erm</u>
<event desc="sound of football match on tv"/>
<u n="2" who="S0187">yeah the</u>
<u n="3" who="S0386"><unclear>really slow</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> centre back <unclear>being</unclear> so slow</u>
<u n="4" who="S0187">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> my the centre backs <pause dur="short"/> well the back line <pause dur="short"/> the three of them <pause dur="short"/> we had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who is my age <pause dur="short"/> probably a year or two older <pause dur="short"/> had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who is <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0187">dropped it?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="8" who="S0187">that's a big <unclear>dip</unclear></u>
<u n="9" who="S0386">I just took the cover off <pause dur="short"/> washed the cover</u>
<u n="10" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0386">it was last weekend <unclear>at work</unclear> <trunc>l</trunc> washed the cover <pause dur="short"/> put a cover <unclear>out there</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> pick up me phone <unclear>and went</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>Tuesday I</unclear> went back to work <pause dur="short"/> he forgot <pause dur="short"/> that it had a cover on</u>
<u n="12" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0386">took it out the pocket to put it in the other <unclear>old</unclear> pocket it dropped <unclear>on the end of</unclear> the bar so pshh <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>and a corner cracked</unclear></u>
<u n="14" who="S0187">gutted mate</u>
<u n="15" who="S0386"><trunc>sm</trunc></u>
<u n="16" who="S0187">smash well not smash but</u>
<u n="17" who="S0386">wasted</u>
<u n="18" who="S0187">yeah that's</u>
<u n="19" who="S0386">they're getting walked all over now aren't they?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0386">getting slaughtered</u>
<u n="22" who="S0187">that's a bad one as well cos it's not <pause dur="short"/> it's bent the shape of two different parts of the frame so</u>
<u n="23" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>bent</unclear> <unclear>pushed it out</unclear></u>
<u n="24" who="S0187">it's not like you can replace the hard screen or anything <pause dur="short"/> you'd have to replace the whole phone like the whole cover <pause dur="short"/> still take it somewhere and see if they'll do it <pause dur="short"/> your insurance might just replace it</u>
<u n="25" who="S0386">they will <pause dur="short"/> for free</u>
<u n="26" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0386">pay twelve quid <vocal desc="laugh"/> a month insurance</u>
<u n="28" who="S0187">I pay <trunc>si</trunc></u>
<u n="29" who="S0386">I</u>
<u n="30" who="S0187">I pay six quid a month <trunc>ins</trunc> no <pause dur="short"/> I pay <pause dur="short"/> about four quid a month insurance but I need to check and see whether it's <trunc>f</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> covering this phone or whether it's <trunc>co</trunc> my old phone</u>
<u n="31" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/> covering your old phone</u>
<u n="32" who="S0187">I think it will be <pause dur="short"/> I remember seeing it on my thing and thinking I need to sort that out and I haven't yet <pause dur="short"/> and that was a month ago</u>
<u n="33" who="S0386"><unclear>ah you need insurance</unclear></u>
<u n="34" who="S0187" trans="overlap">so I don't know if this is insured or not</u>
<u n="35" who="S0386"><unclear>I don't think you can tell when the offer's</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0386"><unclear/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0187">you will when the phone stops working cos you've got <pause dur="short"/> crap in it <pause dur="short"/> yeah these these guys with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who's in his thirties <pause dur="short"/> he's had</u>
<u n="39" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0187">he's had erm <pause dur="short"/> he just talks a lot of crap <pause dur="short"/> and erm he's about six foot <pause dur="short"/> what's that? receipt for <pause dur="short"/> he showed me the receipt</u>
<u n="41" who="S0386">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I said to him send me the receipt</u>
<u n="42" who="S0187">thirty-one pounds?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0386">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0187">so where have you got thirty-two pounds from?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0386">yeah cos that's a different company this is the company</u>
<u n="46" who="S0187">oh right</u>
<u n="47" who="S0386">he's actually bought the stuff off who he was expecting stuff from</u>
<u n="48" who="S0187">ridiculous</u>
<u n="49" who="S0386">so <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna ring him back actually and tell him <unclear/>  see what happened</u>
<u n="50" who="S0187">so how have they? how have? how are the two <trunc>e</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> you must've paid sixty-three quid then if there's two receipts existing</u>
<u n="51" who="S0386">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0187">you have?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0386">yes I have</u>
<u n="54" who="S0187">oh right</u>
<u n="55" who="S0386">cos I've paid for two different items <unclear>actual</unclear> different companies</u>
<u n="56" who="S0187" trans="overlap">I <trunc>th</trunc> yeah I thought you were on I thought you were saying that you're getting a refund for the <pause dur="short"/> for the glove box</u>
<u n="57" who="S0386" trans="overlap">I'll get <trunc>s</trunc> I'll get a refund for that</u>
<u n="58" who="S0187">for the glove box?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0386">yeah but I've gotta send it back <pause dur="short"/> I've gotta send it back</u>
<u n="60" who="S0187">yeah and then you're gonna get a refund for they're gonna they're gonna cancel that order have you gotta send that other order back? when it comes on Tuesday?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0386">no I've got <unclear>you know</unclear> that <unclear/> <unclear>fitted</unclear> on Tuesday I've got this</u>
<event desc="sound of phone ringing"/>
<u n="62" who="S0187">right</u>
<u n="63" who="S0386">alright <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> yes pretty good thank you <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah be fine <pause dur="short"/> okay <unclear/> that's that's great thanks <pause dur="short"/> okey-doke thanks bye</u>
<u n="64" who="S0187">yeah it just sounds like a massive massive chore</u>
<u n="65" who="S0386">cos I've gotta well the post office is shut now I gotta box that up and get it to the post office</u>
<u n="66" who="S0187"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0386">it's not very heavy just <unclear>great big box</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0187" trans="overlap">big box yeah the size of it'll still matter <pause dur="short"/> painful <pause dur="short"/> anyway <pause dur="short"/> these morons at the back <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s about six foot two <pause dur="short"/> just he's not well he is fat but he's like just a standard <pause dur="short"/> a standard middle not middle-aged but getting towards middle age he's probably older than that <pause dur="short"/> getting towards middle age <pause dur="short"/> erm he's definitely older than that he's probably in his forties <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> middle-aged man <pause dur="short"/> so he's heavy <pause dur="short"/> and this other lump who got taken off I think at half time who I'd never met before but is awful <pause dur="short"/> I've got these guys at the back in a back three and we've got wing backs of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who's <trunc>si</trunc> who's seventeen or eighteen he's <pause dur="short"/> he's one of our better players <pause dur="short"/> he's so skinny like he's my height but he is he is weedy as anything</u>
<u n="69" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0187">yeah he joked at me I think what it <trunc>wa</trunc> I can't remember what it was he's <pause dur="short"/> we're in a <trunc>war</trunc> we're er warming up before training of like before Christmas <pause dur="short"/> and he said summat about <pause dur="short"/> being embarrassed cos I knocked him off balance or something <pause dur="short"/> and I started laughing and literally just got me arm and just went like that and threw him <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I was like are you having a laugh? cos he weighs nothing <pause dur="short"/> and I think he just thought that I was in the same boat as him but I'm light but I'm not <trunc>w</trunc>weak <pause dur="short"/> but erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah the I dunno who was right right wing back <pause dur="short"/> but yeah these guys the three slowest centre backs I've ever seen <pause dur="short"/> like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is <pause dur="short"/> probably <pause dur="short"/> about as pacey as a regular centre back at this standard <pause dur="short"/> but he can't judge a ball and doesn't know what he's doing <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> this ball's coming down it's dropping I'm thinking right a proper centre back's just gonna head that away <pause dur="short"/> easy <pause dur="short"/> head it away or bring it down <pause dur="short"/> do something with it <pause dur="short"/> he goes to it and then goes shit no backs off</u>
<u n="71" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0187">let's the ball bounce <pause dur="short"/> so then it's bouncing up <pause dur="short"/> he's off balance <pause dur="short"/> the striker's thinking I've struck gold here <pause dur="short"/> he just goes and nicks if off his head <pause dur="short"/> not and flicks one on to his other strike partner who just gasses our other two slow centre <vocal desc="laugh"/> backs <pause dur="short"/> they run through and score <pause dur="short"/> second thing <pause dur="short"/> I go mental at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like why you letting a ball bounce? like even if you lose the ball from heading it somewhere don't let the ball bounce cos it puts you in a whole world of trouble <pause dur="short"/> like two minutes later <pause dur="short"/> we lose the ball it goes back into them <pause dur="short"/> dunno what happened but the ball goes goes through <pause dur="short"/> they get outpaced again</u>
<u n="73" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0187">keeper misses it keeper looks like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but like a neo Nazi version <pause dur="short"/> covered in tattoos like all down his neck all over his body he looks so scary <pause dur="short"/> he misses the ball <pause dur="short"/> I dunno what he was trying to kick but he missed the ball then he went through scored <pause dur="short"/> two more goals pretty much exactly the same <pause dur="short"/> me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are looking at each other in centre mid we're in centre mid cos they put <pause dur="short"/> we had a five men midfield and they just put the best five players in midfield basically <pause dur="short"/> cos me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were playing upfront but he played really well in centre mid and <pause dur="short"/> I think they just wanted a strong <trunc>s</trunc> a strong midfield <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> we were playing well like we were doing really well <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> but every five seconds they went and attacked <pause dur="short"/> it was like they were gonna score and they scored four <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> managed to score one we made quite a few chances he could've had he could've a hat-trick <pause dur="short"/> he could've have had four maybe but <pause dur="short"/> we're in a situation where we literally <pause dur="short"/> if we don't take every chance we get we'll lose <pause dur="short"/> cos the defence are so bad <pause dur="short"/> we'd benefit loads I think if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went at centre back <pause dur="short"/> cos he heads a ball like no one's business <pause dur="short"/> and he's a <trunc>f</trunc> he's a good footballer <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> he can judge a ball <pause dur="short"/> he's quick <pause dur="short"/> like he's everything you would want at this level in a centre back but <pause dur="short"/> he's wasted at centre back cos <pause dur="short"/> he scores goals <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> yeah sets up attack and stuff it is <pause dur="short"/> it's just minging <pause dur="short"/> hate it so much <pause dur="short"/> knowing that there's nothing nothing I can do no matter how well I play or <unclear>me and</unclear> someone else plays we're gonna lose <pause dur="short"/> we haven't got a game for two weeks now but</u>
<u n="75" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0187">we're erm <pause dur="short"/> it's just yeah it's just crap <pause dur="short"/> there were two lads that used to play for us but they left <pause dur="short"/> wherever they went I should've gone but they turned up to watch the game and they every so often they come and turn up and watch the games <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> even though it's now a completely different team to what it was when they left <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> and they were sat in the car after the game and I was like yeah <pause dur="short"/> he was like what do you think of that I was like yeah <pause dur="short"/> and they started laughing <pause dur="short"/> and er <pause dur="short"/> I was just like the back line is ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> they started laughing their heads off and then I was like yeah so if you know of any er defenders that you know might be knocking around <pause dur="short"/> cos they both play one plays left back another plays <pause dur="short"/> no they both play left back actually but one can play in centre back <pause dur="short"/> was just thinking we lost games last year but the talent in the team <pause dur="short"/> was just we had a crap manager <pause dur="short"/> the talent in the team last year is completely different to what it is now <pause dur="short"/> it's like playing for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear>and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</unclear></u>
<u n="77" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> does he still play football?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0187"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? yeah <pause dur="short"/> say <trunc>b</trunc> I think couple of weeks ago he played against a <trunc>lo</trunc> <trunc>sh</trunc> the <unclear>kids</unclear> <unclear/> the teachers <pause dur="short"/> but he's still captain of he's still captain of the reserves I don't think he's played for the firsts I don't think he's got a sniff for them at the moment <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> especially being captain I always <unclear>found that's a weird thing</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> having captain of the reserves you don't really wanna lose your captain to have him play for the firsts <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <trunc>n</trunc> I think he plays for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s every so often when he hasn't got a game but he's in Wales at the moment so</u>
<u n="79" who="S0386"><unclear/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0187">yeah I don't know either I text him last night and just said I hear you're in Wales <pause dur="short"/> he said yeah first day was pretty good <pause dur="short"/> but these glasses are broken</u>
<u n="81" who="S0386">are they? where?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0187">they're coming apart the lens is coming out <pause dur="short"/> oh no it's not</u>
<u n="83" who="S0386"><unclear/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0187"><vocal desc="laugh"/> my er</u>
<u n="85" who="S0386">I think somebody <unclear>reckon</unclear> <unclear/> <unclear>he must've</unclear> sat on that <unclear>thing</unclear> up there <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> picked up <unclear>didn't he?</unclear></u>
<u n="86" who="S0187">frame's bent</u>
<u n="87" who="S0386">yeah the <unclear>hand</unclear> come off</u>
<u n="88" who="S0187">mm brilliant <pause dur="short"/> what a ball that is</u>
<u n="89" who="S0386"><unclear>I</unclear> have actually got four pairs of glasses <pause dur="short"/> because <unclear/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0187" trans="overlap">you've only got two eyes dad</u>
<u n="91" who="S0386">well I got two pairs last time and I got two pairs this time when I went two years ago or three years ago however long it <trunc>we</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> but I can't see any difference <pause dur="short"/> there obviously is a difference <pause dur="short"/> or maybe there isn't <pause dur="short"/> maybe they just charged me because</u>
<u n="92" who="S0187"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0386">I went</u>
<u n="94" who="S0187">it was a different prescription?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0386" trans="overlap">er <pause dur="short"/> yeah had another eye check and stuff</u>
<u n="96" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0386">and <pause dur="short"/> he said here <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>this is for your new</unclear> glasses <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> he never said to me you know how is it any worse <pause dur="short"/> he <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="98" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0386">he said to me cos I read the fine ones he asked me to read the thing I read I could see them <unclear>completely</unclear> clear at the bottom</u>
<u n="100" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0386">and he said well that's strange because normally people can't read the ones at the bottom</u>
<u n="102" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0386">erm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0187">so your eyes are fine?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but <unclear>well I'm not</unclear> it's just for close I can read for a distance but I can't</u>
<u n="106" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0386" trans="overlap">it's a bit blurred when I get close <pause dur="short"/> when I got the glasses I brought them home <pause dur="short"/> and I can't see any difference between the new ones and the pair I had before</u>
<u n="108" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0386">there must be a very very slight difference if there is <pause dur="short"/> cos I can't look into them I can't see any difference</u>
<u n="110" who="S0187">it might just</u>
<u n="111" who="S0386" trans="overlap">so I've got so I've got four pairs</u>
<u n="112" who="S0187" trans="overlap">it might just be a case of <pause dur="short"/> you can't see a difference but they're looking after your eyes in terms of the little fine differences that you can't see</u>
<u n="113" who="S0386">yeah they're probably <unclear>to be fair</unclear> there erm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0187" trans="overlap">it prevented</u>
<u n="115" who="S0386">there obviously is little difference between them</u>
<u n="116" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0386">but I can't physically see it so I've got four pairs of glasses <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0187">mental</u>
<u n="119" who="S0386">I've got one at work <pause dur="short"/> that was in the car</u>
<u n="120" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0386">there was that pair <unclear>and all the other pairs</unclear></u>
<u n="122" who="S0187"><unclear>though I haven't actually</unclear> got glasses like erm <pause dur="short"/> you know that picture I sent labyrinth</u>
<u n="123" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0187">yeah <pause dur="short"/> those are sick he's got a pair like that but they're just see-through like fashion things they're not proper ones <pause dur="short"/> but I yeah I dunno why he didn't go for them cos the ones he's got <trunc>l</trunc> he looks well geeky</u>
<u n="125" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>said he looked like</unclear> Mr Raccoon</u>
<u n="126" who="S0187">Mr Raccoon?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0386"><unclear>he</unclear> <unclear/> Mr Raccoon</u>
<u n="128" who="S0187">he doesn't no I I didn't I'd heard of him I didn't know what it was <pause dur="short"/> I I have seen that before <pause dur="short"/> just erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I watched it I was like there's I <trunc>f</trunc> watched a four minute video on YouTube and was laughing</u>
<u n="129" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>I wouldn't watch that that <pause dur="short"/> terrible isn't it?</unclear></u>
<u n="130" who="S0187">it's the one where he goes into the gym <pause dur="short"/> he thinks it's a dance studio</u>
<u n="131" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't <unclear>remember I'm sorry</unclear></u>
<u n="132" who="S0187" trans="overlap">and he he wrecks the place</u>
<u n="133" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0187"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> it's well funny <pause dur="short"/> I was watching I think the boys are trying to watch a film or watching d'you know like Soccer Saturday or something like that I can't remember what it was but er <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc> like what the hell are you watching?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> it's funny</u>
<u n="136" who="S0187">I need to do some work</u>
<u n="137" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0187">what time is it? ten to one</u>
<u n="139" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0386">did a stop check yesterday I didn't count them <pause dur="short"/> I didn't add them up</u>
<u n="141" who="S0187">I was gonna say you did a stop check but you didn't count them?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes</u>
<u n="143" who="S0187" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> just looked around at the pigs for a little bit</u>
<u n="144" who="S0386"><unclear/> <unclear>conservation</unclear> so I don't know <unclear>if I've gotta do that</unclear></u>
<u n="145" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="146" who="S0386">I've got to go <unclear/> I've gotta go I've gotta go and buy some bits</u>
<u n="147" who="S0187">yeah what's that like?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0386">it's nice actually <unclear/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0187" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="150" who="S0386"><unclear>they've done</unclear> quite a lot <pause dur="short"/> they've kept it apart from</u>
<u n="151" who="S0187">ooh</u>
<u n="152" who="S0386">ooh how did that not go in there</u>
<u n="153" who="S0187">dunno how the keeper hasn't got the ball yet</u>
<u n="154" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0187">keep smiling</u>
<u n="156" who="S0386">it's great how they've painted they've redecorated the walls and stuff made the walls look</u>
<u n="157" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0386">clean <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> passage <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>it was <trunc>y</trunc> a bit maybe a little bit</unclear> scruffy I did comment on it but</u>
<u n="159" who="S0187">who's looking at it who's like doing that?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0386">mm?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0187">who's doing that?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0386">what?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0187">like <pause dur="short"/> doing all doing work to it?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0386">they're they're they they do it themself</u>
<u n="165" who="S0187">who they live there?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0187">and they're paying rent?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0386">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0187">and you're letting them do it?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0386">eh?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0187">and you're just letting them? are they making it better?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0386">well they've asked me to do to <vocal desc="laugh"/> to paint anything</u>
<u n="173" who="S0187">that should be in the agreement surely whether they're allowed to paint or not</u>
<u n="174" who="S0386" trans="overlap">it is in the agreement <trunc>e</trunc>eh?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0187">whether they're allowed to paint or not should be involved in the agreement</u>
<u n="176" who="S0386" trans="overlap">well they asked me <unclear/> if they could repaint the bedroom and I said yeah so they assumed that <pause dur="short"/> that that was for the whole house</u>
<u n="177" who="S0187" trans="overlap">that they could paint everywhere yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0386">but she said to me yeah we've <trunc>red</trunc> I've redone the bathroom but they just stripped the paper off and painted it</u>
<u n="179" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0386">erm and I said at the time I said to them as long as you're not putting any you're not putting any heavy colours on if you're gonna repaint it with light colours</u>
<u n="181" who="S0187" trans="overlap">pastel colours yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0386">yeah and that's what she's done so I haven't got got a problem</u>
<u n="183" who="S0187" trans="overlap">yeah fair enough <pause dur="short"/> any chance of me living there when I come back?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0386">but <vocal desc="laugh"/> it might be cos <unclear>I dunno</unclear></u>
<u n="185" who="S0187" trans="overlap">I did <trunc>th</trunc> I did think about it but I mentioned it and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went what about you living there? like have you ever thought about living there when you</u>
<u n="186" who="S0386" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0187">finish</u>
<u n="188" who="S0386">pay the rent</u>
<u n="189" who="S0187">well no yeah I <trunc>f</trunc> have to I'd have to pay rent obviously but I thought it's not a bad shout <pause dur="short"/> which means I'd have to live in Grantham but</u>
<u n="190" who="S0386">erm <pause dur="short"/> there's <trunc>g</trunc>got a couple of issues like <pause dur="short"/> the fire <trunc>exting</trunc> the fire <pause dur="short"/> the smoke alarm <pause dur="short"/> he said <pause dur="short"/> he said they left a smoke alarm there but it's obviously was older <pause dur="short"/> he said the fire service come round <pause dur="short"/> went round all the house and put fire alarms up <trunc>sm</trunc>smoke detectors up</u>
<u n="191" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0386">and they lasted <pause dur="short"/> reckon they lasted a couple of years</u>
<u n="193" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0386">and then one of them two of them kept going off <pause dur="short"/> I said just worn the batteries out they said no we've put new batteries in but just every so often they just go off in the middle of the night</u>
<u n="195" who="S0187">yeah <pause dur="short"/> brilliant <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0187">brilliant</u>
<u n="198" who="S0386">so they got angry and took them down and chuck them away <pause dur="short"/> I said why don't you ring the fire service?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0187">yeah I know</u>
<u n="200" who="S0386">they said ah <pause dur="short"/> so I'm gonna go and buy a couple of smoke alarms and give them to put up</u>
<u n="201" who="S0187">no just ring the <trunc>f</trunc> cos you will get them for free they'll just they'll sort out whatever issues it was <pause dur="short"/> cos I rang them up for grandma didn't I? and I'm sure they're <trunc>f</trunc> er dunno whether they <trunc>e</trunc>even bother <trunc>f</trunc>fitting or not but</u>
<u n="202" who="S0386">for grandma?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0187">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos they their things were going off both of them were going off</u>
<u n="204" who="S0386">yeah I know I said to him once I went there I said to him these why doesn't somebody do something about these? but anyway he <unclear/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0187">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I got the</u>
<u n="206" who="S0386">but I also wanna put a <trunc>m</trunc> carbon monoxide monitor in the house</u>
<u n="207" who="S0187">why?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0386">because they've got that back boiler thing</u>
<u n="209" who="S0187">right</u>
<u n="210" who="S0386">and they should have one in there <pause dur="short"/> especially <unclear>given that</unclear> so the guy said <pause dur="short"/> it was leaking slightly</u>
<u n="211" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="212" who="S0386">so I'm gonna go and check it and they say they'll they'll maybe replace it completely <pause dur="short"/> but I'm not sure I'll put a back boiler I might just do a combi boiler</u>
<u n="213" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0386">trouble is there's nowhere in the kitchen to put it</u>
<u n="215" who="S0187">yeah I haven't seen that seen that place in years</u>
<u n="216" who="S0386">haven't been there for years used to drive past and have a look</u>
<u n="217" who="S0187">mm <pause dur="short"/> check it's not burnt down</u>
<u n="218" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/> to check it's not boarded up</u>
<u n="219" who="S0187">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0386">but er</u>
<u n="221" who="S0187">what's the place in Swindon like?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0386">haven't been there for years either <pause dur="short"/> that's</u>
<u n="223" who="S0187">is it making any money?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0386">it's</u>
<u n="225" who="S0187">cos <trunc>i</trunc> you said it makes money when it <trunc>peo</trunc> when it's full but as soon as it's not it's</u>
<u n="226" who="S0386" trans="overlap">when it's full <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's erm <pause dur="short"/> I haven't decided what to do with that it's not really that profitable <pause dur="short"/> cos happily I would've happily I would <unclear/> they've just changed the erm <pause dur="short"/> they've changed the agent <pause dur="short"/> the agency that was doing it sold up to another was bought up by another company</u>
<u n="227" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0386">and that other company's actually charging me less</u>
<u n="229" who="S0187">it's <trunc>de</trunc></u>
<u n="230" who="S0386">erm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0187">it's decent</u>
<u n="232" who="S0386"><unclear>the</unclear> company's doing <pause dur="short"/> and they're actually doing what they're supposed to do cos</u>
<u n="233" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0386">I rung the water board said they kept <pause dur="short"/> they wanna go and check the meter <pause dur="short"/> and they kept <pause dur="short"/> asking me could they <trunc>s</trunc> fix up a time for them to come in cos they think I live there <pause dur="short"/> although they're sending mails here and like and bills here</u>
<u n="235" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0386">I rung the I rung the people and said to them look Thames Water wanna come and check the meter <pause dur="short"/> could you <pause dur="short"/> arrange a time so that somebody could be there either one of the tenants or one of yourselves so that somebody could be there</u>
<u n="237" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0386">to sort it out <pause dur="short"/> and could you ring Thames Water and sort with them <pause dur="short"/> and he give me all sorts of crap of why they couldn't erm <pause dur="short"/> they couldn't guarantee that there would be somebody that <unclear>that was <trunc>avai</trunc> be <trunc>avail</trunc></unclear> I said well get one of the tenants to be there</u>
<u n="239" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0386">just ask one of the tenants roughly when they're gonna be home and arrange or something they'd be there and they give me all sorts of crap but they never went</u>
<u n="241" who="S0187"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0386">cos they we could never <pause dur="short"/> every time they rung you know I said well <pause dur="short"/> in the end I gave them the I rung up and gave them the agency number</u>
<u n="243" who="S0187">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0386">but since this since this erm <pause dur="short"/> company's been charged <pause dur="short"/> they've taken over <pause dur="short"/> they've actually they went and read the water meter and went and read the electric meter</u>
<u n="245" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="246" who="S0386">and I haven't paid electric for any electricity for two quarters <pause dur="short"/> because they couldn't get in they were estimating the bill</u>
<u n="247" who="S0187">right <pause dur="short"/> that can well that can go one of two ways then</u>
<u n="248" who="S0386">well yes</u>
<u n="249" who="S0187">can't it?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0386">it could go very badly <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="252" who="S0386">but I've obviously been overpaying <pause dur="short"/> which is better than not paying enough</u>
<u n="253" who="S0187" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0386">so they know the gas <pause dur="short"/> both the gas and the water for the last two months <pause dur="short"/> in quarters</u>
<u n="255" who="S0187" trans="overlap">do they take it off the bill that you would pay?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0386">yeah <pause dur="short"/> last two quarters I haven't paid any money</u>
<u n="257" who="S0187">good we've got <vocal desc="laugh"/> our water estimate</u>
<u n="258" who="S0386" trans="overlap">I've got it here actually is it?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0187">our water estimate is for a four bedroom house <pause dur="short"/> cos no not four yeah <pause dur="short"/> is it for a four? a three or four bedroom house <pause dur="short"/> is our water estimate</u>
<u n="260" who="S0386">a hundred and thirty quid in debit</u>
<u n="261" who="S0187">a hundred and thirty quid? oh so they owe you a hundred and thirty quid?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0187">decent <pause dur="short"/> yeah we've got gas electric is <pause dur="short"/> obviously we pay on a meter but <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had the choice he was like you either pay do we get a meter for your water and you pay <trunc>a</trunc>as and when based on that <pause dur="short"/> or we'll give you an estimate and pay that <pause dur="short"/> but the house is registered as a three or four bedroom house</u>
<u n="264" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="265" who="S0187">despite there being seven of us living there</u>
<u n="266" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0187">so we pay nothing in comparison to what we actually should be paying</u>
<u n="268" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0187">and we don't pay council tax cos we're students so <pause dur="short"/> decent <pause dur="short"/> saying that I don't pay it but there is a water bill coming up by the way <pause dur="short"/> not that <pause dur="short"/> you pay not that you see it but</u>
<u n="270" who="S0386">this is the gas bill <pause dur="short"/> three hundred and fifty-seven quid in debit</u>
<u n="271" who="S0187">they owe you three hundred and seventy quid?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0386">so they owe me five hundred quid</u>
<u n="273" who="S0187">jeez</u>
<u n="274" who="S0386">altogether <pause dur="short"/> there was an issue with the gas because I <unclear>one year gas</unclear> somebody was in the house and <pause dur="short"/> I got a massive bill I thought who <pause dur="short"/> who's using? who's using all this <trunc>elec</trunc> all this gas?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="276" who="S0386">and I thought it was because somebody new had moved in but when I did check the bill it was an estimated bill</u>
<u n="277" who="S0187">right</u>
<u n="278" who="S0386">and <pause dur="short"/> I keep telling people let the gas people in <pause dur="short"/> trying to <unclear>read</unclear> let them in to read the meter</u>
<u n="279" who="S0187" trans="overlap">just sort it out yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0386">and I keep saying <pause dur="short"/> but it's funny cos they had some company rung here and asked if erm <pause dur="short"/> hey penalty</u>
<u n="281" who="S0187">absolute nightmare defending</u>
<u n="282" who="S0386">asked me if <unclear>I</unclear> wanna change the agencies</u>
<u n="283" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0386">so they obviously knew I was we were getting complaints <pause dur="short"/> from other people <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> just touch him and go over</u>
<u n="285" who="S0187">it's the first time I've seen him play <pause dur="long"/> he still talks to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> every so often apparently</u>
<u n="286" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0187">they were just shouting Chelsea reject at him</u>
<u n="288" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0187"><unclear>these</unclear> people are so rich</u>
<u n="290" who="S0386">like footballers?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0187"><trunc>f</trunc> it's insane <pause dur="short"/> the</u>
<u n="292" who="S0386">oh yeah the on the erm</u>
<u n="293" who="S0187">the lower league ones aren't but <unclear>Hull are</unclear></u>
<u n="294" who="S0386" trans="overlap">this and the <pause dur="long"/> <unclear>on the British</unclear> rich list <pause dur="short"/> whatever it's called <pause dur="short"/> the top twenty-three quarters or footballers or half the footballers or something</u>
<u n="295" who="S0187">really?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0386">they were saying the other night I I just got a glimpse of it something I was watching <pause dur="short"/> I didn't really pay I wasn't really paying attention but then when they said three quarters of <trunc>m</trunc> football I just registered that's what they said but I didn't really</u>
<u n="297" who="S0187">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's not surprising if you think <pause dur="short"/> in they like this is Championship football they get a decent wedge</u>
<u n="298" who="S0386">who's gonna spend a hundred and seventy on <unclear>two houses</unclear> a week</u>
<u n="299" who="S0187"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah but <pause dur="short"/> you have an amazing house which you then have to heat and whatever and</u>
<u n="300" who="S0386">obviously not gonna spend it are you?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0187">depends how nice your house is</u>
<u n="302" who="S0386">well if your house is that nice it wouldn't cost you anything to heat</u>
<u n="303" who="S0187">er true I suppose <pause dur="short"/> it'd cost you lot to buy it though</u>
<u n="304" who="S0386" trans="overlap">because <pause dur="short"/> it'd cost a lot to buy but I mean you buy <unclear/> that's it you <trunc>wi</trunc> you will never have a mortgage</u>
<u n="305" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0386">erm <pause dur="short"/> you'd have it insulated properly so <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="307" who="S0187">so you don't pay yeah</u>
<u n="308" who="S0386"><unclear>paid your heating</unclear> and</u>
<u n="309" who="S0187">solar panels and whatever <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0386">yeah whatever is <pause dur="short"/> even without solar panels if it's well insulated and you have underfloor heating</u>
<u n="311" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="312" who="S0386">it <pause dur="short"/> it erm it's so much cheaper than these blooming things here <pause dur="short"/> I tell you we have <pause dur="short"/> up in that farm I know somebody in the <trunc>f</trunc> in the farm there <pause dur="short"/> I remember I <unclear>do the rest</unclear> this is all next year <unclear>I'm still about</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> we had some lamps <pause dur="short"/> they've got heat lamps that heat the <pause dur="short"/> we still have to use them when we <trunc>s</trunc> the first room first going to heat the room up</u>
<u n="313" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="314" who="S0386">well we had some heat pads we bought some heat pads <pause dur="short"/> put in the in the bottom of the <unclear>crate</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> for the pigs to lie on <pause dur="short"/> they're not very hot they're not as hot as lamps</u>
<u n="315" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0386">obviously neon <pause dur="short"/> but it's made such a big difference to the quality of the pig erm <pause dur="short"/> I haven't measured the <trunc>electric</trunc> but I'm sure it's a lot less electricity erm <pause dur="short"/> using the heat lamps</u>
<u n="317" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0386">cos a lot <pause dur="short"/> they don't <pause dur="short"/> it's not as hot <pause dur="short"/> there's not a lot of wasted heat</u>
<u n="319" who="S0187">can you use halogen lamps?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0386">yeah you can use halogen lamps</u>
<u n="321" who="S0187">cos they're supposed to heat the <pause dur="short"/> don't understand how they work but they don't they heat like the body rather than just heating the surrounding air? or have I misunderstood that?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0386">I dunno they're <pause dur="short"/> halogen lamps isn't for heating they're for <pause dur="short"/> light</u>
<u n="323" who="S0187">yeah but I've heard they they're <pause dur="short"/> they don't yeah they don't get hot but they're warm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0386" trans="overlap">no like you can touch the bulb they don't they don't er</u>
<u n="325" who="S0187">yeah they don't emit heat as such but they</u>
<u n="326" who="S0386">that's why they erm <pause dur="short"/> all of <trunc>y</trunc> all the erm <pause dur="short"/> the new replacement bulbs on on the farm gonna be they're gonna be halogen</u>
<u n="327" who="S0187">halogen yeah <pause dur="short"/> waste as much energy</u>
<u n="328" who="S0386"><unclear>you never have</unclear> <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>but</unclear></u>
<u n="329" who="S0187">they they yeah they're just they're painful it <pause dur="short"/> it's a lot of money that they've got to throw around</u>
<u n="330" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="331" who="S0187">cos if you think like a Premier League footballer <pause dur="short"/> obviously they're talking like the top players but <pause dur="short"/> you mean Phil Jones <pause dur="short"/> I know he's a Manchester United footballer but he's on fifty grand a year <pause dur="short"/> that is a quality a wage for <trunc>someo</trunc> a quality salary</u>
<u n="332" who="S0386">fifty grand a year?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0187">no <trunc>fi</trunc> he earns fiftty grand a week sorry <pause dur="short"/> fifty grand a year is a quality salary for anyone but he gets that every seven days</u>
<u n="334" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="335" who="S0187"><trunc>se</trunc> every seven days</u>
<u n="336" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/> also they can't spend it <pause dur="short"/> because a lot of the stuff that ordinary mortals they go and buy <pause dur="short"/> they get given</u>
<u n="337" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0386">they get sponsored <pause dur="short"/> their boots are free their clothes are free</u>
<u n="339" who="S0187" trans="overlap">yeah they don't have to pay for <trunc>a</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> anything football related they don't have to pay</u>
<u n="340" who="S0386">erm <pause dur="short"/> they would probably get a car given</u>
<u n="341" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0386" trans="overlap"><unclear>they</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> you know a lot of these Land Rovers <unclear>unless</unclear> they go and buy one because especially <unclear>a lot of them</unclear> a lot of these four-by-fours and stuff these guys run around in they're given</u>
<u n="343" who="S0187">mm <pause dur="short"/> barcelona had a <pause dur="short"/> apparently Messi and Iniesta spoke to Alexander Hleb when he went from Arsenal to Barca <pause dur="short"/> they had like a deal with it was either Audi or Mercedes <pause dur="short"/> and Hleb basically went and got the most expensive Mercedes he could</u>
<u n="344" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="345" who="S0187">because he could do and they were like no that's not how we do things over here</u>
<u n="346" who="S0386" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0187">you get get this one but <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was a free car</u>
<u n="348" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0187">so he just got like the most flashy one he could</u>
<u n="350" who="S0386">yeah they give you even in cricket <pause dur="short"/> in cricket erm these people that play for these these</u>
<u n="351" who="S0187">IPL and</u>
<u n="352" who="S0386">yeah but the the county county cricketers get given cars</u>
<u n="353" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0386">because it's advertisement for them</u>
<u n="355" who="S0187">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0386">you see <unclear/> ran around in a big four-by-four everybody who got a little bit of money and that could <trunc>f</trunc> afford would go and wanna go and buy one</u>
<u n="357" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0386">cos he's got one</u>
<u n="359" who="S0187">puts you in the same bracket as him</u>
<u n="360" who="S0386">yeah so they don't they don't they're not gonna spend it</u>
<u n="361" who="S0187" trans="overlap">and one one car to them isn't an isn't a big deal</u>
<u n="362" who="S0386">no <pause dur="short"/> they're not gonna spend it</u>
<u n="363" who="S0187">yeah I <trunc>th</trunc> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> the only thing that you can kinda go well alright is the fact that their career's so short</u>
<u n="364" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="365" who="S0187">which is the trouble for lower league footballers because <pause dur="short"/> they've gotta find something <pause dur="short"/> they have to find something <pause dur="short"/> to do after football to earn money <pause dur="short"/> like a League One or League <trunc>f</trunc> League Two footballer has to have something coming out of football <pause dur="short"/> whereas Frank Lampard's there like yeah I'm on planes a lot so I write books and I went to the publisher and he published my books</u>
<u n="366" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0187">something to do when I finish <trunc>the</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> when I finish football it's like well <pause dur="short"/>  he doesn't need anything</u>
<u n="368" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="369" who="S0187">cos he's got like seven houses he's <pause dur="short"/> on two hundred grand a week</u>
<u n="370" who="S0386">these guys <pause dur="short"/> these guys when they finish <pause dur="short"/> they're gonna do after dinner speeches and do</u>
<u n="371" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="372" who="S0386">yeah they work for broadcasting agencies it's like Henri he just swans round to Sky</u>
<u n="373" who="S0187">does what he wants</u>
<u n="374" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0187">cos he's eloquent he's very eloquent <pause dur="short"/> I love Thierry Henri he's a hero</u>
<u n="376" who="S0386" trans="overlap"><trunc>S</trunc> <unclear>Saturday</unclear> he had like contradicting</u>
<u n="377" who="S0187">Jamie?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0386">yeah what Jamie was saying</u>
<u n="379" who="S0187">everyone <trunc>hat</trunc> everyone contradicts Jamie</u>
<u n="380" who="S0386" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="381" who="S0187"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0386">but they erm</u>
<u n="383" who="S0187">it's yeah but the top ones have got it easy <pause dur="short"/> even look at erm <pause dur="short"/> what's his name? er <pause dur="short"/> I've forgotten his name <pause dur="short"/> he's a moron the one that always talks a load of crap he's Paul Merson</u>
<u n="384" who="S0386">Merson</u>
<u n="385" who="S0187">yeah on Gillette Soccer Saturday</u>
<u n="386" who="S0386" trans="overlap">yeah he just says <unclear>is he gonna? he's gonna</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> I tell on you Sky with Sky Sports <unclear/></u>
<u n="387" who="S0187">yeah he's <pause dur="short"/> he was a <trunc>b</trunc> a big name footballer but he went bankrupt <pause dur="short"/> like he lost all his money betting and stuff his first ever pay cheque <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> cos they met at some day out once <pause dur="short"/> er like some football thing that they won tickets to <pause dur="short"/> and they spoke to him he's like <pause dur="short"/> yeah my first pay cheque <pause dur="short"/> how say it was a hundred quid or whatever <pause dur="short"/> when he first signed a pro contract he went to Ladbrokes lost it and then he's like shit ripped his shirt and went home and told his mum he got mugged</u>
<u n="388" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="389" who="S0187">but he yeah he obviously got rid of loads of his money but because he was a footballer he's now got a job in punditry so he's earning a <trunc>sta</trunc> a steady</u>
<u n="390" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="391" who="S0187">he won't be on he won't be on millions he won't be on probably won't be on hundreds of thousands working for them but <pause dur="short"/> be on a fair whack <pause dur="short"/> like yearly for them lot so <pause dur="short"/> he's earning a good living just from <pause dur="short"/> and he's got that for as long as he wants really I suppose</u>
<u n="392" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="393" who="S0187">cos it's not something that age is gonna dictate <pause dur="short"/> but yeah it's erm <pause dur="short"/> you've gotta you've gotta have your your wits about you I <trunc>th</trunc> I think <pause dur="short"/> rooney's one of them where he's come on <trunc>u</trunc> leaps and bounds in terms of his eloquency like <pause dur="short"/> I mean his eloquence when he's talking <pause dur="short"/> he used to really struggle</u>
<u n="394" who="S0386">mm but Beckham was the same <pause dur="short"/> beckham as a lad he could</u>
<u n="395" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0386">had a squeaky <pause dur="short"/> funny voice that <pause dur="short"/> people <trunc>s</trunc> used to say he couldn't string two sentences together</u>
<u n="397" who="S0187">yeah without going you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="399" who="S0187">know what I mean?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0187">but now yeah he's he's brilliant he's an ambassador for things he's talking in front of people and <pause dur="short"/> he's brilliant <pause dur="short"/> and yeah Rooney is</u>
<u n="402" who="S0386">it's cos people like him you see he can talk all sorts of shit and nobody will</u>
<u n="403" who="S0187">I don't even listen to them I just stare at his face</u>
<u n="404" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> really criticise too much what he says until</u>
<u n="405" who="S0187">the guy makes me sick</u>
<u n="406" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0187"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> but yeah like <trunc>R</trunc> like <trunc>R</trunc>Rooney's just <pause dur="short"/> a very good talker now <pause dur="short"/> and so he he'll have <pause dur="short"/> they've get him in when he retires</u>
<u n="408" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0187">they'll get him in to talk <trunc>f</trunc> ex England captain <pause dur="short"/> bored</u>
<u n="410" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0187"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like and they'll give him money for it <pause dur="short"/> and it's just like <pause dur="short"/> it's just painful like I think about how much I'm gonna owe in terms of tuition fees <pause dur="short"/> and all my all my university fees it'll be <trunc>f</trunc>forty grand plus <pause dur="short"/> which is absolutely nothing to them they'll have watches which are which cost that much</u>
<u n="412" who="S0386" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0187">it's insane</u>
<u n="414" who="S0386">doesn't bear thinking about</u>
<u n="415" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0386">pure madness</u>
<u n="417" who="S0187">the thing is I suppose like with that you give yourself you <pause dur="short"/> they will still have pressures like money pressures at times <pause dur="short"/> but I think that I <pause dur="short"/> I think if I had that much money I would have <pause dur="short"/> a really great house <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't have a ridiculous house <pause dur="short"/> I would have everything to the point where I never had to worry about money <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't go excess to the point where right I'm earning two hundred grand a week but I'm paying out a hundred and ninety-five grand <pause dur="short"/> like I'd keep a spare hundred grand every week <pause dur="short"/> just sit it in</u>
<u n="418" who="S0386">you know even if you did that <pause dur="short"/> if you did that for a month <pause dur="short"/> you couldn't do it for every <pause dur="short"/> you couldn't do it every month <trunc>co</trunc> what you gonna do you're gonna <unclear>run this thing to the bank</unclear>?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0187">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but then you gotta think</u>
<u n="420" who="S0386" trans="overlap">you just start you start buying stuff <pause dur="short"/> you go on a spending spree <pause dur="short"/> you start buying stuff <pause dur="short"/> by the end of the second month you think well what am I gonna buy this month?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0187" trans="overlap">what's there <trunc>le</trunc>left to buy yeah <pause dur="short"/> drake said it in one of his songs like before Christmas <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> one of them was <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> what was it? just just traded two <trunc>Ferra</trunc> just spent two Ferraris on a new Bugatti just cos it's something to do</u>
<u n="422" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0187"><vocal desc="laugh"/> cos he's yeah he makes <pause dur="short"/> he's sponsored by Sprite <pause dur="short"/> him and Rihanna are both sponsored by Sprite and he <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how much he earns but <pause dur="short"/> dare I mention them in the same bracket but they're they're both I know they're both sponsored by Sprite <pause dur="short"/> sprite <pause dur="short"/> they can make like what twenty million in a month worth of shows <pause dur="short"/> like on a just a road trip on a road tour <pause dur="short"/> and he's like yeah it's just something something to do <vocal desc="laugh"/> you get bored</u>
<u n="424" who="S0386">yeah it's</u>
<u n="425" who="S0187">but I'd rather have that much money than than not have it and have to worry about it <pause dur="short"/> but then <trunc>w</trunc> if I if I was earning that much money I would have something set up so that when I left football I always had something to do <pause dur="short"/> oops <pause dur="short"/> so I'd set up a business or something or a charity or <pause dur="short"/> something that would keep my attention and keep me <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>u</trunc> good having a purpose</u>
<u n="426" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="427" who="S0187">it's the car innit?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0386">mm?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0187">it's the car innit?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0386">the car where? <pause dur="long"/> it's <unclear>a lorry</unclear></u>
<u n="431" who="S0187">mm I thought it was mum arriving <pause dur="short"/> she I text her I dunno where she is <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0386">what could it be bringing? <unclear/> they weren't brining <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/> tomorrow bringing <pause dur="short"/> permeate <unclear/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0187">permeate? what's that?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0386"><unclear>looks like wood</unclear></u>
<u n="435" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="436" who="S0386">used to be wood <pause dur="short"/> they take away <unclear/> <unclear>and just</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0187">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="sound of tv"/>
<u n="438" who="S0187">relax</u>
<u n="439" who="S0386"><unclear/> seriously someone's gonna go and buy this <pause dur="short"/> cos they <unclear>won't switch</unclear> the showers <unclear>on</unclear></u>
<u n="440" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0386">they want a <pause dur="short"/> obviously the shower's <pause dur="short"/> thing's leaking <pause dur="short"/> pipe's leaking so I think <pause dur="short"/> he was saying the shower's no good</u>
<u n="442" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="443" who="S0386">but she said <pause dur="short"/> cos she <trunc>s</trunc> she showed me when I went to <unclear/> there <pause dur="short"/> the pipe from the shower to the shower head</u>
<u n="444" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="445" who="S0386">is leaking <pause dur="short"/> obviously that if that's leaking the shower ain't gonna work cos it's gonna drop the pressure <pause dur="short"/> so when we <unclear>came round</unclear> we said <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>have you told them about the</unclear> shower? and she said yeah <unclear>you</unclear> said you'd get us a pipe <pause dur="short"/> now I think <pause dur="short"/> if they were intelligent <unclear>they'd</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> they would change the whole shower because they might there's just that shower's knackered but</u>
<u n="446" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="447" who="S0386">change the pipe first and see if it makes any difference <pause dur="long"/> <unclear>if not it's fucking shit that's</unclear> about sixty quid <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/> today <unclear/> two o'clock</u>
<u n="448" who="S0187">mm</u>
<u n="449" who="S0386">back to work at two</u>
<u n="450" who="S0187">mm <pause dur="short"/> dunno why I'm so tired</u>
<u n="451" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>you try</unclear> <unclear>working</unclear> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0187">I think I <trunc>d</trunc> I <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0386"><unclear/> from Bristol <unclear/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0187">I've always complained about mum moaning about driving in the dark I don't like driving in the dark purely because it just tires my eyes out I think</u>
<u n="455" who="S0386">I love driving in the dark</u>
<u n="456" who="S0187">you love it?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0386">I love driving in the dark it's a lot easier</u>
<u n="458" who="S0187">I much prefer driving in the day</u>
<u n="459" who="S0386">the roads are quieter and if you're driving in the country</u>
<u n="460" who="S0187">but they're not <pause dur="short"/> not in the winter time</u>
<u n="461" who="S0386">if you drive in the countryside <pause dur="short"/> you erm <pause dur="short"/> it's a lot easier to see anything that's coming</u>
<u n="462" who="S0187">yeah you work off lights <pause dur="short"/> but then I get <pause dur="short"/> oncoming cars I get blinded a bit well my vision's obscured by the lights <pause dur="short"/> and because it's winter time it's <pause dur="short"/> it gets dark at the busy times it's not dark in the night</u>
<u n="463" who="S0386" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="464" who="S0187">it's dark <pause dur="short"/> I left at two o'clock <pause dur="short"/> and I went and got petrol <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> and yeah then by <trunc>th</trunc> half three maybe four it was starting to get dark <pause dur="long"/> never seen this advert before <pause dur="short"/> never <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> ridiculous</u>
<u n="465" who="S0386"><unclear/> advert</u>
<u n="466" who="S0187">innit? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0187">that's the thing as well they can just step into anything like <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0386" trans="overlap">they they were erm</u>
<u n="470" who="S0187">Waitrose you want me to do an advert for you? <vocal desc="laugh"/> alright</u>
<u n="471" who="S0386" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> they were criticising Beckham the other day for doing <unclear>some</unclear> advert he did</u>
<u n="472" who="S0187">I've seen a Beckham advert recently I dunno what</u>
<u n="473" who="S0386">and they said oh you shouldn't've done that <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what it was</u>
<u n="474" who="S0187">I dunno why they need to but <pause dur="short"/> why not? I think it'd be quite fun</u>
<u n="475" who="S0386"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> well he's <pause dur="short"/> the companies throw money at them though</u>
<u n="476" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0386">with someone like Beckham <pause dur="short"/> and if they say I'm not interested they say well we've give you a hundred thousand or something</u>
<u n="478" who="S0187">still not interested <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0386">and</u>
<u n="480" who="S0187">two</u>
<u n="481" who="S0386">and they up it to <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="482" who="S0187">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0386">you know? because these people sell stuff <pause dur="short"/> their face sells stuff</u>
<u n="484" who="S0187">and like <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's just the <pause dur="short"/> it's not much time they have to dedicate to it <pause dur="short"/> be like a day if that</u>
<u n="485" who="S0386">like someone like Beckham get loads of money</u>
<u n="486" who="S0187">but yeah I know but like just in terms of</u>
<u n="487" who="S0386">oh the advert?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0187">yeah like</u>
<u n="489" who="S0386" trans="overlap">doing doing the thing yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0187">it's not <pause dur="short"/> if you think how much <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> get paid for <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has got a thing she's got a <unclear>JVC</unclear> thing coming up <pause dur="short"/> erm in the summer <pause dur="short"/> she's gonna be on TV talking about beauty products on one of the like shopping channels <pause dur="short"/> erm I think she said it's around a grand or something she'll get paid for each one <pause dur="short"/> just for going there and talking for a bit and looking good <pause dur="short"/> you like like that's nothing <pause dur="short"/> and then if you're a <trunc>s</trunc> big celebrity imagine how much they're gonna actually pay you <pause dur="long"/> so <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's <pause dur="short"/> it's mental <pause dur="short"/> if you think about the business and stuff I spoke to my tutor had a <trunc>tu</trunc> a meeting with him on Thursday <vocal desc="laugh"/> he was asking what I was doing I was telling him what I was thinking of doing <pause dur="short"/> and er</u>
<u n="491" who="S0386">so what's up with doing <unclear>English</unclear>?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0187">no he loves it he's a <pause dur="short"/> he's a lefel level one coach <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> anything football related he looks over at me and whatever he always talks about football in his lectures he shoe horns it in somewhere <pause dur="short"/> football and sex like <pause dur="short"/> pretty much involved in every single one of my lectures on a Thursday <pause dur="short"/> in some capacity <pause dur="short"/> this week it was <pause dur="short"/> it was rape I think <pause dur="short"/> we were looking at Sun stories and rape came up <pause dur="short"/> but he's obsessed <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah he he he loves football he was talking to me about it we spent the first fifteen minutes of the thingy talking about that <pause dur="short"/> and he was like do you think it like doing English would've benefited you in anyway towards that I was like yeah in bits we spoke about it but <pause dur="short"/> he said I need to go check out Nottingham properly</u>
<u n="493" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="494" who="S0187">and I've just I've been thinking the last couple of days about sponsorships as well</u>
<u n="495" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="496" who="S0187">if I can get hold of a sponsor a decent sponsor <pause dur="short"/> to give me <trunc>m</trunc> five hundred quid for the year or whatever <pause dur="short"/> just for me to have them on their <pause dur="short"/> ooh <pause dur="short"/> just for me to have them on my kit and stuff</u>
<u n="497" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="498" who="S0187">I dunno who <pause dur="short"/> I dunno who erm who I could be able to get kind of thing but <pause dur="short"/> a bit of <pause dur="short"/> just to like help me out <pause dur="short"/> and stuff <pause dur="short"/> every time I <unclear>don't</unclear> think about it I've <pause dur="short"/> I do it in bulk <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I don't do anything with it for a couple of weeks and then I'll spend like till the early hours of the morning looking at stuff <pause dur="short"/> I need to actually get into Nottingham and see what things are like</u>
<u n="499" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="500" who="S0187">and I'm not really pressured with it but <pause dur="short"/> thinking in terms of availability of pictures and stuff like that people have <trunc>star</trunc> for the new season people'll make block bookings at the start of the season where they wanna train or whatever from a certain time to a certain time and in which case I need to get in there early so I can get hold of the facilities <pause dur="short"/> which'd be like August time <pause dur="short"/> or end of July <pause dur="short"/> it's not that far away <pause dur="short"/> and obviously getting in contact with schools and stuff it's <pause dur="short"/> worrying <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="501" who="S0386"><unclear>good you're <trunc>s</trunc>schooled enough in English </unclear></u>
<u n="502" who="S0187">yeah I've already got one <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> going in and having <pause dur="short"/> thing is things need to be sorted because I need to have a <pause dur="short"/> it needs to be a case of right this is a business this is set up it's registered blah blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> I wanna do this with your school will you let me do it? rather than going I'm thinking of doing this and whatever cos I've done that before I did the <trunc>r</trunc> I sent letters and <pause dur="short"/> I rang up and sent emails to people and schools in fish ponds <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> think at the end of the first year just to see if I can go round and do sessions with them <pause dur="short"/> no one got back to me</u>
<u n="503" who="S0386">mm</u>
<u n="504" who="S0187">erm <pause dur="short"/> so I think a need it'd be a case of ringing up and having a meeting with somebody and actually being able to show my face there <pause dur="short"/> and win them over</u>
<u n="505" who="S0386">yeah cos you can probably get so many <unclear>requests out</unclear></u>
<u n="506" who="S0187">yeah exactly and the <pause dur="short"/> some of them were like <pause dur="short"/> yeah we've already got someone that does does football for us we've already got someone that does whatever for us <pause dur="short"/> do you do cricket? no <pause dur="short"/> well okay then <pause dur="short"/> then no <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> so it's like that it's a bit <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit of a stinker cos there are there are a lot of people who <trunc>s</trunc> I know there's there's guys in Lincoln that do it <pause dur="short"/> they've started doing it at uni <pause dur="short"/> at Lincoln Uni and have got a business going <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> they do various sports I think around schools and they do it in school time and whatever they've got that thing set up and they're doing quite well off it <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I met them on a night out once some really arrogant guys but <pause dur="short"/> doing well for themselves <pause dur="short"/> so it's definitely something that's been <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>that</unclear> everyone's doing <pause dur="short"/> but it's not what what I wanna do anyway I just need a bit I need like access to schools <pause dur="short"/> every so often just to put the name out like <pause dur="long"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
