<text id="SJ6L">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:40:00</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0262 S0297</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In ANON's work space in Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Colleagues</relationships>
		<topics>My colleague’s previous profession in recruitment; evaluation of academic literacy in a university lecturer’s course. </topics>
		<activity>My colleague’s previous profession in recruitment; evaluation of academic literacy in a university lecturer’s course. </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0262">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dorchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South of England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0297">
				<exactage>29</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>Australian</nat>
				<birthplace>Sydney</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Australia</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Australia</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Australian</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>Australia</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>29</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>non_uk</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>non_uk</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>non_uk</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Associate lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0262">so now this is it? starting</u>
<u n="2" who="S0297" trans="overlap">right now you say evaluating just to clarify what are <trunc>wha</trunc><trunc>wha</trunc>what the evaluating of what? my teaching? my unit running? okay alright</u>
<u n="3" who="S0262">there there are two things that I'm I'm evaluating</u>
<u n="4" who="S0297">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0262">your erm job as a unit convener</u>
<u n="6" who="S0297">okay</u>
<u n="7" who="S0262">and that's one of the questions</u>
<u n="8" who="S0297">sure <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and then another one of the questions is your previous profession if you had one or your previous position before starting at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0297">okay sure</u>
<u n="11" who="S0262">now actually that is the first question</u>
<u n="12" who="S0297">right</u>
<u n="13" who="S0262">can you tell me a little bit about your previous position before starting at <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0297">er okay so I'm a bit of a unique <anon type="place"/> university story in that sense that erm I didn't necessarily have a career before I started here obviously quite young and erm so basically what I did was I er I got into an honours program and I started teaching erm at tutorial level and then er it shifted into PhD and then I started getting some opportunities er so I guess I've always been sort of academic in nature I taught over at er <anon type="place"/> university in the north <anon type="place"/> campus <pause dur="short"/> oh my god two three years I don't know somewhere around that er before I started here erm and I did some lecturing here all very you know casual sessional stuff you know how it is so I did all that erm I had a couple of things erm while I was doing my degree and even my honours and even er part way through my PhD so I worked erm as what we basically call a resourcer in the city for a company which is basically recruitment so I was in executive level recruitment erm that was part-time and I was probably in that for I can't actually remember how long a a fair while during my degree er or degrees erm yeah so I did that and I was also er my dad is a bit of an entrepreneur and erm without going into a huge amount of details I sort of managed one of his entrepreneurial ventures</u>
<u n="15" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay so tell me about evaluation in that if were you involved what did you erm you know have second-hand experience with people?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0297" trans="overlap">the evaluation of what?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0262">of whatever the business was so you know when you were working in recruitment or when you were working in you know your dad's company you know <trunc>an</trunc>anything</u>
<u n="18" who="S0297">right recruitment was pretty simple in the sense that did we find people for the specific jobs? and you'd evaluate you know and you'd know yourself if you found a good quality person because these were executive level jobs we're talking like two hundred thousand dollars minimum that's what we dealt in all the way up to about a million erm as a base salary and er so I was actually part of team and we'd all sort of basically pitch in depending er the the structure of it was pretty easy we had sort of one main person and there was like three or four quite <pause dur="short"/> quite intelligent part-time people actually who were just clearly doing other things at the time anyway er the way we would evaluate our effort was er we sort of competed so generally the way recruitment work is you want anywhere between five to ten interviews good quality people to put forward to the firm whatever it's about er and ideally within those five or ten you know one or two that's gonna get it now with recruitment then if you got if it's all about that five to ten then it's all about okay how many of those five to ten have you brought forward how many of those that one or two people who are gonna get the job how many have you put forward so it was sort of like that so</u>
<u n="19" who="S0262">what kind of evaluation techniques were you using?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0297">oh very subjective</u>
<u n="21" who="S0262" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="22" who="S0297">because it's it's it's so subjective right? you can't er <trunc>th</trunc> I mean you could do you the only the way you could do quantitative was like we we've had fifteen jobs in this quarter and you've provided forty candidates of which one got a job you know you could do it that way but the reality is that very very difficult to quantitatively evaluate that so it was very much just subjective erm and everyone knew everyone else's role and and because there's certain areas without going into huge amounts of detail very very difficult very very difficult had to be subjective</u>
<u n="23" who="S0262">okay that's fine that's that's good that's good to know so second question</u>
<u n="24" who="S0297">mm mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0262">what sorts of evaluation activities oh no what sorts of evaluation activities are you currently involved in as a convener for your for your unit?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0297">what sort of evaluation activities? very formal LEU LETs which I actually have down there ready and rocking for the unit er and I'm doing that across <unclear>bis</unclear> two O one which I'm the convener in as you know and if you don't then it's on the recording and HRM one O seven which I'm going with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's obviously doing the LEUs for that but I'm still interested in doing LETs formal LETs and for all my tutorials I also ask my tutors to be involved in LETs erm and my understanding is I can't force them to do that er but I do request and you know ask them <trunc>th</trunc> how they're going basically er so that's the formal evaluation side but I always make a note er in tutorials because I find that they're average at best in terms of results erm so yeah I always make it I had <trunc>tha</trunc> all the way through like these last five or so years since I've started teaching erm very subjective asked them in tutorials very relaxed and say look I don't mind speak your mind what worked about this unit? what didn't work about this unit? what worked about my teaching? what didn't work about my teaching? so on and so forth and you need to really do that or I find you need to do that in a tutorial environment because it's much more relaxed it's a smaller group of people and all you need is is as long as you set a nice relaxed atmosphere they'll they'll tell you they'll be honest with you</u>
<u n="27" who="S0262">mm sure and what's the difference between LETs and L</u>
<u n="28" who="S0297">oh right</u>
<u n="29" who="S0262" trans="overlap">whatever exactly is the word</u>
<u n="30" who="S0297">okay so <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> so LEUs are essentially er formal evaluations of the unit hence U at the end</u>
<u n="31" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="32" who="S0297">alright and LETs are learning evaluations of teaching <pause dur="short"/> okay so I'm just gonna show you some very very specific examples because this actually outlines it all for me in a very formal way</u>
<u n="33" who="S0262">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0297">alright learning experience of unit learner experience of teaching and they have different questions that they ask so the unit one asks very specific things you know what did you I can show you er which one is this? this this is an LEU alright so that's an LEU okay so it asks very very specific questions like you know erm how did this unit help you? do you did you think it was clear what was required of you within this unit? did you think it erm examined what you wanted it to <trunc>ex</trunc> or what you thought it should examine? all that sort of stuff</u>
<u n="35" who="S0262">right?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0297">all to do with the unit</u>
<u n="37" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0297">er you're not familiar with these?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="40" who="S0297">right</u>
<u n="41" who="S0262">I think you only really get to see these erm if you're a student or a convener I guess or?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0297">yeah right</u>
<u n="43" who="S0262">I wouldn't really have any reason to</u>
<u n="44" who="S0297">I don't think I have any LETs with me unfortunately but LETs basically just ask similar sorts of questions except rather than about it being about the unit broadly</u>
<u n="45" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="46" who="S0297">it asks very specific things about the teaching so if you're doing lecturing it would ask er what things about this lecture helped you learn what things about this er teacher in your tutorials helped you learn what what things do you think the teacher or lecturer could do more of to assist you in learning erm all that sort of stuff those sorts of questions so they're very very specific around the unit and the actual teaching side of things</u>
<u n="47" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> alright so that's the formal part</u>
<u n="48" who="S0297">that is the formal part yes it's very formal and I just happened to have this here so I showed you</u>
<u n="49" who="S0262">cool thank you erm so with the informal part what's what would you say those activities involve?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0297">the informal part is literally just me at the front and saying look I understand that you guys just filled out this formal part and it's completely anonymous and you know that's great but I find as well that and this is literally the spiel I give them I find as well that you know students tend to be much more open and they think that this is recorded and reflects poorly sometimes on teacher and all that sort of stuff like they kind of miss the mark erm and we're limited as to what we can tell them regarding this so at the end of it it all gets signed and sealed and then they know that this is separate then and I ask them very informally look what did you guys like about? and I I cover the unit or I have covered the unit since I started taking this two O one</u>
<u n="51" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0297">you know what did you like about the unit? and they'll say I liked this assignment I didn't like this assignment <trunc>why</trunc> and I'll ask why er what did you what did you find that helped? some people will flat out say I've had people say look I didn't really like the way you approached this and I was like okay good</u>
<u n="53" who="S0262">right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0297">tell me why that is you know erm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0262">okay so do you have to do an evaluation of your tutors as well or informally kind of monitoring?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0297" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah you you kind of informally my understanding is and I look I could be wrong here because I'm quite junior and I'm a little bit unclear about this but my understanding is that you the only person that has access to that information is the person who gives it so if your tutor gives and er and LET which is a teaching form er then it goes to LET office and they're the only ones who should have access to it okay so only <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s things</u>
<u n="57" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0297">so even if I'm the boss you know quote unquote</u>
<u n="59" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0297">then I don't have access to that that is my understanding</u>
<u n="61" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="62" who="S0297">okay so in terms of formally I can I can say look I think you guys should do this and I do do that but my understanding is that I have no right to ask them what was the feedback?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0262">okay okay loud and clear erm in terms of evaluation activities for curriculum erm designing you know the assignments deciding what content should go into your unit</u>
<u n="64" who="S0297">right</u>
<u n="65" who="S0262">erm do do you find that you take you know you are doing those kind of activities</u>
<u n="66" who="S0297">okay with regard to the unit overall? yeah okay so what sort of evaluations do I do with regards to those?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0297">erm pretty simple I do them myself erm I immediately before I do them I look at what's been done previously in the unit and there are some things I like for example with bis two O one there are some things I liked before there were some things I didn't like and I shifted and changed and some things I kept because they'd gone on and I'd taught them for ages erm and then in terms of that er then what generally happens is that the department calls really peer assessment erm so I guess then what I do is er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who I know you're about to speak to</u>
<u n="69" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0297">he is er my official buddy because I'm quite a junior academic here er so I will actually go to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I'll say what do you think about this? do you think this would work? and that's what I did at the beginning of the semester I'm sure <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can tell you that as well erm okay so I went to him and sort of said you know what do you think of this? blah blah blah and he he will go through for example the unit outline like the bible so to speak of the unit and erm he goes through and I and he goes ah that'll work that'll work and it's not just him erm because I was junior and I you know I didn't wanna make any mistakes in my first semester I was I was anal about it er so I checked and rechecked everything myself I got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to check and recheck it then I got er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who at the time was running basically an IB I'm sorry international business</u>
<u n="71" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0297">okay</u>
<u n="73" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0297">which is what my subject is in so I was saying look what do you think about this? and he was ah yeah that's fine erm and then I also like that's not that's not necessarily formal but I did give them the actual document and then with a couple of other academics I just asked er just general conversation I would sort of say things at the time like I've actually shifted in that way and they're like oh you need to watch out for this or something which I found quite helpful</u>
<u n="75" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's good that's good</u>
<u n="76" who="S0297">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0262">sort of like a peer evaluation</u>
<u n="78" who="S0297">very much so</u>
<u n="79" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0297">and I I I mean I think I don't know if other academics do that to be honest but I know I certainly was heavily involved in that and probably still am just just to make sure I'm on the right track cos sometimes I like to try new things and I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is certainly a man who likes to try new things he's excellent at it er but it's always good to get that second opinion from someone</u>
<u n="81" who="S0262">absolutely couldn't agree more</u>
<u n="82" who="S0297">with a little bit more experience</u>
<u n="83" who="S0262">yeah absolutely that's great thanks <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="84" who="S0297">erm and I know that and I also know that its been more than one so I know it's a number of them feeling that and so and I ask them you know did you put this in the the form at the end of the semester? they said yes I did and I happened to know that some of the academics here have continued on doing those particular things even though I've had pretty strong student feedback to say that what they were doing didn't work now at the time to be fair I was not full-time employed I was I was not in a position to say anything okay erm anyway getting back on to me er I think evaluation is learning because I do actually er read them quite carefully I have them somewhere in one of these things er I actually have all my LETs er from the last god five years every single one and I can actually see ha ha it's funny cos I actually <trunc>s</trunc> I'm gonna use this one erm</u>
<u n="85" who="S0262">go on say it</u>
<u n="86" who="S0297">I can see it is actually a map erm because when I did it initially I didn't think of it this way which is why I put it there I didn't think of it this way initially but five years ago when I got my first LETs I read them cos it was my first time teaching at all this is just a a tutorial level and I read them and I I actually took on the feedback and it it said a few things and it sort of said you know er I was little bit scary I was a little bit blunt with students basically and I was like okay cool that's fair enough I can understand why they're saying so I changed and then of course the next one came along and those criticisms weren't there anymore but there were some other things as well like you know sometimes you you know went off on a little tangent and stuff like this so I was like okay cool got to take that into account and and so on and so it's been this sort of progressive er like like like a map unfortunately er it's been this progressive thing er and I I can see them quite clearly er in the last five years of just doing them again and again and again and I think er my teaching has benefited massively out of it because if I still taught the way I did when I initially taught and I never got that feedback I I would continue teaching that way and er quite frankly I would not be as good as or that sounds a bit egotistical doesn't it? but I don't feel like I would be as good at teaching as I am today</u>
<u n="87" who="S0262">fair enough</u>
<u n="88" who="S0297">so that's why that and I I I were even now I put a lot of weight into that</u>
<u n="89" who="S0262">yeah great and do you want to make a <trunc>redeci</trunc><trunc>ro</trunc>change your mind about the map or?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0297">ah that is quite embarrassing that I used that</u>
<u n="91" who="S0262" trans="overlap">or you can just still run with the map thing</u>
<u n="92" who="S0297">because I hadn't thought about it in terms of a long-term kid of map I was thinking of it as a sort of okay we'll put that away erm <pause dur="short"/> apologies</u>
<u n="93" who="S0262">no that's fine I mean that's part of the activity is that you can change your mind when you see the other things</u>
<u n="94" who="S0297">ah <pause dur="long"/>I'm gonna go with this one evaluation as a factory that's the least one</u>
<u n="95" who="S0262">tell me a little bit about that one</u>
<u n="96" who="S0297">evaluation as a factory tells to me that it's some sort of production line where you know evaluation goes in results come out and my interpretation of that is that's pretty much where it ends and that that is in complete contrast to this which is the learning side of things I I don't see it as that at all I see it as very much an ongoing process it is er <trunc>comple</trunc> you could almost say cyclical in its own sort of way erm it it's definitely not a factory where you simply put it in and you get the results out and then you simply change it it's not that simple it's not point A to B it is a series of tiny tiny tiny little steps that as you move along er and I just I don't agree with this at all this seems cold and distant and not very personal and <trunc>tha</trunc> and that in this particular field er the evaluation should be nothing like that at all you need to personal interaction you need them to be relaxed if it's <vocal desc="cough"/> if it's formal and more importantly if the students see it as a production line which by the way some of them do which is a massive issue because the students receive them for every single subject it's always in week twelve and thirteen it's just they know it takes ten minutes they're bored they don't wanna be doing it they don't think that there is actually a correlation between them putting down certain things and a difference in the teachers and I think they think that because some of the teachers they have are terrible or they think they're terrible some of the teachers they have they think are good and I don't think that they they see that the teachers who are bad have been teaching here for a long time they know they've been teaching here for a long time so they don't really consider the evaluation process to be working and in that sense some of them see it as a factory process I this is this is a terrible thing it <trunc>sho</trunc> it goes completely against what it should be but er yeah so I'm going to go with evaluation as a factory</u>
<u n="97" who="S0262">okay that's very interesting <event desc="recording skips"/> could you now just you know whichever way you want you can either start here and move there or go there and go here whichever way you like but just sort of really elaborate on your decisions</u>
<u n="98" who="S0297">okay so erm er yeah okay so we'll go from left to right which is easier for me if that's alright?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0262">no that's fine yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0297">so here I've put on the left-hand side for the transcript er evaluation as a court trial evaluation as an argument it's engineering and it's economics the reason I put that on there is because er previous provision I felt like evaluation was very much erm <pause dur="short"/> you had to defend yourself as opposed to <pause dur="short"/> showing off your wares and how well you've done you needed to defend your actions and so on and so forth now that wasn't because of any particular reason and I put <trunc>econo</trunc> and that's why I sort of likened it to an argument a court trial erm in terms of the economics and engineering probably engineering it's it's probably one which probably more belongs here to be honest erm but evaluation as economics er is purely because that was linked with pay for pay for performance erm so we were actually er rated with that and erm yeah so that's just the way that it basically so you know you did well you got paid well basically as simple as that er the middle ones here evaluation as investigative journalism moral enterprise sorry I'm just relating to recruitment here and all of their managing</u>
<u n="101" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah that's fine</u>
<u n="102" who="S0297">that's business <unclear/> er so here we have investigative journalism moral enterprise job interview critique risk reflection game and art form right investigative journalism in the sense that you've got to try and figure ha ha you always wanna know your evaluation before you get in there alright? er so in that way you've gotta try and find out you do a little sneaking investigative journalism you ask around so on and so forth what's expected and what's not expected how do you go round certain things how do you emphasise certain things a moral enterprise in the sense that how much do you stretch the truth er is really where I'm aiming at there it's a big part of evaluation unfortunately and everyone does it like this is well known that you know you do a small thing and you you elaborate it you know good response and kind of boost it up a little bit and of course you you minimise the bad things that you've done in the same sense it's a job interview not necessarily for the job you have now but it's an it's an interview for the job you're gonna get in the future in particularly if you're looking at a career so if you're looking at you know here at <anon type="place"/> university with regards to it being a job interview so at the end of the year we've got PDRs I don't know if you have that in <unclear/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0297">oh okay yeah so PDRs and you go in there and have a discussion about all the things you've gotten done and so and and so forth and like that I'm sure most of us if not all of us probably meet roughly that PDR okay on some level but it's all about okay what's happening in the future with regards to that? you know where where is that leading to? erm so in that sense it's kind of like a job interview just without just without the job being present right then and there cos it's about impressions a critique I feel like it's pretty obvious in the sense that they do critique you somehow whether it's good or bad as some sort of critique er evaluation as a risk I put it in there because er any evaluation is a risk should I be going through each and every one of these?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0262">yeah that's good that's what you're doing is right yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0297">right okay so evaluation as a risk just in the sense of you know if you get a bad or if they focus on one particular thing even though it's not necessarily pertinent to your job erm that that's a risk erm you risk you really need to know and I I'll relate this back to these two areas as well where evaluation as a game and evaluation as an art form is that because at the end of the day someone is deciding if you have done a good job a bad job or a neutral job and it's a risk in the sense that if you're very good and you know what's coming and you know how to sell yourself and you know how to promote things or you know the person who's doing the judgement somehow okay then the risk can go down somewhat if you're not very good and there are definitely people like that who are not very good in these situations then the risk goes up and that's an unfortunate consequence of the actual individual as opposed to the process although to be fair you could criticise the process itself because it doesn't tailor to all individuals but anyway erm with regards to a reflection it's a reflection because no matter what you're always thinking about it and my experience has been before any sort of review performance whatever it is er you're always reflecting before it because you get super nervous about what's gonna happen and all that sort of stuff and then you reflect afterwards because they tell you certain stuff and sometimes you think of that wasn't as bad and sometimes you're like well they really seemed to focus on one or two things that I didn't think mattered at all er and it turns out they they were interested in that stuff erm so in that way it's very much a reflection probably more of a reflection than any of erm the other ones in this particular area so that's the both of them now on the far right-hand side which is just for my current profession as an academic right here we have technology map architecture research management statistics learning I'll start with technology the simple reason is we have online er assessment methods er the PDR is online the er units the LEUs and LETs are available online it's all done online and that doesn't necessarily mean I think it works but it is available online erm so evaluation is technology and it you know it spits out a nice number and it gives you a rating I think I've got them in that folder anyway I will show you but it spits out these graphs and diagrams that quite frankly mean absolutely erm but anyway that's the technology component and you know the reason it means sweet FA is because they have these scales but they don't tell you what the scales mean</u>
<u n="107" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="108" who="S0297">right so erm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0262">that's helpful</u>
<u n="110" who="S0297">it is it is</u>
<u n="111" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0297">so it's a scale of nought</u>
<u n="113" who="S0262" trans="overlap">it's a guessing game</u>
<u n="114" who="S0297">nought to five and you let's say you get four point five but you don't know if everyone else if getting four point five you know they they actually do there's a very brief thing of saying you know good or meets it and all you that you know it's because <unclear/> scales right nought to five it does that but then what you really need is a reference point</u>
<u n="115" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0297">you need to know er because the students have relative I'm referring to LEUs and LETs here so back to the unit convening stuff er you need and some sort of reference point as to how everyone else is going you know how how if if if everyone else is getting five and you got a four then a four looks really good four out of five that's</u>
<u n="117" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0297">you know eighty percent</u>
<u n="119" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0297">you know you look at it that way but actually you have no reference points so that's an issue</u>
<u n="121" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="122" who="S0297">erm now you get that reference point purely subjectively by asking around the department</u>
<u n="123" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="124" who="S0297">you ask certain people and you find out that getting a four or above is really good for example</u>
<u n="125" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="126" who="S0297">right</u>
<u n="127" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0297">er and that's how I know that getting a four is good so I always aim to get a four that's that's my goal er at the very least and I know that getting a low three is you know average to need improvement and getting below a three is bad but there's no there's no there's no real weighting anyway that's the technology side of things that's my little criticism of that evaluation as a map is because erm basically what I was telling you before where I was able to nice and easily map it out all the criticisms that I had in the first bit of teaching and I learnt a lot from those criticisms and you know sort of its got me to where I am today er with regards to architecture er I basically put that in there because I feel like er you know architecture being design and the design of the actual evaluation process has become is very structured here er in my previous profession both as the managing er side of things and in the recruitment side it was an unstructured er messy thing erm so here evaluation as architecture just in the sense that that it has a a very clear structure with a very clear out line very clear directive so on and so forth excuse me and erm so that's the reason for that evaluation as research purely on the basis that I want to know how I'm doing er and it wasn't up to me in previous jobs er in in any of my previous jobs to be honest er evaluation was done to me it wasn't done necessarily for me if you understand the distinction</u>
<u n="129" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0297">er so they you know they were adjudicating me in my role but it wasn't necessarily for me to be better it was for them to justify them hiring me or continuing to employ me so evaluation is very much research in this role erm yeah and I must admit I'm perhaps not great for this because I have yet to actually do a PDR because this is my I have yet to complete a full year so I've yet to really comment on on that side of things in great detail but I imagine that going through loosely in the structure of things I imagine would be roughly the same er evaluation of management should yeah we'll put it should really be there actually but er the reason I put management here on the current professions side is purely because it's er the university is so bureaucratic and every level requires you know <trunc>s</trunc> whatever it requires as as various requirements you know so this level requires this much and then of course they report to the next person about the next thing so it's just it's just basically them justifying certain things again and again and again till it reaches the top level and everything's fine er and I have <trunc>ne</trunc> I'm going to say I will never work in such a bureaucratic <pause dur="short"/> place er as as a university whether it be this university or another one erm I don't think if I change careers all of a sudden and go on to a <trunc>complet</trunc> it's just gonna be nowhere near the extreme levels of management bureaucracy that you get to enjoy here at <anon type="place"/> university wonderful wonderful structure that they have in place er statistics purely because of the technology and they spit it out er and the learning I feel like I've already talked about that it is really related to er the research in the sense that I'm able to do it I actually get things from it or I hope I get things from it cos I'm I'm firmly of the belief that er what I've done so far with regards to my teaching unit convening is certainly improved and er well we'll see what happens with the PDR because I haven't gone through the actual evaluation stage of that so I can't comment but I imagine that I'm gonna learn a lot from that initial review</u>
<u n="131" who="S0262" trans="overlap">good yeah that's good you've got a good er attitude towards it then that's that's good that's healthy and so these three that er didn't make er make it for you though we did <trunc>ta</trunc> talk about evaluation as a factory erm previously</u>
<u n="132" who="S0297" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0262">erm are these three more like those two over there?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0297" trans="overlap">yes this one particularly</u>
<u n="135" who="S0262">where they they they don't resonate with yeah?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0297" trans="overlap">doesn't resonate with me at all this one doesn't resonate with me at all I have no idea how evaluation is an experiment</u>
<u n="137" who="S0262">okay just to clarify then these two here erm <pause dur="short"/> in terms of the interplay between the professions</u>
<u n="138" who="S0297" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="139" who="S0262">I'm quite interested in er these two in <trunc>spa</trunc></u>
<u n="140" who="S0297" trans="overlap">right okay</u>
<u n="141" who="S0262">specifically so can you just elaborate a little bit more about</u>
<u n="142" who="S0297">sure</u>
<u n="143" who="S0262">why you chose those two?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0297" trans="overlap">er okay so evaluation as a game and evaluation as an art form erm huh there are different it's it's all gonna be very much me I firmly believe that there are very different types of people with regards to career management there are those people who quote unquote play the game er that is they they know those particular areas of their job that are going to give them the most credibility for future promotion er you know I don't want to call them brown nosers or anything but they know those things that pleases their superiors they know those things that doesn't matter okay? they're there playing the game because they're trying to advance their career nothing wrong with that nothing wrong with that whatsoever that's fine erm you get the other people who <trunc>un</trunc>understand it's a game but don't know how to play it <pause dur="short"/> alright er and so they kind of give up and they do their own thing and you know they're good at some things they're not great at other things but they sort of do it then you have those people who don't believe that it's a game whatsoever maybe this is my cynical perspective coming through there erm <pause dur="short"/> that don't believe it's a game and so they don't really do anything erm and they go on about it now I believe on some level evaluation is a game because at the end of the day you're trying to please one or you know maybe three or four people specifically with regards to the evaluation process so in that way you can absolutely skew the results to shape them so that it makes you look better than perhaps what you actually are and in that way it's a game there are some people do you want me to talk about er there are some people who are brilliant at playing the game I'm new to the game I would say I'm not good at playing the game as of yet give me a few years maybe I'll be better at it <trunc>t</trunc> but to be honest I'm also one of those people who's not interested in playing the game I hate that but you know what at some level I feel like the you know certain point in your career it's almost a necessity now with regards to evaluation as an art form some people are good at playing the game and some people are not in that sense I feel it's an art form I can tell you very specific academics who are brilliant at playing the game erm they know how to shape and shift things and all that sort of stuff and I know people and it's mainly those people who are aware that it's a game but aren't very good at playing it so it's clearly an art form in the sense that you just know those people are going to be very good and other people aren't and I think</u>
<u n="145" who="S0262">it's kind of like a talent for something</u>
<u n="146" who="S0297">absolutely it is a talent but it is it's just not as one talent it's a talent er you you know you need to identify those factors that are most important and then you need to enact upon those factors you know how do you impact upon them? you need to get to know certain individuals you need to be have some sort of er personal <trunc>re</trunc> develop some sort of personal relationship with the individuals who are you know judging you or evaluating you so to speak so it's not it's not just one talent it's a series of talents and in that way it's an art form but then I guess you could say anything is a series of talents so</u>
<u n="147" who="S0262">yeah well that's cool alright so erm I'm just gonna take a photograph of that with my mobile phone</u>
<u n="148" who="S0297">god help us all</u>
<u n="149" who="S0262">and then we've got one more ooh we've got no I'll do that right at the end erm <pause dur="short"/> future approaches activity which metaphor would you select or metaphors would you select to represent an approach that you would like to take in the future to evaluate academic literacy in your unit? <pause dur="short"/> okay let me say it again</u>
<u n="150" who="S0297">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0262">which metaphors</u>
<u n="152" who="S0297">yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0262">would you select</u>
<u n="154" who="S0297">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0262">to represent an approach</u>
<u n="156" who="S0297">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0262">your approach</u>
<u n="158" who="S0297">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0262">that you would like to take in the future to evaluate academic literacy in your unit?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0297">academic literacy? how would I evaluate academic literacy? what is the approach that I would most like to use?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0297"><vocal desc="whistle"/> man I would really like to evaluate academic literacy in my unit I'll tell you that much erm I just got through a whole bunch of marking and my god there's nothing more depressing I feel like I've failed as a teacher erm <pause dur="short"/> right <event desc="recording skips"/> I feel like it needs to be an argument cos I can tell students till I'm blue in the face that they need to do certain things but they don't believe me erm and so in that sense no not all students by any stretch of the imagination but certainly a good portion</u>
<u n="163" who="S0262">so you'd evaluate their argument</u>
<u n="164" who="S0297">no no not their argument I would have to argue with them that they need to change certain things to improve</u>
<u n="165" who="S0262">oh I see okay</u>
<u n="166" who="S0297">erm and I think that's an unfortunate circumstance they're just so stubborn they've got through high school they've passed high school they've passed their subject and they're like <trunc>wh</trunc> you know <trunc>wh</trunc>well I don't need to change anything do I? blah blah blah and so in many ways I think you god you need to argue with them and say well no you've actually done this incorrectly and they will no I haven't and you're like no trust me you have because of these reasons and they walk away and they'll argue with you and they'll walk away and doesn't matter what you tell them they're not gonna believe you and in that way sometimes it needs to be an argument and I don't I don't want that to be the case but</u>
<u n="167" who="S0262">mm okay so we'll take that</u>
<u n="168" who="S0297">it's an unfortunate circumstance</u>
<u n="169" who="S0262">okay so so this is an approach that you can see yourself taking more and more in the future?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0297">er</u>
<u n="171" who="S0262">due due to the</u>
<u n="172" who="S0297">I would never take it as an approach out I would only take it as an approach out of necessity</u>
<u n="173" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="174" who="S0297">if you see my point right?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0297">because you know you can tell students to the till you're blue in the face that you know their writing needs to improve and this is the way they need to improve their writing you know they need to stop using certain words like obviously and you know like the colloquial language and <trunc>ob</trunc> erm informal sentence structure and all this sort of stuff and this is not just applicable to academia this will be applicable to their jobs in the future right?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0262">right?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0297">okay I understand you've gotten away with this so far but this is what's letting you down now this is you know we shift it to this wonderful thing of employability and they don't seem to understand and you need to sort of sometimes argue with them erm that this matters and this is why it matters and this is how it matters and they don't they don't always get that</u>
<u n="179" who="S0262">okay fair enough</u>
<u n="180" who="S0297">and that's an incredibly frustrating thing because you have you have genuinely valuable things to tell them</u>
<u n="181" who="S0262">that's right</u>
<u n="182" who="S0297">and they don't listen</u>
<u n="183" who="S0262">yeah absolutely so if you were to take a more ideological approach</u>
<u n="184" who="S0297">well yeah that's right that's something that might be a necessity</u>
<u n="185" who="S0262">not but that's a fair point that's you being you know saying this is the reality check is that it's more likely to be this but yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0297"><trunc>some</trunc>sometimes look there there are plenty of students as well and I I just read this wonderful email from a student telling me that you know she loves my class and all that sort of stuff incredibly biased I paid her large sums of money</u>
<u n="187" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> five dollars</u>
<u n="188" who="S0297">yeah that's right five dollars erm they're very cheap erm they're students after alright? er and I got a I paid her to write me this wonderful email and I was oh that's really nice you know when you get students like that as well very open and</u>
<u n="189" who="S0262">yeah that's great that makes it all worthwhile</u>
<u n="190" who="S0297" trans="overlap">er <pause dur="short"/> it does it does unfortunately that's the that's the small percentage erm <pause dur="short"/> I'd like to say it's a reflection but they're not gonna reflect you can't force them to reflect you can encourage them to reflect er and the reflection itself is not necessarily in a positive way <pause dur="short"/> which is an issue erm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0262">why is it an issue?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0297">er because they need to reflect in a way with regards to well if we're just talking about academic literacy a lot of them reflect in the way that oh this is good enough and that's their reflection they understand that it could be better</u>
<u n="193" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0297">but in terms of the reflection process they're not linking that reflection with future outcomes</u>
<u n="195" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0297">so that I mean it I <trunc>lo</trunc> reflection's great and I think they everyone should reflect on it I I think I tell all my students this I think the best thing you can do cos a lot of students they they you know they write stuff out and then they hand it in and I say how many of you actually read this before you handed it in? and you'd be surprised like half of the class puts their hand up and I'm like okay how many students in all honesty did not read this? I've already given you the mark so it doesn't matter you know be honest with me</u>
<u n="197" who="S0262">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0297">how many of you <trunc>re</trunc> didn't read this before you handed it in? you know you get the other half of the class and you're like you didn't read it</u>
<u n="199" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0297">in it's totality before you handed it in my are you crazy?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0297">like they just sort of write it and that's fine and I just I struggle with that I I well I don't struggle with it I believe it wholeheartedly but I struggle with the fact that they've reached this sort of conclusion where that's almost acceptable how can they reflect upon their academic literacy if they're not even willing to read their own work at the end of it?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm true</u>
<u n="204" who="S0297">erm so ideologically I love that as an idea erm <pause dur="short"/> in terms of I have to go back to the learning I just have to</u>
<u n="205" who="S0262">yeah okay</u>
<u n="206" who="S0297">it's just it's just the the clearest thing for me cos I think that feedback we give students <vocal desc="laugh"/> is like a map er feedback we give students if literally like you're at point A and we want you to get to point B and these are all the things you did wrong which is why you're not at point B okay? and these are all the things you did right which got you to point A</u>
<u n="207" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0297">that's essentially what it is I kind of refer to this as a shit sandwich I'm sure you've heard that term before right?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="210" who="S0297">okay compliment criticism compliment</u>
<u n="211" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh oh right yeah okay</u>
<u n="212" who="S0297">shit sandwich right?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0262">I always call it a burger it's cool <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0297" trans="overlap">right oh shit burger right okay cool yeah yeah er so</u>
<u n="215" who="S0262" trans="overlap">eat it late at night after the fun</u>
<u n="216" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0297">yeah yeah that's right so with regards to evaluation as learning I would ideologically I'd like them to understand that they have something to learn from the things we write on their sheets of paper I spend a lot of time going through their assignments there's none here that I've actually marked which is very disappointing but you can see I I've gone to a lot of effort and I again I mean we've you've been involved in meetings and some of the academics almost brag about how quickly they go through these assignments and it's like ah you know you spend more than ten minutes on any assignment are you crazy? blah blah blah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0262" trans="overlap">three minutes yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0297">yeah and this is like tick tick tick mark bang</u>
<u n="220" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0297">and I hate that I cos as a student I read the feedback you know and I I looked at it and I did all some of these big key words you know you you can reflected on it and I looked at it and I saw it as a map and all that sort of stuff and it was you know a design to get me to the next stage and these academics who just tick and we used to hate it the students there was a there was a group of us er myself and my friends and this is probably where the my biggest advantage lies I believe is because I'm <trunc>s</trunc> relatively close to being the student most of the academics here are so <pause dur="short"/> so distant erm both in a time sense and almost in a physical sense in the sense that they have they've no interest in it so they don't put themselves out over students they have no interest in the students whatsoever but just in the time sense like it's twenty years since they learned and  the reality is the context in which they learn is completely different to today</u>
<u n="222" who="S0262">absolutely</u>
<u n="223" who="S0297">now it's been since I was in a classroom it has been god six or seven years alright but still it's roughly the same sort of context and a hell of a lot more closer than their the content they're referring to and er myself and my group of friends we all hated the ticking absolutely hated it it's like okay it's great I've got my credit</u>
<u n="224" who="S0262">yeah but what does it mean? yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0297">which would be a disappointing mark right? and and it's like I I don't I don't know why this is an you've you've written like a paragraph at the end saying you've done this well you've done this well but you haven't told me how I've done it well you haven't told me anything like this and I I personally hated that and erm so anyway these these academics this is my little thing don't tell anyone else this</u>
<u n="226" who="S0262">do you want me to press the stop button?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0297" trans="overlap">some of these yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
