<text id="SJ88">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:42:32</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-19</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0192 S0228</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In ANON's flat, Bedford</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Excellent TV Programmes, horrible documentaries, animal harm, organic farming, politics, books, instruments, food, recording, jobs, travelling, spice, friends, you tube videos, Brighton &amp; Hove </topics>
		<activity>Seeing ANON after 2 years in Korea</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling </conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0192">
				<exactage>28</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bedford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>English Language Instructor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2>Spanish</l2>
				<fls>Korean -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0228">
				<exactage>28</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Luton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/Cyprus</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>new wave modern English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>gardener</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>4</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0192">I don't know what it means or why he's got it</u>
<u n="2" who="S0228">do you watch Breaking Bad?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0228">do you like it?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0192">yeah it was really good</u>
<u n="6" who="S0228">it is good but I find <pause dur="short"/> like people rave on about it a bit too much</u>
<u n="7" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="8" who="S0228">because in some bits of it I do find it a bit long</u>
<u n="9" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0228">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0192">some people have said that</u>
<u n="12" who="S0228">I really like Hank and Mike</u>
<u n="13" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0228">I think Hank's quite cool</u>
<u n="15" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah it was so sad with Mike died I thought</u>
<u n="16" who="S0228">I even thought when Hank died mate cos when you first see it</u>
<u n="17" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah right at the end</u>
<u n="18" who="S0228">you think oh just a fucking one of those dickhead coppers who are <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah I didn't like him at first at all</u>
<u n="20" who="S0228" trans="overlap">yeah but he's not man he's like he has those panics attacks and shit and he actually changes quite a bit</u>
<u n="21" who="S0192">yeah he's got his own shit to work through</u>
<u n="22" who="S0228">yeah man and I think he does the right thing with</u>
<u n="23" who="S0192" trans="overlap">to deal with</u>
<u n="24" who="S0228">Hank er what he wants to do with well I mean</u>
<u n="25" who="S0192">you do?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0228">cos while he has like <pause dur="short"/> nearly killed him and at times you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0228">so</u>
<u n="29" who="S0192">it's pretty serious</u>
<u n="30" who="S0228">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> have you watched Sons of Anarchy?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0192">yeah I'm watching it at the minute</u>
<u n="32" who="S0228" trans="overlap">do you like that?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0192">what season six?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0228">no I'm on I'm only on season the end of season three</u>
<u n="35" who="S0192">oh we we watched them ages ago but we're watching season six now</u>
<u n="36" who="S0228" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0192">so we know it was out</u>
<u n="38" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah and the last season's coming out next year or something</u>
<u n="39" who="S0228">yeah I quite like it</u>
<u n="40" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah it's alright</u>
<u n="41" who="S0228">yeah it's alright</u>
<u n="42" who="S0192">I quite like it</u>
<u n="43" who="S0228" trans="overlap">the the first couple of episodes I remember it coming on channel five and I was like that looks so shit</u>
<u n="44" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0228">like years ago but it's actually quite good</u>
<u n="46" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="47" who="S0228">he plays a convincing American though</u>
<u n="48" who="S0192">who's the convincing American?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0228">Jacks</u>
<u n="50" who="S0192">is he not American?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0228">no he's from Newcastle</u>
<u n="52" who="S0192">he looks like he's from Australia or something</u>
<u n="53" who="S0228" trans="overlap">he used to be in er erm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0192" trans="overlap">he should be like a surfer or</u>
<u n="55" who="S0228" trans="overlap">Channel 4 programme Queer as Folk Apparently</u>
<u n="56" who="S0192">oh did he?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0228">yeah and he he's in <pause dur="short"/> he's been in some other British thing</u>
<u n="58" who="S0192" trans="overlap">Jacks <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0228">and er <vocal desc="laugh"/> but he's in he's in that Pacific Rim but I haven't seen it</u>
<u n="60" who="S0192">he is at the minute and he just got with his erm half-sister in Ireland</u>
<u n="61" who="S0228">mm oh they've taken the baby to Ireland?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0228">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0192">so they're like <pause dur="short"/> they're</u>
<u n="65" who="S0228" trans="overlap">it gets so much better man</u>
<u n="66" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0192">sure</u>
<u n="69" who="S0228">yeah mate it does</u>
<u n="70" who="S0192">it's good now but it's not like the best show around but it's</u>
<u n="71" who="S0228">no but it's alright mate cos and there's loads of seasons as well you know</u>
<u n="72" who="S0192" trans="overlap">the acting's surprisingly alright I really don't like the main guy Clay or whatever this name is</u>
<u n="73" who="S0228">Clay yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0192">he just looks like such a Muppet</u>
<u n="75" who="S0228">Ron Perlman</u>
<u n="76" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I've never liked his face</u>
<u n="77" who="S0228">he's the guy who played Hellboy in some</u>
<u n="78" who="S0192" trans="overlap">he's just yeah he does</u>
<u n="79" who="S0228" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0192">I've never liked his face it's got like</u>
<u n="81" who="S0228" trans="overlap">no he's got like one of those <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0192" trans="overlap">long fucking jaw coming down here</u>
<u n="83" who="S0228" trans="overlap">everything's like enlarged on him</u>
<u n="84" who="S0192">yeah he looks like a retard</u>
<u n="85" who="S0228">yeah he proper looks like a Sasquatch I reckon like</u>
<u n="86" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0228">pretty much yeah yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah I quite like the guy that like <pause dur="short"/> jokes about fucking horses and all that dead people and stuff</u>
<u n="89" who="S0228">oh Tig?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0192" trans="overlap">at first I thought he was like really weird</u>
<u n="91" who="S0228" trans="overlap">Tig long hair</u>
<u n="92" who="S0192" trans="overlap">he's a fucking</u>
<u n="93" who="S0228" trans="overlap">he's like scared of dogs and</u>
<u n="94" who="S0192" trans="overlap">he's a fucking creep yeah but he's actually got quite a fun character</u>
<u n="95" who="S0228" trans="overlap">I like Opie man</u>
<u n="96" who="S0192">yeah Opie's cool <pause dur="short"/> erm what he had and they killed Donna didn't they? he kind of let that slide unless that comes back <pause dur="short"/> I was surprised that he didn't do shit to <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0228" trans="overlap">you need to watch it man it gets so much better <pause dur="short"/> but erm what else have we watched? oh mate we've watched some stuff we genuinely like so like it's been alright <pause dur="short"/> but girls like things a lot more civilised you know I mean?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0228">like have you seen one called Falling Skies?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0192">oh my dad likes that <pause dur="short"/> it's like some alien thing or something</u>
<u n="101" who="S0228">yeah yeah and in the first couple you watch you're like oh it's a bit <pause dur="short"/> bit low budget this or whatever but the it actually gets like pretty good it gets alright</u>
<u n="102" who="S0192">does it? it <unclear/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0228" trans="overlap">yeah yeah there's like three seasons it's alright</u>
<u n="104" who="S0192">my dad really liked it</u>
<u n="105" who="S0228">you know they normally make something for a couple of seasons it's it's because people wanna see more of it</u>
<u n="106" who="S0192">mm do you ever watch V?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0228">V</u>
<u n="108" who="S0192">that was low budget as well something where</u>
<u n="109" who="S0228" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0192">like aliens came down but</u>
<u n="111" who="S0228">V?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0192">yeah it was called V I think it was called V I'm pretty sure it was called V but there are actually like lizards of something and like</u>
<u n="113" who="S0228" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="114" who="S0192">ran and got through <trunc>t</trunc>two seasons and then it got cut and it was pretty shit</u>
<u n="115" who="S0228">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0192">so when I thought of Falling Skies I'm just reminded of V it's like and I haven't like</u>
<u n="117" who="S0228" trans="overlap">no no Falling Skies is alright man</u>
<u n="118" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I haven't really given it a try</u>
<u n="119" who="S0228">I mean you tried watching Battlestar Galactica so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0192">did we watch that?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0228">yeah I mean we watched fucking Angel man <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0192">I found my Angel box sets the other day</u>
<u n="123" who="S0228"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0192">like today</u>
<u n="125" who="S0228"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can't believe when I say that I was like I know yeah we <trunc>pret</trunc> I think we watched them all <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I liked them and I still do like them I'll defend them <pause dur="short"/> that was alright</u>
<u n="127" who="S0228">I was just too easily influenced District 9 was on the other day</u>
<u n="128" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0228">Angel was alright when you get into any storyline it can be good</u>
<u n="130" who="S0192">yeah have you ever seen this film Sinister?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0228">no</u>
<u n="132" who="S0192">that's fucking dark</u>
<u n="133" who="S0228">is it?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0228">like what way?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0192">it's the only I've seen recently at the cinema that like actually had me like</u>
<u n="137" who="S0228">have you heard of that <unclear>serburn</unclear> Serbian film? it's blooming fucking horrible it's like in black and white and he's an ex-porn star and he does like <pause dur="short"/> fucks all and mate some horrible things mate some I can't erm even remember mate but it's all like incest and fucking murder and shit like that</u>
<u n="138" who="S0192">no I haven't heard of that</u>
<u n="139" who="S0228">it's fucking meant to be horrible it's like you know <pause dur="short"/> the centipede film?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0192">oh yeah The Human</u>
<u n="141" who="S0228" trans="overlap">The Human Centipede</u>
<u n="142" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah I have The Human Centipede</u>
<u n="143" who="S0228" trans="overlap">and everyone's like that's disgusting well the <unclear>suburbian</unclear> that Serbian film came afterwards and it's meant to be even worse it's meant to be fucking nasty well horrible</u>
<u n="144" who="S0192">I haven't heard of it</u>
<u n="145" who="S0228">no I remember some guy at the gym telling my <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has watched it I ain't seen it mate</u>
<u n="146" who="S0192">do you ever watch that animal programme that I told you to watch? I can't remember if I showed you it or yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0228" trans="overlap">may have had mate who do I put that on and <pause dur="short"/> who did that put that on I put that on for someone but <pause dur="short"/> and they were like oh my god I can't watch this</u>
<u n="148" who="S0192">it's dark <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0228">yeah mate who did I put it on for?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0192" trans="overlap">It's dark <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="151" who="S0228">because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s like don't show them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well what did she think of it?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0228">I I showed it to a few people they're like don't show them</u>
<u n="154" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0228">I haven't even shown the clip where that cow gets turned upside down and it gets its</u>
<u n="156" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0228">trachea pulled out and it's alive</u>
<u n="158" who="S0192">pretty graphic</u>
<u n="159" who="S0228">yeah mate all well yeah but it's you know and when they pick that dog up and throw it in the fucking dustbin</u>
<u n="160" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0228">really there's not much you can show of it all them bits are worse enough but</u>
<u n="162" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0228" trans="overlap">the rest of it's even worse</u>
<u n="164" who="S0192">it's an onslaught as well it doesn't stop</u>
<u n="165" who="S0228">fucking bad man when they skin that fox and he's still alive</u>
<u n="166" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0228" trans="overlap">in its skin its eye looked at me and I was like <pause dur="short"/> I've seen enough</u>
<u n="168" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I remember you getting a bit like</u>
<u n="169" who="S0228" trans="overlap">you got to the medical bit and he was telling about the monkeys and I was like I've seen enough</u>
<u n="170" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0228">I don't wanna see anymore</u>
<u n="172" who="S0192">did we not even finish it?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0228">no we watched like three quarters of it and it was like that's enough mate</u>
<u n="174" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I don't know anyone that's got through the the whole thing you know mate</u>
<u n="175" who="S0228">have you watched the whole thing yet?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0192">it was pretty dark</u>
<u n="177" who="S0228">yeah mate</u>
<u n="178" who="S0192">it was hard I couldn't do it I don't know anyone that's managed to do it the first time I I couldn't do it the first time the first time we <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I stopped it the second time we watched it all the way through</u>
<u n="179" who="S0228">no</u>
<u n="180" who="S0192">I say that to people when they talk about some programme that's swept them off onto off beef or something or some something random like Supersize Me or some bullshit now they don't like McDonald's but I'm like fuck all that shit just watch this</u>
<u n="181" who="S0228">mm</u>
<u n="182" who="S0192">this one film and if you have any qualms about</u>
<u n="183" who="S0228" trans="overlap">no that's nothing that's got nothing to do with food though it's just</u>
<u n="184" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no it didn't put me off eating food at all</u>
<u n="185" who="S0228" trans="overlap">I think it's more of a</u>
<u n="186" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it just treatment of animals just</u>
<u n="187" who="S0228" trans="overlap">outlook on yeah just <trunc>na</trunc> er nature around us</u>
<u n="188" who="S0192">yeah it's speciesism isn't it that's what the whole thing's about it's random that you <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0228" trans="overlap">yeah I I know I think it's just <pause dur="short"/> I don't know the way I see it</u>
<u n="190" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean we treat our own people terribly as well but we're not robbing</u>
<u n="191" who="S0228">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0192">I mean we've done terrible things to our own people so I guess we have so it doesn't really compare but this was just focussed on the er animal trade <pause dur="short"/> the problem is that when you do it to a person any of the things that happen to these animals it's an outrage and like you get tried with full arm of the law but when it's to animals these things just go on for profit generally and just get overlooked</u>
<u n="193" who="S0228"><pause dur="short"/> well yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0192">because things have to and under this paradigm things just have to get cheaper and cheaper and cheaper and easier more easily produced to make more profit the next year I just think at the detriment of animals that's the main problem like I would quite happily pay more for my meat if it were just treated better</u>
<u n="195" who="S0228">mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0192">er it bothers me that like organic food is specialty food you have to pay to not be poisoned</u>
<u n="197" who="S0228">the guy who's in charge of the farms this <anon type="place"/> guy he said <pause dur="short"/> he was talking about the farms we had like an induction on the farms</u>
<u n="198" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0228">a PowerPoint thing he was like we're not organic if you think you're like if everyone wants farmers to be organic a lot of people would die <vocal desc="laugh"/> of starvation and it's true man like</u>
<u n="200" who="S0192" trans="overlap">wouldn't product enough</u>
<u n="201" who="S0228">yeah I think like if you've gotta think where we've come from I understand whatever you're saying I agree with it but if I think the reason why it's gone on is cos <trunc>y</trunc> we like <pause dur="short"/> our ancestors and people before us had gone all through that</u>
<u n="202" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="203" who="S0228">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0228">and made that transition from nomadic to farming then</u>
<u n="206" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but we can make a transition beyond it again</u>
<u n="207" who="S0228" trans="overlap">getting better food and stuff yeah yeah I that's what I think</u>
<u n="208" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you've got to use technology to get beyond</u>
<u n="209" who="S0228">but then</u>
<u n="210" who="S0192">still there's</u>
<u n="211" who="S0228">over thousands of years of that happening you then have things like religion in the mix and they say like in the Bible that you have erm <trunc>mus</trunc> you have <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what how they say it what they it was now but basically they say you have domain or something so over like <pause dur="short"/> erm <trunc>pla</trunc> er animals or domestic and pets and shit like that <pause dur="short"/> oh no pet the feral and fucking domestic so or something</u>
<u n="212" who="S0192" trans="overlap">what were we talking about again I've just forgotten</u>
<u n="213" who="S0228" trans="overlap">er er er why all like erm our treatment on animals and why things meat</u>
<u n="214" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0228">you'd rather pay more</u>
<u n="216" who="S0192">but you were saying not everyone could have organic food but to a certain degree if everyone had a little plot of land that they could farm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0228">do you know where they do that?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and I mean you could product your own organic food and if you didn't do that and you still did mass-produce it then just by the fact that we did it <trunc>mor</trunc> at the minute you've just got like organic food is two or three times more than normal food but</u>
<u n="219" who="S0228">is that looked up in the internet?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0192" trans="overlap">because they're not using pesticides and it's cheaper to do it this way etcetera etcetera but I mean if you mass-produced organic food</u>
<u n="221" who="S0228">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0192">it would bring the price down because you're doing more of it</u>
<u n="223" who="S0228">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0192">er the but the problem is you can't be organic either because</u>
<u n="225" who="S0228" trans="overlap">well what you should do is have you go the internet?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0192" trans="overlap">cos the the ground is already polluted</u>
<u n="227" who="S0228" trans="overlap">in Cuba they in Cuba I think when they had some issue over their fucking government or whatever they were going to be cut off from a major supplier so the government initiated this thing so it's like allotments but it's done on like you're fucking doing it sort of scale</u>
<u n="228" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0228">and it's it produces like loads of food for everyone on the island <pause dur="short"/> so it's basically what you're saying it's already done</u>
<u n="230" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0228">it's just done on a it all depends though where it's <pause dur="short"/> really that's quite <pause dur="short"/> not free even though it is free it's not in of like how to put it? in a Communist sort of government if you know what I mean I don't know if this is going well far-fetched like but their government produced that idea</u>
<u n="232" who="S0192" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="233" who="S0228">and propagate like erm yeah what's the word? your propaganda and everything to influence everyone</u>
<u n="234" who="S0192">propagate</u>
<u n="235" who="S0228" trans="overlap">into that that way of thinking</u>
<u n="236" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0228">so really</u>
<u n="238" who="S0192">I'm not against that personally</u>
<u n="239" who="S0228">mm I know but you say if someone was</u>
<u n="240" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0228">and they did it in a situation where they were gonna go to war and people were gonna die so we've gone through that <trunc>scen</trunc> scenario before in the Second World War and the First World War</u>
<u n="242" who="S0192">oh no we have</u>
<u n="243" who="S0228">we get but now as we've got so many people on this island that if we tried that we wouldn't feed everyone</u>
<u n="244" who="S0192">no no there are much too many people</u>
<u n="245" who="S0228" trans="overlap">more more of our cereals and grains come from Russia</u>
<u n="246" who="S0192">yeah but it but it bothers me though that we</u>
<u n="247" who="S0228" trans="overlap">we don't product enough food this is why the guy said you can't go organic</u>
<u n="248" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah we obviously import</u>
<u n="249" who="S0228" trans="overlap">because you don't produce enough food</u>
<u n="250" who="S0192" trans="overlap">everything pretty much</u>
<u n="251" who="S0228">most of our pork comes from Denmark</u>
<u n="252" who="S0192">but doesn't it bother you that I mean I know that like you go and you buy potatoes and it's from Israel or somewhere like that and you're just like</u>
<u n="253" who="S0228" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="254" who="S0192">well why? English is perfect potato-growing land and what I don't what I find strange when I fly in <pause dur="short"/> is that there is we live all so cramped together and feel like we're really really over-populated and we are really over-populated but there's still so many <trunc>f</trunc> so much farmland when you fly in England is just green all over</u>
<u n="255" who="S0228">mm but I think it's not just that though</u>
<u n="256" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's not only the areas of living and it's like</u>
<u n="257" who="S0228" trans="overlap">now like now I mean like I work as a gardener there is loads of factors what you can take into account first of all you've got the weather and the weather is changing</u>
<u n="258" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0228">and then also there is loads of like <pause dur="short"/> pests hundreds of pests different diseases loads of them different fungal <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but you can control quite a bit of this they've got the technology now to to farm up</u>
<u n="261" who="S0228" trans="overlap">hang on hang on let me finish mate there's loads of stuff</u>
<u n="262" who="S0192" trans="overlap">not just farm along to farm up <event desc="unintelligible"/> hydroponic</u>
<u n="263" who="S0228" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah so some people are doing that yeah some people are doing that but there's loads of stuff what can affect plants mate loads of okay?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0192">no of course I'm not saying</u>
<u n="265" who="S0228">and then they do make they do breed like cultivars which are resistant to certain diseases but you've got to think there's not just diseases above ground there's below ground loads of things going to factor it</u>
<u n="266" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0228">so they do develop and that's why people are pushing for genetically modified crops</u>
<u n="268" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0228">and some people are against it I agree with what you're saying but we haven't refined it that yet</u>
<u n="270" who="S0192">we don't have the technology yet to properly do it we don't have the mastery over the land</u>
<u n="271" who="S0228" trans="overlap">I think and if more emphasis was put on Ray Mears made a good point man like I remember <trunc>wa</trunc> seeing the video clip of him on YouTube and he said <pause dur="short"/> like yeah we've got the farming like we farm now but he says he believes it's still at an experimental stage cos</u>
<u n="272" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0228">we lose more species to like <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc> to habitat loss and that's due to farming things like shooters so the Basc Foundation for like shooting the national one they it more most more money</u>
<u n="274" who="S0192">Basque as in like the country?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0228"><trunc>Bas</trunc> <trunc>ye</trunc> yeah so you know all the shooters shooting</u>
<u n="276" who="S0192"><unclear/> Basque?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0228">fucking pigeons it's like the British Association for Shooting and <trunc>Conserv</trunc></u>
<u n="278" who="S0192">that's in northern Spain Basque?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0228">no no you're thinking of Basque isn't it</u>
<u n="280" who="S0192">Basque yeah Basque</u>
<u n="281" who="S0228" trans="overlap">I'm thinking of Basc B A S C</u>
<u n="282" who="S0192">oh okay sorry</u>
<u n="283" who="S0228" trans="overlap">anyway</u>
<u n="284" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0228">most shooters and like game keepers who people think destroyed <trunc>hab</trunc> like birds or whatever actually get more money than any other government thing</u>
<u n="286" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="287" who="S0228">but my this what he was saying about farming that it just destroys more habitat think how many woods ever everything's lost just for farmland</u>
<u n="288" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="289" who="S0228">to grow one type of crop</u>
<u n="290" who="S0192">obviously</u>
<u n="291" who="S0228">so he was saying people are happy thinking how the farmers <unclear/> and <unclear/> right but really we've only got it at an experimental stage there is still further to know really</u>
<u n="292" who="S0192">but what I'm saying about having a small organic garden per community or whatever</u>
<u n="293" who="S0228">mm</u>
<u n="294" who="S0192">if you took England when I was saying when you're flying in and it we're all living very close together and under the illusion that you know we're having to import in all this stuff and we can't grow very much but yet I see fields everywhere which makes me think if you just spread out where we live so instead of us living</u>
<u n="295" who="S0228" trans="overlap">yeah but mate what you're seeing is not all edible</u>
<u n="296" who="S0192">as not together but a lot more like the States more like America where they all have detached houses and <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0228" trans="overlap">oh what you're saying is if everyone grows yeah but</u>
<u n="298" who="S0192">and then if you grew</u>
<u n="299" who="S0228" trans="overlap">it's it's making the money as well it's making the money</u>
<u n="300" who="S0192" trans="overlap">if you had a plot of land between your small community or something</u>
<u n="301" who="S0228">oh well grow enough food for you to survive the year? I think that's a lot harder than what you think mate</u>
<u n="302" who="S0192">no enough food to supplement so you could <trunc>st</trunc> you could live off still off importing but you didn't you weren't it wasn't a problem if</u>
<u n="303" who="S0228" trans="overlap">thinking you'd rather see</u>
<u n="304" who="S0192" trans="overlap">your ties got cut to countries because you'd have enough food to carry you through it</u>
<u n="305" who="S0228" trans="overlap">yes but the population's massive mate</u>
<u n="306" who="S0192">yeah I know it is ridiculously big but</u>
<u n="307" who="S0228" trans="overlap">and what are you gonna feed them?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but the country's big</u>
<u n="309" who="S0228">what are you gonna feed them?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0192" trans="overlap">when you look at the space when you fly in that's what I'm saying there's there's so much space</u>
<u n="311" who="S0228" trans="overlap">but yeah but what are you gonna feed them? well what crops do you think would be good wheat?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0192">erm I don't think you need to live off wheat I'm talking about smaller things like the community of like say twenty to thirty to fifty to a hundred people have a small farm that they all manage</u>
<u n="313" who="S0228">mm</u>
<u n="314" who="S0192" trans="overlap">therefore that they don't need to put much time into it because they can still do their job because everyone's managing it</u>
<u n="315" who="S0228" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0192">and you just had like corn and runner beans and spinach and</u>
<u n="317" who="S0228" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0192">you know strawberries</u>
<u n="319" who="S0228" trans="overlap">do you know what that's called? that's called intercropping</u>
<u n="320" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0228">they do that a lot in er in Europe and stuff</u>
<u n="322" who="S0192">I'm just saying it's possible here</u>
<u n="323" who="S0228">yeah that is sort of like organic but it's a lot harder than what you think</u>
<u n="324" who="S0192">yeah I'm not saying it's easy you'd need to train people in it</u>
<u n="325" who="S0228">it's like companion planting cos</u>
<u n="326" who="S0192" trans="overlap">mm and we need to equitably spread people out</u>
<u n="327" who="S0228">you can't just <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0192" trans="overlap">because at the minute we're all just like we can't farm around here where are we gonna walk to? through the <unclear>chavs</unclear> <unclear/> to fields where the</u>
<u n="329" who="S0228" trans="overlap">mm yeah it's a dream man I don't think you could do that in this country</u>
<u n="330" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh no of course by you're allowed to dream aren't you?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0228">in some way but that's but that's what I'm saying like</u>
<u n="332" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I just think</u>
<u n="333" who="S0228">you have to have a very on board on board view everyone has to think that <pause dur="short"/> if you've got a weak in the chain it doesn't work <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? <pause dur="short"/> if everyone didn't think that you'd have <unclear/> wasted and it you wouldn't really get the right results</u>
<u n="334" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="335" who="S0228">it's quite Communist</u>
<u n="336" who="S0192"><unclear/> Communism</u>
<u n="337" who="S0228">or or it could be quite Socialist is there any difference between Socialism and Communism?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0192">I'm not really sure I'm gonna bring this thing in so we can think talking</u>
<u n="339" who="S0228">do you think there's any difference between Socialism and Communism er Communism?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0192">I don't think Communism has existed erm in the world outside of traveller societies <pause dur="short"/> since the invention of Capitalism which happened a lot longer ago than they seem to think it did <pause dur="short"/> I think since the agro-industrial revolution of like five thousand years ago we've effectively been Capitalist and only in erm tribal societies <unclear>and gates</unclear> connected from that and they're still able to they have a form of Communism</u>
<u n="341" who="S0228" trans="overlap">but do you know what Socialism is then?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0192">erm Socialism I find hard to demarcate from Communism I can define Communism and Capitalism <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0228" trans="overlap">would you say Labour's Socialist?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0192">I don't care to comment cos I don't <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know anything about British politics now</u>
<u n="345" who="S0228" trans="overlap">well no I think it's just how do you describe Socialism so I'm saying</u>
<u n="346" who="S0192">I have an image of Labour from about six to eight years ago <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0228" trans="overlap">well how the NHS and like benefits you all help one another don't you?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0192">yeah I mean that's Socialism</u>
<u n="349" who="S0228">so yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0192">having benefits</u>
<u n="351" who="S0228">but that could be like <pause dur="short"/> but in America yeah they they cool so you know a Barack Obama wanted an NHS like to have something like the NHS <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0228">cos they pay private healthcare don't they?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0192">Obama care</u>
<u n="355" who="S0228">but most er people who are <pause dur="short"/> live on the streets in America have lost their homes or been bankrupt by trying to pay healthcare</u>
<u n="356" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0228">so that's why we wanted to bring it in it's a major thing</u>
<u n="358" who="S0192">it's terrible trust me all my friends are like you know one single <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0228" trans="overlap">they so but people were saying he was a Communist and and some people were saying he was a socialist</u>
<u n="360" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="361" who="S0228">and they were saying they're the same things</u>
<u n="362" who="S0192">they're pretty similar</u>
<u n="363" who="S0228">oh yeah I think it's just which way you see <pause dur="short"/> people make out Communism to be evil</u>
<u n="364" who="S0192">yeah but I don't think it is</u>
<u n="365" who="S0228" trans="overlap">just cos of the cold war</u>
<u n="366" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0228">but I don't think it is I think it's</u>
<u n="368" who="S0192">well they've been using it as a scapegoat to go to war with some countries for so long it's the it's the the universal threat</u>
<u n="369" who="S0228" trans="overlap">yeah but now they use now they use Islam for extreme now extreme Islam as an excuse</u>
<u n="370" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> this is pretty much done are you hungry?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0228">yeah I'm hungry man oh mate did I give you that book?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0192">erm I think I had a copy</u>
<u n="373" who="S0228">did you fuck off</u>
<u n="374" who="S0192">or did you lose that book then?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0228">I don't know I used to have this book</u>
<u n="376" who="S0192">yeah so did I</u>
<u n="377" who="S0228">and we used to share books all the time</u>
<u n="378" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0228">I'm just saying mate that is a blast from the past mate</u>
<u n="380" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="381" who="S0228">oh mate <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm really I just I just I've got a Tom Clancy book</u>
<u n="382" who="S0192">regardless take it</u>
<u n="383" who="S0228">no no no</u>
<u n="384" who="S0192">no no take it</u>
<u n="385" who="S0228">no no I've read it</u>
<u n="386" who="S0192">so? read it again</u>
<u n="387" who="S0228">no I never I never read I never read <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0192" trans="overlap">have you tried playing a didgeridoo? it's really hard</u>
<u n="389" who="S0228">have you read Born to Run?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0192">no <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0228" trans="overlap">oh man I'm gonna buy you that book at the weekend mate that is a good book it's about running it's crazy I never thought I'd read a book about running but</u>
<u n="392" who="S0192">did you say you were going to borrow me that book?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0228">I'm gonna buy you that book mate</u>
<u n="394" who="S0192">oh buy me</u>
<u n="395" who="S0228">yeah mate</u>
<u n="396" who="S0192">I thought you said you were going to borrow me the book and I was like</u>
<u n="397" who="S0228">it's about running and these like these people he will he'll just make you think about running in a completely different way like Tarahumara and Copper Canyons so you can run like eighty miles a day</u>
<u n="398" who="S0192">er you told me about eh Copper Canyon mate</u>
<u n="399" who="S0228" trans="overlap">yeah I mean have you remember watching something called Last Man Standing? Last Man Standing?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0192">no I don't think I've seen that</u>
<u n="401" who="S0228" trans="overlap">oh mate they go to the they go and see this tribe and they play this game where you kick a little ball in flip-flops where you go for miles as a relay team so you're all in a group running together and the British guys know they've just failed and their <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0192">yeah <event desc="sound of flute"/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0228"><vocal desc="laugh"/> where d'you get that from man?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0192">I don't I don't know it's from Bolivia but I didn't get it from Bolivia so I don't know where it came from</u>
<u n="405" who="S0228"><event desc="sound of didgeridoo"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0228">how are you meant to blow this thing?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0192">relax your mouth</u>
<u n="409" who="S0228"><event desc="sound of didgeridoo"/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0192">you're getting it</u>
<u n="411" who="S0228"><event desc="sound of didgeridoo"/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0192">I can't play it like I haven't played it in ages and I picked it up a bit earlier I got a note out of it but that was about it <event desc="sound of didgeridoo"/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0228">oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<event desc="sound of didgeridoo"/>
<u n="414" who="S0228">I'm blowing right in</u>
<u n="415" who="S0192">yeah I think so</u>
<event desc="sound of flute"/>
<u n="416" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0192">that's pretty good</u>
<u n="418" who="S0228"><event desc="sound of didgeridoo"/></u>
<u n="419" who="S0192">really relax your mouth and like almost let your lips do this <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0228"><event desc="sound of didgeridoo"/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0192">looser like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0228"><vocal desc="laugh"/> do you ever have a proper <unclear/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0192">yeah yeah you get to see it that way</u>
<event desc="sound of didgeridoo"/>
<u n="424" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="425" who="S0228">just <unclear/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0192">oh don't smell it whatever you do</u>
<event desc="sound of didgeridoo"/>
<u n="427" who="S0228">sounds more like an elephant horn</u>
<u n="428" who="S0192">sounds like a riding horn</u>
<u n="429" who="S0228">a <unclear/> horn <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<event desc="sound of didgeridoo"/>
<u n="430" who="S0228">it's getting <unclear>long</unclear> enough <unclear/> to do it</u>
<event desc="sound of didgeridoo"/>
<u n="431" who="S0228">you've gotta do circular breathing</u>
<u n="432" who="S0192">I can't do circular breathing <pause dur="short"/> I used to be able to play better than I can now but</u>
<u n="433" who="S0228" trans="overlap">apparently it's you can practice with a glass of water</u>
<u n="434" who="S0192">yeah or just with a straw</u>
<u n="435" who="S0228">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0192">there's a couple of other instruments in there</u>
<u n="437" who="S0228">is there?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0192">yeah there's a rain maker somewhere</u>
<u n="439" who="S0228">mm</u>
<u n="440" who="S0192">I dunno if this is going to be alright actually I'm gonna</u>
<u n="441" who="S0228">mate it's fine there's no pressure</u>
<u n="442" who="S0192">well I wasn't trying to cook anything amazing I was trying to use up ingredients <pause dur="short"/> I wanna cook you a rendang</u>
<u n="443" who="S0228">a what?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0192">a rendang it's an Indonesian slash Malaysian curry it's the best it's the best curry in the world I'm convinced of it it's like beef chunks you high fry them to like sear them and then I use tamarind kaffir lime lemongrass erm a bit of brown sugar goes quite well in it as well that's the only time I add sugar as well I cook sometime with curry but you like you add a lot of coconut cream to it and then cook it really really low for about four hours until right at the end there's like no sauce left it's just like a really thick dark black paste on it or like a kind of dark brown almost reddy sometimes it's really sweet for curries it's really really good</u>
<u n="445" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0192">and then like erm turn it up really high right at the end to like caramelise it in the beef fat erm or the lamb if you have it</u>
<u n="447" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0192">it's really really good it's like the best curry in the world</u>
<u n="449" who="S0228">sounds nice</u>
<u n="450" who="S0192">it's hard to find a restaurant that does it well but like I picked up a recipe and it's my favourite</u>
<u n="451" who="S0228">is it spicy?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0192">no not really it's got quite a few red chillies in it</u>
<u n="453" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0192">but maybe the ones that <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0228" trans="overlap">so it's got coconut in it?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0192">yeah so that tones it down quite a bit</u>
<u n="457" who="S0228" trans="overlap">that'll be why it's nice then</u>
<u n="458" who="S0192">it's like it's got a spice it's got a lot of clove in it and a lot of cardamom in it and a lot of cinnamon so it gives it a different like flavour</u>
<u n="459" who="S0228" trans="overlap">I wanna grow some er cardamom plants</u>
<u n="460" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="461" who="S0228" trans="overlap">I try them it's hard to germinate</u>
<u n="462" who="S0192">I mean er cardamom and like Norwegian cardamom and lemon cakes they're quite good they're <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0228" trans="overlap">I was just thinking man if anyone listens to this tape recording there's going to be like proper talk about organic living</u>
<u n="464" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0228">then like us blowing on these instruments then you going on about curry</u>
<u n="466" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0228">it's gonna be a weird weird <unclear/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0228">it'll be like Godwin listen to that listen to the tape Godwin</u>
<u n="470" who="S0192">I'll show you some later that I've got of my family it's weird I've got like five hours already <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they pay me pretty well to do it</u>
<u n="471" who="S0228">do they?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0192">yeah it's like eighteen pound an hour</u>
<u n="473" who="S0228">no that's alright</u>
<u n="474" who="S0192">to record</u>
<u n="475" who="S0228">no yeah</u>
<u n="476" who="S0192">on that like I have to do more work on top of it and like think about stuff and like it's possible this recording won't be used if there's too much background noise</u>
<u n="477" who="S0228" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="478" who="S0192">and stuff I've I tried to record in the car and I tried to record outside and it's like too windy</u>
<u n="479" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0192">the car's got like a constant humming sound in the back and I was cooking with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> today and I was listening to it again any time that we turned on the tap</u>
<u n="481" who="S0228">mm</u>
<u n="482" who="S0192">kind of makes it like it's unclear and I think that they can't really use it for the the Corpus</u>
<u n="483" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0192">so I have to like I've got some editing software to like cut out bits and like do whatever <pause dur="short"/> I think that's alright <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0228">I wonder how they made this like carved the the centre <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0192">yeah I don't know</u>
<u n="487" who="S0228">it's one whole bit of wood</u>
<u n="488" who="S0192">yeah it's a big crazy</u>
<u n="489" who="S0228">like they must have drilled up here <pause dur="short"/> they've just cut it into a block <pause dur="short"/> then drilled all the way through <pause dur="short"/> then just actually I imagine it's quite easy if you've got the tools</u>
<u n="490" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0228">but <trunc>ha</trunc> to do it by hand it would be well hard</u>
<u n="492" who="S0192"><pause dur="short"/> thing is it's not authentic I didn't buy it from Bolivia I don't know if it actually came from Bolivia or if it's just from some shop</u>
<u n="493" who="S0228"><pause dur="short"/> that's cool man</u>
<u n="494" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="495" who="S0228">it wouldn't be that hard to make that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="496" who="S0192">no got some random shit <pause dur="short"/> I've got so many CDs</u>
<u n="497" who="S0228" trans="overlap">it would be harder to get the right angle for that <event desc="sound of flute"/></u>
<u n="498" who="S0192">so many CDs</u>
<u n="499" who="S0228"><event desc="sound of flute"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0192">do the trill</u>
<u n="501" who="S0228">I don't think I'm blowing it right</u>
<u n="502" who="S0192">yeah yeah you are</u>
<u n="503" who="S0228"><event desc="sound of flute"/> yes but when I touch this one it makes no difference so if I hold down the blue</u>
<u n="504" who="S0192">yeah it's not great</u>
<u n="505" who="S0228"><event desc="sound of flute"/></u>
<u n="506" who="S0192">I think that's cos you have to add one after the other</u>
<u n="507" who="S0228">oh right <pause dur="short"/> oh that one makes sense</u>
<u n="508" who="S0192">yeah cos otherwise there's too much air coming out</u>
<u n="509" who="S0228"><event desc="sound of flute"/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0192">you see</u>
<u n="511" who="S0228"><event desc="sound of flute"/></u>
<u n="512" who="S0192">it's not very good</u>
<u n="513" who="S0228"><event desc="sound of flute"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0192">erm yeah as I said <unclear/></u>
<u n="515" who="S0228"><event desc="sound of flute"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0192">I'm not sure if I'll have to cut this out though it might be like <pause dur="short"/> the recording doesn't have enough talking</u>
<u n="517" who="S0228">oh sorry mate</u>
<u n="518" who="S0192">no no that's fine</u>
<u n="519" who="S0228">see I got in I was getting into my tribe mode mate</u>
<u n="520" who="S0192">it was good</u>
<u n="521" who="S0228">I was imagining was an apache just</u>
<u n="522" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0228">out there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0192">taking it away</u>
<u n="525" who="S0228">take it away mate</u>
<u n="526" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0228">getting my groove on <pause dur="long"/> oh er</u>
<u n="528" who="S0192">yeah so I'm lucky to have got the job though because obviously I needed a job when I was doing my degree and I don't really you know to find a job where I don't actually need to do</u>
<u n="529" who="S0228">much</u>
<u n="530" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> not much</u>
<u n="531" who="S0228"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0192">I don't you know no I don't need to go for interviews I don't need to go out I don't need to be worrying about I can do it on my own hours or whatever I've just got to meet people I can see it getting difficult <pause dur="short"/> to continue doing it and I <trunc>ha</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came up with a good idea like going into old people's homes cos like old people love talking so</u>
<u n="533" who="S0228">it's <unclear>impossible</unclear> mate as I talk to you now</u>
<u n="534" who="S0192">old people's home <pause dur="short"/> yeah I could just go and see <event desc="unintelligible"/> people</u>
<u n="535" who="S0228">or a pub</u>
<u n="536" who="S0192">yeah a pub a pub might be a bit noisy</u>
<u n="537" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0192">or <pause dur="short"/> do <unclear/></u>
<u n="539" who="S0228">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="540" who="S0192">I need to get good on my editing software <pause dur="short"/> but yeah it's pretty useful mate I hope this tastes alright so I hope it does</u>
<u n="541" who="S0228">is that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> with a moustache? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="542" who="S0192">does he have a moustache?</u>
<u n="543" who="S0228">yeah there</u>
<u n="544" who="S0192">yeah he does</u>
<u n="545" who="S0228">yeah for Movember <pause dur="short"/> cheers mate which one's mine? mate there's loads there</u>
<u n="546" who="S0192">whichever</u>
<u n="547" who="S0228">whichever?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="549" who="S0228" trans="overlap">I'll sit over here <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="550" who="S0192">eat what you can and eat what you can't</u>
<u n="551" who="S0228"><vocal desc="laugh"/> there's loads mate to keep you going <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0192">right I'm gonna do something</u>
<u n="553" who="S0228">do what?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0192">hang on no talking might be good to keep it going actually</u>
<u n="555" who="S0228">but erm cos Naga chillies I think are meant to be the hottest aren't they?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0192">oh it is a bit spicy</u>
<u n="557" who="S0228">do you ever go to Naga then?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0192">yeah that's in India isn't it?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0228">yeah their chillies are really fucking hot</u>
<u n="560" who="S0192">yeah I haven't been there but I've heard of it it's</u>
<u n="561" who="S0228" trans="overlap">on Gordon Ramsay when they were sort of they put them in their eyes</u>
<u n="562" who="S0192">it's next to <unclear>Nagipoor</unclear> Nagipoor and up near Shimla and quite so it's not too far from like Bengal Bangladesh I think</u>
<u n="563" who="S0228">yeah it's like the north isn't it? stuff in the north yeah my parents still like it quite fiery</u>
<u n="564" who="S0192">mm some bits of India were <pause dur="long"/> been having loads of sausages since I've come back</u>
<u n="565" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="566" who="S0192">don't get sausages in Korea</u>
<u n="567" who="S0228">no?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="569" who="S0228">I haven't even had a sausage actually for ages</u>
<u n="570" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0192">it's good</u>
<u n="573" who="S0228">I normally squeeze the meat and turn it into something else</u>
<u n="574" who="S0192">yeah you can make meatballs out of it <pause dur="long"/> <event desc="sound of cat"/> hello there mate <pause dur="short"/> I've never stuffed peppers with mashed potato before</u>
<u n="575" who="S0228">no it is a bit different why don't you have</u>
<u n="576" who="S0192" trans="overlap">okay yeah I just thought <pause dur="short"/> why not? and stuffed it with like rice and shit</u>
<u n="577" who="S0228">maybe you could have grated the <unclear/> in</u>
<u n="578" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="579" who="S0228">with cheese in it</u>
<u n="580" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="581" who="S0228">would have been like</u>
<u n="582" who="S0192">problem was that</u>
<u n="583" who="S0228" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="584" who="S0192" trans="overlap">my brother doesn't have dairy or something so I couldn't he ate his earlier</u>
<u n="585" who="S0228">oh mate does your brother like proper stick to a workout sort of thing?</u>
<u n="586" who="S0192">no I don't think it's that I think he just has a bad stomach or something when he eats it</u>
<u n="587" who="S0228" trans="overlap">oh right you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0192">yeah so he's like lacto intolerant or some shit</u>
<u n="589" who="S0228" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="590" who="S0192">he thinks he's not sure</u>
<u n="591" who="S0228">mm might have it slightly</u>
<u n="592" who="S0192">he's just trying to avoid it to see <pause dur="short"/> so I couldn't add cheese into it</u>
<u n="593" who="S0228">apparently a lot of people have like problems with gluten but they just don't realise it it can just give you a bloated or upset stomach and</u>
<u n="594" who="S0192">yeah for he has had a bad stomach <unclear/></u>
<u n="595" who="S0228">that's why people like go on <unclear/> or erm they rave on about it</u>
<u n="596" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="597" who="S0228">you just don't get that bloated feeling from eating fucking white bread or something <pause dur="short"/> or loads of carbs like rice <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="598" who="S0192">yeah it's definitely a good idea to <event desc="sound of rustling"/> I think I have to put this here so it doesn't get all the like vibrations from the <pause dur="long"/> yeah this is for like er linguistics research</u>
<u n="599" who="S0228">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="600" who="S0192">I tell you what I'd really to do Sean with travelling man if I could get involved with some research into some pidgin or creole language in some random part of Africa or <pause dur="short"/> you know some fucking Papua New Guinea or something it would be</u>
<u n="601" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="602" who="S0192">absolutely amazing</u>
<u n="603" who="S0228">did you learn Korean when you were in</u>
<u n="604" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="605" who="S0228">cos I remember you saying actually you was going I'm definitely gonna learn Korean this time</u>
<u n="606" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I did for about six months I did</u>
<u n="607" who="S0228">mm</u>
<u n="608" who="S0192">intensively for about six months and then I just again got really deflated with it</u>
<u n="609" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="610" who="S0192">really deflated with it</u>
<u n="611" who="S0228">I've still done my Greek it means you need <unclear/> range for the top of that</u>
<u n="612" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="613" who="S0228"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dad can speak like four different languages man</u>
<u n="614" who="S0192">wow</u>
<u n="615" who="S0228">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="616" who="S0192">I take it you were doing that on Rosetta Stone?</u>
<u n="617" who="S0228">yeah yeah yeah that one you got me</u>
<u n="618" who="S0192">I didn't get you that did I?</u>
<u n="619" who="S0228">yeah yeah you gave me the crap version</u>
<u n="620" who="S0192">oh okay not that erm <pause dur="short"/> cos you got that physical version haven't you?</u>
<u n="621" who="S0228">mm</u>
<u n="622" who="S0192">you've got that that bought one on your side</u>
<u n="623" who="S0228">I think I've got <unclear/></u>
<u n="624" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0228">can't believe I bought that what a lot of money</u>
<u n="626" who="S0192">but you use the other you use the one I gave you</u>
<u n="627" who="S0228"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0192">shit <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="629" who="S0228">it's not your mum is it? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="630" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="631" who="S0228"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="632" who="S0192">I think <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="633" who="S0228">yeah it's definitely your mum <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="634" who="S0192">it looks like some famous rock star or some sort of</u>
<u n="635" who="S0228">or Bonnie Tyler I think <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="636" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="long"/> oh I'm never going to be able to eat all this</u>
<u n="637" who="S0228">it's a lot</u>
<u n="638" who="S0192">need to eat it in stages sorry made too much</u>
<u n="639" who="S0228">what's in this sauce? it's like a gravy or something</u>
<u n="640" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's the food processor it like chopped it <vocal desc="laugh"/> no you know I put it in a blender? erm</u>
<u n="641" who="S0228">it's nice man</u>
<u n="642" who="S0192">erm comes up better</u>
<u n="643" who="S0228">looks like one of those when you get it from an Indian</u>
<u n="644" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="645" who="S0228">like the texture</u>
<u n="646" who="S0192">like a curry <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's not meant to be a curry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="647" who="S0228">it's spicy that one</u>
<u n="648" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I know</u>
<u n="649" who="S0228">what was it though?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's not it's not meant to be</u>
<u n="651" who="S0228">a fusion of Italian and Indian <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="652" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah is that is that a bad thing?</u>
<u n="653" who="S0228">you could just say <trunc>mid</trunc> Middle Eastern you know</u>
<u n="654" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well Turkish I think it's just celery carrot erm onions garlic</u>
<u n="655" who="S0228">it's probably the celery what's giving it that texture I think you can <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="656" who="S0192">mm <pause dur="long"/> if you don't like it man or don't want it don't worry</u>
<u n="657" who="S0228" trans="overlap">tastes nice <pause dur="long"/> alright I bet that's easy to do with one leg missus poor cat</u>
<u n="658" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> sorry mate <pause dur="short"/> it's really staring at me now</u>
<u n="659" who="S0228">give me a glug of it</u>
<u n="660" who="S0192">no <pause dur="short"/> definitely not <pause dur="long"/> wow I didn't mean for it to be spicy sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/> my brother probably didn't like it</u>
<u n="661" who="S0228">does he not like spice at all?</u>
<u n="662" who="S0192">er he likes spice but not you know maybe this would be about his limit maybe <pause dur="long"/> how about you?</u>
<u n="663" who="S0228">probably about my limit</u>
<u n="664" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="665" who="S0228">yeah I think if if things just get too spicy just there's no flavour apart from spice</u>
<u n="666" who="S0192">you can get quite a bit spicier than this and still have flavour I think</u>
<u n="667" who="S0228">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I'm more of a more of a <pause dur="short"/> european sort of guy I like my like Italian flavours me I don't mind spice I like spice</u>
<u n="668" who="S0192">sorry <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="669" who="S0228">well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0192">I cooked the wrong thing</u>
<u n="671" who="S0228">oh no no</u>
<u n="672" who="S0192">I blame the chillies</u>
<u n="673" who="S0228">no I mean no I like middle eastern food cos it's it's got spice and stuff so it's just when you can <trunc>sa</trunc> when people say spice I mean it's so there's so many spices it's just a don't like food what's hot</u>
<u n="674" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="675" who="S0228">do you know what I mean? like that sort of spiciness that er he</u>
<u n="676" who="S0192">mm parts of India like you couldn't I couldn't eat there <pause dur="short"/> went to a one state in particular there <pause dur="short"/> I don't know they didn't have many tourists there at all so they didn't like temper it down for the tourists</u>
<u n="677" who="S0228"><pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="678" who="S0192">it was so so hot to a point where I thought I was you know getting worried that I couldn't eat like it was just blip blisteringly hot</u>
<u n="679" who="S0228">chillies there they're really spicy so I mean I like mussels yeah with ginger coriander and chilli it's proper nice mate</u>
<u n="680" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="681" who="S0228">and it's like spicy but it's not like just too unbearable do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0192">I don't like mussels</u>
<u n="683" who="S0228">oh mate they're nice</u>
<u n="684" who="S0192">I don't like erm you were talking before about <pause dur="short"/> you know fish picking up heavy metals they're like bottom feeders</u>
<u n="685" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="686" who="S0192">and they like erm</u>
<u n="687" who="S0228">yeah like if you get ones where</u>
<u n="688" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and the heavy metals pick up radiation as well</u>
<u n="689" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="690" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so like I'm around Korea and like Japan Fukushima is still going off and I'm like er I'm not gonna eat them</u>
<u n="691" who="S0228" trans="overlap">but they erm er</u>
<u n="692" who="S0192">mussels cos I don't even like the taste and I'm certainly not gonna</u>
<u n="693" who="S0228" trans="overlap">they can grow them in erm in artificial environments</u>
<u n="694" who="S0192">mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't like the texture of shell fish</u>
<u n="695" who="S0228">well it's so soft</u>
<u n="696" who="S0192">it's horrible</u>
<u n="697" who="S0228">oh it's so soft though there's no texture to it it's so soft like if you over cook them they're chewy</u>
<u n="698" who="S0192">mm <pause dur="short"/> koreans probably don't cook them in the best way</u>
<u n="699" who="S0228">mm</u>
<u n="700" who="S0192">they don't have too much finesse in their cooking I don't think</u>
<u n="701" who="S0228">if you cook it with like white wine and ginger I mean white wine and garlic the classic it's proper nice mate <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said he had soft shell crab out there he said it's disgusting</u>
<u n="702" who="S0192">yeah I had that too</u>
<u n="703" who="S0228">oh he showed me I took him to</u>
<u n="704" who="S0192">you eat the whole thing they're not very big</u>
<u n="705" who="S0228">mm</u>
<u n="706" who="S0192">the shell's not particularly soft they're still really crunchy</u>
<u n="707" who="S0228" trans="overlap">they have there's an oriental supermarket in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="708" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="709" who="S0228">a massive one I took him there he he showed me loads of stuff he used to eat</u>
<u n="710" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="711" who="S0228">I got lobster a live lobster from there</u>
<u n="712" who="S0192">how long did he stay here for? <pause dur="short"/> about a year?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0228">about a year yeah</u>
<u n="714" who="S0192">yeah so you see him a fair bit?</u>
<u n="715" who="S0228">yeah you we see each other quite a bit</u>
<u n="716" who="S0192">good show <pause dur="short"/> did he ever miss Korea?</u>
<u n="717" who="S0228">erm I dunno</u>
<u n="718" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="719" who="S0228">I think he liked it here</u>
<u n="720" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="721" who="S0228">but got er a job just doing some of the games ain't he?</u>
<u n="722" who="S0192">yeah he's not anymore I don't think last I heard from him</u>
<u n="723" who="S0228">is he not? wonder what he's doing now</u>
<u n="724" who="S0192">he says he's working in a school or something</u>
<u n="725" who="S0228">oh really?</u>
<u n="726" who="S0192">mm he said the job was good</u>
<u n="727" who="S0228">just didn't pay enough</u>
<u n="728" who="S0192">just was crap pay yeah</u>
<u n="729" who="S0228">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="730" who="S0192">hopefully I'm gonna see him soon but he's terrible at contacting me <pause dur="short"/> mostly awful</u>
<u n="731" who="S0228">he is bad man</u>
<u n="732" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="733" who="S0228"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> eat this last meatball mate <pause dur="short"/> I hope I ain't eaten too much</u>
<u n="734" who="S0192">do it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="735" who="S0228">I don't really eat much in the day at work</u>
<u n="736" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you can have you can have another one of mine er yeah</u>
<u n="737" who="S0228">we eat but I just don't wanna eat too much alright</u>
<u n="738" who="S0192">help me finish this one I'm not gonna</u>
<u n="739" who="S0228">no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="740" who="S0192">I said I'll cook you that curry at some point <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="741" who="S0228">so when do you actually go to Brighton?</u>
<u n="742" who="S0192">next Wednesday</u>
<u n="743" who="S0228">when do you start your thing?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0192">a couple of weeks after that <pause dur="long"/> about the twentieth <pause dur="short"/> pretty sure</u>
<u n="745" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="746" who="S0192">my brother's going down about the same time</u>
<u n="747" who="S0228">wonder what you mum's gonna think</u>
<u n="748" who="S0192">bit nervous about studying again obviously</u>
<u n="749" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="750" who="S0192">I think a masters is gonna be quite difficult</u>
<u n="751" who="S0228">the house is going to be very quiet and</u>
<u n="752" who="S0192">yeah I think it will <pause dur="short"/> oh it's not gonna be very quiet at all they've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="753" who="S0228">oh yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="754" who="S0192">he's extremely noisy</u>
<u n="755" who="S0228">well there'll be less traffic you could say</u>
<u n="756" who="S0192">mm <pause dur="long"/> I don't think I can eat anymore for a bit I've kind of knackered myself out I moved all these boxes down from the loft earlier</u>
<u n="757" who="S0228">I like spice but like <trunc>mid</trunc> know what I mean Middle Eastern spice like it's not it's not like Italian food where it's herby and tomato-y</u>
<u n="758" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="759" who="S0228">it's like the it's more like cinnamon and nutmeggy and</u>
<u n="760" who="S0192">yeah there was nutmeg in the potato</u>
<u n="761" who="S0228" trans="overlap">it's alright</u>
<u n="762" who="S0192">in this one</u>
<u n="763" who="S0228">apparently if you eat two tablespoons of nutmeg you'll trip out</u>
<u n="764" who="S0192">no I haven't</u>
<u n="765" who="S0228">like it's meant to be really fucking manky and you throw up loads and things</u>
<u n="766" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah no that wasn't <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="767" who="S0228">I don't think I'd eat two tablespoons of powdered nutmeg</u>
<u n="768" who="S0192">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's not worth it</u>
<u n="769" who="S0228">have you seen people do that cinnamon challenge?</u>
<u n="770" who="S0192">no exactly <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="771" who="S0228">they eat a tablespoon of cinnamon <pause dur="long"/> it looks bad</u>
<u n="772" who="S0192">surely that's hard</u>
<u n="773" who="S0228">yeah you wanna see it the film powder they're in action so it goes like <vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's like everywhere man it's bad man</u>
<u n="774" who="S0192">it's a proper powder</u>
<u n="775" who="S0228">have you got the internet?</u>
<u n="776" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="777" who="S0228">yeah I'll have to show you later</u>
<u n="778" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="779" who="S0228">but I see this funny video clip <vocal desc="laugh"/> of where this kid like I'll have to show you it mate it's just like two brothers you might be able to relate to it it's like two brothers like fucking about in the front room</u>
<u n="780" who="S0192">what was that TV programme we liked before the Inbetweeners or something?</u>
<u n="781" who="S0228">Inbetweeners yeah</u>
<u n="782" who="S0192">you showed me that when er you were at home last time erm I didn't think about it again until about a month ago</u>
<u n="783" who="S0228">yeah the movie was out</u>
<u n="784" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I was looking out at other things or something and I came across it is it good?</u>
<u n="785" who="S0228">yeah yeah it is it's worth watching once yeah it's good I mean there's more</u>
<u n="786" who="S0192">what kind of good do you like Peep Show?</u>
<u n="787" who="S0228">I watch it but I'm not like one of those fans who are like the Peep Show like some people are about like Game of Thrones</u>
<u n="788" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="789" who="S0228">like I I I don't go on a forum and be like I love it episode six or <trunc>seas</trunc></u>
<u n="790" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="791" who="S0228">season three</u>
<u n="792" who="S0192">probably not but I quite like Peep Show</u>
<u n="793" who="S0228">big Suze was amazing</u>
<u n="794" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's so <trunc>frus</trunc> it's so frustrating it's so <trunc>frust</trunc> er oh it's just so quotable I think</u>
<u n="795" who="S0228">what's the guy who it's like his mate who's like</u>
<u n="796" who="S0192">Super Hans</u>
<u n="797" who="S0228">Super Hans <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="798" who="S0192">he he lives in <anon type="place"/> my friend sees him around a</u>
<u n="799" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="800" who="S0192">mm er as well as erm who's that ah Chris Eubanks <vocal desc="laugh"/> the little crazy boxer</u>
<u n="801" who="S0228" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that had the monocle?</u>
<u n="803" who="S0228">his son's proper weird <pause dur="short"/> chris Eubank he drives a massive fucking lorry is he in <anon type="place"/> yeah I thought he lives in like <anon type="place"/> or somewhere</u>
<u n="804" who="S0192">yeah <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> is er</u>
<u n="805" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="806" who="S0192">same place</u>
<u n="807" who="S0228">shit <anon type="place"/> is just outside isn't it?</u>
<u n="808" who="S0192">I'm actually in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="809" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="810" who="S0192">but I'm like a five minute walk from <anon type="place"/> station</u>
<u n="811" who="S0228">cos apparently do you know why it's called <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="812" who="S0192">cos have was the city there?</u>
<u n="813" who="S0228">yeah basically it's because it was all whenever things were happening it was always classed as <anon type="place"/> and people were like no we're <anon type="place"/> and</u>
<u n="814" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="815" who="S0228" trans="overlap">and there'd be like a big movement to say</u>
<u n="816" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="817" who="S0228">no we are <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="818" who="S0192">it does say it</u>
<u n="819" who="S0228">that's why it's <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="820" who="S0192">I realised that there's they just if you've</u>
<u n="821" who="S0228" trans="overlap">I know but some people don't think about where that is</u>
<u n="822" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="823" who="S0228" trans="overlap">they just think they just think it's called <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="824" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="825" who="S0228">like <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> oh it's just <anon type="place"/> there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="826" who="S0192">I know no I erm if you just follow a map along the coast it's just never <trunc>end</trunc> it for quite a while it just doesn't stop it's just like <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> or something like and it just keeps going <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> and like it just doesn't stop it's like completely connected for ages <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="place"/> is so close to <anon type="place"/> basically anything to the right of the train station on a map is <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="827" who="S0228">yeah</u>
<u n="828" who="S0192">the rest is <anon type="place"/> and then all the way on the other end <anon type="place"/> is really quite similar actually from us</u>
<u n="829" who="S0228">where were you going for that <unclear>slinky</unclear></u>
<u n="830" who="S0192">oh god that was in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="831" who="S0228">was it I thought it was <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="832" who="S0192">no oh I think we went through <anon type="place"/> it was in <anon type="place"/> pretty</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
