<text id="SJAW">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:20:37</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-31</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0264 S0265</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Dinner at participants' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Travel and domestic arrangements</topics>
		<activity>Travel arrangements</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, announcing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0264">
				<exactage>60</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Crickhowell</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South Wales/Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>23</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>tutorial fellow</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate; Dutch -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0265">
				<exactage>56</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harworth, Nottinghamshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>e_midlands</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>technical analyst</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0264">I can't I don't know what <pause dur="short"/> there's no spare <pause dur="long"/> I'm gonna sleep in in the study when they come <pause dur="short"/> is it Thursday?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0265">you can have your own bed they they there are only two of them coming they'll sleep in my bed</u>
<u n="3" who="S0264">they don't want to share a bed surely?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0265">they're used to it</u>
<u n="5" who="S0264">well I'm used to sleeping on the floor I in fact I'd almost prefer it because my separate out of the way</u>
<u n="6" who="S0265">you're not you don't need to do anything? they can have my bed it's only one night and when they come back it's one night</u>
<u n="7" who="S0264">yeah but what if they don't sleep the night before travelling? that wouldn't be a good idea would it? <pause dur="long"/> how come there's only one piece of carrot?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0265">because there wasn't any carrot this is this is what was erm left over from yesterday <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0264">oh what time's the flight?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0265">two forty-five</u>
<u n="11" who="S0264">mm have you got the rail tickets?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0265">not yet <pause dur="long"/> there're gonna they'll get their tickets to Gatwick when they arrive here erm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0264">why?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0265">cos they've got passes I suppose they could they could buy them from any railway station couldn't they?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0264">but what's the advantage of? oh yeah the theoretical yes <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0265">oh erm <trunc>wh</trunc>when I come up on Tuesday do I should I get a travel card how how many tube journeys are we going to be making?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0264">three</u>
<u n="18" who="S0265">oh it's worth getting one then</u>
<u n="19" who="S0264">cos he'll cos you won't want to walk to Piccadilly you won't have time</u>
<u n="20" who="S0265">no</u>
<u n="21" who="S0264">and then there'll be Piccadilly to South Kensington and then back from South Kensington to Victoria</u>
<u n="22" who="S0265">yeah I thought so</u>
<u n="23" who="S0264">well do you know where this restaurant is?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0265">yes I've looked on erm the map</u>
<u n="25" who="S0264">where?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0265">is it <anon type="place"/> something like that? it's just off erm Piccadilly isn't it?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0264">yes it is but it's confusing and erm isn't it erm near <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0265"><unclear>no</unclear></u>
<u n="29" who="S0264">well I think it is anyway it's confusing because it's not a big street it's probably not clearly signposted and the restaurant is erm in the basement</u>
<u n="30" who="S0265">erm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0264">so you won't see a restaurant probably on at street level</u>
<u n="32" who="S0265">there must be something outside which which says that the restaurant's there what's it called? <anon type="place"/> or something <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0264">there probably is but you know what it's like in that area there's loads of street furniture and street signs</u>
<u n="34" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0264">well erm I recommend that you have a look at the menu today or tomorrow cos it'll be up for the week</u>
<u n="36" who="S0265">ah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0264">and decide before you go and that'll save a lot of time</u>
<u n="38" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0264">cos if they go away cos they wouldn't cos they <unclear/> then they may not come back for a long time</u>
<u n="40" who="S0265">yes we just <unclear/> one immediately <unclear>to</unclear> sit down</u>
<u n="41" who="S0264" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="long"/> and that includes erm drinks because nobody ever seems prepared to order drinks and that'll that could cause a long delay thinking about what about whether whether or not you want a drink or just have tap water</u>
<u n="42" who="S0265">mm <pause dur="long"/> and the concert finishes about ten o'clock I suppose</u>
<u n="43" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0265">so I should be able to get the quarter to eleven train out of Victoria</u>
<u n="45" who="S0264"><vocal desc="cough"/> well you might even be able to get the twenty-two seventeen er it officially finishes at erm nine fifty</u>
<u n="46" who="S0265">oh right</u>
<u n="47" who="S0264">and that's the erm estimate but</u>
<u n="48" who="S0265">yeah depending how quickly you can get out</u>
<u n="49" who="S0264" trans="overlap">the yes exactly and I might have erm well you can go ahead if you want to erm cos I suppose I'll need to take erm small case</u>
<u n="50" who="S0265">oh cos you're going up to erm Cambridge aren't you <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah I can't really I don't know how I can't I can't use that bag any more have you seen the state of it?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0265">oh you mean that's like strap</u>
<u n="53" who="S0264" trans="overlap">rucksack</u>
<u n="54" who="S0265">oh the rucksack no I haven't seen the state of it why? what's wrong with it?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0264">well it's falling to pieces literally things have</u>
<u n="56" who="S0265" trans="overlap">is that the one you got in Australia?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0264">yes it's things in that yeah in that arcade things are falling out of it erm loose stuff is falling out because it's all it's ripped it's got holes in <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0265">no there's plenty of places where it can get you get a new one they're quite cheap</u>
<u n="59" who="S0264">well I thought I'd get I thought I'd have a look in Tesco that's where I got the one before and that <trunc>la</trunc> that was quite that that was quite good quality it seemed to last a long time</u>
<u n="60" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="61" who="S0264">that one that was with a mouse that we never used it was for <unclear/> it was for laptops or something</u>
<u n="62" who="S0265">no <pause dur="short"/> mm the best rucksack I had I got from Marks and Spencer and it was only fifteen pounds and it <unclear/> lasted ages</u>
<u n="63" who="S0264">yeah was it a sale or what?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0265">erm don't think well it might have been yeah it might have been in a sale</u>
<u n="65" who="S0264">you can't erm <vocal desc="cough"/> you can't trust Marks and Spencer though they automatically you think of that that erm umbrella that I got</u>
<u n="66" who="S0265">yes I know I I bought one</u>
<u n="67" who="S0264" trans="overlap">it's rubbish</u>
<u n="68" who="S0265">I told you didn't I? I took it back</u>
<u n="69" who="S0264">oh you took yours back?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0265">I took mine back and I said I'd only had it a couple of weeks and he said yes it looks new and I showed him what was wrong with it and he cos I he said you should take it up to customer services and they'll probably exchange it for you cos I was just gonna buy a new one</u>
<u n="71" who="S0264">and did you have your receipt?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0265">no that's why I was just gonna buy a new one cos I hadn't got the receipt with me and I needed a brolly urgently cos it was very it was raining very heavily it was my lunchtime the umbrella had broken</u>
<u n="73" who="S0264">which Marks and Spencer was this then?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0265"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0264">you mean <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0264">well how come you were up there? that's nowhere near your work</u>
<u n="78" who="S0265">it is I was I was out in my lunchbreak I think</u>
<u n="79" who="S0264" trans="overlap">surely you don't walk that far in your lunchbreak</u>
<u n="80" who="S0265">yeah it's not far</u>
<u n="81" who="S0264">it's down one hill and up another hill</u>
<u n="82" who="S0265">yeah so what? I often do that</u>
<u n="83" who="S0264"><vocal desc="cough"/> ah I suppose it's good in</u>
<u n="84" who="S0265" trans="overlap">yeah I like to you know get get a good walk in</u>
<u n="85" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0265">I don't do it every day but erm <pause dur="short"/> I do it maybe once er maybe twice a week</u>
<u n="87" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0265">just walk up to churches where that that area and then back then sometimes I walk along the seafront and then up</u>
<u n="89" who="S0264">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0265">is it <anon type="place"/> street? and back through the town centre or vice versa</u>
<u n="91" who="S0264"><vocal desc="cough"/> <anon type="place"/> street <pause dur="long"/> anyway so I'm going I'll I'll probably take that case and no rucksack but it'll be a nuisance because I suppose I'll have to check it into the cloakroom</u>
<u n="92" who="S0265" whoConfidence="low">mm you would</u>
<u n="93" who="S0264">and that means</u>
<u n="94" who="S0265">more time</u>
<u n="95" who="S0264">at the end it could cause a delay in leaving and then you don't know how long the applause will take and if they do an encore</u>
<u n="96" who="S0265">mm <trunc>tr</trunc></u>
<u n="97" who="S0264" trans="overlap">I think it's unlikely isn't it? because erm encores would usually be for soloists that would be the first half wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0265">mm I can't remember the programme now what what is it? the Rachmaninov a symphony second? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0264">and a new composition <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="100" who="S0265">a new composition by some Russian</u>
<u n="101" who="S0264">Chinese</u>
<u n="102" who="S0265">ah yes <pause dur="long"/> is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> going to that one?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0264">he's not going to it any more</u>
<u n="104" who="S0265">oh <pause dur="short"/> there's not many left anyway</u>
<u n="105" who="S0264">well yeah I think it finishes next Saturday doesn't it?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0265">mm no maybe it was the Saturday after it's about the twelfth twelfth of September isn't it?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0264">I don't know</u>
<u n="108" who="S0265">thirteenth I think's the last one <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0264">anyway <vocal desc="cough"/> I'll erm I'll probably take her I can take her Circle line as far as Victoria when you go afterwards</u>
<u n="110" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0264">if it's convenient and then I'll change but erm my train I'll expect I'll get the quarter to eleven train</u>
<u n="112" who="S0265">right</u>
<u n="113" who="S0264">cos I don't think I'd make the erm I doubt if I'd make the ten fifteen because it's a long walk to the tube</u>
<u n="114" who="S0265">right</u>
<u n="115" who="S0264">that's the problem with that place <pause dur="long"/> yeah it does it</u>
<u n="116" who="S0265">what place the Royal Albert Hall?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0264">well yes and and South Kensington tube station where they it takes a long time to walk there <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't look far but it is it takes you know ten fifteen minutes doesn't it?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0265">and there'll be loads of people doing the same thing <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0264">well I wonder whether there's any point in doing it</u>
<u n="120" who="S0265">what rush it?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0264">no I mean going at all it's supposed to be to celebrate birthday but the whole thing is meaningless <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0265">what do you mean the whole thing is meaningless? <unclear/> to celebrate birthdays with having a meal and enjoy the concert <pause dur="short"/> it just means erm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0264">it's no no where it's weeks <vocal desc="cough"/> it's weeks after the event and there's no relationship is there?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0265">it's alright <pause dur="short"/> you probably wouldn't have done it were it not for birthdays <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0264">do you want erm pineapple or erm plums or an orange?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0265"><unclear/> do those erm mandarins need using up?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0264" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0265">cos I saw one looked a bit black a bit manky yes</u>
<u n="129" who="S0264">well anyway you probably wouldn't want to eat it but anyway do you want a mandarin and something?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0265" trans="overlap">yeah I'll have a mandarin yes <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0264">they're not gonna taste very nice are they if they haven't been?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0265">well if they're not very nice I won't eat it</u>
<u n="133" who="S0264">no I mean because they've been in the fridge</u>
<u n="134" who="S0265">oh they'll be cold yes <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0264">anyway this is this is from yesterday they brought a very strange selection of fruit I I wonder who decides these things because erm last a week a week yesterday there was one red apple green apples and erm mm don't know whether there were mandarins or not but anyway yesterday there were only green apples and oranges</u>
<u n="136" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0264">and <trunc>ever</trunc>everybody knows that people don't like oranges cos they're messy</u>
<u n="138" who="S0265">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0264">erm and erm and the sandwiches were quite strange as well cos I I remember erm last last week there were erm I don't are they called shrimp or prawn?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0265">prawn probably</u>
<u n="141" who="S0264">and <trunc>may</trunc> yeah sandwiches but erm I think they're quite expensive aren't they prawns? anyway there was nothing like that</u>
<u n="142" who="S0265" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0264">there was there was tinned salmon and cucumber er yesterday that was quite nice because of the cucumber</u>
<u n="144" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0264">that was the nicest and then there was also some cheddar sort of erm what do you call it when the cheddar is put through a sieve? <pause dur="short"/> grated</u>
<u n="146" who="S0265">grated cheese</u>
<u n="147" who="S0264">grated cheese sandwiches and probably had bits mm anyway <pause dur="short"/> there's nothing to write home about</u>
<u n="148" who="S0265">brown bread or white?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0264">oh I don't know there's <trunc>no</trunc>nothing properly brown <pause dur="short"/> there was definitely white there and there was something that was off white <pause dur="long"/> and there was enough an average of probably there was enough for everybody to have three hearts which in a way was sufficient because I think they add olive oil or something to fill you up <unclear/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0265">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0264">they used to do that at <anon type="place"/> the the sandwiches were actually indigestible</u>
<u n="152" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="153" who="S0264">they they they'd look alright and then you'd eat them and you'd suddenly feel queasy maybe it was salmonella</u>
<u n="154" who="S0265">mm <vocal desc="cough"/> I'd have thought if it was something like salmonella you'd have had pain and vomiting</u>
<u n="155" who="S0264">yeah well I remember taking it up with them I think I might have found out I think I might have asked one of the people serving what was in them</u>
<u n="156" who="S0265">so did you need to eat your own sandwiches that you took <pause dur="short"/> as well?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0264">yesterday?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0265">yeah or did you have that at in the evening or something?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0264">I had them on the train</u>
<u n="160" who="S0265" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="161" who="S0264">on the way home I didn't I told you it was a we weren't moving around we were tied <vocal desc="cough"/> we were just sat behind a desk for <pause dur="long"/> from nine o'clock till four or five o'clock</u>
<u n="162" who="S0265">yes</u>
<u n="163" who="S0264">it's horrible and and also in the afternoon for the first time cos of security erm they it was like an exam we had to move the desks from the horseshoe shape to exam style</u>
<u n="164" who="S0265">oh yes</u>
<u n="165" who="S0264" trans="overlap">a metre a metre apart plus we got given different erm sets of paper anyway and you know that bloke from <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> who I told you about?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0265">erm which one? I can't remember</u>
<u n="167" who="S0264">anyway erm once again did it rather like last Saturday erm I heard a I heard a noise and it throwing things into his bag and stuff and he walked out and he just like he just just zipped through it and finished in an hour or something</u>
<u n="168" who="S0265">oh</u>
<u n="169" who="S0264">I thought that was strange I mean you can you you could do that you could probably do that <pause dur="short"/> you could do that in an on an ordinary working Saturday but that that was that was more you had to get it right if you didn't if you don't get it right you have to re-do it so I thought that was a bit of a risk taking that attitude</u>
<u n="170" who="S0265">mm maybe it's maybe it's it's all stuff he's done for years and years and years</u>
<u n="171" who="S0264">yeah but I know he's a new person</u>
<u n="172" who="S0265">oh really?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0264">he might have been doing it before somewhere else but</u>
<u n="174" who="S0265">mm strange</u>
<u n="175" who="S0264">it's just his attitude anyway I was one of the last people there and makes me think maybe my brain is slowing down</u>
<u n="176" who="S0265">it's probably just more conscientious</u>
<u n="177" who="S0264">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> it's true that if there's a deadline then you speed up and there wasn't actually there wasn't a deadline particularly you could theoretically I think you could have carried on till seven o'clock</u>
<u n="178" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0264">if you'd wanted to</u>
<u n="180" who="S0265">and were you the last person?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0264">no I was the last but one</u>
<u n="182" who="S0265">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0264">or the last but two cos when I finished somebody else finished as well</u>
<u n="184" who="S0265">mm</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
