<text id="SJDK">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:16:13</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-12</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0486 S0527</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In the ticket office at Creech-St- Michael.</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Aquaintences</relationships>
		<topics>Work, boating, building, model engineering, family matters.</topics>
		<activity>Taking a break from the working party.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, Inquiring anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0486">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Well, Somerset</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/Wales</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>I may have a slight Somerset accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Taunton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>40 years on and off</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>retired artist and antique dealer/gallery owner</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0527">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Taunton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South West</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Taunton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>48 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Carpenter</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>4</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0486">right <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's really good of you to talk to me today so we're on and we're active</u>
<u n="2" who="S0527">right</u>
<u n="3" who="S0486">and erm would you like to tell me how long you've lived in in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0527">er forty-eight years erm</u>
<u n="5" who="S0486" trans="overlap">forty-eight years?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0527"><trunc>ye</trunc>yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0486" trans="overlap">gosh</u>
<u n="8" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah <trunc>ye</trunc></u>
<u n="9" who="S0486" trans="overlap">so where were you born?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0527"><anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="12" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah born and bred</u>
<u n="13" who="S0486">right erm so then you've probably got more of a local accent than anybody</u>
<u n="14" who="S0527">I would so say so yeah I mean</u>
<u n="15" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0527" trans="overlap">some people say I've got a real <anon type="place"/> accent but I I don't really take any notice of it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0486">and I I know you've been in a family business for years</u>
<u n="18" who="S0527">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0486" trans="overlap">haven't you?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0527">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0486">erm and you're erm er a carpenter by trade?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah that's it</u>
<u n="23" who="S0486">yeah?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0527" trans="overlap">carpenter yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0486">and erm what sort of work do you do?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0527">well carpentry joinery buildings extensions conversions anything really in the <trunc>b</trunc> in the construction line really</u>
<u n="27" who="S0486">what do you favour yourself mostly?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0527">erm the joinery side of things making windows doors staircases and maybe putting kitchens in and</u>
<u n="29" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="30" who="S0527">er things like that yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0486">right and so where did you learn your trade?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0527">er I learnt my trade with my father I was er he sort of er said why don't you come on and work for me? so I said alright and I'll give it a go sort of thing cos er I I I'd left school about four years and hadn't really sort of thought about doing that and erm then started and never looked back</u>
<u n="33" who="S0486">right I see and er but you didn't actually go formally to college? you were an apprenticeship?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0527">oh yeah yeah I done a full apprenticeship four</u>
<u n="35" who="S0486" trans="overlap">did you?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0527">four year apprenticeship</u>
<u n="37" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="38" who="S0527">going through erm the basic three years carpentry and joinery and then the one years of arts craft</u>
<u n="39" who="S0486">right and what?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0486"><trunc>wh</trunc>where did you go? did you go to?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0527">well I had to go travel for that I had for the first three years I had to go to <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> college</u>
<u n="43" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="44" who="S0527" trans="overlap">of er further education</u>
<u n="45" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0527">erm because they didn't run the course in <anon type="place"/> and then on my advanced craft I could do it in <anon type="place"/> because they were running the course then</u>
<u n="47" who="S0486">right right things were very different in those days weren't they? because erm <anon type="place"/> college used to be a really top notch place for</u>
<u n="48" who="S0527" trans="overlap">well it it did yes</u>
<u n="49" who="S0486" trans="overlap">trades</u>
<u n="50" who="S0527">oh for trades yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0527" trans="overlap">you can't learn anything these</u>
<u n="53" who="S0486" trans="overlap"><trunc>n</trunc></u>
<u n="54" who="S0527" trans="overlap">very much these days</u>
<u n="55" who="S0486" trans="overlap"><trunc>n</trunc></u>
<u n="56" who="S0527" trans="overlap">in there</u>
<u n="57" who="S0486">no</u>
<u n="58" who="S0527" trans="overlap">and it's it's changed the way they run the apprenticeships are</u>
<u n="59" who="S0486">absolutely</u>
<u n="60" who="S0527" trans="overlap">not not good for the the construction industry</u>
<u n="61" who="S0486">no I'm sure they're not erm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0486">the erm I I mean I did an art degree erm five years ago erm at <anon type="place"/> college with <anon type="place"/> university</u>
<u n="64" who="S0527">right</u>
<u n="65" who="S0486">erm and it was very different and er the principal has got rid of all the erm art erm</u>
<u n="66" who="S0527">oh right</u>
<u n="67" who="S0486">yeah at that level there aren't any degree courses for fine art now I think I was the</u>
<u n="68" who="S0527" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="69" who="S0486">penultimate well there was one other after my course erm but anyway <trunc>i</trunc>it er was the <anon type="place"/> college of arts and technology erm and it all she's really interested in in hairdressing apparently <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0527">oh <trunc>ri</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0486">the according to the tutors who all got made redundant they were quite you know cross about that anyway back to you which is far more important so you're a model engineer today and you're</u>
<u n="72" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="73" who="S0486">and you're here to do the working party yeah?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0527">well I've I've stopped in just to drop some materials off really</u>
<u n="75" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh have you? oh <trunc>ri</trunc></u>
<u n="76" who="S0527" trans="overlap">for for for all the rest of them to do something</u>
<u n="77" who="S0486">oh <trunc>ri</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0527"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0486"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0527"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0486">oh <trunc>ri</trunc> yes well that's right line them up and get them</u>
<u n="82" who="S0527">yeah this is it</u>
<u n="83" who="S0486" trans="overlap">and get them get them working</u>
<u n="84" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah give them something to work with</u>
<u n="85" who="S0486"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm and erm and so you've been in the model engineers for how long?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0527">erm oh on and off for oh <trunc>m</trunc> expect thirty years really I suppose</u>
<u n="87" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="88" who="S0527" trans="overlap">but er I dropped away for a for quite a while it was probably ten or fifteen years erm really not having so much to do with it cos it was more my father's hobby</u>
<u n="89" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0527">erm unfortunately when he passed away I decided that you know I'd come and sort of help them do a few bits and pieces and then er I've got back into it a bit more since then but er yeah it's it's really er I'm but I've been involved in some <trunc>res</trunc> way or form for a long time really</u>
<u n="91" who="S0486">what are you working on at the moment?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0527">er well I've erm <trunc>j</trunc> not not on the model engineering side except for they've just made three carriages or three carriage</u>
<u n="93" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="94" who="S0527" trans="overlap">bases in there which I'll make all the woodwork tops for</u>
<u n="95" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right yes</u>
<u n="96" who="S0527" trans="overlap">sort of thing so</u>
<u n="97" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="98" who="S0527" trans="overlap">erm cos they're hoping to have a an open day next year</u>
<u n="99" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="100" who="S0527" trans="overlap">erm and they want some extra carriages</u>
<u n="101" who="S0486">oh right yes I've heard about the open day that that should be interesting <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0527"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0486">I think there are several schools of thought on that aren't there?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yes there's a yes there's erm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0486" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0527">it's er should be interesting anyway but er yeah so we can get the carriages made and I'm also making a couple of my own so</u>
<u n="107" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="108" who="S0527" trans="overlap">I'll get those as well and then they'll have plenty of er carriages to run on their railway here</u>
<u n="109" who="S0486" trans="overlap">jolly good jolly good that's great erm because erm this model engineers is in a park here isn't it? can you tell can you describe the park to me this morning?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0527">er yes the park's erm probably about er five hundred yards across and five hundred <trunc>y</trunc> six or seven hundred yards deep erm it's er originally was a recreation field erm with a football pitch erm with some tennis courts on the side the tennis courts got very badly vandalised and er disused and we were invited here by the parish council erm to er rent a bit of land and to give the parish council some income at that time erm so that er they could carry on doing other things and then we've built a track round the periphery of the park erm which er you know we've got a track running all the way around that does a complete loop tack to a turntable at the other end</u>
<u n="111" who="S0486">right yeah and erm it it's a <trunc>lov</trunc> er it is a lovely park</u>
<u n="112" who="S0527">it is</u>
<u n="113" who="S0486">yeah and the we're we're very near the motorway in the background you can hear the motorway erm and that's that's not a problem erm I used to live in <anon type="place"/> and have this noise all the time and it didn't worry me after a while you don't notice it do you?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0527" trans="overlap">no to be honest you don't I mean</u>
<u n="115" who="S0486" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="116" who="S0527">we we work next to a railway line in our workshop and people have come in to us before and said christ bet you enjoy this cos the trains aren't running today and you go what trains? cos you really don't take any notice of the</u>
<u n="117" who="S0486" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="118" who="S0527">you know <trunc>m</trunc> it's right next to the main line</u>
<u n="119" who="S0486">well I mean also I expect you've got a lot of equipment on the go haven't you? noisy equipment</u>
<u n="120" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah there's a lot of times yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0486" trans="overlap">and you've got ear defenders on I expect and all that sort of thing</u>
<u n="122" who="S0527" trans="overlap">most of the time yeah yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0486" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so you wouldn't so erm I know that your father was instrumental and your family in building the large building here</u>
<u n="124" who="S0527">er</u>
<u n="125" who="S0486" trans="overlap">which you know</u>
<u n="126" who="S0527" trans="overlap">that's it yeah was erm the the carriage was the carriage shed er there was named in his honour after unfortunately after he passed away</u>
<u n="127" who="S0486">oh</u>
<u n="128" who="S0527">and they named it in his honour and cos because he was sort of like the driving force behind it if you like</u>
<u n="129" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="130" who="S0527">erm in getting it built and that well and for the model engineers for a quite a <trunc>whi</trunc> you know a long a lot of years really</u>
<u n="131" who="S0486">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0527" trans="overlap">he was er very much involved from about nineteen eighty I think when <anon type="place"/> park</u>
<u n="133" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="134" who="S0527" trans="overlap">originally started up</u>
<u n="135" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="136" who="S0527">erm so yeah it's er it's nice to sort of like er have the knowledge that there's something's named in his er honour out here really you know</u>
<u n="137" who="S0486" trans="overlap">wonderful</u>
<u n="138" who="S0527" trans="overlap">it's quite a privilege really yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0486" trans="overlap">wonderful given the local politics you know that ebb and flow around the place erm it's great that <trunc>h</trunc> you managed to get it up really</u>
<u n="140" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0486" trans="overlap">isn't it?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0527" trans="overlap">this is it yeah this is it</u>
<u n="143" who="S0486" trans="overlap">bit of an achievement</u>
<u n="144" who="S0527" trans="overlap">er yeah it is really considering er you know <trunc>wha</trunc> well considering we had a lot of vandalism to start with because</u>
<u n="145" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0527" trans="overlap">as they were building it</u>
<u n="147" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0527" trans="overlap">whenever night time when all people went home somebody <trunc>f</trunc> kind person from the village used to come up and push the walls over</u>
<u n="149" who="S0486">really?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0527" trans="overlap">at night time yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0486" trans="overlap">really? yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah sort of thing just sort of and they did find out it was one particular person er I don't know who it was now but lived in a bungalow down across the way and he could see it being put up during the day and obviously didn't like the idea of somebody building up here and come up in the night time and pushed the walls over</u>
<u n="153" who="S0486">I didn't hear that story</u>
<u n="154" who="S0527">oh right</u>
<u n="155" who="S0486" trans="overlap">I hadn't heard the story</u>
<u n="156" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0486" trans="overlap">I did hear cos the twenty years ago when I met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I was living in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0527">oh right</u>
<u n="159" who="S0486" trans="overlap">and I had a house in fact they're building in you know at the back of it now and I'm <trunc>gl</trunc> jolly glad I was always worried that they were going to build cos there was a lovely field behind and erm one of the things that was in the news at the time was about the bulldozer?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0527">right</u>
<u n="161" who="S0486">and it how it bulldozed the pavilion down?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0527">yeah yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0486" trans="overlap">and I remember that and when later they said oh they're going out to <anon type="place"/> I said oh <trunc>th</trunc>they mustn't do that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> and now</u>
<u n="164" who="S0527"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0486">it's a terrible place</u>
<u n="166" who="S0527" trans="overlap">a terrible place <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> and so now I've heard that you you know you had trouble with your builder</u>
<u n="168" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah this is it yeah as we've built it up they they'd come up the next day or the next week</u>
<u n="169" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0527" trans="overlap">and find all the walls were pushed over sort of thing and had to rebuild them</u>
<u n="171" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh how do you feel about that?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0527">well it's I just think this is just there's er <trunc>th</trunc>there's too many people with er too much time on their hands if they can come up and do that you know</u>
<u n="173" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0527" trans="overlap">they'd rather vandalise something than actually construct something</u>
<u n="175" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="176" who="S0527" trans="overlap">you know and er they you know instead of just coming along and saying well you know why are you here? and why do you wanna be here? and understand the reasons for it</u>
<u n="177" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0527">they'd rather just come up on their own and erm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0527">destroy other people's hard work</u>
<u n="181" who="S0486">yes I mean even if you ask them to to join and come they probably wouldn't come</u>
<u n="182" who="S0527">no no but they'd rather you know they'd rather spoil everybody else's thing and</u>
<u n="183" who="S0486" trans="overlap">spoil everybody's work yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0527" trans="overlap">they cost people money at the end of the day you know and</u>
<u n="185" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh definitely</u>
<u n="186" who="S0527" trans="overlap">and I think at the end of the day it was criminal damage as well you know</u>
<u n="187" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0527">er</u>
<u n="189" who="S0486" trans="overlap">erm <trunc>h</trunc> did you ever feel at any time about giving up? I mean given the situation?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0527">well I mean I wasn't that involved at that point</u>
<u n="191" who="S0486">no</u>
<u n="192" who="S0527" trans="overlap">erm I mean it was because it was more my father's hobby</u>
<u n="193" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0527" trans="overlap">I thought no you know he's happy doing that and it's his hobby er and it wasn't until after he went we sort of we said well you know we just will go out there and help er do finish off something he started cos</u>
<u n="195" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0527" trans="overlap">it was very unusual because usually he was helping finish something we started</u>
<u n="197" who="S0486">right right</u>
<u n="198" who="S0527" trans="overlap">erm so we thought we'd go out and sort of help finish it and we were out here sort of thing erm and the clubhouse had been finished by that point</u>
<u n="199" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="200" who="S0527">erm but I mean I know when he used to come back and he used to say you know sort of thing people had been up here and vandalised it they you know</u>
<u n="201" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0527" trans="overlap">they spent a day building walls and had to then</u>
<u n="203" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0527">rebuild them</u>
<u n="205" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="206" who="S0527">sort of thing which is really</u>
<u n="207" who="S0486" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="208" who="S0527">rather disheartening for people</u>
<u n="209" who="S0486">oh definitely</u>
<u n="210" who="S0527">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0486" trans="overlap">definitely erm one of the things that really I really admire about the model engineers above any other society is that they're all well you all are craftsmen and you're all engineers</u>
<u n="212" who="S0527">of some description yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0486" trans="overlap">of some description</u>
<u n="214" who="S0527">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0486" trans="overlap">and that you all make things and sometimes from scratch erm mostly from scratch erm er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying he spends three hours a day in his workshop</u>
<u n="216" who="S0527">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0486" trans="overlap">and if he can't go in he gets grumpy</u>
<u n="218" who="S0527"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0486" trans="overlap">er er does that apply to you? if you can't make something?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0527" trans="overlap">er well I no I well I I enjoy getting away</u>
<u n="221" who="S0486" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0527">from the work I have to admit</u>
<u n="223" who="S0486" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh right well you do</u>
<u n="224" who="S0527">yeah yeah I do enjoy getting away from the work</u>
<u n="225" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah right</u>
<u n="226" who="S0527" trans="overlap">erm but I mean I also I've got a boat as well you see</u>
<u n="227" who="S0486">oh have you?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0527" trans="overlap">so er I enjoy sort of</u>
<u n="229" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="230" who="S0527" trans="overlap">like er using that which is er something so that's my escape from work and that's</u>
<u n="231" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="232" who="S0527">that's on a marina down in <anon type="place"/> and er</u>
<u n="233" who="S0486">ah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0527" trans="overlap"><trunc>i</trunc>if I'm down there I can't be on the phone just</u>
<u n="235" who="S0486" trans="overlap"><trunc>n</trunc></u>
<u n="236" who="S0527">somebody can't get hold of me easily to say come and do this and come and do that</u>
<u n="237" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0527">because the phone is always on twenty-four seven but erm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0486">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0527">I mean it's nice to be away and then you can say well I'm too far away to <trunc>co</trunc>come and do it you know?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes exactly and you don't take a mobile with you obviously</u>
<u n="242" who="S0527">I I do but that's only for emergencies really</u>
<u n="243" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="244" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0486" trans="overlap">so erm well well tell me about your boat that's wonderful erm how many foot long is <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0527" trans="overlap">erm it was twenty twenty-four feet feet long</u>
<u n="247" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right yes</u>
<u n="248" who="S0527" trans="overlap">erm it's a it's a fishing a type of fishing boat</u>
<u n="249" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0527">er it was originally they made them as fishing boats but they</u>
<u n="251" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="252" who="S0527">they've they call still call them a fishing boat but it's more of a pleasure boat now</u>
<u n="253" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="254" who="S0527" trans="overlap">rather than a fishing boat erm the they gradually evolved from giving less deck space at the back and giving more cabin space</u>
<u n="255" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="256" who="S0527">erm which is quite nice and it sleeps about four people</u>
<u n="257" who="S0486">oh I see</u>
<u n="258" who="S0527" trans="overlap">and er</u>
<u n="259" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0527">you know you've got a little cooker and fridge and</u>
<u n="261" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0527">just just just er pleasurable to get out and get out on the sea really</u>
<u n="263" who="S0486">so erm are you you're not nervous obviously about taking it out?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0527">oh not at all</u>
<u n="265" who="S0486">erm what what sort of weather would put you off? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0527">erm to be honest as long as long as we're under sort of twenty-two miles an hour</u>
<u n="267" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0527" trans="overlap">we're we're alright and then it depends on the direction of the wind er down in er where I'm <unclear/> in <anon type="place"/> if it's easterlies</u>
<u n="269" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0527" trans="overlap">er they're particularly bad they have a tendency</u>
<u n="271" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="272" who="S0527">to really chop the sea up</u>
<u n="273" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="274" who="S0527" trans="overlap">erm but if it's southerly winds and it's offshore</u>
<u n="275" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="276" who="S0527">you're not too bad</u>
<u n="277" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="278" who="S0527" trans="overlap">usually the sea stays fairly flat</u>
<u n="279" who="S0486">good</u>
<u n="280" who="S0527">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right so so whereabouts is it berthed? did <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="282" who="S0527" trans="overlap">er <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0486">oh <anon type="place"/> I know</u>
<u n="284" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0486"><anon type="place"/> it's lovely</u>
<u n="286" who="S0527">yeah it is beautiful</u>
<u n="287" who="S0486" trans="overlap">but do you find difficulty getting down there in the summer when there are so many <trunc>holidayma</trunc>?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0527" trans="overlap">it it can be yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0486" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="290" who="S0527">you can long as you go down early in the morning no I mean it's averages about an hour and ten hour and twenty minutes?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh that's not too <trunc>ba</trunc></u>
<u n="292" who="S0527" trans="overlap">so it's not too bad</u>
<u n="293" who="S0486">no</u>
<u n="294" who="S0527">and of a night time when I come home and it's late</u>
<u n="295" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0527" trans="overlap">er I can usually do it in about an hour and five</u>
<u n="297" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="298" who="S0527" trans="overlap">or an hour and ten minutes</u>
<u n="299" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="300" who="S0527" trans="overlap">easily erm and they also are building a new the bypass through <anon type="place"/> past <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh are they?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0527">now</u>
<u n="303" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="304" who="S0527">which takes you straight from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0486">good yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0527" trans="overlap">er so it saves a lot that's gonna save a lot of time</u>
<u n="307" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="308" who="S0527">hopefully <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0486" trans="overlap">good good so you're planning a lot more I bet you're waiting for next summer or do you</u>
<u n="310" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah this is it</u>
<u n="311" who="S0486" trans="overlap">do you go down all the year round?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0527">I do yes</u>
<u n="313" who="S0486">do you?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yes I'm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0527" trans="overlap">going down next Friday</u>
<u n="317" who="S0486">are you?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0527" trans="overlap">to take it for a service</u>
<u n="319" who="S0486">oh right</u>
<u n="320" who="S0527" trans="overlap">or we've got a day off next Friday</u>
<u n="321" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh wonderful</u>
<u n="322" who="S0527">to take it to <anon type="place"/> for service</u>
<u n="323" who="S0486">and and what's is it a she? what's she called?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0527">er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0486"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0527" trans="overlap">so yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right okay</u>
<u n="328" who="S0527" trans="overlap">sort of thing er it was named by the previous owner</u>
<u n="329" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="330" who="S0527">I don't know why</u>
<u n="331" who="S0486">no</u>
<u n="332" who="S0527" trans="overlap">it was named <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but to be honest it's quite an easy name</u>
<u n="333" who="S0486" trans="overlap">it is</u>
<u n="334" who="S0527" trans="overlap">when you're on a radio</u>
<u n="335" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="336" who="S0527">if you're radioing in</u>
<u n="337" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="338" who="S0527" trans="overlap">to somebody it's easier</u>
<u n="339" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0527" trans="overlap">to say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> rather than a long</u>
<u n="341" who="S0486">a great big</u>
<u n="342" who="S0527" trans="overlap">drawn out name</u>
<u n="343" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0527">sort of thing</u>
<u n="345" who="S0486" trans="overlap"><trunc>ye</trunc> Catherine of Portugal</u>
<u n="346" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah this is the thing</u>
<u n="347" who="S0486" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> or something like that</u>
<u n="348" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah which is</u>
<u n="349" who="S0486"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0527" trans="overlap">and if you've got to spell out in <unclear><trunc>phononi</trunc></unclear> er <unclear>phonenics</unclear></u>
<u n="351" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="352" who="S0527"><vocal desc="laugh"/> sort of thing it's er it's quite a thing whereas that's just <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and you're done <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="353" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah you're done</u>
<u n="354" who="S0527" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah well that's a very good name I mean</u>
<u n="356" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0486" trans="overlap">I can see the value in that erm I I was lucky myself once to have erm a job for the summer erm to crew on a on a twenty-four foot</u>
<u n="358" who="S0527" trans="overlap">oh lovely</u>
<u n="359" who="S0486">I can't remember what it was called erm it was erm it was a friend of my sister's and my sister didn't want to go with him so I went and erm I had to cook and clean and just like you know help</u>
<u n="360" who="S0527">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0486" trans="overlap">cast off and you know do all the things</u>
<u n="362" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0486">and I did it and we went all around the Isle of Wight over to the Isle of Wight all you know it was it was it was great because er we had an Indian summer and the weather was very good we've got another two minutes?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0527">yeah that's alright</u>
<u n="365" who="S0486">to do? so erm er do you go away on holiday as well?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0527" trans="overlap">er well <trunc>ye</trunc> I stay down there occasionally but this is a fairly new boat to me I only bought it in July this year</u>
<u n="367" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="368" who="S0527">er before that I had an open boat which you couldn't sort of sleep on</u>
<u n="369" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="370" who="S0527">erm but I had that for a year just to see if I would use it</u>
<u n="371" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0527">and then I thought right I'll change up to something with a cabin and</u>
<u n="373" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0527">so a bit more</u>
<u n="375" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0527" trans="overlap">luxurious</u>
<u n="377" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="378" who="S0527" trans="overlap">if you like erm but I mean I would like a sailing boat but I can't afford a sailing boat so</u>
<u n="379" who="S0486" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="380" who="S0527" trans="overlap">I've gotta have a motorboat</u>
<u n="381" who="S0486" trans="overlap">no oh it's a</u>
<u n="382" who="S0527" trans="overlap">er</u>
<u n="383" who="S0486" trans="overlap">a <trunc>mo</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah it's a motorboat</u>
<u n="385" who="S0486" trans="overlap">ours was a sailing boat as well we had</u>
<u n="386" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0486">we had power</u>
<u n="388" who="S0527" trans="overlap">I've done a <trunc>l</trunc> mm</u>
<u n="389" who="S0486" trans="overlap">but we had sail as well</u>
<u n="390" who="S0527" trans="overlap">that's it</u>
<u n="391" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0527" trans="overlap">I've done a lot of sailing in the past cos I used to have very good friends down in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0527">had erm sailing boats and that but unfortunately erm they're getting older well one unfortunately passed away one's</u>
<u n="395" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0527">getting very much older which he doesn't do very much</u>
<u n="397" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="398" who="S0527">but I do prefer sailing I have to admit</u>
<u n="399" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0527">it's lovely to be out sailing</u>
<u n="401" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="402" who="S0527">but erm unfortunately it's the length it's the upkeep</u>
<u n="403" who="S0486">yes exactly</u>
<u n="404" who="S0527" trans="overlap">erm cos</u>
<u n="405" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0527" trans="overlap">it's every time you go up er three feet of stuff you you're paying more on your moorings for</u>
<u n="407" who="S0486" trans="overlap">absolutely absolutely</u>
<u n="408" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0486">so erm yeah I can imagine that the erm yeah so erm now what have we got to do next? oh yeah erm so erm do you take people with you?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0527">I do yeah I take my partner down and my</u>
<u n="411" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0527" trans="overlap">stepdaughter</u>
<u n="413" who="S0486">oh</u>
<u n="414" who="S0527" trans="overlap">erm there's also quite a few people I know friends of mine</u>
<u n="415" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0527" trans="overlap"><trunc>th</trunc> often say oh well if you're going down the boat <trunc>c</trunc> we can come</u>
<u n="417" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="418" who="S0527" trans="overlap">sort of thing and I've got quite a few people erm er I've taken the erm er <trunc>s</trunc> my partner's erm sister and her husband</u>
<u n="419" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="420" who="S0527">and the two children out on it</u>
<u n="421" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="422" who="S0527">I've taken a friend of mine and her two children only youngsters about five and six years old sort of thing</u>
<u n="423" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0527">they've come out erm and providing they're well behaved it's fine you know</u>
<u n="425" who="S0486" trans="overlap">it's fine</u>
<u n="426" who="S0527" trans="overlap">sort of thing</u>
<u n="427" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0527" trans="overlap">cos you've gotta be obviously sensible</u>
<u n="429" who="S0486">oh yeah</u>
<u n="430" who="S0527" trans="overlap">for for safety really</u>
<u n="431" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="432" who="S0527" trans="overlap">but I mean we <trunc>al</trunc> I always make er make sure they you know we all wear life jackets</u>
<u n="433" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0527">er so that's the main thing cos you've got</u>
<u n="435" who="S0486" trans="overlap">do do you swim from the boat?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0527">er I haven't er no</u>
<u n="437" who="S0486" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="438" who="S0527" trans="overlap">but I mean it's <trunc>i</trunc>in the summer down there yeah it's quite feasible to do it</u>
<u n="439" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah it is</u>
<u n="440" who="S0527" trans="overlap">sort of thing cos the</u>
<u n="441" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0527" trans="overlap">water temperature does get quite good down there</u>
<u n="443" who="S0486">yeah I'm sure</u>
<u n="444" who="S0527" trans="overlap">in in the summer</u>
<u n="445" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="446" who="S0527">er especially if you get into the bay sort of thing</u>
<u n="447" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0527">the water temperature can come up quite considerably</u>
<u n="449" who="S0486">yeah I was taken out by some people in <anon type="place"/> once who had a little a small erm little <trunc>p</trunc> a powerboat and I I was taken out and then they stopped and said threw the anchor down and said come on now you can go swimming and we swam and it was lovely</u>
<u n="450" who="S0527">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0486" trans="overlap">I never thought er I would being absolutely terrified because I'm not really a very good swimmer but the thing is if you just go round the boat and</u>
<u n="452" who="S0527">yeah that's it and stay close</u>
<u n="453" who="S0486" trans="overlap">there's someone who does sing er swim well</u>
<u n="454" who="S0527">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0486" trans="overlap">you know</u>
<u n="456" who="S0527">and being in salt water you always seem a bit more buoyant in salt water as well</u>
<u n="457" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh exactly exactly</u>
<u n="458" who="S0527" trans="overlap">rather than <trunc>sw</trunc> a swimming pool</u>
<u n="459" who="S0486">and so can you swim well?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0527">I can swim enough if I if my life depended on it</u>
<u n="461" who="S0486"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="462" who="S0527">I could swim well enough</u>
<u n="463" who="S0486"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0527">but if I'm just pleasure swimming I do get tired quickly mm</u>
<u n="465" who="S0486">yeah well exactly</u>
<u n="466" who="S0527">but er if er if my life depended on it I expect I could</u>
<u n="467" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="468" who="S0527" trans="overlap">keep going <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="469" who="S0486">well that chap Walliams isn't it? Walliams he <trunc>sa</trunc> he he swam the Channel didn't he?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0527" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="471" who="S0486">erm and erm I I mean I don't know how he did that but they managed to do it somehow so erm look we're at sixteen minutes so we're alright there erm</u>
<u n="472" who="S0527">very good</u>
<u n="473" who="S0486">so I can</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
