<text id="SJDM">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:00:31</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-05</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0017 S0018 S0019</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Birmingham</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Learning how to drive, car insurance, holidays, plans for the week, family</topics>
		<activity>Parents and daughter talking about driving, holidays, plans for the week and family.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0017">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Woburn, Buckinghamshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>35 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Accountant</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner; German -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0019">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>35 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Court usher</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0017">why does it show?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0018">so <trunc>h</trunc> how much is your insurance?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0017">it would be without the discount about seven hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="4" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> between the two of you?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0017">no each</u>
<u n="6" who="S0019">no each</u>
<u n="7" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="8" who="S0017">Cos each of us has the other as a nominated second driver</u>
<u n="9" who="S0018">oh is that  is that  why it costs more?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0017"><trunc>D</trunc> it shouldn't be much more for that for us because of the length and because it's only occasional use <pause dur="short"/> each of us for the other car</u>
<u n="11" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0017">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but um</u>
<u n="13" who="S0019"><vocal desc="cough"/> Yours would be more but it wouldn't be as much as if you were a young you know sort of eighteen nineteen year old <pause dur="short"/> um your age will tend to lower their premiums a bit</u>
<u n="14" who="S0018">even though I've got no experience?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0019">mm <pause dur="short"/> if you are a newly qualified driver of what? Seventeen eighteen <pause dur="short"/> although women's tends to be lower than men's but they've</u>
<u n="16" who="S0017">it has been <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0019">bought this equalisation thing</u>
<u n="18" who="S0017">but you could be paying two thousand four thousand pounds</u>
<u n="19" who="S0019" trans="overlap">two thousand</u>
<u n="20" who="S0018">how much?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0019">yeah <pause dur="short"/> for one year</u>
<u n="22" who="S0018" trans="overlap">for one person for one year?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0017">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0019">mm hm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0018"><trunc>B</trunc> em</u>
<u n="26" who="S0019">as you are much older than that yours won't be as high</u>
<u n="27" who="S0017">the risk factor is in young people</u>
<u n="28" who="S0019">mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0017">starting to drive</u>
<u n="30" who="S0019">they are more likely to have accidents</u>
<u n="31" who="S0018">so I doubt whether yours would be anything like that much</u>
<u n="32" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes I guess they've got they might have less life experience so that might make them more prone to accidents but <pause dur="short"/> I think a twenty year old brain is so</u>
<u n="33" who="S0019">not at all</u>
<u n="34" who="S0018">it assimilates new things a lot more quickly and</u>
<u n="35" who="S0019">not at all</u>
<u n="36" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> no I think it's true</u>
<u n="37" who="S0017">yes but it that it tends to build confidence where confidence isn't justified</u>
<u n="38" who="S0018">true <pause dur="short"/> true <pause dur="short"/> but I think you get used to things a lot more quickly?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0019">yes but you tend to be a bit more reckless</u>
<u n="40" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0019">young males particularly</u>
<u n="42" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0019">the number of young males who have a an accident within the first twelve months of getting their license is fairly considerable <pause dur="short"/> not so great for women <pause dur="short"/> cos I think majority of women tend to be a bit more cautious</u>
<u n="44" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0019">but boys certainly don't</u>
<u n="46" who="S0018">so why did they <trunc>con</trunc> why didn't they continue to let women pay less insurance?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0019">because of a silly EU directive</u>
<u n="48" who="S0017">em equality</u>
<u n="49" who="S0018">but you could argue the equality case for anything <pause dur="short"/> surely like</u>
<u n="50" who="S0017">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's why it's stupid</u>
<u n="51" who="S0018">that's ageist to charge me more money on a bus just because you know my grandmother could only pays seventy-five P that's ageist <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="52" who="S0017">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0019">no it it is a ridiculous thing</u>
<u n="54" who="S0017">when insurance has always been based on statistical probabilities</u>
<u n="55" who="S0018">huh <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="56" who="S0017">the level of risk</u>
<u n="57" who="S0018">yup</u>
<u n="58" who="S0017">and age is acknowledged as being a significant additional risk <pause dur="short"/> but and up till now</u>
<u n="59" who="S0018">youth</u>
<u n="60" who="S0017">women's risk rate has been lower than young women's been lower than men's but they are now saying that you can't make that discrimination anymore which is shows how ludicrous discriminatory laws become</u>
<u n="61" who="S0019">absolutely it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="62" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so age or youth is more of a risk than lack of experience?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0017">I think there's a</u>
<u n="64" who="S0019">well there's a correlation</u>
<u n="65" who="S0017" trans="overlap">they probably go together on a graph and it becomes a point where um your inexperience um has less effect than your age</u>
<u n="66" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0019">it's the old saying a lot of familiarity breeds contempt <pause dur="short"/> that a lot of young drivers are so supremely confident in their own ability that it leads them to reckless driving <pause dur="short"/> and that's what gets them into most of the problems</u>
<u n="68" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes I think I'll be super safety-conscious all the time <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0017" trans="overlap">and the young ones are rather more to imbibing</u>
<u n="70" who="S0019">yes</u>
<u n="71" who="S0017">um reckless quantities of red wine <pause dur="short"/> um which I'm sure you've grown out of</u>
<u n="72" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0019">no <pause dur="short"/> it it it is a stupid ruling and it's come out of the EU as of most of stupid rulings do and it's ludicrous</u>
<u n="74" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0019">but no you'll be  you'll be  fine</u>
<u n="76" who="S0017">I'm amazed the insurers and politicians didn't fight it much more strongly</u>
<u n="77" who="S0018">well I guess the insurers don't care because what they lose on the male's paying they'll just add to the female's bills</u>
<u n="78" who="S0019">but it won't mean the males will pay any less it just means that females will pay the same</u>
<u n="79" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0019">uh-huh</u>
<u n="81" who="S0018">oh they were probably laughing all the way to the bank then that's probably why they didn't fight it</u>
<u n="82" who="S0019">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah <trunc>d</trunc> there's no reduction for the men's charge <pause dur="short"/> it just means that the women's goes up</u>
<u n="83" who="S0017">we don't know if that's the truth</u>
<u n="84" who="S0019" trans="overlap">to match the men's <pause dur="short"/> we do <pause dur="short"/> well we'll see <pause dur="short"/> but no <trunc>t</trunc> there's no way of telling and I <pause dur="short"/> you have to shop around as well for insurance</u>
<u n="85" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0019">you have to get you know as many sort of quotes you can possibly get because some are more expensive than others</u>
<u n="87" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0019">and it very much depends I suppose on what sort of car you have as well <pause dur="short"/> you want to get a car that's in the lowest insurance band</u>
<u n="89" who="S0018">what kind of car would that be?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0017">it's eh not a specific kind in terms of make but eh not anything that is high performance not anything that is modified to perform better <pause dur="short"/> so it would be in general the basic models in most ranges and the smaller car's the better</u>
<u n="91" who="S0019">the smaller engine capacity um tend to be the best ones <pause dur="short"/> does do emissions have any bearing on insurance?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0017">no</u>
<u n="93" who="S0019">no?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0017">no</u>
<u n="95" who="S0018">that's road tax is it?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0019">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so you want to go for one that has the lowest emissions and lowest engine capacity</u>
<u n="97" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0019">to get the cheapest outcome</u>
<u n="99" who="S0018">and what was it I heard about there's some kind of little black box that's being installed into cars that tracks <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what it tracks but then that informs the insurance company of how much to charge you or something?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0017">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0019">it records the moments before any accident or anything</u>
<u n="102" who="S0017">no it's more than that <pause dur="short"/> it's actually recording</u>
<u n="103" who="S0019">all the times is it?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0017">the types the driving style <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether it's sampling or recording a hundred percent of the time but um and the amount of hours driving and the distance driven</u>
<u n="105" who="S0019">but if you have one of these in the car it pushes your <trunc>insu</trunc> your insurance premiums down</u>
<u n="106" who="S0017">but we I pay less <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what mileage we've set for yours but mine is based on nine thousand miles a year <pause dur="short"/> your mother's is based on I forgot it no idea maybe five thousand miles a year</u>
<u n="107" who="S0019">sounds about right</u>
<u n="108" who="S0017">em and we get a reduction for that? Sorry are you picking that up on the recording?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0018">for for only going  for only going  a certain distance?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0019">mm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0019">well if you for the sake of argument you were working in Oxford and you had a car <pause dur="short"/> you'd probably find it more cost-effective to use public transport to get there and back because of the petrol consumption parking charges <pause dur="short"/> cos if you work at a place that provides parking spaces then you get done in tax cos that's taxable <pause dur="short"/> it's considered a perk <pause dur="short"/> so they tax you on it</u>
<u n="113" who="S0018">if you don't pay for parking?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0019">no if you do pay for <trunc>p</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> if you don't if you're if you have a parking space provided at your place of work they do you <pause dur="short"/> they charge you extra tax</u>
<u n="115" who="S0018">on what?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0017">it's a taxable benefit so that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0018">yeah I know but what do they pay you on? What do they charge you tax on?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0017">on a notional value of the parking space</u>
<u n="119" who="S0018"><trunc>B</trunc> when do you end up paying that with your road tax?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0017" trans="overlap">it's in your <pause dur="short"/> no it's in your  in your  employment tax</u>
<u n="121" who="S0018">how stupid</u>
<u n="122" who="S0019"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm hm <pause dur="short"/> the only time when you would find having a car useful is in um when it's chucking it down with rain or it's absolutely freezing cold</u>
<u n="123" who="S0018">so most of the year?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0019">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="125" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0019">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> that's not right at all and you know it <pause dur="short"/> um you just have to go see what the costs are and the problem is of course that once you've got a car you are tempted to use it all the time</u>
<u n="127" who="S0018">well I'm not going to buy one just to keep it in the garage</u>
<u n="128" who="S0019"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You'll be lucky if you get a garage ducks <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0018">well whether I have a car or not at least I'm using this time</u>
<u n="130" who="S0019">mm hm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0018">to learn how to drive</u>
<u n="132" who="S0019">exactly <pause dur="short"/> you know it's something that you you really needed to do</u>
<u n="133" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0019">so</u>
<u n="135" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's just difficult to mentalize all the different processes going on at the same time and wonder how long it's gonna take for that to become</u>
<u n="136" who="S0019">it won't take you long</u>
<u n="137" who="S0018">automatic</u>
<u n="138" who="S0019">it won't take you long <pause dur="short"/> I would say probably at the end of three lessons you'll be doing without even thinking about it</u>
<u n="139" who="S0018">you think so?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0019">mm hm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0018">was that was it like that for you?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0019">I only had ten lessons</u>
<u n="143" who="S0018">oooh</u>
<u n="144" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0018">but did did you go out practicing?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0019">no</u>
<u n="147" who="S0018">no?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0019">oh I'm sorry I drove to <anon type="place"/> swimming baths once a week <pause dur="short"/> and that's it <pause dur="short"/> because a certain person sitting next to me is an absolutely rotten passenger when you are trying to learn to drive <pause dur="short"/> there is the famous example after I had passed my test <pause dur="short"/> we were on this caravan site in Wales <pause dur="short"/> a big wide road</u>
<u n="149" who="S0017">in Wales?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0019">yes it was South Wales</u>
<u n="151" who="S0017">we've never been</u>
<u n="152" who="S0019">yes we have</u>
<u n="153" who="S0017">oh it wasn't <anon type="place"/> it was down in Devon</u>
<u n="154" who="S0019">no it wasn't <pause dur="short"/> it was <anon type="place"/> we had a Triumph Help and there was big concrete islands and I was driving up to this perfectly normally at a reasonable speed</u>
<u n="155" who="S0017">about to run over a man in sandals</u>
<u n="156" who="S0019" trans="overlap">and suddenly your father shouts clutch and brake <pause dur="short"/> clutch and brake <pause dur="short"/> frightened the living daylights out of me</u>
<u n="157" who="S0018">what was he saying?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0019">clutch and brake</u>
<u n="159" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="160" who="S0019">so I stopped the car and I said if you want to drive drive <pause dur="short"/> if not shut up <pause dur="short"/> But he's a terrible passenger <pause dur="short"/> I do not advise you under any circumstances to go out with him sitting next to you</u>
<u n="161" who="S0018">I thought maybe he'd be quite good?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0017">I am really</u>
<u n="163" who="S0018"><trunc>W</trunc> what and this is said after the the sailboat incident where he was trying to teach me how to change direction</u>
<u n="164" who="S0019">yes</u>
<u n="165" who="S0018">and said he'd give me one set of instructions <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0019">yes</u>
<u n="167" who="S0018">and then when he actually came to it he said something completely different <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0019">yes</u>
<u n="169" who="S0017">it's intuitive</u>
<u n="170" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0019">it's it's like him trying to teach me how to use the computer <pause dur="short"/> instead of sticking</u>
<u n="172" who="S0018">yes</u>
<u n="173" who="S0019">to the basics</u>
<u n="174" who="S0018">trying being the operative word <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0019">instead of sticking to the basics only the things I need to know he starts saying um and then if you want to do this you press this that and then when you want to do that you press that and I'm thinking hello? I haven't got the slightest idea what you're talking about <pause dur="short"/> And then he gets ratty when I don't understand and I was just saying to you the other day wasn't I? Shades of granddad and maths</u>
<u n="176" who="S0017">mm</u>
<u n="177" who="S0019">this is exactly the same reaction</u>
<u n="178" who="S0018">I can remember you doing that to me when we were doing maths</u>
<u n="179" who="S0019">mm hm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0018">okay so to be able to understand how to do this you need to understand how to do that <pause dur="short"/> and I was like no we've already done that and we need to do this and I need to do it in twenty minutes because I've got something on TV <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0017"><trunc>T</trunc> that's a big problem with schooling that each generation does these things in a different way</u>
<u n="182" who="S0019">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's true</u>
<u n="183" who="S0017">um</u>
<u n="184" who="S0019">that's true</u>
<u n="185" who="S0017">so ideally with any problem you never start from here</u>
<u n="186" who="S0019">no it always ended up in tears if granddad tried to teach me anything in maths <pause dur="short"/> because it for him he could understand it just like that and couldn't understand why I couldn't <pause dur="short"/> so he'd explain it and I couldn't do it <pause dur="short"/> so he'd explain it again in exactly the same way and I still couldn't do it <pause dur="short"/> then he started getting ratty <pause dur="short"/> and it was not a good situation <pause dur="short"/> it always ended up in tears <pause dur="short"/> so and he engenders the same feelings <pause dur="short"/> so just stick with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> and your driving instructor <pause dur="short"/> did he say roughly how many lessons people tend to have?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0018">he said <trunc>pe</trunc> everyone asks him</u>
<u n="188" who="S0019">can't tell</u>
<u n="189" who="S0018">and he can never answer but um <pause dur="short"/> I think if I pay for ten and probably have another ten after</u>
<u n="190" who="S0019">see how you get on</u>
<u n="191" who="S0018">yeah but I mean if I'm not going to go out practicing <pause dur="short"/> I think I prefer to have twenty lessons</u>
<u n="192" who="S0017">mm <pause dur="short"/> well he will say</u>
<u n="193" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0017">if he thinks after ten lessons that you're ready to take you test or he'll say you need a couple more lessons before taking your test <pause dur="short"/> so so you can judge it then</u>
<u n="195" who="S0019">mm <pause dur="short"/> you got a theory test to do as well now haven't you?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0017">yes you do <pause dur="short"/> the theory test before you can apply for your</u>
<u n="197" who="S0019">yep</u>
<u n="198" who="S0017">main test</u>
<u n="199" who="S0018">but you can do practice ones on</u>
<u n="200" who="S0017">did he mention anything about a theory test?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0018">nope</u>
<u n="202" who="S0017">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0019">you can do practice ones on the computer as well</u>
<u n="204" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0019">so</u>
<u n="206" who="S0018">well it's good that you can actually learn how to drive before you pass your theory test <pause dur="short"/> because in Spain you have to pass your theory test before you can get behind the wheel of a car</u>
<u n="207" who="S0019">really?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0018">yeah which is what put me off doing it for so long <pause dur="short"/> because you can't even learn how to drive until you've you've already signed up paid all your thousands of Euros and done the theory part of the test <pause dur="short"/> and you have to learn out about how the car works as well all the mechanics</u>
<u n="209" who="S0019">really? Oh crikey if that had been me that would have been I'd never learn to drive <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Depends on how deeply they go into the mechanics</u>
<u n="210" who="S0018">well it just always put me off</u>
<u n="211" who="S0019">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can understand why</u>
<u n="212" who="S0018">I probably would have jumped in a car and learnt how to drive before if had I not had to</u>
<u n="213" who="S0019">I didn't realise it was quite as onerous as that in Spain</u>
<u n="214" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="215" who="S0019">and yet their standard of driving is so abysmal <vocal desc="laugh"/> So</u>
<u n="216" who="S0018">is it?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0019">oh yes</u>
<u n="218" who="S0018">do you notice it? Really?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0019">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="220" who="S0018">I'd say more the <trunc>r</trunc> roads <pause dur="short"/> I'd I'd definitely say the roads are laid out in a less logical way and a more dangerous way but</u>
<u n="221" who="S0017">I think that is it's difficult really to make that assessment because the driving that you tend to do when you're abroad is not typical of the driving you'd be doing at home <pause dur="short"/> cos you'd be travelling somewhere unfamiliar on time</u>
<u n="222" who="S0018">no but when I was in Spain around</u>
<u n="223" who="S0017">I'm talking about us <pause dur="short"/> your mother's</u>
<u n="224" who="S0018">oh right to compare</u>
<u n="225" who="S0017">your mother's  comparing <pause dur="short"/> but the worst driving we saw was in France</u>
<u n="226" who="S0019">oh that was</u>
<u n="227" who="S0017">when we drove down to</u>
<u n="228" who="S0019">dire absolutely dire <pause dur="short"/> mind you there's a lot of driving in this country that is appalling</u>
<u n="229" who="S0017">mm <pause dur="short"/> but we I <trunc>d</trunc> don't think we saw as many patently reckless incidences of people going at massive</u>
<u n="230" who="S0019">no probably not</u>
<u n="231" who="S0017">speeds in inappropriate conditions</u>
<u n="232" who="S0019">mm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I think that driving in France made me a lot more nervous than driving in Spain</u>
<u n="233" who="S0017">mm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0019">but more nervous than here <pause dur="short"/> but then that maybe just cos I'm used to it here</u>
<u n="235" who="S0018">why?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0017">oh love <pause dur="short"/> you don't like driving beyond your four mile radius of here <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="237" who="S0019">now that's not true <pause dur="short"/> it's alright as long as I can do a recce first and find out exactly where I'm going <pause dur="short"/> I can't cope with not knowing where I'm going and having to drive as well</u>
<u n="238" who="S0017">okay</u>
<u n="239" who="S0019">that's my major problem</u>
<u n="240" who="S0018">what is it about the way they drive in France that makes you less confident?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0019">they were driving much faster than the conditions dictated and doing pulling out and passing in in the most ridiculous places <pause dur="short"/> it was urgh frightening</u>
<u n="242" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0019">really frightening <pause dur="short"/> actually that's going back a long way as well isn't it?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0017">no it's not that many years <pause dur="short"/> it's in the last</u>
<u n="245" who="S0018">oh you mean when you went to France the last time?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0017">no <pause dur="short"/> the time we went and stayed near who's your wine merchant?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0018"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0017"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s place</u>
<u n="249" who="S0018">what</u>
<u n="250" who="S0017">yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0019">yeah I suppose</u>
<u n="252" who="S0017">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that was  that was  where we really saw it</u>
<u n="253" who="S0019" trans="overlap">that was about five years ago? Six years ago? Something like that</u>
<u n="254" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0017">they just discovered today in making the booking for going to Paxos <pause dur="short"/> that it was two thousand and three the last time we went when we went to Kefalonia and we had the villa for a week and the yacht for a  and the yacht for a  week <pause dur="short"/> can you see the the levels?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0019">but the um even though it's that long ago since we had the villa and the boat we still get a discount on this year's booking</u>
<u n="257" who="S0018">how come?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0019">because they consider that a loyalty reward</u>
<u n="259" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0019">even though it was along nearly ten years ago</u>
<u n="261" who="S0017">yes</u>
<u n="262" who="S0018">so you're going to exactly the same place?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0019">it's one of the places that we sailed to from Corfu</u>
<u n="264" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> paxos</u>
<u n="265" who="S0019">oh and didn't we have a villa on Paxos?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0017">yes</u>
<u n="267" who="S0019">yes we did</u>
<u n="268" who="S0017">yes</u>
<u n="269" who="S0019">it was the quaint little place with the outside loo <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0018">so are you sailing? Doing any sailing?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0019" trans="overlap">well I'm not</u>
<u n="272" who="S0017">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="273" who="S0019">he'll probably hire a motor boat cos you won't be able to keep him off the water <pause dur="short"/> but eh we're not having a a yacht</u>
<u n="274" who="S0017">unless <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s down there</u>
<u n="275" who="S0019">too bloody expensive</u>
<u n="276" who="S0018">who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0017">he's the rigger of the boatyards</u>
<u n="278" who="S0019">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0017">and he spends quite large chunks of the summer out in that area in the Ionian area um getting these charter company's boats ready for use and then doing repairs and during season</u>
<u n="280" who="S0019">not  surely</u>
<u n="281" who="S0017">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no it's for the company that is connected with Ionian Island holidays</u>
<u n="282" who="S0019">nisos</u>
<u n="283" who="S0017">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> that was when we did it it was <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> now it's Island Sailing or something</u>
<u n="284" who="S0019">I wonder if <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is still going?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0017">yes they are</u>
<u n="286" who="S0019">mm <pause dur="short"/> with the same people?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0018">where?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0017">who knows</u>
<u n="289" who="S0019">who knows</u>
<u n="290" who="S0018">where is Paxos?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0017">do you know where Corfu is?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="293" who="S0017">paxos is a little island seven miles south of Corfu</u>
<u n="294" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="295" who="S0017">A a mere step as your mother would tell you</u>
<u n="296" who="S0018">can you fly directly?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0017">you fly to Corfu and then get the ferry down to Paxos</u>
<u n="298" who="S0018">so you will be doing a little sailing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0019">the ferry if it's the eh hydrofoil it's not what you'd call sailing <vocal desc="laugh"/> It doesn't take very long to get there <pause dur="short"/> but I came back on it didn't I that once?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0017">mm <pause dur="short"/> that wasn't a hydrofoil I'm sure <pause dur="short"/> that was an ordinary</u>
<u n="301" who="S0019">no it wasn't it was hydrofoil <pause dur="short"/> definitely was a hydrofoil</u>
<u n="302" who="S0017">that's <trunc>no</trunc> not what I envisage as a hydrofoil <pause dur="short"/> the hydrofoils I've been on in Greece have been the old Russian built ones which are sort of enclosed and they're</u>
<u n="303" who="S0019">well this one was</u>
<u n="304" who="S0017">but <pause dur="short"/> but I'm sure I saw you out on deck</u>
<u n="305" who="S0019">no</u>
<u n="306" who="S0017">when you went past there</u>
<u n="307" who="S0019">nope <pause dur="short"/> there was nowhere on deck <pause dur="short"/> it was all</u>
<u n="308" who="S0017">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0019">it was like a bus really</u>
<u n="310" who="S0017">they they make an awful noise <pause dur="short"/> they rattle like mad</u>
<u n="311" who="S0019">I don't think this one rattled from what I can remember but it was it didn't take long <pause dur="short"/> cos I left at about <trunc>f</trunc> four five o'clock in the evening?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0017">I can't remember</u>
<u n="313" who="S0019">and I was back um you'd set off in the morning to sail back and I was back about the same time as you <pause dur="short"/> so it really was a a quick and quite comfortable journey <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't bad at all <pause dur="short"/> where was it that we got picked up in that speed boat?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0017">that was to go from Corfu to Paxos</u>
<u n="315" who="S0019">the little one?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0017">but the first time yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0019">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the very first time</u>
<u n="318" who="S0017">we paid extra to have this high speed service</u>
<u n="319" who="S0019">that's right <pause dur="short"/> yep that's right <pause dur="short"/> that was quite exciting wasn't it?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0017">yes</u>
<u n="321" who="S0019">A bit hard on the back cos it sort of bumped just like you driving <unclear/> speed <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh that was fun</u>
<u n="322" who="S0017">yes</u>
<u n="323" who="S0019">yes <pause dur="short"/> but it was jolly hard on the back</u>
<u n="324" who="S0017">that's where you got your driving practice</u>
<u n="325" who="S0019">yeah <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="326" who="S0018">I think I'm better at steering a car than I am steering a motor boat</u>
<u n="327" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0019">Good <pause dur="short"/> I am relieved <vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh that was fun <pause dur="short"/> that area isn't particularly nice but it was</u>
<u n="329" who="S0018">why did you decide to go there in the end?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0019">that's a very good question</u>
<u n="331" who="S0017" trans="overlap">which one?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0018">paxos</u>
<u n="333" who="S0017">oh Paxos</u>
<u n="334" who="S0019">oh Paxos</u>
<u n="335" who="S0017">right yes <pause dur="short"/> no I think you were talking about Delta <unclear/> weren't you?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0019">mm</u>
<u n="337" who="S0018">why did you decide to go to Paxos?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0019">we liked Paxos didn't we?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0017">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's eh to some extent in desperation at deciding on somewhere <pause dur="short"/> if you go somewhere different you don't know what to experience <pause dur="short"/> we've been to Paxos a couple of times um <pause dur="short"/> so we have a good idea what it's going to be like <pause dur="short"/> and it's</u>
<u n="340" who="S0019">and the time of year there will still be a lot of the flowers and it will still be quite green</u>
<u n="341" who="S0018">is it quite pretty?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0019">yes in a</u>
<u n="343" who="S0017">yes it is</u>
<u n="344" who="S0019">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is in a quaint sort of way</u>
<u n="345" who="S0017">mm</u>
<u n="346" who="S0019">it's very different to what we call pretty here</u>
<u n="347" who="S0017">there are a lot of olive groves so you've got sort of rocky soil with olive trees in and then but also there are a fair amount of other greenery and shrubbery</u>
<u n="348" who="S0019">mm <pause dur="short"/> no it's it's very pleasant and we we walked didn't we? To Logos?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0017">I'm not so sure we didn't walk to  on one occasion</u>
<u n="350" who="S0019">no we didn't walk to  that was too far <pause dur="short"/> we did walk to Logos and it takes you up all over the hill and it's very very pretty</u>
<u n="351" who="S0017">Will take me new walking shoes this time</u>
<u n="352" who="S0019">or I should just take my trainers as per usual</u>
<u n="353" who="S0018">how far was it?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0017">mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0019">two three miles?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0017">yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0019">but it was very very pretty</u>
<u n="358" who="S0017">mm hm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0019">they've still got the the some of the pretty spring flowers <pause dur="short"/> um I must say it was very green cos later on in the season it isn't <pause dur="short"/> it's like a lot of places it's brown <pause dur="short"/> but eh no very nice and there are little villages loads of flowers and plants in pots in window boxes and things like that very pretty</u>
<u n="360" who="S0017">and Paxos is a low tourist resort not a not like Corfu which is overwhelmed with tourists</u>
<u n="361" who="S0017">mm</u>
<u n="362" who="S0019">oh Corfu was vile the last time we went there wasn't much Greek left there</u>
<u n="363" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="364" who="S0019">it was just a giant tourist island <pause dur="short"/> it was <pause dur="short"/> not nice</u>
<u n="365" who="S0017"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I remember the smells that night we moored up in Corfu harbour</u>
<u n="366" who="S0019">urgh <pause dur="short"/> corfu town <pause dur="short"/> urgh urgh</u>
<u n="367" who="S0017">it was great to get away</u>
<u n="368" who="S0018">when were you not worried about the Greek situation?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0017">I was concerned but bearing in mind we're flying with um <pause dur="short"/> it will be Thompson or I can't remember if it was Thomas Cook or Thompson</u>
<u n="370" who="S0019">one of the two</u>
<u n="371" who="S0017">um and you're not actually going on to the Greek mainland so if there are air traffic it's less likely to be air traffic than ground staff can problems aside</u>
<u n="372" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0017">I think Paxos and the other islands are less at risk than the mainland airports <pause dur="short"/> I may be wrong but</u>
<u n="374" who="S0018">oh were you worried about it for strike action?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0017">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0018">oh they'll probably do just do what Spain did <pause dur="short"/> and when the air traffic controllers went on strike they just got the army in <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0017">mm</u>
<u n="378" who="S0019">yep</u>
<u n="379" who="S0018">keep the <trunc>touris</trunc> because <trunc>G</trunc> Greece is pretty much relying on tourism now no for?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0017">A lot of  A lot of  the islands have no other income at all</u>
<u n="381" who="S0019">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's right <pause dur="short"/> so I think they would be extremely silly to do anything like that but eh with the rioting that's been <pause dur="short"/> although there was a letter in the paper the travel section of the Telegraph that said somebody had been to Athens where there was supposedly</u>
<u n="382" who="S0017">oh yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0019">all these riots and they said there was really very little <pause dur="short"/> so you don't know who to believe do you?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0018">well obviously they've been happening <pause dur="short"/> it's just you're not</u>
<u n="385" who="S0019">yes</u>
<u n="386" who="S0018">if if people are rioting they're not gonna be rioting all the time and in all areas of the city</u>
<u n="387" who="S0019">yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0018">it's going to happen in specific places at specific times that</u>
<u n="389" who="S0019">but this person indicated that where it was reported that there were real big riots they saw very little <pause dur="short"/> there were some people on the streets they said um but it was a couple of hours and that was it <pause dur="short"/> so you don't know what to believe</u>
<u n="390" who="S0018">well if it's a riot for a couple of hours it's a riot isn't it?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0019">it is but it doesn't seem</u>
<u n="392" who="S0018">but you never know what whether to trust the newspaper because they're reporting it out of proportion or they're reporting it less because they don't want people to think that the situation is as important or as critical as it is <pause dur="short"/> it's you never trust</u>
<u n="393" who="S0019" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="394" who="S0017">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0019">but you can't <pause dur="short"/> we've just got to eh hope for the best because there wasn't anywhere else that was getatable from here that we wanted to go <pause dur="short"/> I mean we'd have liked to have gone back to France but there's nowhere you can get to that we want to go without at least a two and a half hour three hour drive</u>
<u n="396" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="397" who="S0019">and more actually <pause dur="short"/> um you know we would have liked to have gone around the Biaritz area <pause dur="short"/> but there's no airport anywhere near there</u>
<u n="398" who="S0018">no?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0019">nope</u>
<u n="400" who="S0018">is there not a Biaritz airport?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0017">no there's no airport where you can fly direct from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0019" trans="overlap">from <anon type="place"/><pause dur="short"/> they all go through Paris</u>
<u n="403" who="S0017">and that was  And that was  the limitation we put on</u>
<u n="404" who="S0018">eh yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0019">you don't really want to fly into Paris and then have to fly out again</u>
<u n="406" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="407" who="S0019">Cos the Gaulle Airport was its signage was abysmal</u>
<u n="408" who="S0018">it's like a rabbit warren isn't it?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0019">it is <pause dur="short"/> and there are no signs to tell you where you're supposed to go <pause dur="short"/> I thought it was all awful <pause dur="short"/> I hated it <pause dur="short"/> I can't even remember why we went what we were doing</u>
<u n="410" who="S0017">probably visited somebody that was living and working there</u>
<u n="411" who="S0019">I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> but it wasn't very nice <pause dur="short"/> not nice at all</u>
<u n="412" who="S0018">and so when are you going?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0017"><trunc>S</trunc> fourth of June</u>
<u n="414" who="S0019">that's the Monday?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0017">yes</u>
<u n="416" who="S0019">we're going on the Monday</u>
<u n="417" who="S0018">for two weeks?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0017">yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0018">super</u>
<u n="420" who="S0019">so we don't quite know what the position of the cats will be</u>
<u n="421" who="S0018">let's see how things turn out</u>
<u n="422" who="S0019">mm</u>
<u n="423" who="S0018"><trunc>Wha</trunc> what's going on?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0019">mm hm</u>
<u n="425" who="S0018">but I'm sure that I mean if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or or if <trunc>who</trunc> or whichever neighbour is coming in to deal with yours that they could somehow deal with mine if we need to</u>
<u n="426" who="S0019">I <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't like to ask <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to deal with yours as well as ours</u>
<u n="427" who="S0018">why?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0019">because we've got to work out how we deal with yours because we can't leave them out all the time with the food out</u>
<u n="429" who="S0017" trans="overlap">I I don't think that is yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think the bigger problem is the cat flap <pause dur="short"/> that yours will eventually find out how to get outside</u>
<u n="430" who="S0018">oh I don't think that's a problem because one one cat can't get through the cat flap cos it's too fat</u>
<u n="431" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0017">he it might block it and none of them can get back in <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0018">and the other one if she hasn't learnt by now how to use it from watching the others use it and I've opened it for her as well and she's gone through <pause dur="short"/> but she's not even tried to work out how to open it herself <pause dur="short"/> I don't think all of a sudden she's going to learn when you're on holiday</u>
<u n="434" who="S0019">I I'm just a bit nervous about leaving them out all day and the fact that our bloody cats eat your cat's food</u>
<u n="435" who="S0018">but when you go away on holiday does someone come round and lock your cat in for the night?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0017">no</u>
<u n="437" who="S0018">so you're cats can go out <pause dur="short"/> well if it's going to be summer why don't we just <trunc>st</trunc> um restrict your cats to downstairs and my cats to upstairs?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0019">well we can't really other than</u>
<u n="439" who="S0017">doesn't work does it? The the barrier</u>
<u n="440" who="S0018" trans="overlap">kitchen door</u>
<u n="441" who="S0019">mm <pause dur="short"/> it just means that whoever comes in to feed them has got to make sure that they're in there um they don't escape</u>
<u n="442" who="S0018">well they're hardly going to escape are they?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0019">no but it's difficult when you've got four of them to try and round up particularly <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they are much more difficult to control</u>
<u n="444" who="S0017">I think the the bigger problem is each eating the others food than <pause dur="short"/> I think yours yours are quite relaxed in wandering about the house and apart from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> creating explosions at intervals the others aren't that fussed</u>
<u n="445" who="S0019">no I suppose the only problem is the the food situation <pause dur="short"/> I think it would be better if if eh well whoever comes to feed them clicks the cat flap so that they can't get out but can get in</u>
<u n="446" who="S0018">what? When?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0019">when they come in at night to feed them</u>
<u n="448" who="S0018">oh so you do normally do that?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0017">we haven't ever asked whoever's looking after them to do that</u>
<u n="450" who="S0018">Cos normally you get someone to come in once a day nay?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0019">no <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because it's just our cats <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> coming twice a day</u>
<u n="452" who="S0017" trans="overlap">morning and evening</u>
<u n="453" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="454" who="S0019">but <pause dur="short"/> I would rather he did the morning and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did the evening <pause dur="short"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is not very reliable on doing the cat trays</u>
<u n="455" who="S0018">or the setting the house alarm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0017">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0019">no <pause dur="short"/> that's another problem <pause dur="short"/> um I think if we got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to do the morning and asked <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to do the evening <pause dur="short"/> it would be better</u>
<u n="458" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0019">because there's your cat trays to be done as well</u>
<u n="460" who="S0018">yeah but if you're away for two weeks what I can just do is leave four cat trays</u>
<u n="461" who="S0019">oh the smell</u>
<u n="462" who="S0018">yeah I know but eh <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how much we can actually ask other people to do or</u>
<u n="463" who="S0019">mm</u>
<u n="464" who="S0018">if I'm in the country I'll just come back at the weekends to sort things out</u>
<u n="465" who="S0017">we've got to make provisional arrangements and then sort it out once we know specifically what's happening where you're going to be and</u>
<u n="466" who="S0017">we'll see what happens</u>
<u n="467" who="S0019">unless <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> could come in and do the trays</u>
<u n="468" who="S0018">the only problem is I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has booked a holiday with her family in the south of Spain around that time</u>
<u n="469" who="S0019">right</u>
<u n="470" who="S0018">but again if nobody's here the fact that there are four cat trays sitting there isn't going to inconvenience anybody <pause dur="short"/> but mm I'm more worried about I think I think they should be probably kept separate <pause dur="short"/> either my cats upstairs in those two rooms or my cats using the house and your cats having the kitchen the conservatory and the garden</u>
<u n="471" who="S0019">I think it's better that way because I would hate now to confine your two since they've been used to wandering the house <pause dur="short"/> I think it would be awful to shut them in those two rooms for two weeks <pause dur="short"/> I don't think that's fair at all</u>
<u n="472" who="S0018">but do you think it's equally fair on your cats to?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0019">yes</u>
<u n="474" who="S0017">well at least they've got the conservatory and in summer they do spend more time in the conservatory and they'll often sleep overnight in the conservatory</u>
<u n="475" who="S0019">and also</u>
<u n="476" who="S0017">and they've got the garden</u>
<u n="477" who="S0019">yup <pause dur="short"/> and in the summer I mean when we've been away before</u>
<u n="478" who="S0017">mm</u>
<u n="479" who="S0019">we've shut all the doors so that they've had really only the landing and the hall extra</u>
<u n="480" who="S0017">and one bedroom</u>
<u n="481" who="S0019">and one bedroom</u>
<u n="482" who="S0017">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I can't really see that that would be a problem</u>
<u n="483" who="S0017">yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0019">if we shut them in the kitchen they've got plenty of room <pause dur="short"/> they've got plenty of beds in the kitchen and the conservatory and if it's nice weather they'll go out into the garden anyway</u>
<u n="485" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0019">so I think that's probably the best solution</u>
<u n="487" who="S0018">yes <pause dur="short"/> I don't <pause dur="short"/> I just feel a bit bad constricting your cats to</u>
<u n="488" who="S0019">they'll survive don't worry</u>
<u n="489" who="S0018">I know they will but <trunc>o</trunc> obviously if it would be more difficult if someone was locking them in at night <pause dur="short"/> and they still only had the kitchen then again they're only used they're used to only being able to go in the kitchen aren't they?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0017">mm night time though</u>
<u n="491" who="S0019">yeah kitchen and conservatory <pause dur="short"/> so it isn't going to make any difference to them</u>
<u n="492" who="S0018">we'll see</u>
<u n="493" who="S0019">it'll be difficult because this is the first time we've left the kittens for more than a couple of days</u>
<u n="494" who="S0018">they're not really kittens anymore though?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0019">no <pause dur="short"/> but I say the kittens to differentiate them from the others <pause dur="short"/> but they've never been left</u>
<u n="496" who="S0017">no</u>
<u n="497" who="S0019">for that length of time <pause dur="short"/> it's only been three or four days at the most <pause dur="short"/> so but they'll cope <pause dur="short"/> it won't be a problem</u>
<u n="498" who="S0017">well that's right <pause dur="short"/> we got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or his wife's parents came in while we were away <pause dur="short"/> yeah sorry</u>
<u n="499" who="S0019">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they kitten sat</u>
<u n="500" who="S0018"><trunc>J</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> from the upholsterers?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0017">yes</u>
<u n="502" who="S0019">well it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s parents</u>
<u n="503" who="S0018">oh they came and lived here?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0017">yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0019">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> no it went very well but can't even remember where we went <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's gone <pause dur="short"/> in the mist</u>
<u n="506" who="S0017">no</u>
<u n="507" who="S0018">somewhere sunny as long as it has sun for you you don't care where it is</u>
<u n="508" who="S0017" trans="overlap">memorable</u>
<u n="509" who="S0019" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="510" who="S0017" trans="overlap">no it wasn't anywhere like that</u>
<u n="511" who="S0019">no it <trunc>wa</trunc> it wasn't <pause dur="short"/> I haven't been anywhere sunny <pause dur="short"/> this June will be two years</u>
<u n="512" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="513" who="S0019">since we went to France</u>
<u n="514" who="S0018">when was the last time?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0019">when we went to France</u>
<u n="516" who="S0018">yeah but when was that?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0019">two years ago in June <vocal desc="laugh"/> Remember you did the correspondence?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0018">oh yeah yeah um Arcechamp</u>
<u n="519" who="S0019">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> that was two years ago <pause dur="short"/> so I haven't been anywhere since</u>
<u n="520" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="521" who="S0019">so I've had no sun for two years <pause dur="short"/> cos last summer here was not very good</u>
<u n="522" who="S0018">isn't every summer here not very good?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0019">no no <pause dur="short"/> we have had some nice weather but last year was awful wasn't it?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0017">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0019">we didn't get any at all <pause dur="short"/> can you do that parcel and then I can go and post it?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0018">what plans have you got for the afternoon?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0019">absolutely none</u>
<u n="528" who="S0018">nothing?</u>
<u n="529" who="S0019">nope <pause dur="short"/> until tennis tonight</u>
<u n="530" who="S0018">have you got a lesson?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0019">it's the course <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s course</u>
<u n="532" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="533" who="S0019">so that's all I've got to do today <pause dur="short"/> been in to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> been to the bank done some shopping <pause dur="short"/> eh those are the total commitments for today <pause dur="short"/> mm tomorrow is a bit busier <pause dur="short"/> cos I got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> eh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> chris coming at half past nine it is half past nine and then I've got tennis at two <pause dur="short"/> so that's it <pause dur="short"/> and then Wednesday I've got <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> coming at half past nine again I've got to get nanny to the hairdressers by half past eleven <pause dur="short"/> I've got the osteopath at half past three and then I've got aqua aerobics at six o'clock</u>
<u n="534" who="S0018">that one's a busy one there</u>
<u n="535" who="S0019">so Wednesday is going to be busy <pause dur="short"/> but that's okay I can cope <pause dur="short"/> I can cope</u>
<u n="536" who="S0018">I mean are you still thinking of going to Australia to visit the family or?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0019">we have to decide fairly soon what we're going to do <pause dur="short"/> um we have to make the decision because I've got to find somewhere for nanny to go for the month that we're away</u>
<u n="538" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="539" who="S0019">um <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> unless you'd like to go and live with her for a month <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="540" who="S0018">I wouldn't mind I just don't know where I'm gonna be so</u>
<u n="541" who="S0019">no that's ok</u>
<u n="542" who="S0018">that's the problem</u>
<u n="543" who="S0019">and it's impossible to travel from <anon type="place"/> to wherever you're going to be if you carry on with the course</u>
<u n="544" who="S0018">Don't know <pause dur="short"/> might be driving by then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="545" who="S0019">you might <pause dur="short"/> you might <pause dur="short"/> I just have to play it by ear <pause dur="short"/> I can't  I can't  think that far ahead</u>
<u n="546" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="547" who="S0019">yeah it's it's too much for my little brain</u>
<u n="548" who="S0018">but when would you go if you went?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0019">em probably March I think <pause dur="short"/> em February it's probably still rather warmer than your father likes <pause dur="short"/> so March <pause dur="short"/> and then we might possibly be there for eh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s baby's first birthday</u>
<u n="550" who="S0018">isn't she having another baby?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0019">mm hm</u>
<u n="552" who="S0018">when's she?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0019">like now</u>
<u n="554" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> she's already?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0019">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> the baby's due very shortly</u>
<u n="556" who="S0018">I lose track</u>
<u n="557" who="S0019"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yes its sometime in March it's due <pause dur="short"/> um I don't know when</u>
<u n="558" who="S0018">it?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0019">she</u>
<u n="560" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh she's having another girl?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0019">she is having another girl <pause dur="short"/> I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is there any vague possibility that it might actually get at a boy this time <pause dur="short"/> she said no we don't seem to do boys <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="562" who="S0018">and eh <trunc>ana</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> pregnant again?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0019">nope <pause dur="short"/> nope <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="564" who="S0018">maybe they'll have a boy next time</u>
<u n="565" who="S0019">mm who knows? And I can't remember what birthstone is for March <pause dur="short"/> I think it's amethyst</u>
<u n="566" who="S0018">no amethyst is May</u>
<u n="567" who="S0019">no emerald is May</u>
<u n="568" who="S0018">oh really? I thought May was amethyst</u>
<u n="569" who="S0019">nope <pause dur="short"/> emerald is May</u>
<u n="570" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="571" who="S0019">because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday was the first of May and I sent that emerald <pause dur="short"/> the little flower emerald thing <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="572" who="S0018">did you get a thank you letter in the end?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0019">in the end</u>
<u n="574" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> How long did it take?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0019">well I <trunc>s</trunc> I told you what I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? I said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can I ask you a sensitive question? She sort of said yes <pause dur="short"/> Have we done something to upset <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? And she said no <pause dur="short"/> not that I know of <pause dur="short"/> why? And I said well we have never had an acknowledgement from them for anything we've ever sent for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> And there was a sort of silence and eh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> obviously talked to them and they were both horrified because each of them thought that the other one had done it <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said they lead such chaotic lives <pause dur="short"/> they are not organised at all about anything um so she can quite understand why each of them thought the other one had done it</u>
<u n="576" who="S0018">is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> working?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0019">yes eh part time I think <pause dur="short"/> I don't think she's working full time</u>
<u n="578" who="S0018">what does she do?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0019">um she works for some fundraising organisation <pause dur="short"/> I don't know exactly what um but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has had <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure she has her on a regular basis but she's certainly had her on and off <pause dur="short"/> but I mean she's what? Seventy-two and looking after <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I've no doubt she'll look after the little one as well <pause dur="short"/> I think she's beginning to find it all a little bit too much <pause dur="short"/> I mean when she was looking after um <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she was a lot younger <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0018">how old are they now?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0019">eh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is eight I think and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think will be seven this month <pause dur="short"/> the end of this month <pause dur="short"/> I think there's about eighteen months between them <pause dur="short"/> but their style of grandparenting I can quite understand why she's exhausted <pause dur="short"/> cos those kids are never allowed to do anything by themselves <pause dur="short"/> if they paint then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got to be painting with them <pause dur="short"/> if they go and play in the sandpit then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have to be out there with them and I'm thinking to myself well this doesn't encourage individual play and you know I just</u>
<u n="582" who="S0018">maybe she will start leaving them in the sandpit on their own</u>
<u n="583" who="S0019">well they ought to be able to by now <pause dur="short"/> but oh I went out to play in the sandpit with them but my idea of playing is different to to theirs <pause dur="short"/> mine is give them an idea and let them get on with it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="584" who="S0018">distract them</u>
<u n="585" who="S0019">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I did potato printing with them um and we did eh collecting leaves and dipping the leaves in paint and making the leaf prints <pause dur="short"/> things like that and different things out of the kitchen that you can make patterns with <pause dur="short"/> um and what did we do in the sand pit? Oh I that's right <pause dur="short"/> cos the sand was quite damp and I said oh see if you can make tunnels in the sand dig down and see if you can get the tunnels to to meet in the middle and things like that and just let them get on with it <pause dur="short"/> and the response after we'd gone was that um aunty <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were better at play than nana and grandpa <pause dur="short"/> which I thought was a little bit difficult but no they don't develop imagination and thinking for themselves if you're always doing things with them <pause dur="short"/> you've got to give them the idea and then let them go</u>
<u n="586" who="S0018">that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> katie's daughter I mean she's eighteen months old but I think maybe cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s a single mum it's <pause dur="short"/> she's had to let her do stuff on her own <pause dur="short"/> but she she keeps herself occupied for half an hour on her own? No problem just sit there playing and you hear her go na na na na na na like she's pretending to have conversation's between different teddy bears and</u>
<u n="587" who="S0019">but that's what I used to do with you two <pause dur="short"/> andrew was not so good at it with you <pause dur="short"/> but no they those were your toys play with them <pause dur="short"/> that's what they're there for <pause dur="short"/> I mean obviously there are times when you sit down and play as well and you sit and you read but not be with all the time telling them what to do and that's just far too child intensive for me</u>
<u n="588" who="S0018">I do remember I have a memory of the sand pit we used to have out back here</u>
<u n="589" who="S0019">mm hm</u>
<u n="590" who="S0018">but for some reason the only memory I have of it is what it tasted like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0019">that wasn't the object of the exercise but if that is the case then you and your brother are very similar <pause dur="short"/> when we were in <anon type="place"/> by then he was eighteen months old <pause dur="short"/> he was out in the sand pit and then he came across towards me chewing and I fled out to the kitchen and said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what have you got in your mouth? And he beamed at me and he said spider</u>
<u n="592" who="S0018">urgh <pause dur="short"/> in that case I'm totally not at all like my brother because I would not have gone near the spider let alone put it in my mouth</u>
<u n="593" who="S0019">no <pause dur="short"/> I I couldn't <pause dur="short"/> urgh <pause dur="short"/> and of course by the time I looked in his mouth there was nothing to be seen</u>
<u n="594" who="S0018">urgh</u>
<u n="595" who="S0019">it's all extra protein <pause dur="short"/> yes I know</u>
<u n="596" who="S0018">urgh</u>
<u n="597" who="S0019">Strange boy</u>
<u n="598" who="S0018">didn't he eat a a bulb off a lamp or something?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0019">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> dismantled a back lamp on somebody's bicycle took the bulb out and swallowed it</u>
<u n="600" who="S0018">and there was that night where he had to be taken to hospital</u>
<u n="601" who="S0019">oh yes</u>
<u n="602" who="S0018">for the</u>
<u n="603" who="S0019">drinking the Calpol yes <pause dur="short"/> dear God <pause dur="short"/> oi yoy yoy</u>
<u n="604" who="S0018">cats are a lot easier than children are they?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0019">you're not kidding You're not kidding  Then there was the time he painted <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> with mummy's nail varnish and he shaved himself with granddad's razor <pause dur="short"/> took all the skin off his chin</u>
<u n="606" who="S0018">ow</u>
<u n="607" who="S0019">yep <pause dur="short"/> oi oi oi oi <pause dur="short"/> not my carpet <pause dur="short"/> thank you</u>
<u n="608" who="S0018">Don't scratch the carpet</u>
<u n="609" who="S0019">cheeky</u>
<u n="610" who="S0018">how old was he when he did that?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0019">what? Shaved himself? mm <pause dur="short"/> three</u>
<u n="612" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0019">possibly <pause dur="short"/> it was around the same time that he painted <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and that was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well I have to say <pause dur="short"/> they were the two of them at it <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="614" who="S0018">was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> involved as well or was it against his will?</u>
<u n="615" who="S0019">I've no idea <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was there but of course <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was that knew where the nail varnish was <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know <pause dur="short"/> well I wouldn't like to attribute blame for that</u>
<u n="616" who="S0018"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> obviously <pause dur="short"/> I must say granddad always used to make <trunc>l</trunc> shaving look such an interesting <trunc>ex</trunc> experience</u>
<u n="617" who="S0019">yes well</u>
<u n="618" who="S0018">it was all a ritual in the morning of he put his eye in he put his teeth in</u>
<u n="619" who="S0019">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> mm hm</u>
<u n="620" who="S0018">and then he's start shaving</u>
<u n="621" who="S0019">uh-huh</u>
<u n="622" who="S0018">but he'd get brush and the foam and put that all on his face first then take the the blade <pause dur="short"/> it was fun to go and watch granddad in the bathroom in the morning</u>
<u n="623" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="624" who="S0019">yes <pause dur="short"/> hm <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> well the time you needed to worry with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is when you hadn't heard or seen him for a while <pause dur="short"/> eh it was always a worry as to what he was doing <pause dur="short"/> so it was the same when we went to Australia <pause dur="short"/> when he got lost and out of the back gate of <anon type="place"/> Street <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="625" who="S0018">where did he go?</u>
<u n="626" who="S0019">eh I don't know whether you remember <anon type="place"/> Street?</u>
<u n="627" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0019">no <pause dur="short"/> do you?</u>
<u n="629" who="S0018">yes</u>
<u n="630" who="S0019">yes of course cos you were there when you were older <pause dur="short"/> you know down by the flat where grandma used to live there was a gate at the back and then the alleyway that went both ways and then turned back down <anon type="place"/> Street again <pause dur="short"/> well he obviously opened the gate to see where it led and the dog had got out <pause dur="short"/> so he goes after the dog <pause dur="short"/> can't find the dog and of course your father jetlagged had gone to bed so we had to get him up and I went round the streets with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in the car and found him walking down <anon type="place"/> Street crying <pause dur="short"/> so I leapt out of the car and I can't get that dog back was all he could say</u>
<u n="631" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="632" who="S0019">and when I got him home I said well weren't you worried that you were lost? And he said no <pause dur="short"/> and I said well why not? And I said well how did you know where you were going and which house it was? He said well it's the only house in the road that's got a blue door <pause dur="short"/> he was absolutely right</u>
<u n="633" who="S0018">he was lucky that it was the only house on the road that had a blue door</u>
<u n="634" who="S0019">oh no <pause dur="short"/> he'd noticed <pause dur="short"/> we all we'd done was to drive down the road in the car and stop and unload and somehow he managed to suss that there was only one house in the road that had a blue door</u>
<u n="635" who="S0018">and did you get the dog back?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0019">yes</u>
<u n="637" who="S0018">where was the dog?</u>
<u n="638" who="S0019">the dog came back</u>
<u n="639" who="S0018">the dog  The dog  knew where he lived anyway</u>
<u n="640" who="S0019">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so it wasn't a problem <pause dur="short"/> oh but oh dear</u>
<u n="641" who="S0018">was he so <trunc>he</trunc> is he adopting a dog permanently or is that?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0019">no no it's no a dog <pause dur="short"/> he fostered a dog and the dog has gone back now to somebody he knows has adopted him</u>
<u n="643" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="644" who="S0019">um so there won't be any more dogs but he's having this kitten <pause dur="short"/> there's a picture on Facebook of it and it's only four weeks old</u>
<u n="645" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="646" who="S0019">poor little thing</u>
<u n="647" who="S0018">when is he getting it?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0019">well certainly not for another week <pause dur="short"/> um I'm surprised they'll let it go because even Cats Protection League wouldn't let us have the kittens until they were nearly twelve weeks old</u>
<u n="649" who="S0018">yes but they were super</u>
<u n="650" who="S0019">yeah</u>
<u n="651" who="S0018">anal about things weren't they?</u>
<u n="652" who="S0019">yes if you get it from some private individual they'll usually let them go until after eight weeks seven or eight weeks <pause dur="short"/> em but they've got to be inoculated defleed checked over by a vet <pause dur="short"/> because the one worry about having them from those sort of conditions this cat flu em this feline leukaemia thing <pause dur="short"/> so they've got to be checked over by a vet um <pause dur="short"/> then he's got to make arrangements for somebody to come and feed it while he's at work</u>
<u n="653" who="S0018">oh of course</u>
<u n="654" who="S0019">Cos it's too little to be left all day um</u>
<u n="655" who="S0018">can't he take it to work in his pocket?</u>
<u n="656" who="S0019"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Bring your cat to work week <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="657" who="S0018">it'll be tiny <pause dur="short"/> put it in his pocket</u>
<u n="658" who="S0019">so until he gets all that sorted eh he can't make any arrangements as to when he can have the kitten <pause dur="short"/> and I am assuming that it's been taken away from the house and into the rescue centre</u>
<u n="659" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="660" who="S0019">but I'm not absolutely sure</u>
<u n="661" who="S0018">but was it the woman who phoned the rescue centre to get them to come and pick them up or is it</u>
<u n="662" who="S0019">I don't know whether it was a concerned family member or neighbour or what I have no idea <pause dur="short"/> but eh it certainly looks a cute little thing</u>
<u n="663" who="S0018">little black cat</u>
<u n="664" who="S0019">yeah <pause dur="short"/> a little fluffy</u>
<u n="665" who="S0018">is it female or male?</u>
<u n="666" who="S0019">male <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="667" who="S0018">yeah alright but</u>
<u n="668" who="S0019"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="669" who="S0018"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> could be female name too? He's got a female cat called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0019">yes but her name is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? I suppose it could be <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> I suppose like my goldfish <pause dur="short"/> that we called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="671" who="S0018">when it was a female goldfish?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0019">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I won it at the fair <pause dur="short"/> brought it home in a plastic bag put it in a fish bowl on the sideboard and that was fine except when we moved we decided we didn't really want to take a goldfish with us so we gave it to my uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who had a fish pond in his garden and <vocal desc="laugh"/> Then we discovered that it wasn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> but it led a charmed life because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to sit on the side board and he would feign indifference until he would realise that we weren't looking and in went the paw tried to catch it <pause dur="short"/> he never did <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> it's was the best place for it really <pause dur="short"/> it's cruel  It's cruel  to keep a goldfish in a round small round bowl</u>
<u n="673" who="S0018">it is <pause dur="short"/> but did it survive okay in the fish pond?</u>
<u n="674" who="S0019">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh it lasted for years in the fish pond</u>
<u n="675" who="S0018">it wasn't too cold?</u>
<u n="676" who="S0019">no</u>
<u n="677" who="S0018">and didn't it <trunc>fro</trunc> freeze over in the winter?</u>
<u n="678" who="S0019">I don't know what he did initially when he to but it it survived remarkably well</u>
<u n="679" who="S0018">where did he live?</u>
<u n="680" who="S0019"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="681" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="682" who="S0019">I can't remember whether you ever went there <pause dur="short"/> I think you did actually</u>
<u n="683" who="S0018">oh is he <pause dur="short"/> would he be the father the cousin that's just died?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0019">nope <pause dur="short"/> that's on granddad's side</u>
<u n="685" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="686" who="S0019">this was nanny's side <pause dur="short"/> it's nanny's brother <pause dur="short"/> one of nanny's brothers</u>
<u n="687" who="S0018">she had six?</u>
<u n="688" who="S0019">she had five brothers and one sister</u>
<u n="689" who="S0018">and she's the only one left?</u>
<u n="690" who="S0019">yep</u>
<u n="691" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="692" who="S0019">yep <pause dur="short"/> last of the line</u>
<u n="693" who="S0018">and what about granddad's brothers and sisters?</u>
<u n="694" who="S0019">no <pause dur="short"/> none of those left</u>
<u n="695" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="696" who="S0019">nope <pause dur="short"/> aunt <anon type="place"/> was the last one to go <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and that was some time ago</u>
<u n="697" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> end of a <trunc>li</trunc> of an generation</u>
<u n="698" who="S0019">yes it's unfortunate there are no <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>' left</u>
<u n="699" who="S0018">oh that's the end of a line as well</u>
<u n="700" who="S0019">mm</u>
<u n="701" who="S0018">yup</u>
<u n="702" who="S0019">there's no one with the surname <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="703" who="S0018">I think you should change your name back in a</u>
<u n="704" who="S0019">no I don't think dear</u>
<u n="705" who="S0018">A bid to continue the <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>we</trunc></u>
<u n="706" who="S0019">I don't think so</u>
<u n="707" who="S0018">well let's face it there's enough <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>s in the rest of the world</u>
<u n="708" who="S0019">yes <pause dur="short"/> that's very true and it has to be said we don't know how many little <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>s there are running around Singapore</u>
<u n="709" who="S0018">why is that?</u>
<u n="710" who="S0019">my uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and Hong Kong <pause dur="short"/> uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was stationed there for a long time</u>
<u n="711" who="S0018">was he in the army?</u>
<u n="712" who="S0019">navy</u>
<u n="713" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="714" who="S0019">and you know the old story about what a girl in every port <pause dur="short"/> I have an idea that he had several girls in every port</u>
<u n="715" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="716" who="S0019">so I know not</u>
<u n="717" who="S0018">when when was he there?</u>
<u n="718" who="S0019">um the fifties <pause dur="short"/> he he did a long stint in the Far East through choice</u>
<u n="719" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="720" who="S0019">um and I would be about oh gosh twelve? Thirteen?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0018">was he involved in combat?</u>
<u n="722" who="S0019">yeah</u>
<u n="723" who="S0018">all the time?</u>
<u n="724" who="S0019">not <pause dur="short"/> well I don't know about all the time <pause dur="short"/> but there he was on convoy duty and because he was playing in a football match and he broke his toe so he couldn't sail with the convoy and his boat sunk</u>
<u n="725" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="726" who="S0019">and that happened twice</u>
<u n="727" who="S0018">lucky <pause dur="short"/> blimey</u>
<u n="728" who="S0019">the second time <vocal desc="laugh"/> he went AWOL <pause dur="short"/> he was drunk and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was sailing <pause dur="short"/> the number of times he got busted down from chief petty officer <pause dur="short"/> they offered him a commission but he wouldn't have it <pause dur="short"/> so the highest rank he ever <trunc>ra</trunc> reached was chief petty officer <pause dur="short"/> but he went down to  many times <pause dur="short"/> his disciplinary record was um a little checkered</u>
<u n="729" who="S0018">naughty boy</u>
<u n="730" who="S0019">yes he was a naughty boy</u>
<u n="731" who="S0018">he obviously passed his genes onto my brother then did he?</u>
<u n="732" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
</body>
</text>
