<text id="SJE3">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:54:51</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-03-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0525 S0615</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANONs home, Sutton Coldfield</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Holidays, new job, Easter cakes, family, Christening</topics>
		<activity>Mother and daughter catching up over coffee.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, announcing, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T04</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0525">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lichfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>26 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation></occupation>
				<socgrade>unknown</socgrade>
				<nssec>unknown</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0615">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Litchfield</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>no</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Sutton Coldfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>11 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Primary School Tearcher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0525">so is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> happy to go on this trip to Iceland with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0615">as far as I know erm yeah it's just er money-wise for us and we worked it out last night and it's gonna be about a thousand pounds for both of us so</u>
<u n="3" who="S0525">well if it's too much I mean you know don't we won't but you've definitely got to</u>
<u n="4" who="S0615">yeah yeah no we'll er we'll definitely try and save for it <pause dur="short"/> so hopefully we'll be able to get up enough money</u>
<event desc="sound of dog crying"/>
<u n="5" who="S0525">does she wanna go out?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0615">maybe shall I go and see? let's go</u>
<u n="7" who="S0525">okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah I just wanted to make sure that erm he didn't have any issue with</u>
<u n="8" who="S0615" trans="overlap">no there's no issue</u>
<u n="9" who="S0525">the company</u>
<u n="10" who="S0615">oh god no</u>
<u n="11" who="S0525">oh good that's alright then <pause dur="short"/> nice out there for you <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0615">she's been on a walk this morning</u>
<u n="13" who="S0525">mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0615">I'm probably just going to stand by the door</u>
<u n="15" who="S0525">well the accommodation they came up with did they say how much that was gonna be then per person?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0615">I think it was about a <trunc>hund</trunc> was it a hundred and twenty a night for a couple?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0525">so that's quite pricey isn't it? I mean the other thing is we go back to the hotel idea</u>
<u n="18" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0525">cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had it cheaper then didn't he? oh not really it was five hundred per person wasn't it but that did include the trips</u>
<u n="20" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that that I think that's the that's the big one there and if they wanna do the Blue Lagoon I mean that's another forty or fifty quid each isn't it?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0525">is it?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0615">yeah cos they said that was quite expensive so we haven't even factored the food into that</u>
<u n="23" who="S0525" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="24" who="S0615">thousand pounds</u>
<u n="25" who="S0525">it's gonna be a lot</u>
<u n="26" who="S0615">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="27" who="S0525">mm oh well we'll see what they come up with</u>
<u n="28" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0525">nice flowers what were they for?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0615">Mother's Day</u>
<u n="31" who="S0525">oh they've lasted well</u>
<u n="32" who="S0615">yeah I got them</u>
<u n="33" who="S0525">yes</u>
<u n="34" who="S0615">they're wilting somewhat now</u>
<u n="35" who="S0525">well your dad's gone off to his meeting obviously his hour meetings when I expect to see him at five o'clock tonight</u>
<u n="36" who="S0615">oh yes well those meetings</u>
<u n="37" who="S0525">well he went at half past ten yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0615">half past ten to six o'clock</u>
<u n="39" who="S0525">he said he was gonna be back by lunchtime</u>
<u n="40" who="S0615">oh okay</u>
<u n="41" who="S0525">and had done some shopping</u>
<u n="42" who="S0615">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0525">there's a few things on the list</u>
<u n="44" who="S0615">me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have just been up to the shop to get some healthy stuff</u>
<u n="45" who="S0525">oh yeah it's a bit depressing I've got to</u>
<u n="46" who="S0615" trans="overlap">indeed</u>
<u n="47" who="S0525">stop eating now this is ridiculous</u>
<u n="48" who="S0615">stop eating just stop altogether</u>
<u n="49" who="S0525">well I haven't it's been good I haven't been to the shops to look at clothes for ages I didn't</u>
<u n="50" who="S0615" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="51" who="S0525"><unclear/> for a fortnight</u>
<u n="52" who="S0615">mm a fortnight <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah but normally you just go out don't you and look</u>
<u n="54" who="S0615">well I bought a jacket</u>
<u n="55" who="S0525">oh did you?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0615">from New Look the other week and a couple of tops</u>
<u n="57" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0615">the tops one of them fits me the other one doesn't and the jacket doesn't fit me yet over my arms that's why I need to</u>
<u n="59" who="S0525">well why have you bought them then?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0615">because I'm gonna get into them</u>
<u n="61" who="S0525">oh I never do that</u>
<u n="62" who="S0615">that's the incentive</u>
<u n="63" who="S0525">oh I would never do that <unclear/> cheap</u>
<u n="64" who="S0615" trans="overlap">well I know I'm gonna lose weight anyway so eh?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0525">I take it they were cheap?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0615">they weren't that expensive I think the jacket was only about well</u>
<u n="67" who="S0525" trans="overlap">what colour?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0615">twenty-five it's nice it's like a erm it's not I don't know how to describe it erm it's not like a solid colour is kind of a it's not a pattern either I'll show you what</u>
<u n="69" who="S0525" trans="overlap">what to wear with jeans or?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0525">oh nice</u>
<u n="72" who="S0615">I wore <unclear/> jacket for the it's not that lightweight but you know it'll be nice for spring so I'm going to lose some weight from my arms so it'll fit</u>
<u n="73" who="S0525">lovely</u>
<u n="74" who="S0615">so I tried it on in the shop with this jumper and I thought oh it'll just be the jumper it's fine</u>
<u n="75" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0615">but then I got back and I tried it on</u>
<u n="77" who="S0525">oh and it was still a bit tight?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0615">and it was like you know when you can't move your arms?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0615">and you think this isn't comfortable</u>
<u n="81" who="S0525">New Look always do that for me though I think they do very small</u>
<u n="82" who="S0615">small</u>
<u n="83" who="S0525">I I think they do because I can never get my arms into <trunc>any</trunc> mind you my arms are fat but I can never get them into anything</u>
<u n="84" who="S0615">they do it differently with every piece of clothing cos that coat out there's a ten from New Look and that still fits me</u>
<u n="85" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh yeah mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0615">and it's tight when I do it up</u>
<u n="87" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0615">but the arms are fine</u>
<u n="89" who="S0525">well like I said seeing that that dress online I'll have to find it the one I quite fancied from Wallis</u>
<u n="90" who="S0615" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0525">and then looking at the picture I'm not sure if it's a bit short</u>
<u n="92" who="S0615">oh okay</u>
<u n="93" who="S0525">it's a high neck</u>
<u n="94" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0525">erm and <trunc>the</trunc>they always put it on models that are five foot ten don't they?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0615">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0525">so it mightn't be quite that long but quite well short but I don't know</u>
<u n="98" who="S0615">is this for the christening?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0525">yeah but whether I get myself any I have got plenty <trunc>I</trunc>I've got I like that red one I've got and I wore that to your graduation the lace</u>
<u n="100" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yes mm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0525">and I've got the blue one</u>
<u n="102" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah it's nice</u>
<u n="103" who="S0525">as well and it's also like that shift dress in the lace with the white underneath</u>
<u n="104" who="S0615">and you've got the patterned one haven't you?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0525">then I've got that patterned one that's in the photo</u>
<u n="106" who="S0615" trans="overlap">all green and white and black</u>
<u n="107" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah and I've got all the all the colours in there they're all nice with heels and a jacket</u>
<u n="108" who="S0615">yes</u>
<u n="109" who="S0525">I have got quite a lot</u>
<u n="110" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0525">I don't know if the shift ones will fit at the moment the coral and the navy</u>
<u n="112" who="S0615">mm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0525">that other one is stretchier</u>
<u n="114" who="S0615" trans="overlap">stretchy</u>
<u n="115" who="S0525">and I've got a nice one from Phase Eight I've not worn yet it's it's</u>
<u n="116" who="S0615" trans="overlap">oh oh really?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0525">blue and white I bought it</u>
<u n="118" who="S0615" trans="overlap">you've got a few choices</u>
<u n="119" who="S0525">did I buy it last year or did I buy it the year before? I think I've had it two years</u>
<u n="120" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I don't know</u>
<u n="121" who="S0525">every time I put it on I think oh I just look a bit fat in it</u>
<u n="122" who="S0615">well how long have we got a month?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0525">five weeks come on let's</u>
<u n="124" who="S0615" trans="overlap">five weeks</u>
<u n="125" who="S0525">oh we've got Easter in the middle of that though</u>
<u n="126" who="S0615">yeah Easter is in the middle of it and it's gonna fall apart isn't it?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0525">well Easter is just gonna have to be one day</u>
<u n="128" who="S0615">I'm gonna allow myself yeah one day fit</u>
<u n="129" who="S0525">one day so do you want an Easter egg?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0615">no let's not add to the</u>
<u n="131" who="S0525">let's not add to the trauma</u>
<u n="132" who="S0615">to the feast</u>
<u n="133" who="S0525">does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> want an Easter egg?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0615">no don't bother what?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0525">it's a bit mean isn't it?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0615">what do you mean it's a bit mean?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0525">well not buying <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> an Easter egg cos we're on a diet</u>
<u n="138" who="S0615">well okay buy him a mint Aero one then because I don't like mint Aero</u>
<u n="139" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh okay alright then</u>
<u n="140" who="S0615">I think he only likes yeah he likes mint Aero I bought him a</u>
<u n="141" who="S0525" trans="overlap">what he does or you think he does?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0615">I've bought him a peanut M and M one</u>
<u n="143" who="S0525">egg?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0525">oh you've bought them already?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0615">I've got I saw it in Sainsbury's the other day</u>
<u n="147" who="S0525">oh</u>
<u n="148" who="S0615">it's hidden in the boot of my car but then he went to get the pram out and could see it was in there</u>
<u n="149" who="S0525" trans="overlap">do you like Snickers?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0615">he likes Snickers</u>
<u n="151" who="S0525">do you?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0615">yes</u>
<u n="153" who="S0525">oh</u>
<u n="154" who="S0615">it'll be alright buy me it and I'll just tell him to the problem is he doesn't eat them quickly</u>
<u n="155" who="S0525">I know</u>
<u n="156" who="S0615" trans="overlap">like he just kind of has a bit and then puts it back</u>
<u n="157" who="S0525" trans="overlap">I know how do they do that?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0615">and I'm like why don't you just eat the whole egg? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0525">well it's nice yeah if we're going to eat it we're going to eat it aren't we?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0615">well yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0525">properly or you'd have to sort of</u>
<u n="162" who="S0615" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0525">and he'll have to eat them all on Easter Sunday</u>
<u n="164" who="S0615">well yeah that's what I was saying to him and I was saying we can't have any of these left on Monday</u>
<u n="165" who="S0525">well I'll see mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0615">okay yeah if you see one you know but don't go out of your way to get one</u>
<u n="167" who="S0525">well I've got to go and get some I'll have to get one for the boys</u>
<u n="168" who="S0615">oh yeah I suppose</u>
<u n="169" who="S0525" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0615"><unclear/> what?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0525">you don't need to get the boys anything</u>
<u n="172" who="S0615" trans="overlap">no no no I'm talking about you</u>
<u n="173" who="S0525">I I'll take them one and then</u>
<u n="174" who="S0615">I might just take some chocolate around there on Easter Sunday and I'll just get them all kind of</u>
<u n="175" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0615">I'll just take a</u>
<u n="177" who="S0525">I would</u>
<u n="178" who="S0615">I might get just a big egg for them all or something</u>
<u n="179" who="S0525">that's a good idea</u>
<u n="180" who="S0615">I'm making a cake anyway aren't I? so</u>
<u n="181" who="S0525">yeah you are</u>
<u n="182" who="S0615">let's not go mad</u>
<u n="183" who="S0525">the trouble they they could just eat and eat and eat those boys couldn't they?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0615">of course they could</u>
<event desc="sound of dog crying"/>
<u n="185" who="S0525">are you going to let her in? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I'll just go and let the dog in so yeah I'm making I planned planned to make that cake <pause dur="long"/> stop making such a noise</u>
<u n="187" who="S0525">how is it constructed that one how is it like that M and M cake where you've</u>
<u n="188" who="S0615" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0525">got to have some sort of pipe cleaner or something inside it to?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0615">well my mother-in-law bought me a set at Christmas</u>
<u n="191" who="S0525">a set of what?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0615" trans="overlap">she bought me a proper like it's a you have a base</u>
<u n="193" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0615">and then attached to it is a tube that goes up like that</u>
<u n="195" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="196" who="S0615">like a plastic tube</u>
<u n="197" who="S0525">especially for making these</u>
<u n="198" who="S0615" trans="overlap">especially for making those types of cakes</u>
<u n="199" who="S0525">cos that that one</u>
<u n="200" who="S0615">so I'll use that and it'll be easier</u>
<u n="201" who="S0525" trans="overlap">that one had a chocolate egg didn't it and then it had little eggs coming out of it?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah so I'll just I'll royal ice it to it or something so it'll stick the eggs around the tube</u>
<u n="203" who="S0525" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="204" who="S0615">and then the and it had like chocolate cake around the bottom with flakes around the outside</u>
<u n="205" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0615">to look like a nest</u>
<u n="207" who="S0525">flakes look good a nest yeah that'll look good</u>
<u n="208" who="S0615">yeah and I'll make that <unclear/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0525" trans="overlap">but then you've got to transport it</u>
<u n="210" who="S0615">yeah I know I never think about that bit</u>
<u n="211" who="S0525">that's I know it's great when you make it and put it on the work surface it's carrying them isn't it?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0615">well none of them have fallen apart yet touch wood</u>
<u n="213" who="S0525">no no they haven't no I don't know how you do it?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0615">and to be honest they are quite sturdy once you've</u>
<u n="215" who="S0525">you couldn't' assemble it and put the egg on at the other end maybe?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0615">well it'll just take</u>
<u n="217" who="S0525">oh it takes too long does it?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0615">I could put the egg on cos I could just really put that on the top and it wouldn't be a</u>
<u n="219" who="S0525">no that wouldn't be a problem</u>
<u n="220" who="S0615">I'll see</u>
<u n="221" who="S0525">how long is it going to take to make? is it an all-day job again?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0615" trans="overlap">oh I don't know erm no because it's just a basic chocolate cake and then it's not a really like intricate icing is it? it's there's not a lot of cutting out shapes of</u>
<u n="223" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0615">rolled icing which seems to take the time whenever I do make a cake</u>
<u n="225" who="S0525">oh right</u>
<u n="226" who="S0615">it's all just putting it together and making sure it doesn't fall apart <pause dur="short"/> we'll see</u>
<u n="227" who="S0525">fair enough</u>
<u n="228" who="S0615">I'm hoping it'll be alright</u>
<u n="229" who="S0525">well I didn't leave a note to tell your dad where I was I was gonna say erm don't bother about the dishwasher it seems to have fixed itself</u>
<u n="230" who="S0615" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0525">spend some time fixing the light</u>
<u n="232" who="S0615">mm <unclear>we did that</unclear> last night unloaded the whole thing</u>
<u n="233" who="S0525">mm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0615">and then I thought to myself oh I'll just see if it shuts <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> looked and he went oh for god's sake</u>
<u n="235" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0615">yeah it was gonna happen that way wasn't it?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0525">so this job he's got</u>
<u n="238" who="S0615">mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0525">erm he's gonna get deals on cars presumably?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0615">I hope so</u>
<u n="241" who="S0525">so when he was talking</u>
<u n="242" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I don't know</u>
<u n="243" who="S0525">oh he's well he's he's bound he's bound to get <unclear/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0615">yeah but not enough to maybe bring it down underneath the price of a I don't know he's looking at a SEAT one as well he's he's got loads in mind for me so</u>
<u n="245" who="S0525">oh has he?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0615">I said just get me a big one</u>
<u n="247" who="S0525">but Jaguar Land Rover do they just do Jaguars and Land Rovers or do they have <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I don't know <unclear/> cars yeah yeah I think so I mean it's all I mean things like Audi and VWs and</u>
<u n="249" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0615">Fiat and Alfa and Ferrari</u>
<u n="251" who="S0525" trans="overlap">but I'm thinking if that's the company you're working for is it just those models?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0615">I don't know what</u>
<u n="253" who="S0525">not that they're bad models but they're very expensive models aren't they?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0615">yeah exactly that's it so I don't know whether he'll look into it and he'll get the best deal anyway he spends enough time looking at cars</u>
<u n="255" who="S0525">he likes cars so when when's his deal is up first isn't it on his car?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0615">yeah erm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0525">so is he changing his first?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0615">I don't know I don't know what he's planning with his erm he wants if I get a big car he wants a saloon</u>
<u n="259" who="S0525">does he why?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0615">yes I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0615">I don't know anyway he'll er</u>
<u n="263" who="S0525">big dog big cars eh <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>? eh? big house next</u>
<u n="264" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0525">yes with a big garden for you yes sit down there</u>
<u n="266" who="S0615">I just want a car that I don't have to clamber into the back seat to put him in and</u>
<u n="267" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0615">take the wheel off the pushchair to get it in the boot and</u>
<u n="269" who="S0525" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="270" who="S0615">I can actually put the seat and the pushchair in the boot rather than have to put the seat</u>
<u n="271" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0615">on the chair and</u>
<u n="273" who="S0525">have you got erm an airbag in the front of yours you'd have to turn off if you put him in the front?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0615">well why did you have the Fiat? I said well I didn't exactly plan having a baby this soon did I?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0525">no you changed all your plans well you did plan on having a baby you brought your plans forward</u>
<u n="276" who="S0615" trans="overlap">that's it</u>
<u n="277" who="S0525">you didn't think about didn't think about the Fiat</u>
<u n="278" who="S0615">no of course I didn't think about the Fiat</u>
<u n="279" who="S0525">yeah well I spoke to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yesterday and she was oh yeah we're gonna go off to Canada erm so you'll have none and I said oh that's fine and er like I said we'd have <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0525">and he'd be in his highchair by then and keeping us all busy and then she said erm she said oh well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will be pregnant again by then and I said by this Christmas I don't think so</u>
<u n="282" who="S0615" trans="overlap">alright</u>
<u n="283" who="S0525">I said I think she's waiting so she can have a natural labour next time instead and what? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was horrified why would you do that? I said well I can understand the whole thing about not wanting a planned epidural and a section it'd be a bit but yeah but we both agreed it would be easier but then you've got a longer recovery time still probably so and then not being able to drive once you've got two kids is a</u>
<u n="284" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0525">is a big thing so I said they told you you had to wait well I don't know three or maybe two years before you get pregnant I don't know</u>
<u n="286" who="S0615">well it's it's the whole house situation as well and I need to be</u>
<u n="287" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0615">back at work and you know stable like back at work so that we could have a mortgage on another house and</u>
<u n="289" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0615">because otherwise you know there's no chance of a <pause dur="short"/> and we can't have another one in this house no way so it's all go isn't it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0525">well you did everything in the first year didn't you?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0615">oh yeah had the year now</u>
<u n="293" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0525">you got it all you got the house got the dog got the baby</u>
<u n="295" who="S0615">do it again <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> I'll just stick with you I think <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0525">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> the dinosaur you're enough of a dog aren't you?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0615">half horse half dog</u>
<u n="298" who="S0525">mm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0615">mm oh</u>
<u n="300" who="S0525"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said erm oh no I said well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said I'll have to childproof the house and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes oh you're not gonna bother with any of that are you?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0615"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0525">I said well she goes well we never even did it for ours I said you didn't bother? and she goes oh not for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they never had a stairgate up</u>
<u n="303" who="S0615" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0525">yeah they never had anything</u>
<u n="305" who="S0615" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="306" who="S0525">a fireguard mind you if they were in that house they didn't need one stairgates no because I said cupboard locks? no I said oh she said oh no just let him wander around he was fine</u>
<u n="307" who="S0615"><vocal desc="laugh"/> making their own mistakes</u>
<u n="308" who="S0525">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> put his hand on the hob didn't he? and burnt his hand cos it was</u>
<u n="309" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0525"><unclear/> cooking didn't they on the side?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0615">oh he did lots when he was up on the work surfaces</u>
<u n="312" who="S0525">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got him into cooking and he used to like cooking all his food with him and then of course he won't eat it unless it's a pizza</u>
<u n="313" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0525">tried to for all the good that did him</u>
<u n="315" who="S0615">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/> wasted time</u>
<u n="316" who="S0525"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was asking how old <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was because <unclear/> when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was sixteen weeks old</u>
<u n="317" who="S0615">yeah she was saying to me when they kept her <unclear/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0525" trans="overlap">is he seventeen or eighteen now?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0615">he'll be eighteen tomorrow</u>
<u n="320" who="S0525" trans="overlap">eighteen tomorrow</u>
<u n="321" who="S0615">I think yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0525">is it already? crikey <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0615">whoa</u>
<u n="324" who="S0525">you're getting so big <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0615">it'll be his birthday before we know it</u>
<u n="326" who="S0525">I know what are you doing for that? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0615">a cake</u>
<u n="328" who="S0525">a cake</u>
<u n="329" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I'll be off for it because it's a Thursday</u>
<u n="330" who="S0525">ah yes</u>
<u n="331" who="S0615">is it Thursday? yes it is</u>
<u n="332" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yes it is born on a Tuesday</u>
<u n="333" who="S0615">because he was born on a Tuesday a leap year I'll be at home with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yes and hopefully <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is going to get more flexi time</u>
<u n="334" who="S0525">oh is he?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0525">oh that's good</u>
<u n="337" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I was a bit annoyed when I thought about it that they didn't offer it him you know where he is at the moment</u>
<u n="338" who="S0525">as in terms of what were what were the arrangements because?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0615">well he you know he'd have the opportunity to maybe do a seven till three working day or an eight till four and get home a little bit earlier or</u>
<u n="340" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm oh that's good</u>
<u n="341" who="S0615">work from home one day if he ever needed to erm I just think they could have offered cos he goes in and unless he's got a client meeting it's very much like well he sits at a computer and he takes calls and answers emails and it's like well he could do that at home</u>
<u n="342" who="S0525">mm</u>
<u n="343" who="S0615">you know if he needed to</u>
<u n="344" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0615">and for example you know there's gonna you know there's gonna come a time in the next couple of years where he's gonna be ill and it's like oh well we don't wanna put him in a nursery that day well obviously we can't put him in a nursery that day</u>
<u n="346" who="S0525" trans="overlap">they wouldn't let you either?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0615">no or erm you know we don't want to bring him over to you or and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and it's not a case of I can just get a day off</u>
<u n="348" who="S0525" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="349" who="S0615">that quickly</u>
<u n="350" who="S0525">no</u>
<u n="351" who="S0615">I can't yeah kids come to me to be taught erm so it would be good if he can then just say oh I wanna work from home today</u>
<u n="352" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0615">erm</u>
<u n="354" who="S0525">oh yeah you need flexibility when they're</u>
<u n="355" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0525">when they're little like that</u>
<u n="357" who="S0615">well yeah that's it and I was a bit annoyed at the job that he was in at at the moment that they didn't offer him that I thought they would have kind of said oh erm you know if you ever need any time or I mean he's got a key to open up and things he could have gone in at eight o'clock and left at four you know? they never said to him oh</u>
<u n="358" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0615">I don't think he really asked but he's always in for half past eight anyway and they never say to him at half past four oh just go</u>
<u n="360" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah I wonder what they'll say? when is he going to tell them?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0615">well this week when he gets his yeah he keeps er he said to me last night he said oh I know exactly what they'll say when</u>
<u n="362" who="S0525" trans="overlap">they'll offer him more money and he'll stay?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0615" trans="overlap">well he doesn't no he doesn't think they will</u>
<u n="364" who="S0525">oh I'll be amazed if they didn't</u>
<u n="365" who="S0615">that's what I thought but there's</u>
<u n="366" who="S0525" trans="overlap">what do you think'll happen then?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0615">well he thinks because they'll you know they'll get a new trainee kind of like that and and I said yeah but they have invested quite a lot of time in you</u>
<u n="368" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="369" who="S0615">erm so they'll know they haven't been that that brilliant erm always but you know <trunc>you</trunc>you're through your exams or your or your foundation ones and they're not stupid you know they they are aware that you work very hard and</u>
<u n="370" who="S0525" trans="overlap">earn them a lot of money</u>
<u n="371" who="S0615">exactly yeah that he does earn them a heck of a lot of money cos he doesn't get paid a fraction of what he should be for the work that he's putting out and he does</u>
<u n="372" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0615">work for the other people as well</u>
<u n="374" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0615">erm his supervisings or whatever erm but yeah so I was just yeah he he just doesn't seem to think that they'll what well what <unclear/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0525" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0615">he said he said at Christmas he very much got the impression that erm cos quite a few of them have left the trainees that started at the same time as him there's no one within the <anon type="place"/> office but they're all in <anon type="place"/> and quite a few of them have left</u>
<u n="378" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0615">and erm</u>
<u n="380" who="S0525">are they expecting him to leave then do you think?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0615">well I don't know but at Christmas time it was like he I think they realised that this well it probably happens kind of every few years when they get a bulk of trainees in</u>
<u n="382" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0615">and they obviously kind of erm tail out and I don't know whether they thought oh erm it looks like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is going all the something I mean he hasn't been enjoying his job in a while but he said from the sound of it at Christmas they they didn't want to they didn't want me to go anyway from the things they were saying to me and he said it was interesting cos a couple of weeks ago one of his well his main boss if you like it's it's all a very weird setup the amount of people that he kind of works under</u>
<u n="384" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0615">he said it's confusing more than anything and he looks forward to kind of going somewhere and having one line manager and that's it</u>
<u n="386" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0615">erm but yeah one of them said to him oh you are you still enjoying work are you still enjoying yourself? and I think he said well not as much as I was</u>
<u n="388" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="389" who="S0615">but you know just say that</u>
<u n="390" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0615">erm and this guy was like oh well I I do try you know I'm trying to bring you work down from <anon type="place"/> that because he's got this is one of the guys that kind of goes</u>
<u n="392" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0615">up and down and works in both offices and and he said oh yeah well I'm you know I am trying erm and hopefully you know I'll get I'll get you more and more stuff that you're kind of erm interested in</u>
<u n="394" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0615">so I think that's the way that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> played it and he was like well yeah there's stuff that I'm getting isn't really stuff that I'm interested in or that I thought I'd get</u>
<u n="396" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="397" who="S0615">erm so it's <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0525">mm</u>
<u n="399" who="S0615">difficult cos well he he doesn't he doesn't know and I know I've said I'll be surprised if they don't</u>
<u n="400" who="S0525">try and keep him</u>
<u n="401" who="S0615">try and keep you</u>
<u n="402" who="S0525">yeah I think they will</u>
<u n="403" who="S0615">because the other you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the one who's had a</u>
<u n="404" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0615">midlife crisis?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0615">so <trunc>he</trunc>he's handed in his notice three times and they've kept him</u>
<u n="408" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0615">by offering him you know more money as they do erm but yeah <trunc>h</trunc>he said oh cos I'm only part-qualified and they'll they'll probably just say to me oh see you in a few years when you're fully qualified</u>
<u n="410" who="S0525">I think I think they'll offer him more</u>
<u n="411" who="S0615">that's what I said to him I said I'll be <trunc>su</trunc> I'll be really surprised</u>
<u n="412" who="S0525" trans="overlap">they'll probably ask him what what he's gonna get and see if they can match it</u>
<u n="413" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah cos you cos you'd be <trunc>definit</trunc> they can definitely afford to offer him more let's you know say that</u>
<u n="414" who="S0525" trans="overlap">and is he prepared for what he's gonna say whether that happens?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0615">no I need to ask him tonight</u>
<u n="416" who="S0525" trans="overlap">he wouldn't he wouldn't cos yeah he needs to know because if they say you know we'll give you another ten grand</u>
<u n="417" who="S0615">yeah yeah yeah I'll say I'm going to ask him what <unclear/> gonna be</u>
<u n="418" who="S0525" trans="overlap">and if that's more than his actual increase in this new one</u>
<u n="419" who="S0615">yeah I mean they're gonna they're gonna turn around and say well look you're the benefits are private you know being in a private practice rather than in-house you'll be you can get further on the you know pay scale wise</u>
<u n="420" who="S0525">right</u>
<u n="421" who="S0615">cos yeah they are gonna ask him why he's gonna leave aren't they? but</u>
<u n="422" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0615" trans="overlap">so and and</u>
<u n="424" who="S0525">I think he needs to be ready for for that cos if they did</u>
<u n="425" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0525">throw another ten grand in</u>
<u n="427" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0525">he needs to have thought about actually what he does want just in case</u>
<u n="429" who="S0615">yeah yeah but</u>
<u n="430" who="S0525" trans="overlap">cos I don't know how much more this company is paying him to start with but erm</u>
<u n="431" who="S0615" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="432" who="S0525">but you know he needs to he needs to just think about it</u>
<u n="433" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah definitely when does it become <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0525" trans="overlap">because they might say they might say to him what are they offering you? or <trunc>w</trunc>we're gonna match that</u>
<u n="435" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0525">well we'll beat it</u>
<u n="437" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0525">that's what if it any company that values him and I think he he will be valued</u>
<u n="439" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0525">he's probably more valued than he realises</u>
<u n="441" who="S0615" trans="overlap">than he realises yeah definitely</u>
<u n="442" who="S0525" trans="overlap">I think I think so he needs to be ready for that one</u>
<u n="443" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0525">he needs to know <unclear/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I'll ask him what his response is to that</u>
<u n="446" who="S0525">because he's gotta think about it <trunc>be</trunc> and he's got to think now well if you know they might not offer it him fine and he's <unclear/></u>
<u n="447" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0525">but if they do he needs to know now what what</u>
<u n="449" who="S0615" trans="overlap">is it worth it?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0525">he would rather do yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0615">mm <unclear>they were</unclear> saying somewhere that he really doesn't like it but getting that but getting more or moving <unclear/> yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0525" trans="overlap">with the potential of getting better work or or thinking now I've given it long enough and I really do wanna move and I don't want to have to go in this process of erm</u>
<u n="453" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0525">being interviewed again you know and not turn turn somebody down now I've had a good offer</u>
<u n="455" who="S0615" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0525">especially if it's a firm he wants to work for which it is</u>
<u n="457" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0525">and I think he's probably erm yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I think I think it's gonna take something quite big for</u>
<u n="460" who="S0525" trans="overlap">he hasn't got to stay with the new company forever</u>
<u n="461" who="S0615" trans="overlap">no no no that's it yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0525">you know but if he does two or three years there and wants to move on again and er absolutely</u>
<u n="463" who="S0615" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="464" who="S0525">so I I don't envisage him staying somewhere for life because that's probably the the way you're going to earn more money anyways by moving companies half the time</u>
<u n="465" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="466" who="S0525">because otherwise you just you do get stuck</u>
<u n="467" who="S0615" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="468" who="S0525">but it's when you come up with a job offer and they'll say oh they'll realise they're underpaying you and go right come on we wanna keep you and we'll give you this</u>
<u n="469" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0525">so</u>
<u n="471" who="S0615">mm I don't know what his cut off point is gonna be? I <unclear/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0525" trans="overlap">well you know there may not be one the the fact of the matter is he may really wanna move to this job</u>
<u n="473" who="S0615">yeah which I think is</u>
<u n="474" who="S0525" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0615">to be honest</u>
<u n="476" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah and he</u>
<u n="477" who="S0615">and he really doesn't want to be where he is at the moment</u>
<u n="478" who="S0525" trans="overlap">and if that's what he wants to do he's getting more money for it anyway and he's happy and he needs to move then it probably er that's probably what he wants and that he should do what</u>
<u n="479" who="S0615" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="480" who="S0525">he wants to do it shouldn't be all just about the money it should be</u>
<u n="481" who="S0615" trans="overlap">no I know and he and he he well he's turned around to me in the last few weeks and just said oh it's you know it's not about the money and I said well good</u>
<u n="482" who="S0525">yes he's been that miserable and he needs to do something he wants to do</u>
<u n="483" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0525">so I think a change is probably a really good idea anyway</u>
<u n="485" who="S0615">I said to him with regards to telling his mum</u>
<u n="486" who="S0525">oh yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0615">I said you should just wait until like they actually ask you how work is</u>
<u n="488" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0615">like a few months a time and say oh by the way <vocal desc="laugh"/> I've moved jobs</u>
<u n="490" who="S0525">I think I would</u>
<u n="491" who="S0615">yeah? don't bother?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0525">no unless he wants to tell his dad cos he does get on well with his dad doesn't he?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean his mum never never asks anyway never asks how we are never asks erm what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has done this week it's all <unclear/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0525" trans="overlap">well she never asks about anything by the sound of it</u>
<u n="495" who="S0615" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="496" who="S0525">she doesn't have anything to talk about why doesn't she ask?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0615" trans="overlap">she doesn't she doesn't she just doesn't</u>
<u n="498" who="S0525" trans="overlap">why doesn't she make conversation when she only sees you once a a or twice a month?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="500" who="S0525">well no does she see you every week? not always</u>
<u n="501" who="S0615">not always no</u>
<u n="502" who="S0525">once a fortnight</u>
<u n="503" who="S0615">they're away aren't they a lot? they're away at Easter oh we'll have to drop your Easter presents around next week</u>
<u n="504" who="S0525">oh are they going away for Easter? oh well that's good then so you haven't got another invitation you have to turn down</u>
<u n="505" who="S0615" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="506" who="S0525">because you're not getting one</u>
<u n="507" who="S0615">well we won't get one</u>
<u n="508" who="S0525">where are they going? abroad are they?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0615">Spain</u>
<u n="510" who="S0525">oh</u>
<u n="511" who="S0615"><unclear/></u>
<u n="512" who="S0525">I know they don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0615" trans="overlap">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s retiring he's got nine days left at work <pause dur="short"/> then he's getting his new car and retiring</u>
<u n="514" who="S0525">oh right so what's he having?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0615">he's having a Mazda that's what he had previously</u>
<u n="516" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0615">he's having a high spec he's thinking of getting himself a retirement present as well</u>
<u n="518" who="S0525">such as what?</u>
<u n="519" who="S0615">a personalised number plate</u>
<u n="520" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0615">and I'm sat there and I'm like mm okay do you still want petrol money <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? this is interesting and I was just like for god's sake</u>
<u n="522" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0615">I was thinking okay but there was no no there was no mention of oh now <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is retiring maybe he wants to come up more and have <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for an afternoon or something or</u>
<u n="524" who="S0525">they didn't say anything?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0615">no</u>
<u n="526" who="S0525">maybe they're waiting for you they they think there's no need at the moment as well because you're not working</u>
<u n="527" who="S0615">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="528" who="S0525">there's maybe that but I <trunc>do</trunc> I don't know</u>
<u n="529" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0525">do you think do you think he will want to? well no I don't suppose you will see more of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when he's retired because it's not like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is around in the day so</u>
<u n="531" who="S0615">no no I won't no I won't see any more of him definitely not and I mean I know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has one day off a week like during the week she always has Sunday off and then she has one day during the week off</u>
<u n="532" who="S0525" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="533" who="S0615">and she works from home one day which <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> told me as well yesterday</u>
<u n="534" who="S0525" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="535" who="S0615">which is why I was even more</u>
<u n="536" who="S0525">well she could easily pitch up one every now and again to see him or</u>
<u n="537" who="S0615">oh yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="538" who="S0525" trans="overlap">so she could take him out for a walk or something</u>
<u n="539" who="S0615">yeah no she erm she's not interested though so I was so surprised when she came around yesterday</u>
<u n="540" who="S0525">well I'm not and I think it's because of the godmother thing</u>
<u n="541" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="542" who="S0525">I think I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wanted her there because then you with her right who are you having as godparents?</u>
<u n="543" who="S0615">who? well it was like who have you who have you chosen?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0525" trans="overlap">here we are here here's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="545" who="S0615" trans="overlap">who have you chosen? and it's like</u>
<u n="546" who="S0525">and she should be your first choice</u>
<u n="547" who="S0615">yeah and to be <trunc>hon</trunc> as I said to you yesterday to be honest if she wasn't there I would have perhaps said something like well erm we we did want <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but erm we don't really feel as if erm she's spent enough time with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> since he's been born</u>
<u n="548" who="S0525">no</u>
<u n="549" who="S0615">and I would have said that I I think if she wasn't there</u>
<u n="550" who="S0525" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="551" who="S0615">it's kind of all a bit</u>
<u n="552" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="553" who="S0615">it was just so awkward</u>
<u n="554" who="S0525">did she hold him? did they?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0615">yeah yeah erm cos he was cos he'd been up since half past five yesterday morning</u>
<u n="556" who="S0525">oh right</u>
<u n="557" who="S0615">and they came around at half ten</u>
<u n="558" who="S0525">and he hadn't had his sleep in that time?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0615" trans="overlap">he had had a little sleep but from quarter past nine until half past nine so</u>
<u n="560" who="S0525" trans="overlap">okay yeah</u>
<u n="561" who="S0615">he was really like grouchy still so he was in his pushchair in the kitchen watching <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> try and fix the dishwasher and erm anyway then they came around and so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was in the kitchen and I saw them at the door and I was like huh your sister's here and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like what? <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I was like yeah yeah I know right here we go erm anyway so I brought <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in and erm I gave him to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I said oh er you know he is a bit he's a bit grouchy he hasn't really slept this morning but erm here you go have a have a cuddle and stuff so yeah</u>
<u n="562" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0615">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had him and then I came I kind of was going in and out with the dog and then came back in and I think <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> had him and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had him and er you know <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> was taking a picture of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> with him but yeah</u>
<u n="564" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="565" who="S0615">we get a get a rare rare picture then it was so funny because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was sitting there and she was like smile <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> smile smile smile and I was like don't you dare tell my son to smile when you won't crack a smile on a photo</u>
<u n="566" who="S0525" trans="overlap">I know she never has a smile on her face does she?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0615">no I know so I thought don't you sit there and try and force him to smile</u>
<u n="568" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh dear</u>
<u n="569" who="S0615">he doesn't know who told him he hasn't got a clue who you are so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then cos I was sat down on the floor with the dog <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then went behind cos they were sat here and he went behind there and he smiled straightaway</u>
<u n="570" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0615">erm but I just thought oh</u>
<u n="572" who="S0525">well you won't have to have them on the christening photos I think you just want a few informal ones you can do a few nice ones</u>
<u n="573" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0525">with you and the godparents and that that's really what <unclear/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I mean hopefully it'll be be like this <unclear/></u>
<u n="576" who="S0525" trans="overlap">well if it's like this it'll be lovely won't it? mm</u>
<u n="577" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah with the church it'll be or outside at the back of the conservatory <unclear/></u>
<u n="578" who="S0525" trans="overlap">I must remember to ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to take a camera I'm sure she will anyway</u>
<u n="579" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah and I imagine <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will <unclear/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yes he'll he'll bring his anyway I'm sure <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will</u>
<u n="581" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="582" who="S0525">yeah that'll be nice</u>
<u n="583" who="S0615">yeah it will be erm</u>
<u n="584" who="S0525">you haven't heard back from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="585" who="S0615">no not yet erm</u>
<u n="586" who="S0525">what days does she work in the bridal shop?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I think she's in the bridal shop on Wednesday this week so I might just might pop over on the way over to you</u>
<u n="588" who="S0525">okay</u>
<u n="589" who="S0615">yeah I might do yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0525">it would be easier to go on the way back <pause dur="short"/> oh no you <trunc>ca</trunc></u>
<u n="591" who="S0615">I can't it's</u>
<u n="592" who="S0525" trans="overlap">no I'm just thinking of the</u>
<u n="593" who="S0615">it would be far too late <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="594" who="S0525">yes I'm just thinking of the position of the where it is</u>
<u n="595" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I know but getting him off to sleep anyway so</u>
<u n="596" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="597" who="S0615">I'll go in the afternoon at some some point erm we saw him in panto him on TV</u>
<u n="598" who="S0525">oh on yes the ventriloquist didn't he win the America's Got Talent?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0615">did he?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0525">I think so</u>
<u n="601" who="S0615" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="602" who="S0525">and he's made it big in the States</u>
<u n="603" who="S0615">oh</u>
<u n="604" who="S0525">but yeah he was on there</u>
<u n="605" who="S0615">well look at it his eyes huh?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0525" trans="overlap">he's got how much makeup is he wearing?</u>
<u n="607" who="S0615"><unclear/> in my life yeah</u>
<u n="608" who="S0525">oh somebody's <unclear/></u>
<u n="609" who="S0615">oh yes they were doing the smoky eyes <unclear/></u>
<u n="610" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh they've made him up have they? yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="611" who="S0615">oh my life</u>
<u n="612" who="S0525">good old Gino what does he look like?</u>
<u n="613" who="S0615"><unclear/></u>
<u n="614" who="S0525">smoky eyes oh I wonder if he's done it for a joke</u>
<u n="615" who="S0615">yeah so I'm gonna I might ask <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> to do something for the christening so then I thought <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said well we haven't even invited her and I said oh well I could</u>
<u n="616" who="S0525">oh right</u>
<u n="617" who="S0615">he said well I was gonna ask the erm cos I thought it'd be nice not a tree but like having a baby in a like a sling thing and then balloons and people's fingerprints as the balloons</u>
<u n="618" who="S0525">oh to do a oh I see</u>
<u n="619" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="620" who="S0525">it'll give her a whole new er <vocal desc="laugh"/> a whole new thing to do</u>
<u n="621" who="S0615">but I'll send her a picture of kind of what I've finished</u>
<u n="622" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah I'm sure she would</u>
<u n="623" who="S0615">yes</u>
<u n="624" who="S0525">I don't know that you'd need to invite her you you could do but</u>
<u n="625" who="S0615">but I thought he was gonna he was gonna do it when we're there cos I'm not standing with him <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="626" who="S0525">no that's true yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0615" trans="overlap">so I don't really want to ask anyone else</u>
<u n="628" who="S0525">I mean don't forget you've not invited <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and that lot I mean</u>
<u n="629" who="S0615">yeah I know</u>
<u n="630" who="S0525">is that something you're thinking though it's got quite big?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0615">well <pause dur="short"/> what I might do is I won't ring them I'll just get his number or have you have you got his number?</u>
<u n="632" who="S0525">no I haven't but your dad'll have it</u>
<u n="633" who="S0615">I might just text dad's phone</u>
<u n="634" who="S0525" trans="overlap">text him yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0615">I'll yeah get the number off dad</u>
<u n="636" who="S0525" trans="overlap">I think because it's got as big as it has it's</u>
<u n="637" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah I know they won't come anyway so</u>
<u n="638" who="S0525" trans="overlap">well they probably won't will they? or there'll there'll be an excuse or maybe she won't</u>
<u n="639" who="S0615">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="640" who="S0525" trans="overlap">it won't be so bad it's not like a wedding so and that'll be fine then if she comes</u>
<u n="641" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I tell you what I might text dad now and just say look</u>
<u n="642" who="S0525">ask for his number</u>
<u n="643" who="S0615">can you send me Uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s number?</u>
<u n="644" who="S0525">yeah just because I think it seems to have got yeah and then nobody will ever need know we were considering not inviting them</u>
<u n="645" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="646" who="S0525">I think if it was a smaller affair you know and you were talking about twenty people cos there's another five of them and fair enough but now we're up to numbers we're up to but like I say I wouldn't necessarily add on to the catering for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="647" who="S0615">no no no I'm just doing it</u>
<u n="648" who="S0525" trans="overlap">because there'll be plenty of food cos she always does masses on her buffets doesn't she?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0615">yeah yeah she's not gonna stand there and headcount for goodness sake</u>
<u n="650" who="S0525">oh no of course not</u>
<u n="651" who="S0615">send me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s number please to tell them about the christening I think right okay yeah I mean he won't have been in touch with grandma or Auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to know that there's a christening so far so I doubt there will be any issues</u>
<u n="652" who="S0525">I imagine your dad will go and see them today because he hasn't seen them for a week</u>
<u n="653" who="S0615" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="654" who="S0525">I don't think he saw them last week with him being in Scotland</u>
<u n="655" who="S0615">oh okay</u>
<u n="656" who="S0525">so I imagine he'll go today</u>
<u n="657" who="S0615">yeah when he gets home from his</u>
<u n="658" who="S0525">I think he's working Tuesday Wednesday</u>
<u n="659" who="S0615">six-hour meeting</u>
<u n="660" who="S0525">yeah Tuesday Wednesday Saturday I think</u>
<u n="661" who="S0615">mm</u>
<u n="662" who="S0525">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s off tomorrow</u>
<u n="663" who="S0615">tomorrow is she?</u>
<u n="664" who="S0525" trans="overlap">and Thursday and Sunday is what she's I think because she didn't have that day off last week she's <unclear/></u>
<u n="665" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yes I knew she was having an extra one off this week</u>
<u n="666" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah I do fancy going to Birmingham to look at erm outfits cos I I liked that you know the the House of Fraser they've got there? it's</u>
<u n="667" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0525">that we went to before with the Wallis section and you came with me didn't you?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="670" who="S0525">cos they have so many more things there than they do</u>
<u n="671" who="S0615">I could go on Thursday</u>
<u n="672" who="S0525">well we haven't lost any weight yet</u>
<u n="673" who="S0615">if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants to come oh I'm not looking for an outfit I've got one</u>
<u n="674" who="S0525">I don't really need one either but I just wanna have a look I might leave it a couple of weeks</u>
<u n="675" who="S0615">I'm got my own yeah I'm gonna wear that one that I've got upstairs you know the dress with the</u>
<u n="676" who="S0525">the blue and white?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0615">mm</u>
<u n="678" who="S0525">yes because you had another one but that was for your baby shower was that pink and blue?</u>
<u n="679" who="S0615">yeah pink and blue yeah</u>
<u n="680" who="S0525">the similar style with the polka dots</u>
<u n="681" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0525">is that the one?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0615">it was different material</u>
<u n="684" who="S0525" trans="overlap">but <trunc>ob</trunc>obviously but that was when you were eight months pregnant</u>
<u n="685" who="S0615" trans="overlap">eight months pregnant</u>
<u n="686" who="S0525">so you're not talking about that dress?</u>
<u n="687" who="S0615" trans="overlap">no I'm not wearing that one I think that's the <trunc>mater</trunc> that's the maternity one as well</u>
<u n="688" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="689" who="S0615">no the other one I had was it's</u>
<u n="690" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh it wasn't a maternity dress?</u>
<u n="691" who="S0615"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s wedding</u>
<u n="692" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yes it was just the</u>
<u n="693" who="S0615" trans="overlap">no do you remember they were in Debenham's</u>
<u n="694" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="695" who="S0615">was it Debenham's?</u>
<u n="696" who="S0525">much smaller little</u>
<u n="697" who="S0615" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="698" who="S0525">polka dot on it tiny</u>
<u n="699" who="S0615">well it's not it's not even I don't think it's a polka dot</u>
<u n="700" who="S0525" trans="overlap">no it's not</u>
<u n="701" who="S0615">it's like bows or something like that</u>
<u n="702" who="S0525">yeah it's so <trunc>i</trunc>it's mainly blues yes that's right</u>
<u n="703" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="704" who="S0525">yes when <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> asked you if you're sure you weren't having twins or something <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="705" who="S0615">she'll probably ask me if I'm sure I'm not pregnant again at the <trunc>ch</trunc> at the christening</u>
<u n="706" who="S0525">oh she better not</u>
<u n="707" who="S0615">I'll say er how about a smile <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="708" who="S0525">yeah yeah you should point the camera smile <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="709" who="S0615">smile</u>
<u n="710" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="711" who="S0615">smile oh no yes no it's going to be great standing up in a church oh could the godparents please come forward?</u>
<u n="712" who="S0525">yes</u>
<u n="713" who="S0615">that'll be my sister <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="714" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="715" who="S0615">and our friends</u>
<u n="716" who="S0525">mm</u>
<u n="717" who="S0615">mm oh I don't know it's not as if she hasn't got the time to</u>
<u n="718" who="S0525">well she hasn't said if she's coming to the christening has she?</u>
<u n="719" who="S0615">well no I don't know</u>
<u n="720" who="S0525">any of them haven't replied have they? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't</u>
<u n="721" who="S0615">oh no well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't reply but so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> texted them and said oh</u>
<u n="722" who="S0525">oh that's right pushed them and they said yes</u>
<u n="723" who="S0615">she better not just turn up with like a million bracelets or something I don't want them</u>
<u n="724" who="S0525" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="725" who="S0615">or like sparkles for the table or she can throw them <unclear>everywhere</unclear></u>
<u n="726" who="S0525">it's the fact she won't let you know it's the fact she just muscles in on everything</u>
<u n="727" who="S0615">I know that was exactly like it for the wedding like I gave her the tables I think I'd given her tables</u>
<u n="728" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="729" who="S0615">she'll like that and yes okay they they did contribute so she needed something</u>
<u n="730" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0615">but then it was like oh by the way I've bought this oh by the not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what do you think of this?</u>
<u n="732" who="S0525" trans="overlap">I know I know</u>
<u n="733" who="S0615">you know as the bride</u>
<u n="734" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="735" who="S0615">maybe oh well I've seen these what do you think or erm I've done you you know you know er do you think these would look nice or what are your thoughts on these?</u>
<u n="736" who="S0525">they're very manipulative that whole family is</u>
<u n="737" who="S0615" trans="overlap">oh yeah they are</u>
<u n="738" who="S0525">they're really manipulative</u>
<u n="739" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="740" who="S0525">everything that they do is geared to</u>
<u n="741" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="742" who="S0525">getting their own way and it's ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> really from the same family?</u>
<u n="743" who="S0615">well I know and I'm just like I mean he has</u>
<u n="744" who="S0525" trans="overlap">well I can't imagine <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like it he just puts up with her but</u>
<u n="745" who="S0615">yeah he does</u>
<u n="746" who="S0525">he never seems he never comes across as?</u>
<u n="747" who="S0615">no no he's quite a rare a rare breed</u>
<u n="748" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="749" who="S0615"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> putting up with that</u>
<u n="750" who="S0525">it's yeah it's just the way they use every situation like she did with the erm well the hen do she invited her own person didn't she? she invited her friend to the hen do</u>
<u n="751" who="S0615">yeah big <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="752" who="S0525">that's right and then the baby shower when she just forwarded the text and told me she'd invited people without even asking and now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s done this with the christening it's erm it's not on <trunc>i</trunc>it</u>
<u n="753" who="S0615">I mean yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> put it nicer than <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> put it</u>
<u n="754" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="755" who="S0615">but at the same time it was like well what on earth are we meant to say to that?</u>
<u n="756" who="S0525" trans="overlap">well yeah there's <unclear/></u>
<u n="757" who="S0615">obviously before she'd texted her back</u>
<u n="758" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="759" who="S0615">she'd been straight on to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and said</u>
<u n="760" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="761" who="S0615">oh have you had a text? and he'd obviously replied and said no</u>
<u n="762" who="S0525">yeah and that's why I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> asked you if you were if you had a problem with them having the baby boy because I think they obviously told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they weren't invited</u>
<u n="763" who="S0615" trans="overlap">oh of course yeah of course they told them</u>
<u n="764" who="S0525">straightaway so they think you've got an issue with them</u>
<u n="765" who="S0615">yeah yeah yeah yeah erm</u>
<u n="766" who="S0525">I think not the fact that you're trying to keep it down</u>
<u n="767" who="S0615" trans="overlap">and she's obviously I think she's annoyed with us</u>
<u n="768" who="S0525">oh on DVD <unclear/></u>
<u n="769" who="S0615" trans="overlap">mm yeah that'll be good er</u>
<u n="770" who="S0525">I want to see that one</u>
<u n="771" who="S0615">she's obviously I don't think she's erm offered to do anything for the christening because of that whole oh you're not inviting my whole family where you should think well you <unclear/></u>
<u n="772" who="S0525" trans="overlap">well her family are invited</u>
<u n="773" who="S0615">of course they are but it <trunc>wa</trunc> you know but they weren't originally</u>
<u n="774" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="775" who="S0615"><unclear/> and she obviously <unclear/></u>
<u n="776" who="S0525">well only <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you'd invited <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and</u>
<u n="777" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah exactly yeah I know and</u>
<u n="778" who="S0525"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and</u>
<u n="779" who="S0615">her and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="780" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="781" who="S0615">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can't come</u>
<u n="782" who="S0525">oh can't he?</u>
<u n="783" who="S0615">no he's been he's got some VIP concert experience and he's been waiting for thirty-five years to see this this band so</u>
<u n="784" who="S0525" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="785" who="S0615">yeah yeah I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went oh yeah great nice one <unclear/></u>
<u n="786" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah that's right the fewer of them that come the better</u>
<u n="787" who="S0615">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="788" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="789" who="S0615">he's also not like them</u>
<u n="790" who="S0525">no he's a bit more laid-back isn't he?</u>
<u n="791" who="S0615" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="792" who="S0525">is he he's her twin isn't he?</u>
<u n="793" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="794" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="795" who="S0615">he's alright <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="796" who="S0525">I was going to say why his wife doesn't bother with any of them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="797" who="S0615">well exactly you <trunc>a</trunc> you really can and I've said this to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I said well</u>
<u n="798" who="S0525">you've never met her have you?</u>
<u n="799" who="S0615">no I said you I said I know that you that that you think that it's the reason what happened was I think the whole reason behind it is they were in Florida one year and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had one day when they were erm I think they were just they were doing nothing or it was they'd had a day off from the parks or something</u>
<u n="800" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="801" who="S0615">and they were just sat in their rooms and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had asked <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> if erm he wanted to go on this boat ride</u>
<u n="802" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mhm</u>
<u n="803" who="S0615">but hadn't asked <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and so I don't like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> probably wasn't old enough at the time to think anything of it or was he? no I think he was about twelve erm so he he I think he just thought okay but then that was a massive problem that he hadn't asked <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well</u>
<u n="804" who="S0525" trans="overlap"><unclear/> for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="806" who="S0525">mm</u>
<u n="807" who="S0615">and so then I think she just said something to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s wife</u>
<u n="808" who="S0525">right</u>
<u n="809" who="S0615"><unclear/> just say it to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I don't know but anyway she had to say something to her and erm but that's the story that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been told and I'm thinking well why would she have a massive problem with them for that?</u>
<u n="810" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="811" who="S0615">erm but I think I think there's much more to it than that erm I I don't know what you know what she's done but</u>
<u n="812" who="S0525">it's funny cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> obviously knows the wife and met her years ago</u>
<u n="813" who="S0615">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="814" who="S0525">you should erm you should take <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> around or you'd probably get on with her if she was out of the situation</u>
<u n="815" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah definitely yeah</u>
<u n="816" who="S0525">of of all of the family</u>
<u n="817" who="S0615">and so that would what would that that would do to his mother?</u>
<u n="818" who="S0525">do you know where he lives? because if ever you were passing that way say</u>
<u n="819" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I don't know where he lives</u>
<u n="820" who="S0525">oh give give your uncle a call and see if we can call in cos his wife you know your auntie hasn't met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="821" who="S0615" trans="overlap">his <unclear/> like Birmingham to be honest so we <trunc>ne</trunc> we'd never pass there but erm</u>
<u n="822" who="S0525" trans="overlap">never be there but there'd be no reason not to and</u>
<u n="823" who="S0615" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="824" who="S0525">likewise she's perfectly pleasant and she's got her issues with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> well no everybody else has as well</u>
<u n="825" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="826" who="S0525">and you'd probably have er</u>
<u n="827" who="S0615">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="828" who="S0525">you'd probably get on fine</u>
<u n="829" who="S0615">yeah I think I mean I it is a bit I just</u>
<u n="830" who="S0525">it's got to be <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s fault cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is family</u>
<u n="831" who="S0615">oh yeah I just reckon I think it's a bit odd that she really doesn't have anything to do with any of them like and she'd like obviously you've had your fair share of</u>
<u n="832" who="S0525">grief</u>
<u n="833" who="S0615">the brunt from dad's side but</u>
<u n="834" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="835" who="S0615">I mean yes okay you won't go row with them every single time you see them but if there's ever kind of a a big thing like a big birthday or and everyone's going you you won't purposefully not go I mean you'll say oh do we have to? but</u>
<u n="836" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh yeah I'll always go to it</u>
<u n="837" who="S0615">of course you will but so that's something that she never you know never do this woman so</u>
<u n="838" who="S0525" trans="overlap">well that's what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s doing that's what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s trying to do</u>
<u n="839" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="840" who="S0525">stay out of everything</u>
<u n="841" who="S0615">yeah so then you think okay she could be a little bit like her because</u>
<u n="842" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="843" who="S0615">but then again <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s family are just they're just so oh everything is just</u>
<u n="844" who="S0525">well I don't know why <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants to be surrounded by them because she doesn't get on with any of them</u>
<u n="845" who="S0615">no</u>
<u n="846" who="S0525">I mean at your baby shower she didn't even speak to her sister</u>
<u n="847" who="S0615" trans="overlap">no I know</u>
<u n="848" who="S0525">who she personally invited</u>
<u n="849" who="S0615">I know it's awful</u>
<u n="850" who="S0525" trans="overlap">because I must admit I'd forgotten about inviting them and if she'd have said oh can we? I'd have gone yes of course</u>
<u n="851" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="852" who="S0525">but she sent me <trunc>t</trunc> I have I have invited them</u>
<u n="853" who="S0615" trans="overlap">why should you invite? them she's my</u>
<u n="854" who="S0525" trans="overlap">well yes yeah</u>
<u n="855" who="S0615">husband's auntie it's not like</u>
<u n="856" who="S0525">nothing to do with you no you're right</u>
<u n="857" who="S0615">no nothing to do with me whatsoever</u>
<u n="858" who="S0525">oh look they're on the trampettes on there I need to get mine back out <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="859" who="S0615">but erm yeah I know because there's no connection with me and them whatsoever</u>
<u n="860" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="861" who="S0615">erm I don't you know particularly get on with them and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can't I mean every <trunc>t</trunc> every time we go out for any sort of family get-together you know after it's like hours of oh well you know all this and you just think oh</u>
<u n="862" who="S0525" trans="overlap">she just competes with her sister for who can do the most erm</u>
<u n="863" who="S0615" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="864" who="S0525">outrageous presents for everybody and it's just a competition anyway and I know that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="865" who="S0615" trans="overlap">presents are the competition</u>
<u n="866" who="S0525">yeah like <unclear/> why she wanted them there and then and and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't eat a single thing did she?</u>
<u n="867" who="S0615">no</u>
<u n="868" who="S0525">oh not for me thank you oh not but in the end I just bypassed her and not <unclear/></u>
<u n="869" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah bye yeah not for you</u>
<u n="870" who="S0525">not for you not for me thank you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="871" who="S0615">oh dear</u>
<u n="872" who="S0525">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> made a big sigh and I thought well you've invited them and she got wasted didn't she? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="873" who="S0615">that's what she's going to do at the christening and I'll say well bring your own wine if you want to do that</u>
<u n="874" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh well if she's gonna bring her own hopefully she won't bring that much and she'll be alright</u>
<u n="875" who="S0615">mm she'll drink everyone else's</u>
<u n="876" who="S0525">I won't bring any red</u>
<u n="877" who="S0615">no no</u>
<u n="878" who="S0525">because that's all she drinks</u>
<u n="879" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="880" who="S0525">I'm only taking white</u>
<u n="881" who="S0615">erm no definitely</u>
<u n="882" who="S0525">do we have to provide glasses or? okay</u>
<u n="883" who="S0615">no no no they're all there</u>
<u n="884" who="S0525">she'll have the glasses if we want like a Prosecco and a toast or something</u>
<u n="885" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah they will be there</u>
<u n="886" who="S0525">will she? because we should maybe</u>
<u n="887" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I'll text her about that</u>
<u n="888" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="889" who="S0615">but yeah they've done like all the</u>
<u n="890" who="S0525">but you could also mention on the invite to your friends nearer the time you know</u>
<u n="891" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="892" who="S0525">it is it's it's a it's a bring a bottle</u>
<u n="893" who="S0615">yeah yeah yeah I will do <pause dur="long"/> oh</u>
<u n="894" who="S0525">cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like to get through their drinks as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="895" who="S0615">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="896" who="S0525"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does yeah</u>
<u n="897" who="S0615">not in the middle of the day though not on a like a</u>
<u n="898" who="S0525">well it's a Sunday evening it's four o'clock yeah</u>
<u n="899" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah they'll bring their own mm fun fun fun <pause dur="short"/> well I'm planning in the on that Sunday morning to go and put some things out like I'll get a few blue balloons or something and if I do this</u>
<u n="900" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh okay and decorate it a bit</u>
<u n="901" who="S0615">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> a play corner for the babies <pause dur="short"/> down there</u>
<u n="902" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what's going in the play corner?</u>
<u n="903" who="S0615">toys</u>
<u n="904" who="S0525">oh</u>
<u n="905" who="S0615">toys toys toys</u>
<u n="906" who="S0525">okay yeah will there be somewhere to put them?</u>
<u n="907" who="S0615">yeah yeah yeah I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> leave a corner free</u>
<u n="908" who="S0525">to lie them but what can you lie them on?</u>
<u n="909" who="S0615">I'm gonna take some blankets</u>
<u n="910" who="S0525">oh okay</u>
<u n="911" who="S0615">it'll be alright</u>
<u n="912" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="913" who="S0615">perfect</u>
<u n="914" who="S0525">that'll be nice if we can go outside as well well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can take his football can't he?</u>
<u n="915" who="S0615">yes</u>
<u n="916" who="S0525">he'll be happy</u>
<u n="917" who="S0615">yes he can</u>
<u n="918" who="S0525">it's a nice venue actually the way she's got it <pause dur="short"/> well it's quite</u>
<u n="919" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah it is nice</u>
<u n="920" who="S0525">isn't this a shame watching all these newborn lambs and we're all going to eat them at Easter?</u>
<u n="921" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I know yeah yeah</u>
<u n="922" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="923" who="S0615" trans="overlap">it's sad isn't it?</u>
<u n="924" who="S0525" trans="overlap">all these lovely lambs being born but yes</u>
<u n="925" who="S0615">oh yeah</u>
<u n="926" who="S0525">did you see the one they did this morning? she had triplets</u>
<u n="927" who="S0615">no</u>
<u n="928" who="S0525">but this was really unusual for a lamb but then they announced that the mum had died</u>
<u n="929" who="S0615">oh</u>
<u n="930" who="S0525">yeah but there's three they're the three black ones they've got there</u>
<u n="931" who="S0615">oh really?</u>
<u n="932" who="S0525">two boys and a girl yeah</u>
<u n="933" who="S0615">oh</u>
<u n="934" who="S0525">but the mum died</u>
<u n="935" who="S0615">it's yeah</u>
<u n="936" who="S0525">couldn't cope with all three</u>
<u n="937" who="S0615">mm</u>
<u n="938" who="S0525" trans="overlap">it's a shame</u>
<u n="939" who="S0615">oh look at them</u>
<u n="940" who="S0525">mm</u>
<u n="941" who="S0615">oh no I don't think that could work for me</u>
<u n="942" who="S0525">yeah I'll have to get some Easter eggs for er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I suppose and I don't know if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants one</u>
<u n="943" who="S0615">oh yeah oh well ask her the day before</u>
<u n="944" who="S0525">yes she hasn't replied to whether she wants tea tonight</u>
<u n="945" who="S0615">oh okay</u>
<u n="946" who="S0525">I told her what it was so she's got in a fighting chance of</u>
<u n="947" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="948" who="S0525">she liked it last time she had it</u>
<u n="949" who="S0615">oh okay well she might not like it this time</u>
<u n="950" who="S0525" trans="overlap">this time no no that's right <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> sure</u>
<u n="951" who="S0615">yes don't want that yuck</u>
<u n="952" who="S0525">she might go to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s if she's erm <pause dur="short"/> not working tomorrow</u>
<u n="953" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="954" who="S0525">she's gone on the train anyway her car's still on the drive</u>
<u n="955" who="S0615">oh <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>we</trunc>well she'd be in touch with dad then later won't she? pick me up please <pause dur="short"/> I just need to get home somehow</u>
<u n="956" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she can walk it'll be easier as well when the clocks change in a couple of weeks</u>
<u n="957" who="S0615">right <pause dur="short"/> yes well <pause dur="short"/> they do don't they?</u>
<u n="958" who="S0525">has he had to?</u>
<u n="959" who="S0615" trans="overlap">forward</u>
<u n="960" who="S0525">has he got to wake up now too much sleep?</u>
<u n="961" who="S0615">well he's had two hours</u>
<u n="962" who="S0525">he's had two hours has he?</u>
<u n="963" who="S0615">yes I think that's my cut off point <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="964" who="S0525">you're coming out <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> how snuggly you are in there</u>
<u n="965" who="S0615" trans="overlap"><unclear/> everyone</u>
<u n="966" who="S0525">it's time to wake up <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="967" who="S0615">oh <pause dur="short"/> it's alright don't try and sit</u>
<u n="968" who="S0525" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> don't try and sit</u>
<u n="969" who="S0615">trying to sit</u>
<u n="970" who="S0525" trans="overlap">we we weren't you know you were saying about when I was talking about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> going on her trip to Canada?</u>
<u n="971" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="972" who="S0525">and you were saying oh yeah I'd love it I'd like to do that erm I thought oh we'll never get the chance to do all that together cos <trunc>yo</trunc>you only get some school holidays <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="973" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="974" who="S0525">always working especially Christmas time</u>
<u n="975" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="976" who="S0525">then she won't wanna pay premium in February</u>
<u n="977" who="S0615">no</u>
<u n="978" who="S0525">so</u>
<event desc="sound of baby"/>
<u n="979" who="S0615">oh</u>
<u n="980" who="S0525">he says well mum you've woken me up what do you want me to do? stick a dummy in my mouth</u>
<u n="981" who="S0615">well just calm for a minute while I take that off <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="982" who="S0525" trans="overlap">it's a nice snug fit <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="983" who="S0615">well <unclear>we'll do</unclear> other things and <pause dur="short"/> when he's older then</u>
<u n="984" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="985" who="S0615">I won't be a teacher forever <pause dur="long"/> no I don't reckon I'll <pause dur="short"/> stick it out forever no way</u>
<u n="986" who="S0525">don't you think?</u>
<u n="987" who="S0615">it's not one for <pause dur="short"/> family and work life balance I don't think</u>
<u n="988" who="S0525">but you get all the summer holidays</u>
<u n="989" who="S0615">yeah I know but</u>
<u n="990" who="S0525">that's a massive plus</u>
<u n="991" who="S0615">oh of course but</u>
<u n="992" who="S0525">if you can get it down to doing less work in between classes cos that's where it all comes from</u>
<u n="993" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="994" who="S0525">it's the it's all the extra</u>
<u n="995" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah but it's it's either you <pause dur="short"/> you do a really good job of it or you</u>
<u n="996" who="S0525">mm</u>
<u n="997" who="S0615">do cut down and then you don't do such a good job of it</u>
<u n="998" who="S0525">yeah I suppose</u>
<u n="999" who="S0615">and I'm not really agreeing with where the whole <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>I</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> well industry and where the education sector is going and it's all it's all geared towards running businesses now where running schools are concerned it's not <pause dur="short"/> I just keep thinking oh I couldn't imagine working for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in a school <pause dur="short"/> could you imagine?</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0525">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> I wonder how long she'll carry on work for?</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0615">oh well she's got to compete with her sister who's already retired</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0525">is her sister sister older?</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0615">five years</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0525">oh is she?</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0615">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh there we go</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0525">yeah did she retire at fifty-five then?</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0615">I think so</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0525">fifty-six maybe</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0615">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yep <pause dur="short"/> cos I don't when's is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sixty next year?</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0525">oh is he? is he fifty-nine at the end of this month?</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0615">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will be <trunc>twen</trunc> or is it two years? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will no I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will be twenty-nine in August <pause dur="short"/> and then because they both turn they she turns thirty and he turns sixty</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0525">in the same year next year</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0615">and so there'll be some sort of holiday</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0525" trans="overlap">you may not be invited</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0615">we we won't be invited I know that for sure</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0525">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1019" who="S0615">no we won't be <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it'll be a shame <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether they'll go anywhere the four of them this year</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0525">we'll have to do Florida would be nice we'll have to do it when</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0525">when you're on maternity leave next</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0615">maternity leave next what so I've oh yeah after I've had the baby?</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0525">er either way yeah oh yeah you wanna go on rides</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0615"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I wanna go on them</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0525">yeah when you'd when you have so we'd have a baby and and a toddler won't we <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? yes</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0615">wa wa wa wa wa</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0525" trans="overlap">the innocent go and feed the alligators</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0615">mm oh</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0525">what does his top say?</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0615">handsome little fella just like daddy</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1033" who="S0615">oh a big yawn do you want some milk?</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0525">he said oh I'm just waking up</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0615">I know that but do we want milk when we've finished waking up?</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1037" who="S0615"><unclear/> so we best prepare</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0525">very true</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0615">do you want this? <unclear/> are you just you know waking up? that's it there we go</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0525">let's hope you're gonna like having er water on your head in the church <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you better be on your best behaviour you like the water don't you?</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0525">oh you were gonna go swimming today</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0615">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0525">were you gonna go with erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> still?</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0615" trans="overlap">maybe I'll go with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on Thursday</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0525">ah yes</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I'll text <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and see what she's doing</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0525">good idea Auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can go</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0615" trans="overlap">and take Auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and see what she's doing on Thursday and we'll go swimming</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1051" who="S0615"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1052" who="S0525" trans="overlap">I can come and watch again</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0615">oh yes</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0525">and start shouting my mummy's dropping you</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0615">dumping you in the water ah right oh so much fun</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0525">ah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has still got his cold</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0615">oh dear</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0525">she says he can't hear a thing he's all bunged up and she goes it's so annoying <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1059" who="S0615"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1060" who="S0525">well they had parents' evening and erm you know what's his name? the Mr the PE teacher? <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="1061" who="S0615"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0525">you know was was talking about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't do the cross-country last <trunc>Tues</trunc> last Monday</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0615">oh okay</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0525">he said</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0615" trans="overlap">what because of the cold?</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0525">no he said he'd forgotten his shoes</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0615" trans="overlap">oh oh</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0525">which he might have done but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thought he he was getting a bit worn out with it all</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0525">and we had said maybe give the cross-county a miss anyway so he hadn't done it so Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> had made some comment about you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> isn't dedicated he really needs to put the time in and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said erm she said it was just banter with him</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0525">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said well actually <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is thinking of not taking PE he's thinking of taking art instead</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0615"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1074" who="S0525">and he just went oh really I hear art's quite hard to do with two broken arms</u>
<u n="1075" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1076" who="S0615">okay</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0525" trans="overlap">the PE <unclear/></u>
<u n="1078" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1079" who="S0615">oh I must say</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0525" trans="overlap">and I said blimey and that's how that's how parents' evening went for PE</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0615">lovely yes</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0525" trans="overlap">it was it was must for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> come on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> coming to nanny? hello sweetheart hello little look at</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0615" trans="overlap">shall we have some milk?</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0525">you eh?</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0615">hi</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0525"><trunc>n</trunc>nanny's here yeah yeah are you wanting some milk? say go on mum</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0615">yes I think so</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0525">go and make me a bottle go and make me a bottle</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0615">please may I have some milk?</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0525">oh you are so snuggly and cuddly aren't you?</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0615"><unclear/> am I cuddly?</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0525">you are</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0615">are you?</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0525">you are snuggly</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0615">are you?</u>
<u n="1096" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1097" who="S0615">yes yes I am <unclear/></u>
<u n="1098" who="S0525">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oh you're gorgeous yes you are yes nanny's little baby nanny's little baby mm</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0615">do you want a drink while I'm in here?</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0525">oh yes put the kettle on and I'll have a cup of coffee thank you very much what time are you making your stuffed mushrooms?</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0615">mummy's getting hungry</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0525">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oh sweetheart let's have a look eh what have you been up to today eh? what have you been up to today? you've had a long sleep you've been walking with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> haven't you? you have you what are you doing mm? say come on mummy make that milk come on mummy and make that milk eh are you ready for something to eat? yes yes</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
