<text id="SJJK">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:52:15</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-23</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0618 S0619</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In a newly-opened bistro in Tarnow, Poland</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>The newly-opened bistro, addiction, identity, dreams, fitness, friendships, shops, periods. </topics>
		<activity>Two friends talking about various topics (see 9 above) in a newly-opened bistro in Tarnow, Poland.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0618">
				<exactage>42</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge/Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months on and off</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>unemployed/ Some part-time private TEFL teacher/ Semi-retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0619">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury, Lancashire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Nort West: Lancs, Greater Manchester</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>nearly 4 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher of English as a foreign Language</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0619">oh hello</u>
<u n="2" who="S0618">so <vocal desc="laugh"/> right so yes anyway talking about erm yeah <pause dur="short"/> coffee</u>
<u n="3" who="S0619">but I think places like this <pause dur="short"/> in this part of Poland I just get the impression they spend a lot of their money on the design and all this that and the other but no one comes either because they don't know it's here mm and I just think eating out in general is not a thing done by people unless they have loads and loads of money and if you had loads and loads of money you wouldn't come here and I don't think it's very close to schools either so I I imagine it would attract lots of teenagers but I don't know where the nearest school is</u>
<u n="4" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is next door to Lidl's car park so they might get</u>
<u n="5" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> with parking facilities definitely</u>
<u n="6" who="S0618">yeah they might get the</u>
<u n="7" who="S0619">people wandering in</u>
<u n="8" who="S0618">yeah I mean I would pop in for a coffee when I'm Lidling and actually I would be really happy to meet you here if you fancied a coffee I just hope the next one is not in a paper cup <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's a little bit disappointing when everything else is so nice and nice fit out nice design nice coffee</u>
<u n="9" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> really nice <pause dur="short"/> we could have our own cups <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0618">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah we could do <vocal desc="laugh"/> you could just buy one in Lidl <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0619">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> well I was going to say keep them behind the bar</u>
<u n="12" who="S0618">a pound's worth of mug just pop it in there it would good <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0619">we could write our names on them</u>
<u n="14" who="S0618">yeah my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he lives near Brisbane in Australia he's erm his local coffee shop has his cup there and when he he sits there and passes the time of day with them the morning drinking his morning coffee and when he's finished he goes round the back and washes it up ready for tomorrow</u>
<u n="15" who="S0619" trans="overlap">that's nice <pause dur="short"/> that's nice and puts it <pause dur="short"/> yeah when I work in <anon type="place"/> we always have cups and we have got to write our names on them because otherwise people you know will start using each other's cups so we started doing it with pen permanent pen and it would just wash off you know you just er rub it off with your finger and use the cup so then we did it with nail varnish and that was slightly more effective</u>
<u n="16" who="S0618" trans="overlap">that doesn't last though does it? <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> okay oh that's a good hint</u>
<u n="17" who="S0619">yeah write your name on it in nail varnish</u>
<u n="18" who="S0618">so nail varnish survives the washing up?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0619">but I would still just use someone else's cup anyway</u>
<u n="20" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0619">I don't think it matters yes so confession time a strange confession <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0618">mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0619">I think I need to tell somebody</u>
<u n="24" who="S0618">okay that's your Catholic upbringing</u>
<u n="25" who="S0619">but for the last or two or so years I've had this weird addiction to this medication and I've decided to stop taking this medication it's not a physical addiction in that there's nothing chemically inside this medication that makes you need to take it it's like a psychological addiction to it where if you <pause dur="short"/> it's basically to do with like decongestion and noses and it's one of these things where the more you take it when you stop using it the more the symptoms the original symptoms are worse so it gets worse and worse and it's been like two years and I imagine it's what it's like if you start taking loads and loads of drugs like the inside of your nose is sore it's bleeding to the point where it scratches <unclear/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> uhu <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> okay cold relief <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> you've got that now?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0618">oh okay</u>
<u n="29" who="S0619">and I'm starting to think eventually my nose is just going to like fall off <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0618">fall off <vocal desc="laugh"/> so you might think okay yeah so you're going to look like you're a a coke head</u>
<u n="31" who="S0619">yeah a coke addict yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0618">like a big hole in it or something yeah okay</u>
<u n="33" who="S0619">so you know which is why me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went to buy that sort of nose inside nose washer <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0618">oh you didn't go and get it?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0619">no we did we did</u>
<u n="36" who="S0618">oh you did okay</u>
<u n="37" who="S0619">and I'm hoping that with a mixture of that and sort of willpower I will be able to break this habit but I was googling it I've googled it in the past I googled it again today and it's like loads of people are saying I've been addicted to this for ten years</u>
<u n="38" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh wow well if people have been addicted for ten years presumably their noses haven't fallen off</u>
<u n="39" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they are still attached to their face</u>
<u n="40" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0619">but I'm just trying to break this habit so it's really awful because it means that I can't breathe through my nose until I learn to breathe again without relying on medication to help me breathe so it's just going to be</u>
<u n="42" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh no okay <pause dur="short"/> the people on this site said how long it's taken before their nose gets back to normal?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0619">they are saying like a few weeks but people are sort of going on it <pause dur="short"/> the people who are writing on this forum that when they start and I sort of think if they are not writing about it sort of weeks later then it must be because it's a positive because you would only write about something if it's negative</u>
<u n="44" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> if it's yeah if it's a problem yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0619">yeah so I'm hoping that in a couple of weeks</u>
<u n="46" who="S0618">yeah that you will be alright again</u>
<u n="47" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0618">that's cool</u>
<u n="49" who="S0619">so it's rubbish</u>
<u n="50" who="S0618">in the meantime yeah that saline stuff probably wouldn't hurt and also steam baths sticking your head over a bowl of hot water with a towel possibly with some baking soda or salty stuff Epsom salts I don't know can you breathe them in?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah we've had salts <pause dur="short"/> yeah they had something like really you know like menthol like type things</u>
<u n="52" who="S0618">well Vicks is good but by god it makes you blind if you are not careful <vocal desc="laugh"/> if you accidentally open your eyes when you are breathing it in</u>
<u n="53" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I'm just I'm hoping that sort of fresh air and being distracted and I think something like that will help <pause dur="short"/> it's worse at night but</u>
<u n="54" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well good for you my god you are a woman on a mission you are really clearing out everything that's toxic in your life aren't you? it's like tick next</u>
<u n="55" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> I know and I feel like if I do it all at the same time I'm just going to implode the lot</u>
<u n="56" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> booze yeah man yeah nasal stuff yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> the inside of my brain</u>
<u n="58" who="S0618">what's next?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0619">yeah I know</u>
<u n="60" who="S0618">yeah good for you though just I suppose new year new beginnings it's erm yeah I mean you can recreate yourself at any time</u>
<u n="61" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah exactly</u>
<u n="62" who="S0618">yeah I was listening to last Sunday's Johnnie Walker's Sounds of the Seventies when I was cooking this morning and it was really interesting the first hour was dedicated to David Bowie and there were interviews with him sort of talking about inventing himself and becoming the character and things like that which I thought was just really interesting and quite wonderful and it sounds like he got a bit confused at some times as to whether he really was that character which of course he was if he was acting the role then of course he was <pause dur="short"/> but I suppose equally it sort of opens up for all of us the idea that we can be whoever we want to be and we can perform a role in life that we want to perform be the character we want to be so there's nothing false about it it's just do it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah me and my friend have talked about this before where sort of if you're <vocal desc="sigh"/> if you are acting for want of a better word erm is it a good thing or a bad thing? and will you eventually become that person who you are acting as? but if you are acting as it then it's because you are already that person</u>
<u n="64" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> you already are yeah it's a bit like people who affect a silly laugh and then after a while that is their laugh <vocal desc="laugh"/> it sort of stops becoming ironic and amusing and just becomes</u>
<u n="65" who="S0619">mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> your laugh</u>
<u n="66" who="S0618">your laugh that people then take the piss out of because it's amusing so yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0619">so I don't know</u>
<u n="68" who="S0618">yeah interesting now I think my view is that as human beings we're dynamic changing evolving there is no this is me it's <pause dur="short"/> you know you are as you are in the moment so be who you wanna be man you know</u>
<u n="69" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm we shall see anyway anyway anyway I'm just a bit <unclear>er</unclear> at the moment but I'm trying to stay I'm positive I am positive about the future but it is just like</u>
<u n="70" who="S0618">are you positive about now?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0619">I am I am positive about now</u>
<u n="72" who="S0618">that'll do</u>
<u n="73" who="S0619"><trunc>an</trunc> and in terms of the future I'm kind of thinking god do I have to do all of these things all of the time? it's so exhausting <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0618">no you don't you just do it now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0619">yeah just do it now don't think about it</u>
<u n="76" who="S0618">exactly just do it now yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0619">that's good yes</u>
<u n="78" who="S0618">yeah the future doesn't really exist anyway so yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I've been struggling again with not being on alcohol and I'm almost desperate for January to end so I can have some alcohol <vocal desc="laugh"/> but it's kind of <pause dur="short"/> I'm a bit concerned really it's highlighted to me that perhaps there's a deeper issue there and I'm starting to feel I think I said to you the other day that something changed something clicked in me a few days ago and I feel like a whole different person and that's carrying on and I really do I'm getting more energy now I'm starting to feel really good and I wonder if part of that is detoxing</u>
<u n="79" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well yes and what's the date today? it's like what the twenty-third?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0618">twenty-<trunc>se</trunc> twenty-third it's my nephew's birthday</u>
<u n="81" who="S0619">yeah so it's twenty-one days to break a habit</u>
<u n="82" who="S0618">is it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0619">possibly <vocal desc="laugh"/> or twenty-eight</u>
<u n="84" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0619">or a hundred and two I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0618">oh I meant to send you those</u>
<u n="87" who="S0619">twenty-one days to break a habit I'm sure that's true</u>
<u n="88" who="S0618">Abraham-Hicks thing on Facebook the other day basically saying people say it takes thirty days twenty-eight days twenty-one days whatever to break a habit but actually it only takes a moment because there's only now so you have broken it now erm yeah I was going to send that to you I forgot I might have photographed it actually let's see if I can show you that without bollocksing up the recording let's have a look <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah it's still recording that's good okay camera roll yeah I did here are look oh no that's not the one okay <pause dur="long"/> is it that one? no it's not that one <vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="89" who="S0619">he's got a lot of interesting things to say <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0618">no no I didn't save it to my phone</u>
<u n="91" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well if this twenty-one day thing is true then you know you by now we should be feeling the positive effects</u>
<u n="92" who="S0618">yeah but you know I do wonder if I've got <pause dur="short"/> about the psychological addiction because it's not really a physical addiction anymore because after a few weeks it's sort of out of my system so it's only psychological addiction I'm thinking now maybe I need to not drink in February as well but then I think well <vocal desc="laugh"/> let's have a really big binge on the first of February <vocal desc="laugh"/> but then I would probably be pissed on half a shandy so we will see</u>
<u n="93" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> I used to think or I used to do when I was at uni kind of I wouldn't drink really very much at all for a few weeks or a few months and then have a massive binge and realise why I wasn't drinking</u>
<u n="94" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but then you can stop again</u>
<u n="95" who="S0619">it's like a second wind oh yeah there's another month <pause dur="short"/> erm I could easily do another month not drinking just because I don't think anything good comes of it erm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0619">because then I'm relying so heavily on some of the negative experiences at the end of December I'm just you know you are using them to my advantage which is why I don't want that to happen again <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to be that oh yeah I don't want <pause dur="long"/> yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> you don't want to be <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0619">well no it's not that I don't want to be that person because that's putting it on me and I don't think it's me</u>
<u n="100" who="S0618">mm well you still have a role to play in any situation</u>
<u n="101" who="S0619">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0618">so in some form if not in the physical world then at least in some sort of vibrational level you've invited a challenge at some level</u>
<u n="103" who="S0619">uhu yeah yeah so</u>
<u n="104" who="S0618">and in a way if you think about how good you are feeling now maybe you can <pause dur="short"/> I don't know maybe it will take a bit longer but at some point you might be able to look back on December and say oh my god best thing that ever happened</u>
<u n="105" who="S0619">thank you it changed yeah it changed something</u>
<u n="106" who="S0618">yeah yeah that's really cool</u>
<u n="107" who="S0619">yeah yeah yeah so <pause dur="short"/> but it is I think not drinking because we've been talking about barriers so much not drinking puts a huge barrier around you in some ways erm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0618">mm how much of that is real and how much of that is psychological?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0619">I don't know in terms of people don't <pause dur="short"/> well certain people especially don't want anything to do with you</u>
<u n="110" who="S0618">mm you don't get invited to parties or</u>
<u n="111" who="S0619">yeah or yeah at the same time you don't want to go to parties sometimes because it will be more miserable or you enjoy yourself you don't want to bring other people down I don't know it's kind of a combination of things</u>
<u n="112" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I really struggled when we went bowling I felt so boring that's why I went home when you all went on to play pool in town but I realised that you know <vocal desc="sigh"/> I think that was just where I was at at the time and part of the detox process possibly I'm quite capable of carrying a party head on dancing the night away and being stone-cold sober but in that moment I wasn't so <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I do wonder if a big bit of me kind of reaches the point where I think no I'm not really into this scene anymore you know at some point somebody always arrives with a tray of shots and that sometimes leads to another tray of shots and there have been times in my life when that's a fantastic thing keep it rolling let's go yeah yeah yeah but for the most part I kind of think actually no I don't want to be in that scene <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's not such fun <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I kind of think drugs are better from that viewpoint because <vocal desc="laugh"/> you don't have a stinking hangover in the morning</u>
<u n="113" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> no I don't</u>
<u n="114" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0619">I could keep this up for another month just because I've really sort of riding this wave of everything is okay and especially because we are on holiday as well it's sort of helped I thought it would be rubbish being on holiday and not being able to drink but actually it's been a bit of a godsend in a way because you can do things</u>
<u n="116" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> you can get out for a walk you can get to the gym</u>
<u n="117" who="S0619">yeah your days are so much longer because erm you are not I don't know lying in bed hungover or you've got the energy to get up in the morning</u>
<u n="118" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah you can enjoy the daylight enjoy the fresh air go out for a day trip</u>
<u n="119" who="S0619">yeah and we've done we've done so much I mean I'm not saying if we had er <pause dur="short"/> if I had been on loads of nights out that wouldn't have happened it would have just happened but I would have you know been drinking the next day to to keep my spirits up or whatever</u>
<u n="120" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and perhaps on a teaching week you'd be more likely to be out on a Friday night or out on a Saturday night or even out on a Thursday night so yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so it's nice</u>
<u n="122" who="S0618">it's kind of taken the pressure off Thursday Friday Saturday eve for not being drinking nights</u>
<u n="123" who="S0619">I thought today was Monday</u>
<u n="124" who="S0618">because we meet up in the week</u>
<u n="125" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0618">yeah that's true I need to remember it is Saturday for the bus timetable</u>
<u n="127" who="S0619">I have no idea what's going on at all</u>
<u n="128" who="S0618">oh shit I've done that before <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh that was just after New Year when I was back and I walked into town and was waiting for this bus back and it was like minus seventeen or something ridiculous and I had been at this bus stop and I thought oh thank god only five minutes to the bus and I waited and waited and waited and waited and then I realised fuck it's Saturday and it was more than half an hour oh no I'm never ever doing that again so I'm quite <pause dur="short"/> yeah remember to look what day it is</u>
<u n="129" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh my god <pause dur="short"/> oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0618">but no feeling good and I keep having these dreams last night's dream was wonderful and I quite often dream about buildings or houses and I'm exploring them or I'm renovating them and I look on these as part of my psyche or different aspects of self and the dream <pause dur="short"/> I'm also having lots of kitten dreams I told you about that</u>
<u n="131" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah you said yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0618">which I think is sort of my higher self saying it's time to have some fun because I associate kittens with fun and laying on the ground and rolling around on the floor and playing basically so there's I feel like I feel a lot more light-hearted than I've felt in a while so I'm feeling a bit more kittenish but I think I probably am attracting kittens as well so I expect some cats to be arriving soon little cats <pause dur="short"/> but yeah so a couple of nights ago I had this dream and I was kind of in this big mansion and at the top of the hallway and it was mine my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was painting and she had done this purpley turquoise colour which is impossible but it's possible in dreamland and she had painted a bit over the white ceiling oh fuck she's gone over the line never mind I will do that again when she's gone home when it's dried and then opposite that I was doing a turquoisey colour and there was a mirror there and I had friends around all helping which was really nice <pause dur="short"/> but it just felt really warm homely the mirror was reflecting the light and it was great and this one last night I was in this massive mansion again and it was really old fashioned with old fashioned sofas and things and I went into a room I'd never been in before and opened all of the massive dusty curtains and it was a big high ceiling room there were windows all about so I was letting light in again so I think this is all quite symbolic and there was a guy on the outside riding his bike and with every sort of second foot it went <vocal desc="misc"/> on the bike <vocal desc="misc"/> so I knew he was there and I felt a bit threatened by him but it was almost like well I need to take the risk if I'm to let light in that there might be some nastiness out there but you know I can see it all and it's only my perception that there might be nastiness maybe it will maybe it won't who knows? and a friend of mine was with me there as well and she's actually a painter and decorator for a living so there's almost that sort of freshening up renovating sort of theme going on again so that's two dreams with painting and decorating and renovating light letting light in in kind of the darkened rooms of my psyche so bring it on</u>
<u n="133" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> uhu <pause dur="short"/> that was nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> uhu <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> uhu <pause dur="short"/> very nice <pause dur="short"/> good good good keep clearing out keep changing keep renovating</u>
<u n="134" who="S0618">yeah and physically I had a bloody good clear out yesterday with you know everybody has got that junk drawer well I've I've got junk shoe boxes and the junk wooden box and I cleared all of those out yesterday and just got two metal box things to go and that's all of the real junk junk tackled so I'm going to do that today</u>
<u n="135" who="S0619">oh easy-peasy yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes I'm feeling good</u>
<u n="136" who="S0618">hey</u>
<u n="137" who="S0619">yeah just happy happy</u>
<u n="138" who="S0618">that's good</u>
<u n="139" who="S0619">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> with a <pause dur="short"/> it's a sort of leading quite a simple life at the moment but it's quite nice</u>
<u n="140" who="S0618">simple is good as well</u>
<u n="141" who="S0619">you don't need to be doing and drinking and</u>
<u n="142" who="S0618">but you aren't doing</u>
<u n="143" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0618">because you are gyming</u>
<u n="145" who="S0619">yeah man</u>
<u n="146" who="S0618">are you walking?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0619">I had a lovely gym this morning it was so nice</u>
<u n="148" who="S0618">good what did you do this morning?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0619">I'm just trying to work out what is really the best thing to do if I've got this man for two hours a week and it's really sort of intense heavy stuff that takes up time to recover and some time to sort of build up to I don't want to be doing too much sort of lifting stuff on my own</u>
<u n="150" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah you need more aerobic stuff than to stretch you out</u>
<u n="151" who="S0619">yeah so I was just doing lots of yeah cycling and climbing endless stairs <vocal desc="laugh"/> climbing and climbing and then lots of stretching as well because I haven't sort of been stretching since before summer</u>
<u n="152" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> mm stretching is amazing <pause dur="short"/> I love stretching</u>
<u n="153" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah and I hate it's been miserable no it doesn't make me miserable I'm not very good at it so I need to practise practise and practise it's one of those sort of things where your body really responds to it quite quickly but you have to do it you have to do it a lot or otherwise your body won't learn</u>
<u n="154" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and breathe I think stretching in particular breath is so very important <pause dur="short"/> yeah they say that in yoga if your body is struggling your natural instinct is to hold your breath but what you really need to breathe through breathe deeply through it yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah you need to breathe through <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="156" who="S0618">yeah don't forget to breathe it sounds so stupid but people just do <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu <pause dur="short"/> yeah so it's been nice and I've been listening to podcasts and stuff while I'm cycling away it's really nice</u>
<u n="158" who="S0618">good</u>
<u n="159" who="S0619">to have someone chatting away in my ears</u>
<u n="160" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> coming in your ears <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> coming in your ears <pause dur="short"/> still so funny</u>
<u n="162" who="S0618"><unclear/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I've had a lot of the Sounds of the Seventies on the radio Iplayer I didn't realise cos I maybe it's my favourite I loved Johnnie Walker I didn't realise there are three that I haven't heard so that's three weeks I haven't been listening to it I thought where have I been? what have I been doing to not listen to it? but so I had a couple last night while I was tidying out the junk shoe boxes and the junk boxes and the one today which was the Bowie one when I was cooking it's just I love it it's <pause dur="short"/> and I have realised I was <pause dur="short"/> when I walked here today it took me about an hour and a quarter and I was just playing music all the way and really into it music really moves me incredibly so and I think seventies music in particular you know seventies rock disco whatever it might be a bit of ska today as well er a bit of reggae it's just brilliant erm and through my walking as well it just <pause dur="short"/> I don't know literally you see you don't really feel like you are exercising you just are on another plain it's just wonderful but it did strike me listening to my Ipod on random I don't seem to have any eighties stuff I don't know why</u>
<u n="163" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> sort it out</u>
<u n="164" who="S0618">and I like eighties I do like it so I've got seventies and then I've got a little bit of nineties and a lot of noughties <pause dur="short"/> mm and a bit of sixties</u>
<u n="165" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu <pause dur="short"/> I was sweating so much this morning I forgot my towel because I put it in the wash after my last workout erm because it was disgusting</u>
<u n="166" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh no <pause dur="short"/> have you only got one towel?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0619">yeah only one gym towel that's like that sort of not so big but it you know drowning you <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was just really you know dripping down onto the machine you know everything was wet my arms were wet my face er because I sort of had my head down climbing these stairs so I didn't fall over I was just <pause dur="short"/> you know when you are sort of breathing and oh just spray sweat everywhere I was just oh that spray I need to go and get some tissue</u>
<u n="168" who="S0618">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> everywhere lovely <pause dur="short"/> there's something quite satisfactory about that though quite enjoyable</u>
<u n="169" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it is also this sort of detox you are getting rid of stuff not just getting rid of that's just mainly from my forehead <vocal desc="laugh"/> straight out straight everywhere</u>
<u n="170" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah why not? it's all good</u>
<u n="171" who="S0619">is that two o'clock? how has that happened?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0618">ah it's magic it doesn't exist anyway</u>
<u n="173" who="S0619">it does</u>
<u n="174" who="S0618">it doesn't it's now</u>
<u n="175" who="S0619">oh god there's so much to do</u>
<u n="176" who="S0618">the time is now what have you got to do?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0619">I'm kidding I don't have anything to do <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0618">there you go <vocal desc="laugh"/> don't worry about it it's all good</u>
<u n="179" who="S0619">yes so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I don't know not a clue I will text her</u>
<u n="180" who="S0618">yeah well send her a message from my Polish phone what sort of time three?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0619">yeah whenever she is ready I suppose <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0618">yeah that's cool and then</u>
<u n="183" who="S0619">I've got no plans until eight</u>
<u n="184" who="S0618">are you hungry?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0619">I'm always hungry</u>
<u n="186" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay so I've got some <unclear>gnocchi</unclear> stuff actually out of Lidl and it crossed my mind while I was carrying my heavyish rucksack for an hour and a quarter <vocal desc="laugh"/> we are next door to Lidl so yeah it is like a spinach <unclear>gnocchi</unclear> and then the pesto <pause dur="short"/> funnily enough the cheapest pesto is in Alma cheaper than Tesco's cheaper than Lidl it's probably shit but anyway we will try it it looks good it looks quite thick stuff and then I bought six cloves of garlic with me because we are in Poland <vocal desc="laugh"/> so it's the law you have to reek of garlic all the time so we can put one or none or six or any number in between in our lovely <unclear>gnocchi</unclear> and I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was going to do a salad and I've bought the stereo thing to plug into your laptop for proper movie sound</u>
<u n="187" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I'm lazy <pause dur="short"/> oh nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah you could have just got it from here <pause dur="short"/> oh nice <pause dur="short"/> interesting <pause dur="short"/> oh nice <pause dur="short"/> uhu <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh my gosh no <pause dur="short"/> uhu <pause dur="short"/> uhu <pause dur="short"/> oh nice <pause dur="short"/> yes and I be able to</u>
<u n="188" who="S0618">how do you do the projector thing? is that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0619"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is projecting</u>
<u n="190" who="S0618">yeah anyway where were we?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0619">if you text her</u>
<u n="192" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0619">ask if she will bring her laptop</u>
<u n="194" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0619">because mine is really tiny for watching and yeah hers is is sort of a normal-sized one</u>
<u n="196" who="S0618">okay <pause dur="short"/> I hate this Polish phone look what ate you up to? and then if I want to go back and replace the T in ate with an R for are I mean that's actually done it quite sensibly but sometimes I'm just clicking at various bits it's because it's <event desc="sound of banging phone"/> cheap plastic shit anyway what are you up to? <pause dur="long"/> er I'm with <vocal desc="sigh"/> in for frig sake look come on I'm yeah that's just annoying anyway I'm with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and it's oh I have to put the apostrophe in oh I will have to fault myself it's nearly film o'clock</u>
<u n="197" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah it clicks <pause dur="short"/> yes but these poor people they've just been stood around all day</u>
<u n="198" who="S0618">I know</u>
<u n="199" who="S0619">well someone is going to get <unclear/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0618">I think that must be so difficult when you start a business like that</u>
<u n="201" who="S0619">yeah and you've just got to wait and you are so excited for customers and you have put all of your life savings into it</u>
<u n="202" who="S0618">yeah I hope they know it's possibly I think they say erm the first year of a business you make a loss the second year you break even and the third year you make a profit and I observed <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who are a Polish couple who erm moved to my arse end of nowhere in Northern Ireland the bottom of the peninsula village and they had successful restaurant business but the way they did it was they were always open seven days a week so you knew if you fancied a coffee or a fry or whatever if you wandered down to the shore you knew they would be open</u>
<u n="203" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah they would be open but that's not good it's not good for them is it?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0618">well no I used to say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well because they used to work seven days a week and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to say well I didn't come over here to have a holiday you think well you know that's some heck of a work ethic and I think that idea is to make shitloads of money and then come back to Poland as rich people and not work but I'm too much in my now for that and I just imagine you work your arse off for ten years and then drop down dead and you would be looking down on your body going shit I wish I hadn't bothered but anyway</u>
<u n="205" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I can't do things like that <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> but no one has ever said from the deathbed I wish I'd worked harder <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know exactly so</u>
<u n="207" who="S0619">you know they've gone I'd <pause dur="short"/> I really I'd wish I'd travelled the world or done this or done that I don't know <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0618">yeah so <pause dur="short"/> I will just say what time will you be here? and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says</u>
<u n="209" who="S0619">hello <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0618">can you please bring your laptop? <pause dur="long"/> there we are</u>
<u n="211" who="S0619">very good</u>
<u n="212" who="S0618">okay done <pause dur="long"/> so if we leave that there with the volume up let's see if she's text back yes so you think you might be up for no booze in February? I'll join you binge on the first</u>
<u n="213" who="S0619">no</u>
<u n="214" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you are so good</u>
<u n="215" who="S0619">you can you go and do whatever you want I just</u>
<u n="216" who="S0618">well no I don't actually have any good quality alcohol in the house I've got sort of I've got cooking whisky that you gave me left over from your party erm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> have all the shit</u>
<u n="218" who="S0618">I've got this white wine that I've just bought it looks like it's Russian or Slovakian or something there's some interesting looking characters on it and it probably tastes really awful erm and what else have I got? I've actually got another bottle of wine that's halfway reasonable and I've got a cherry liqueur thing actually I really a fancy a go at that</u>
<u n="219" who="S0619">oh yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0618">that's only fifteen percent so I might drink that bottle on the first of February throw up a bit get really sick and then decide</u>
<u n="221" who="S0619">yeah remember why you stopped drinking</u>
<u n="222" who="S0618">yeah so I think out of all of the booze that's the one I fancy the most</u>
<u n="223" who="S0619">why not?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0618">so I might just drink that on the first of February what day is the first of February?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0619">it's a Monday</u>
<u n="226" who="S0618">okay well I haven't got any students on a Monday right <vocal desc="laugh"/> so breakfast <vocal desc="laugh"/> cherry liqueur</u>
<u n="227" who="S0619">no I I kind of think now all of my friends here in this country you know good friends don't care if I'm drunk or sober and the ones who want me to get drunk I think if you want me to get drunk then that means that you might not like me as much so why why should I be your friend? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> uhu <pause dur="short"/> I wonder if the ones like you drunk are the ones who maybe have alcohol issues themselves and it's probably not so much about you as about them</u>
<u n="229" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's true that is true yeah if it's because they want to drink <unclear/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0618">yeah to no offence but you could be anyone</u>
<u n="231" who="S0619">yeah true <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's true</u>
<u n="232" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0619">but we shall see</u>
<u n="234" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0619">so yes <pause dur="short"/> I feel I'm for it</u>
<u n="236" who="S0618">I'm thinking now I might like to sort of support you in you giving up your nasal thing as well <vocal desc="laugh"/> as something what else can I give up?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> this is</u>
<u n="238" who="S0618">that would be really good to give up?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0619">this is this is the hardest thing this is way harder than giving up alcohol or giving up chocolate or giving up fags or whatever else so this is like <pause dur="short"/> because I'm not addicted to anything else I'm not addicted to alcohol or smoking I just do these things because I enjoy them <vocal desc="laugh"/> but this is like addiction because I can't breathe and breathing is very important <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and not being able to breathe <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> it is kind of important</u>
<u n="241" who="S0619">so I just have to breathe through my mouth like a loser</u>
<u n="242" who="S0618">oh I bet you snore something chronic at the minute?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0619">that's what I mean I kind of don't want to either don't want to go to <anon type="place"/> I'm gonna have to start taking this medication for the trip</u>
<u n="244" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh oh in my junk drawers I found about four pairs of ear plugs so we will be alright <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't mind paying for a separate room because</u>
<u n="246" who="S0618">you are going to potentially keep everybody awake yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0619">so I just have to work through it</u>
<u n="248" who="S0618">you've just reminded me of this really passive aggressive guy I met when hostelling around New Zealand he was this arsehole of an arrogant Essex man who was also hostelling his way around New Zealand on this large motorbike and he basically he went to the boss of every hostel and said look I really really really snore so you need to give me my own personal hostel room at the same price as a shared room bed because I'll keep people awake and you will get complaints and I just thought what a dick you know I mean he was kind of dressing it up as I'm concerned about everybody else erm but really he was just wanting something better for nothing he invariably got it so yeah I was thinking <unclear/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's funny <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> uhu</u>
<u n="250" who="S0618">yeah I didn't like his vibe so yeah <pause dur="long"/> this is weird there's a sort of a bit of heat coming out of this chipboard thing can you feel it?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0619">well there's a radiator</u>
<u n="252" who="S0618">oh it's up there look <pause dur="short"/> there's a radiator behind here</u>
<u n="253" who="S0619">I can't feel it because I'm very warm in this sort of</u>
<u n="254" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so anyway yeah we'll see <pause dur="short"/> but don't don't worry on my account <event desc="sound of telephone"/> because oh there's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0619">oh hello</u>
<u n="256" who="S0618">because erm I'm quite used to sharing with my brother <vocal desc="laugh"/> when we have been places and he can snore for England</u>
<u n="257" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu <pause dur="short"/> I don't <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm really trying but I know that I am at the moment because there's just like stuff going on</u>
<u n="258" who="S0618">do you wake up with a sore throat?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0619">er with a really dry mouth but it's only been one night so far <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0618">yeah it will pass yeah good for you though</u>
<u n="261" who="S0619">you know these people on this website said like they only used this sort of medication once a day and tried to wean themself off it or they only used it in one nostril they had to do it that way so it's like</u>
<u n="262" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> are you cold turkey?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0619">so I'm going to try but it has been a few hours so I might sort of die before then</u>
<u n="264" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0619">I just don't want to</u>
<u n="266" who="S0618">I think cold turkey is the way</u>
<u n="267" who="S0619">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> keeps ringing me oh well</u>
<u n="268" who="S0618">mm yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0619">this is something that I need to give up but I don't really know how to approach the giving up <vocal desc="laugh"/> the giving up part it is not so easy to give up an actual person</u>
<u n="270" who="S0618">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="271" who="S0619">I can't just you know pour him down the sink <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0619">or put him in the bin or give him to a friend until I come back</u>
<u n="274" who="S0618">I can be really black and white about people sometimes and I can just switch off I'm not sure where that comes from self-preservation instinct I suppose</u>
<u n="275" who="S0619">I know no I can it's like I did it before I can switch someone off like a light switch but I'm never very good at sort of telling them I just go cold turkey with people in the sense that I never speak to them and if they text me I don't reply and if they call me I don't answer and when I see them I blank them which is all horrible things that I shouldn't do</u>
<u n="276" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> why?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0619">well because I don't think it is fair people sometimes need explanations and but I don't I'm not the sort of person I just don't have the capability to say this isn't working I'm not therefore I can't do it no sorry bye</u>
<u n="278" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm maybe <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> to my mind this is a situation where selfishness is vitally important and I suppose there is some sort of circumstances or situations where it might be a kindness to the other person or I don't know compassionate thing to have the conversation with them but at other times</u>
<u n="279" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> you got to do it for yourself</u>
<u n="280" who="S0618">yeah you've got to do it for yourself <pause dur="short"/> I find I can sometimes be a little bit aggressive then sometimes which isn't like me and I will tell someone to fuck off if need be but <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm thinking about an ex-friend <vocal desc="laugh"/> who a few years ago and I was a little bit the same I was just blanking her for a while we had a huge falling out and I just thought well fuck you and have the space then to look back on the friendship and relationship and just to think actually that's not really healthy for me and I don't want anything to do with that so off you go then</u>
<u n="281" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what we were saying in the car the other day I want somebody for whom you know after themselves I'm the most important person in their life and that's not this person you know I will never be the most important person in his life er</u>
<u n="282" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I completely agree I'm in a relationship I want to be adored</u>
<u n="283" who="S0619">I am the centre of your world <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0618">yeah I don't mean that in a completely self-centred way</u>
<u n="285" who="S0619">yeah no no neither do I</u>
<u n="286" who="S0618">but I just want somebody to really value and appreciate me and if they don't really value and appreciate me you know like you say as well as having their own life and their own interests</u>
<u n="287" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah everyone is you should be the centre of your own world you should be the most important person</u>
<u n="288" who="S0618" trans="overlap">exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> first and foremost I agree</u>
<u n="289" who="S0619">but I want to be a presence and I don't think I am</u>
<u n="290" who="S0618">yeah and to feel important and to feel considered and to <pause dur="short"/> I suppose that's a true partnership isn't it?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0619">and I think I'm the sort of <pause dur="short"/> right now in this thing that is ending I don't think it even began but you know I'm sort of at a</u>
<u n="292" who="S0618">is ending or has ended?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0619">has ended is ending is ending erm you know I'm a sort of fair weather person it is like oh I don't know what to do so I will call this person it was like oh I don't know what to do so I will call this person or I need to get out of <anon type="place"/> so I'll call this person and it's not you know I'm desperate to see you <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="294" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not the best reasons really is it?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no I know</u>
<u n="296" who="S0618">you might think in a relationship that you know the motivating factors would be more like yeah desperate to see you or not in a can't live my life without you kind of a way you expect the other individual to be exactly that individual who is perfectly complete in on themselves who brings something to the table so you can be a complete person they are a complete person but when you get together you're a kind of <unclear>gestalt</unclear> organism of something greater than the sum of the parts erm and create something beautiful together that really benefits you both that expands you both that challenges you both but</u>
<u n="297" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu <pause dur="short"/> uhu <pause dur="short"/> where are these people? <vocal desc="laugh"/> I haven't found one</u>
<u n="298" who="S0618">I have <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0619">and I think it's because I'm working <pause dur="short"/> stuff out and I have to be alone</u>
<u n="300" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I want to be alone <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0619">no it's not that I want I don't want to be but I am have to be until I work out whatever this is whatever is going on and I think this is the sort of the turning point the sort of the pinnacle sort of <pause dur="short"/> what's the word? the pivot</u>
<u n="302" who="S0618" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> I think that's important <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah the pivotal point yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0619">yeah and people who come into my life now will be because they are interested in this sort of strange sober person you know maybe I need a gym somebody from the gym because people are healthy and they don't drink and they don't judge for going to bed at ten o'clock because they are doing it too I think that's what I need and not an alcoholic <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I suppose yeah that is the thing when you change you know you <vocal desc="sigh"/> yeah you do need your friends to I don't know not change I don't know <unclear/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0619">not not change for you but you need people on a similar a similar wavelength or in a <trunc>sim</trunc> in a similar routine with similar erm interests not necessarily interests but things that are important or</u>
<u n="306" who="S0618" trans="overlap">on a wavelength <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I guess when I think about you I see somebody who is evolving or <pause dur="short"/> I mean you know how we are dynamic creatures we are always evolving we always changing you know I I don't think a personality is ever set but I suppose you have certain characteristics or a certain resonance or a certain vibe that you get on for a period of time because it suits you and you explore everything within that vibe and then something shifts or changes and you move and you do become a different person on a cellular level on a <trunc>de</trunc> and well on a cellular level you are not you are a completely different human being to the physical organism you were seven years ago everything about you has shifted and changed and also sort of psychologically spiritually emotionally well you are a different person in every moment you are reinvented in every now but I do think you hit these like you know you are at one now which is a life changing oh okay choice of two big paths and there's another probable you that's carrying on business as usual but this wider path is the you that is now recreating or creating something new <pause dur="short"/> and I think good for you be assertive and be proud of who you are don't do yourself down or call yourself a sad git for going to bed at ten o'clock you know be proud of that</u>
<u n="307" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> uhu <pause dur="short"/> uhu <pause dur="short"/> it's great I am <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0618">it is fabulous if it feels good do it</u>
<u n="309" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0618">but be proud to be that person and the more you embrace and feel joy at being that person the more you will attract people to you who are on that vibe definitely like attracts like it's the law <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah and I think like does attract like but er especially in this situation when we are here it is harder to attract because there are so many kind of layers of like filter almost you know you have to say right erm can you speak English?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> uhu <pause dur="short"/> yeah definitely first and foremost</u>
<u n="313" who="S0619">so you know if you are playing a game of Guess Who? and you are putting down faces that's like a part of your board gone</u>
<u n="314" who="S0618">yeah that's the first one isn't it? that's more than half your board</u>
<u n="315" who="S0619">yeah yeah you are thinking I am going to try it okay erm</u>
<u n="316" who="S0618">so most likely it's going to be <trunc>En</trunc> English people who are teachers that you get to know and I guess the question how do you meet more natives? <pause dur="short"/> I don't know you go to Spain <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah and then it's like <pause dur="short"/> yeah exactly you can't do it here can you speak English? are you in the vicinity of this city? more or less</u>
<u n="318" who="S0618">mm yeah within an hour or two bus drive yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0619">and then you know you can get more and more specific into what you sort of want or like or</u>
<u n="320" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0619">anyway I need to go to the toilet do you mind pausing the?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0618">can you do a pause on this?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0619">otherwise you can sit and talk to yourself</u>
<u n="324" who="S0618">can you do a pause thing on a recording?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0619">I think you just stop and then you can just carry on again</u>
<u n="326" who="S0618">can you? okay there we are</u>
<u n="327" who="S0619"><unclear/> so it should just continue <unclear/> I will have to have a little break</u>
<u n="328" who="S0618">jolly good I sent <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a text to say we would be back at your flat by two forty-five at the latest</u>
<u n="329" who="S0619">yeah I walked home from her house last night and it didn't take me long it took about twenty-five thirty minutes</u>
<u n="330" who="S0618">oh that's not long</u>
<u n="331" who="S0619">yeah and it was just a straight line</u>
<u n="332" who="S0618">I should think it feels like ages in the van <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's probably because we always go the wrong way <vocal desc="laugh"/> and have to turn round and go back</u>
<u n="333" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah and I think we go a long way round maybe <pause dur="short"/> no I don't know I don't know</u>
<u n="334" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah mm <pause dur="short"/> that will be <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s satnav for you</u>
<u n="335" who="S0619">yeah right so I'm just going to research this</u>
<u n="336" who="S0618">yeah I might look at this bistro menu particularly where it says burrito for fifteen <foreign lang="pol">grosz</foreign> something like two pound fifty for a burrito</u>
<u n="337" who="S0619">I don't know yeah what we will get in it though</u>
<u n="338" who="S0618">I know probably something dead <event desc="sound of telephone"/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0619">erm sure I was trying to see what else they have that is vegetarian and I don't think there is so much because even the salads have stuff apart from dried tomato salad but that's like it and erm there's potato cakes with with mushroom sauce</u>
<u n="340" who="S0618">ah now erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said that potato cakes with mushroom sauce generally have something dead floating around as well</u>
<u n="341" who="S0619">yeah and some <foreign lang="pol"><unclear>peorogi</unclear></foreign> come with like lardy stuff on top</u>
<u n="342" who="S0618">yeah <foreign lang="pol"><unclear>ruggi ruski</unclear></foreign> is normally alright what are you looking for?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0619">oh just some lip balm my lips are dead sore</u>
<u n="344" who="S0618">do you want some Vaseline?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0619">no I have I have <event desc="sound of rustling"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0618">I've got loads of these tins of Vaseline</u>
<u n="347" who="S0619">yeah so have I</u>
<u n="348" who="S0618">I'm sure of them are like thirty years old <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0619">I've got yeah I've got because I never use Vaseline because I always hear mixed er reports on how good it is as a moisturiser and that it</u>
<u n="350" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I've got one that was going rusty <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's more of a barrier</u>
<u n="351" who="S0619">yeah stops stuff getting in but doesn't actually actively moisturise</u>
<u n="352" who="S0618">no but I quite like that because I wonder with moisturisers I try not to use them because I think</u>
<u n="353" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah yeah just sort of <pause dur="short"/> chemicals into your face I suppose</u>
<u n="354" who="S0618">well yeah and parabens and shit but no I erm like hands or whatever for example I think the more you use a moisturiser the more you need it</u>
<u n="355" who="S0619">the more your skin needs them yeah and I used to have really dry hands but because I've been like really hammering the water I haven't had dried hands and it's been like and I rarely wear gloves because I'm such a forgetful</u>
<u n="356" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh good <pause dur="short"/> good <pause dur="short"/> because you've been yeah okay so hydrating from the inside</u>
<u n="357" who="S0619" trans="overlap">hopefully the water <pause dur="short"/> yes I'm just going to drink some water now would you like another? oh I suppose if we are going back in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s and we've got coffee at home so we don't need to have a</u>
<u n="358" who="S0618">yeah that's cool</u>
<u n="359" who="S0619">well we'll have a sit and maybe have a long walk home <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0619">I don't know how we can lengthen the journey er <pause dur="long"/> I might nip and get some milk er</u>
<u n="362" who="S0618">in Lidl?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0619">er anywhere I'm just trying to think if there's anything I need I've got tea coffee and milk</u>
<u n="364" who="S0618">I like Lidl but I find I used to love Lidl in Northern Ireland every Thursday it was oh all the new things are in and on a Thursday it would be packed and I used to go on a Thursday because I used to drive a forty mile round trip to get the only organic vegetables that are available in the whole of Northern Ireland from the Holywood Camphill Community so I used to be uptown every Thursday anyway and call into Lidl and the quality was excellent but I find Lidl here the quality of all of the stuff it's all just polyester and stuff really give you bad electric shocks so don't go near anything metal so er yeah so I haven't bought hardly anything from the all the knicky-knacky new sections in the middle of Lidl but the Biedronka the Polish Lidl is brilliant and they have erm stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's made in Poland and the quality is great</u>
<u n="365" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> nice <pause dur="short"/> nice <pause dur="short"/> what like the clothes and stuff? <pause dur="short"/> uhu <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I never go to Biedronka in fact I didn't even know there was one near Alma until today there is another one over that way across that little roundabout you know at the end of <pause dur="short"/> er if you pick me up <pause dur="short"/> then there's a roundabout near the flat</u>
<u n="366" who="S0618">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> uhu <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah and then drive towards <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0619">yeah kind of or drive towards Gemini there's a Biedronka around there but I never think to go maybe I will be start going to Biedronka</u>
<u n="368" who="S0618">okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> no it's good it's good</u>
<u n="369" who="S0619">because I went to Alma on the way back from the court</u>
<u n="370" who="S0618">I know because it's easy and you are passing it</u>
<u n="371" who="S0619">for for kind of basically bits and then Tesco at the moment because it's next to the gym <pause dur="short"/> creature of habit</u>
<u n="372" who="S0618">no Biedronka is brilliant for all of their like bits in cages that are bargains in the middle erm yeah really good and also they are really good for Saudi things a bit like Lidl actually I found them in Lidl how you you get those tubs of <foreign lang="pol"><unclear>kapusta</unclear></foreign></u>
<u n="373" who="S0619">mm <pause dur="short"/> uhu <pause dur="short"/> coleslaw and stuff</u>
<u n="374" who="S0618">yeah coleslaw or the carrot or beetroot or cabbage or whatever they might be and they are really cheap and really nice so yeah I tend to buy those in Biedronka and they've quite often got rows of pick and mix nuts or seeds or fruits which are pretty good as well and incredibly cheap I saw dried kiwis the other day which was really interesting yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0619">oh how exciting <pause dur="short"/> I was looking for some dried pineapple and it was dead expensive and that was in Galeria <unclear>Krakowska</unclear> in <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> you know there's a big supermarket oh no was I there? I was somewhere yeah I was there</u>
<u n="376" who="S0618" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0619">yeah or maybe it was in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="378" who="S0618">oh the French supermarket</u>
<u n="379" who="S0619">yeah I was somewhere anyway and they had dried pineapple but it was dead expensive</u>
<u n="380" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> is that Carrefour of applicator tampon fame?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0619">no that's Rossmann</u>
<u n="382" who="S0618">oh Rossmann okay yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0619">the applicator tampon</u>
<u n="384" who="S0618">I'm alright I brought a load from England</u>
<u n="385" who="S0619">yeah I I bought some the other day from Rossman</u>
<u n="386" who="S0618">I've been really tempted to try a mooncup</u>
<u n="387" who="S0619">yeah my friend mooncups erm and she swears by it erm I don't know how I feel</u>
<u n="388" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> no I am not very I'm not sure I could be bothered with all of that and the mess</u>
<u n="389" who="S0619">but I think you know if you are sort of in public toilets for example it's just you'd have to take that and you'd have to take wipes just because you'd just you know</u>
<u n="390" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah you be blobbing everywhere while you are washing the thing out</u>
<u n="391" who="S0619">well all over your hands and stuff it's alright in the comfort of your own home but yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0618">yeah I don't know I wonder I'll see because yeah I maybe when I'm living with a hippy dippy community it might be the way to go</u>
<u n="393" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="395" who="S0619">but my friend says it's no problem and it's sort of easy and quick and comfortable</u>
<u n="396" who="S0618">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> there are YouTube videos that I haven't watched and I think maybe if I watched them that might decide me</u>
<u n="397" who="S0619">spur you on</u>
<u n="398" who="S0618"><unclear><anon type="place"/></unclear> up <anon type="place"/>  in Cambridge sells them <pause dur="short"/> the last time I was in Cambridge I was in there picking up my fluoride-free toothpaste <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I saw them oh shall I? shan't I? shall I'shan't I? but anyway I will ponder it a bit longer but I think I probably will <pause dur="long"/> yeah <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="399" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we'll see I just think if it is not broke don't fix it</u>
<u n="400" who="S0618">well it is sort of is for me living in Poland because I do like my applicator tampons and I can't be doing with the non-applicator ones I mean biologically speaking it's just not happening quite frankly</u>
<u n="401" who="S0619">well then I know but then mooncups are not far removed from that you still have to do a lot of poking around</u>
<u n="402" who="S0618">I managed one of them what's that contraceptive thingy?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0619">coils</u>
<u n="404" who="S0618">no not coil is it cap?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0619">like a dam is it called dam or something?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0618">yeah I managed one of them for a year when I actually went out with a man and that was fine <pause dur="short"/> yeah so I don't know <pause dur="short"/> we'll see we shall see</u>
<u n="407" who="S0619">oh sorry</u>
<u n="408" who="S0618">anyway yeah so <vocal desc="laugh"/> where are we? I suppose on that note we probably ought to think about having a wander back to your flat to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for look still afternoon</u>
<u n="409" who="S0619">good luck for transcribing that section <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0618">okey doke</u>
<u n="411" who="S0619">okay bye</u>
<u n="412" who="S0618">bye <pause dur="short"/> oh hang on oh I'm not very good at this technical stuff there we are bye</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
