<text id="SJLP">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:14:53</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-19</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0189 S0192</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Brother's kitchen, Bedford</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Sickness, travelling, hotels, cooking</topics>
		<activity>Cooking with my brother</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T03</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0189">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bedfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Artworker</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0192">
				<exactage>28</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bedford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>English Language Instructor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2>Spanish</l2>
				<fls>Korean -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0189">but luckily like it was kind of comfy there and it was cheap and like the toilet was good so it wasn't too bad <unclear/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0192" trans="overlap">did you have air con?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0189">yeah I did</u>
<u n="4" who="S0192">course you did</u>
<u n="5" who="S0189">yep</u>
<u n="6" who="S0192">it wasn't so bad in Cambodia without it though was it?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0189">no cos the fan was massive but in Battambang it was horrible</u>
<u n="8" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0189">er but yeah I had air con in the dorm there and it was needed cos Chiang Mai was quite hot</u>
<u n="10" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0189">and after I started taking the antibiotics like on the day after I was much better</u>
<u n="12" who="S0192">did you do er that after I told you to cos I told you to take antibiotics didn't I</u>
<u n="13" who="S0189">no</u>
<u n="14" who="S0192">I recommended a few antibiotics to you and then the next thing I knew was that you'd been taking them</u>
<u n="15" who="S0189" trans="overlap">yeah I used I used your suggestions</u>
<u n="16" who="S0192">yeah good stuff</u>
<u n="17" who="S0189">and found that Ciprofloxacin</u>
<u n="18" who="S0192">the Ciprofloxacin yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0189">yes</u>
<u n="20" who="S0192">I do that when I've had it for like four or five days now it's time to take some antibiotics</u>
<u n="21" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0192">and usually within two or three days it clears up again <unclear/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0189">yeah within within the day it felt so much better like for the first time I woke up and didn't need to immediately shit</u>
<u n="24" who="S0192">yeah just don't get into the habit of taking them every time you get sick you know cos it's there's not much you could do probably</u>
<u n="25" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0192">but erm I'm glad you did cos you started talking about going to the doctors and I was thinking no no no you need to at least try a course of antibiotics on your own before you before you do that</u>
<u n="27" who="S0189">mm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0192">if that doesn't clear it up then go to the doctors</u>
<u n="29" who="S0189">yeah but that sorted me out and then I I went zip lining</u>
<u n="30" who="S0192">oh sweet</u>
<u n="31" who="S0189">erm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0192">was that fun?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0189">yeah it was good I did a cooking course</u>
<u n="34" who="S0192">it wasn't like that episode of South Park?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0189">no</u>
<u n="36" who="S0192">have you seen that one?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0189">yes</u>
<u n="38" who="S0192">little did they know that something or other is fun</u>
<u n="39" who="S0189">erm I did a cooking course</u>
<u n="40" who="S0192">so I'm not going to keep all this fat erm I'm gonna put a bit in here</u>
<u n="41" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0192">sweet <pause dur="short"/> flavour</u>
<u n="43" who="S0189">and I did like a two day tour where I saw the erm national park and like the <trunc>temp</trunc>temple on the hill</u>
<u n="44" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="45" who="S0189" trans="overlap">so yeah of</u>
<u n="46" who="S0192">you you did elephant something or other but it wasn't the same as what I was talking about was it it was like</u>
<u n="47" who="S0189">yeah it was different have you seen this picture?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0192">the one of you riding on its head?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0189">no this one</u>
<u n="50" who="S0192">oh the one that you got mum?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0192">yeah I did see that</u>
<u n="53" who="S0189">that was in Chiang Rai that was like a cultural <unclear/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0192">heritage place yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0189">thing and there was a bunch of dancers like <unclear/> in front of me</u>
<u n="56" who="S0192">this is a bit random</u>
<u n="57" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="short"/> er I enjoyed that</u>
<u n="58" who="S0192">sounds good</u>
<u n="59" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0192">I'm glad you had such a good time travelling</u>
<u n="61" who="S0189">yeah I did I had a really good time <pause dur="short"/> and after that I</u>
<u n="62" who="S0192">you can see why I've been doing it so much</u>
<u n="63" who="S0189">yeah it's amazing</u>
<u n="64" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0189">I'd kind of be I'd be willing to go on my own again definitely</u>
<u n="66" who="S0192">yeah good</u>
<u n="67" who="S0189">erm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0192">just bear in mind that some places aren't quite as easy to travel</u>
<u n="69" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0192">as those parts of the world but as you get more and more experience it will be easy</u>
<u n="71" who="S0189">yeah er then I got the bus to Pai <pause dur="short"/> which wasn't that bad I'd heard horror stories about the little mini van</u>
<u n="72" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0189">but it was</u>
<u n="74" who="S0192">what from me or from other people?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0189">just from other people like oh my god you nearly die <pause dur="short"/> they speed all the way there <pause dur="short"/> and the roads are really bumpy and people were being sick</u>
<u n="76" who="S0192">I mean people are pansies sometimes <unclear/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0189">yeah the the <trunc>s</trunc> people on the bus had to take their sickness pills but I was alright</u>
<u n="78" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0189">it was kind of just fun <pause dur="short"/> erm it was fine it was quite nice views going up there</u>
<u n="80" who="S0192">and you motorbiked back from there didn't you?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0192">which is pretty fun <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0189">oh did you see my hotel I got in Pai?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="85" who="S0189">it was outrageous it was all pink</u>
<u n="86" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0189">it was a Hello Kitty hotel</u>
<u n="88" who="S0192">oh I think I did see that</u>
<u n="89" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0192">I was like what?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0189">it was a Hello Kitty hotel <pause dur="short"/> it was actually a nightmare</u>
<u n="92" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> why?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0189">staying there <pause dur="short"/> erm I only stayed there because like I was looking when I was in Chiang Mai</u>
<u n="94" who="S0192">it's a bit of a random place to stay in Pai isn't it? it's not</u>
<u n="95" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think I'll stay at the Hello Kitty hotel</u>
<u n="97" who="S0189"><vocal desc="laugh"/> when I was in Chiang Mai I was I er knew I was going to Pai the day after so I was looking through Agoda <pause dur="short"/> and like I saw this ridiculously pink hotel so I I was showed the er <pause dur="short"/> spanish girl and she was like oh my god you have to stay there so I was like oh I'm feeling completely crazy at the moment so I might as well</u>
<u n="98" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0189">so I booked a couple of days there and I get there and oh my god it's all pink</u>
<u n="100" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0189">like the whole building is pink</u>
<u n="102" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0189">and inside is pink and the bed sheets are pink and you've got Hello Kitty bed sheets and alarm clock and <pause dur="short"/> but like the first room they gave me was it <trunc>w</trunc> stank of mould</u>
<u n="104" who="S0192">oh no</u>
<u n="105" who="S0189">yeah so I like went and complained and then obviously they don't speak very good English so I had trouble trying to actually converse with them <pause dur="short"/> and then they stuck me in some shitty other room where I went in and there was like a frog <pause dur="short"/> let me get this <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> what are you trying to do? this one?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0192">that yeah <pause dur="short"/> is it that one?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you won't get that on</u>
<u n="108" who="S0192">they stuck you in another room and there was a frog?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0189">there was like a frog jumping around there were erm oh <pause dur="short"/> there were lots of bugs in there there were erm like worms coming out the drain</u>
<u n="110" who="S0192">ugh</u>
<u n="111" who="S0189">and the shower <pause dur="short"/> there was a a line of ants that went up the wall and went under the bed</u>
<u n="112" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0189">it was pretty bad</u>
<u n="114" who="S0192">so it was classic</u>
<u n="115" who="S0189">yeah and there was tons of mosquitos as well and the door didn't properly close</u>
<u n="116" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0189">and you had to use like erm a padlock erm er</u>
<u n="118" who="S0192">your own padlock?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0189">no a padlock they gave you but er it it the door would like hang out and then it was just a padlock kind of <pause dur="short"/> which obviously the mosquitos just came in</u>
<u n="120" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0189">so easily</u>
<u n="122" who="S0192">not good then</u>
<u n="123" who="S0189">anyone outside would have just heard me like er ah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0192">did you have the uhu</u>
<u n="127" who="S0189">no I didn't have that</u>
<u n="128" who="S0192">uhu</u>
<u n="129" who="S0189"><unclear/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0189"><unclear/> seeing the islands in the south part <unclear/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0192">Pai is nice though isn't it</u>
<u n="133" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0192">I imagine it's changed quite a bit now from how it was</u>
<u n="135" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0192">when I was there</u>
<u n="137" who="S0189">but I wasn't happy with the room again cos it was shit and it was actually not that cheap</u>
<u n="138" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="139" who="S0189">so I was like well I'm paying the proper rate here for a crappy room erm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0189">so I went and complained again and I ended up having to phone up the manager and like arguing with him and saying look I want my money back I'm gonna write you a bad review <unclear/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0192">right</u>
<u n="143" who="S0189">and eventually they gave me a better room and that one was okay</u>
<u n="144" who="S0192">oh fortunate so complaining worked?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0192">I normally don't complain I just leave <pause dur="short"/> find somewhere else</u>
<u n="147" who="S0189">I felt like leaving but I was out of money</u>
<u n="148" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0189">and my budget was spent and I was over budget already</u>
<u n="150" who="S0192">through your own fault?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0192">well you did choose to go to Hello Kitty hotel</u>
<u n="153" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0192">surely the guy at the end was like why are you here?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was full of like Chinese guys <pause dur="short"/> but not like on their own they er just came as packs <pause dur="short"/> families and things like that <pause dur="short"/> so like no one would like talk to me</u>
<u n="156" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="157" who="S0189">and like I'd I'd be getting picked up to go on like erm that elephant trek and erm like they they pull up outside the road in a in a a pickup truck with people just hanging out the back for you to get in <pause dur="short"/> and like everyone is just staring in awe at this pink hotel <pause dur="short"/> like I come strolling out with my shades</u>
<u n="158" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0189">and I'm like er you can see them all looking at me and I don't know laughing I'm like you should see inside my room it's even better</u>
<u n="160" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0189">so it was quite funny</u>
<u n="162" who="S0192">so it was worth the experience</u>
<u n="163" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0192">random <pause dur="short"/> why did it take you so long to get back to us? mum and I were a bit like</u>
<u n="165" who="S0189">oh</u>
<u n="166" who="S0192">I presume you were just busy or something weren't you</u>
<u n="167" who="S0189">er what do you mean? when I was in Pai or Chiang Mai?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0192">yeah you were sick in Chiang Mai and we didn't get a reply from you for ages and it like worried the crap out of mum and then <unclear/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0189" trans="overlap">oh like I was just the same <pause dur="short"/> there wasn't any turn like I wasn't getting worse but I wasn't getting better</u>
<u n="170" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0189">so I didn't really see any need to update</u>
<u n="172" who="S0192">it's just cos you scared mum cos you'd send a really short message to say I'm still sick <pause dur="short"/> and that would be it so she's like oh my god is he alright? you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0189"><unclear/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's just sending such a <trunc>sh</trunc>short message yeah she does <pause dur="short"/> she worries less as long er when you go on longer</u>
<u n="175" who="S0189">yeah but Pai was so cool <pause dur="short"/> I had rented a bike for like every day I was there</u>
<u n="176" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0189">and I just went exploring on the scooter</u>
<u n="178" who="S0192">that's nice as well</u>
<u n="179" who="S0189">they give you a map now I don't know whether you had one of those</u>
<u n="180" who="S0192">I don't think I did</u>
<u n="181" who="S0189">there are so many like different places to go <pause dur="short"/> it pissed me off though when I got there that I rented the bike down the high street <pause dur="short"/> and like no one tells you where the petrol stations are so I'd assumed it was just like the south</u>
<u n="182" who="S0192" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0189">where any direction you go there'll be er little petrol pumps</u>
<u n="184" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0189">to use and people sat on the roads on the side of the street no <pause dur="short"/> so like I pick a direction after I pick up the bike and I'm like okay the fuel tank's pretty low I need to find petrol so I'll go that way and I'm sure I'll find some <pause dur="short"/> no no petrol</u>
<u n="186" who="S0192">nothing?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0189">so I start to panic and I go another way and I'm like shit okay I can't find any so I head back</u>
<u n="188" who="S0192">into town?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0189">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and like the bike dies on the way</u>
<u n="190" who="S0192">oh no</u>
<u n="191" who="S0189">so I had to start fucking pushing the damn thing</u>
<u n="192" who="S0192">how far?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0189">and asking people like where the hell is the damn petrol?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0192">how far did you have to push it?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0189">oh probably about ten minutes <pause dur="short"/> not too bad</u>
<u n="196" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh it wasn't too bad</u>
<u n="197" who="S0189">no</u>
<u n="198" who="S0192">yeah normally it just people with like coke bottles or something</u>
<u n="199" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0189"><unclear/> keep going on the potato?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0192">quicker <pause dur="short"/> otherwise some's gonna be boiled and some's not gonna be boiled</u>
<u n="203" who="S0189">I'm really slow with potatoes</u>
<u n="204" who="S0192">I haven't decided yet do you think it's better to cut these in half or to just have them standing up?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0189">they look nice like that</u>
<u n="206" who="S0192">you reckon?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0189">yep</u>
<u n="208" who="S0192">do you ever do stuffed peppers?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0189">no <pause dur="short"/> never done them</u>
<u n="210" who="S0192">you can do what my friend used to do <pause dur="short"/> you can't I haven't done it since cos we don't have it it's stuffed erm marrow <pause dur="short"/> and marrows are really big so like it's good <pause dur="short"/> you stuff it with loads of meat and potatoes and eggs and whatever <unclear/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0189" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0192">whatever you want <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's not too bad if you're feeding quite a few people</u>
<u n="213" who="S0189">I'm sure you can have a stuffed sour gourd <pause dur="short"/> that'd be nice</u>
<u n="214" who="S0192">that was horrible</u>
<u n="215" who="S0189">it was</u>
<u n="216" who="S0192">whatever that veg was I couldn't really eat it it grossed me out</u>
<u n="217" who="S0189">sour marrow of some kind</u>
<u n="218" who="S0192">I don't like bitter anyway <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit of a weird thing to give us</u>
<u n="219" who="S0189">yes</u>
<u n="220" who="S0192">I guess they just wanted us to try some of the local food</u>
<u n="221" who="S0189"><unclear/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0192">the problem is like some of these aren't gonna stand up <pause dur="short"/> like this one</u>
<u n="223" who="S0189">after erm being in Thailand right I didn't find the Cambodian cuisine like amazingly interesting</u>
<u n="224" who="S0192">no it's not no it's not <pause dur="short"/> so I mean the Philippines is really boring I think their food is terrible</u>
<u n="225" who="S0189">mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0192">what baking pans do you have? what things can I put all these peppers in at the end?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0189">okay</u>
<u n="228" who="S0192">so is that big enough? oh there's two of them <pause dur="short"/> I'm tempted to cut the peppers in half so I can lay them down <pause dur="short"/> I can get one two peppers three peppers four and a half that'd be fine <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm gonna cut the peppers in half</u>
<u n="229" who="S0189"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0192">oh we've got trapped <pause dur="short"/> quicker</u>
<u n="231" who="S0189">you do know it's on lowest right?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0192">yeah I'm talking about that</u>
<u n="233" who="S0189">yeah you do know it's on its lowest</u>
<u n="234" who="S0192">that's fine I'm not telling you to boil quicker I'm telling</u>
<u n="235" who="S0189">oh</u>
<u n="236" who="S0192">you to do it quicker</u>
<u n="237" who="S0189">do I need to do any more after this one?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0192">maybe</u>
<u n="239" who="S0189">oh right</u>
<u n="240" who="S0192">what do you think?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0189">I don't really want to do any more</u>
<u n="242" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> tough <pause dur="short"/> sous chef does want them so</u>
<u n="243" who="S0189">we need a potato peeling machine</u>
<u n="244" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't matter if you get a bit of skin on them <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't have to be perfect</u>
<u n="245" who="S0189">I'm kind of tempted to get a rice cooker for in here</u>
<u n="246" who="S0192">do you know what's better than that?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0189">what?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0192">is a knife</u>
<u n="249" who="S0189">no I'm no quicker with a knife</u>
<u n="250" who="S0192">oh mate where's a knife? where's like a small knife?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0189">er I've tried it before I know better</u>
<u n="252" who="S0192">where is a small knife?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0189">in there</u>
<u n="254" who="S0192">show me a good one <pause dur="short"/> there's gotta be a small knife here</u>
<u n="255" who="S0189">no none of them are good</u>
<u n="256" who="S0192">what's the name of the small that that's here</u>
<u n="257" who="S0189" trans="overlap">I don't think it's gonna fit any more in there</u>
<u n="258" who="S0192">you could</u>
<u n="259" who="S0189">maybe one</u>
<u n="260" who="S0192">if you can get it like this <pause dur="short"/> you know kind of picking it round</u>
<u n="261" who="S0189">god that's so much quicker</u>
<u n="262" who="S0192">it is isn't it</u>
<u n="263" who="S0189">but I can't do that</u>
<u n="264" who="S0192">why can't you do it?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0189"><unclear/> you're losing a lot</u>
<u n="266" who="S0192">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="267" who="S0189" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0192">I'm I'm rushing it but if you do it quicker and you get better at it you lose less potato <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> do you want to give it another try?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0189">no I'm alright <pause dur="short"/> I'm done with potatoes</u>
<u n="270" who="S0192">oh you're done with them</u>
<u n="271" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0192">I see <pause dur="short"/> give up <pause dur="short"/> so you're not gonna have cheese is that what you've decided?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0189">yeah no cheese <pause dur="short"/> by the time I finish this I'm gonna have to start cooking so I can eat so that I can go to kickboxing</u>
<u n="274" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0189">this is bullshit</u>
<u n="276" who="S0192">well you could just eat this now <pause dur="short"/> you could eat yours now</u>
<u n="277" who="S0189">that's probably good</u>
<u n="278" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we can just put yours in the oven <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0192">and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I will eat ours later</u>
<u n="281" who="S0189">yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0192">yeah I did take big chunks off but it's not exactly like you were you weren't doing the same with the peeler</u>
<u n="283" who="S0189">you can't take massive chunks off with the peeler</u>
<u n="284" who="S0192">you were taking some pretty big chunks off</u>
<u n="285" who="S0189">oh maybe</u>
<u n="286" who="S0192">I mean look at that you did that</u>
<u n="287" who="S0189">ah what one? no that one's yours</u>
<u n="288" who="S0192">whatever all these bits chunky chunk that's yours</u>
<u n="289" who="S0189">well I don't think it is cos it doesn't fit through the peeler <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so how did I do that? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's yours</u>
<u n="290" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah do you just want to eat this then before you go?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0189">that'd be good <pause dur="long"/> do you reckon that's enough potato?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0192">mm <pause dur="short"/> don't know we're three grown men <pause dur="short"/> I can't believe you've been using the peeler I hate those peelers</u>
<u n="293" who="S0189">oh well I should really learn to use a knife</u>
<u n="294" who="S0192">yeah you get better at it I'm not always terrible like sometimes you can go just below the skin but I rushed that one</u>
<u n="295" who="S0189">mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0192">and to be honest I haven't peeled a potato before <pause dur="short"/> you've gotta just hold it with your thumb like that and hold the knife in front of you</u>
<u n="297" who="S0189">yeah just practice I guess</u>
<u n="298" who="S0192">where are you off to? do you wanna clean up a bit and then we're done pretty much <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0189">where are the nice apples?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0192">in the fridge <pause dur="short"/> you say nice apples but I didn't get a nice one</u>
<u n="301" who="S0189">I think this one's nice</u>
<u n="302" who="S0192">I'll put that back</u>
<u n="303" who="S0189">that bit goes on here doesn't it?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0192">yeah and erm just clean up and then we're done</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
