<text id="SJTT">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:45:27</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-04</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0018 S0033</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A café in a tennis club, Solihull</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Acquaintances</relationships>
		<topics>Weather, work, sport, education, family, living abroad, travel, music</topics>
		<activity>Acquaintances having a coffee in the tennis club café</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T14</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0033">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British (Dual Australian)</nat>
				<birthplace>Brisbane</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Australia</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>12 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Tennis coach</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0018">it's a shame because last week I came in erm and did a couple of people here and we were outside cos it was beautiful weather</u>
<u n="2" who="S0033" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> unless you want to get soaking wet there's no point going out there</u>
<u n="3" who="S0018">and freezing</u>
<u n="4" who="S0033">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0018">it's a bit cold in there</u>
<u n="6" who="S0033">even walking to my car is too much</u>
<u n="7" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm just learning how to drive and I'm getting quite glad that I am because I hate catching public transport in this weather <pause dur="short"/> it's so cold <pause dur="short"/> horrible <pause dur="short"/> so yeah tell me what you do here then and how long you've been working here</u>
<u n="8" who="S0033">um I'm a tennis coach <pause dur="short"/> I've been working here for eight months now something like that</u>
<u n="9" who="S0018">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0033">I think just finished since last August so I just  and all that sort of stuff and now coaching full time and doing quite well with it so</u>
<u n="11" who="S0018">oh super</u>
<u n="12" who="S0033">not doing too bad but it was just kind of it was something I fell into when I came back from France</u>
<u n="13" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="14" who="S0033">Cos I lived over there for two years</u>
<u n="15" who="S0018">oh really?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0033">and I knew <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the sports manager</u>
<u n="17" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="18" who="S0033">so I went up to he was at <anon type="place"/> at that point so</u>
<u n="19" who="S0018">is there a <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0033"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0033">so I went over to there and then I just didn't do very well over there like <pause dur="short"/> there's just not as much money</u>
<u n="23" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="24" who="S0033">in that area so I was struggling a little bit and then he ah he moved down here and asked me to come with him cos they needed a bit of a performance programme for the kids so</u>
<u n="25" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> oh so do you do mainly kids here or?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0033">well I mainly do performance</u>
<u n="27" who="S0018">aha what's that?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0033">like kids trying to make it nationally or professionally or</u>
<u n="29" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="30" who="S0033">cos I've been in that my whole life as well <pause dur="short"/> I mean I played on the pro tour</u>
<u n="31" who="S0018">aha</u>
<u n="32" who="S0033">just it's what I've been used to do <pause dur="short"/> I mean I coached my sister as well and she made top four under sixteens top ten under eighteens and</u>
<u n="33" who="S0018">oh brilliant</u>
<u n="34" who="S0033">now she's at university in America <trunc>stud</trunc> for free</u>
<u n="35" who="S0018">to ah she got on a tennis scholarship?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0033" trans="overlap">scholarship yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0018">brilliant <pause dur="short"/> whereabouts is she?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0033">um Tampa Bay</u>
<u n="39" who="S0018">Florida is that?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0033">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0018">ah nice</u>
<u n="42" who="S0033">because of the contacts I had over there she just sort of she asked me she said oh I can't I don't really want to play serious that much</u>
<u n="43" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="44" who="S0033">anymore and I'd like to go to uni and I said well you're not going in England I said if you can get it for free in America and she said ah oh ok and I went choose a place that you wanna go and I said I'll call my friends and they'll get you in over there and then she said Florida so</u>
<u n="45" who="S0018">blimey who are your friends?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0033">I know a lot of people</u>
<u n="47" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> is that through the tennis circuit?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0033">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I keep getting job offers over there in Dubai and Australia and</u>
<u n="49" who="S0018">really? Why are you pretty pretty much based in England? Why not go somewhere else?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0033" trans="overlap">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I've I've got I run a company and I've got three other businesses going at the moment so I</u>
<u n="51" who="S0018">oh really? Blimey that's good what's that?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0033">um my parents well we all  we all  run a pub in <anon type="place"/> which is where I live</u>
<u n="53" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="54" who="S0033">trek here and back every single day</u>
<u n="55" who="S0018" trans="overlap">where is <anon type="place"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0033">it's ah do you know the M6 well?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0018">no not that well</u>
<u n="58" who="S0033">okay erm it's like in the middle from Birmingham and Wolverhampton</u>
<u n="59" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="60" who="S0033">it's up near <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="62" who="S0033">so it's in the middle of nowhere so it's a big drive here and back but yeah we run a pub and um my mum imports um jewellery like freshwater pearls and beads from China and sells them</u>
<u n="63" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh huh oh wow <pause dur="short"/> uh huh</u>
<u n="64" who="S0033">and my dad's a stand up comic and he still does it now</u>
<u n="65" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0033">and um I do gigs as well I play guitar and I sing so I go all over the place doing that</u>
<u n="67" who="S0018" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="68" who="S0033">and a just a do as much as I can to survive I suppose</u>
<u n="69" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And do you live around here?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0033">no</u>
<u n="71" who="S0018">you live by?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0033">I live in <anon type="place"/> still in the pub like</u>
<u n="73" who="S0018">ah okay</u>
<u n="74" who="S0033">so but um it's not great but</u>
<u n="75" who="S0018">no it's fine if you can you've obviously managed to get that balance between sport and ah enjoying yourself <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Go play tennis right now I'll have a pint</u>
<u n="76" who="S0033">yeah but um it's alright</u>
<u n="77" who="S0018">it's ah what what were you doing in France then?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0033">I was coaching tennis</u>
<u n="79" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="80" who="S0033">at one of the biggest academies in the world</u>
<u n="81" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="82" who="S0033">it's like one of the top five in the world and I loved it over there <pause dur="short"/> but it's expensive and and the job wasn't the greatest</u>
<u n="83" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="84" who="S0033">so at the end of the day all my friends left because the job wasn't the greatest and then I kinda was like I love it here but I'm not gonna stay here any longer it's everything kinda went sour</u>
<u n="85" who="S0018">oh what a shame <pause dur="short"/> whereabouts is that in France?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0033">um just next to Nice a little town called Sophia Antipolis</u>
<u n="87" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0033">it's like a big business complex and university type place</u>
<u n="89" who="S0018" trans="overlap">ah yeah <pause dur="short"/> one of those yeah like kind of it's got all the industrial parks and all the big businesses</u>
<u n="90" who="S0033" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and just hotels and businesses and schools and colleges</u>
<u n="91" who="S0018">aha</u>
<u n="92" who="S0033">it's just a massive town like that but it was only about twenty twenty-five minutes away from Nice and twenty minutes from Cannes and</u>
<u n="93" who="S0018">aha</u>
<u n="94" who="S0033">just a bit further inland but it was brilliant out there and I adored it <pause dur="short"/> absolutely adored it</u>
<u n="95" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Were they were all your clients like the CEOs of all these big</u>
<u n="96" who="S0033">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0018">japanese companies and stuff?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0033" trans="overlap">you'd like to think they're the CEOs <pause dur="short"/> whether or not their parents were doing a bit more dodgy business you have no idea</u>
<u n="99" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know that's the kinda idea I get from all those little well big complexes like that in France</u>
<u n="100" who="S0033" trans="overlap">well the thing is who's got</u>
<u n="101" who="S0018" trans="overlap">because they just seem really sterile and everybody seems like they are behaving themselves too much so what's going on under the surface</u>
<u n="102" who="S0033" trans="overlap">but the thing is is who who can afford thirty grand just to send their kids to play tennis for a year? They do their school and they play tennis but it's thirty grand and then they got to play extras for tournaments and whatever else the kids are doing but they're all Russian and Serbian and</u>
<u n="103" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0033">all sorts <pause dur="short"/> everyone from every country really</u>
<u n="105" who="S0018">and what they send their kids to that tennis school for a year or are the parents living there as well?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0033">no they just send them there <pause dur="short"/> like one a <trunc>mo</trunc> one the reason like I didn't like my job so much is because of what it entailed was I was a tennis coach coached like six to eight hours a day</u>
<u n="107" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0033">I lived in the dormitories with the kids and had to look after them until they went to sleep <pause dur="short"/> I was a taxi driver there and back from the airport every single time they um needed a taxi driver to any of the tournaments they needed to go to</u>
<u n="109" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0033">I I worked seven days a week</u>
<u n="111" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0033">which was nonstop ten twelve hours a day</u>
<u n="113" who="S0018">like a <trunc>surro</trunc> surrogate parent-cum-coach</u>
<u n="114" who="S0033">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know it was just you know I I don't think I had a day off in two years</u>
<u n="115" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0033">and the summer's intense over there because the amount of kids that they get to go over</u>
<u n="117" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0033">it's um two months of just you know you're looking after between eighty and a hundred and twenty kids a week</u>
<u n="119" who="S0018"><vocal desc="whistle"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0033">you've got maybe maybe eight staff</u>
<u n="121" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0033">at the place</u>
<u n="123" who="S0018" trans="overlap">frightening <pause dur="short"/> it's crazy isn't it?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0033">just got hundreds and hundreds of kids just passing in and out and you got eight hour day in thirty-six degree heat</u>
<u n="125" who="S0018">blimey</u>
<u n="126" who="S0033">and then you got to get back and look after them then look after them on the weekends as well</u>
<u n="127" who="S0018">and when do you get days off? Or time off?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0033" trans="overlap">you don't  you don't</u>
<u n="129" who="S0018">is that not against the law?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0033">well not for the way that they hired me no</u>
<u n="131" who="S0018">really? <vocal desc="laugh"/> What was it just ah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0033">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0018">hey would you like some paid work? Yes alright good was that a nod? Yes ok that's a contract there <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0033">they they they kinda dodgy in those places as well to be honest with you</u>
<u n="135" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0033">but erm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0018">was it like a chain of tennis courts or</u>
<u n="138" who="S0033" trans="overlap">no if anything they've only just branched out <pause dur="short"/> they've branched out to Paris now as well</u>
<u n="139" who="S0018">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0033">so they got um they're starting to get a bit bigger and stuff but it's only because where they are at the moment it's so expensive that they can't really run what they're doing down there cos they run it from a Mercure hotel <pause dur="short"/> at the back of this hotel they've got like sixteen courts at the back of it it's so beautiful it's just ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> proper red clay courts with everything um they have to hire that they have to hire a building at the university so everyone can stay there and also use the golf course cos it's also a joint golf academy as well</u>
<u n="141" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> is that where you were living? At the university? Nice <pause dur="short"/> nice in Nice <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0033">no it was beautiful <pause dur="short"/> I mean I loved it but just due to the fact that I was like nineteen twenty and I enjoyed going out and doing stuff that when you work for ten hours go out on a night and then try and wake up at six am the next morning and do it for the rest of the week especially when you go out two or three nights a week I mean at one point I had a band out there and we were doing three or four gigs a week so we'd be out till two AM and then up at six AM</u>
<u n="143" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm yep <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> gosh <pause dur="short"/> yeah you can only do that when you're nineteen <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0033"><trunc>Yea</trunc> I remember  I remember  the one summer I went back home I had two two weeks holiday back at home after the summer and I went home and I honest to God slept for two weeks just didn't wake up <pause dur="short"/> cos I'd been living off three hours sleep for two months</u>
<u n="145" who="S0018">mm nightmare <pause dur="short"/> you can't really function properly off that especially when you're looking after kids cos kids just suck so much energy out of you don't they they <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0033">and then just</u>
<u n="147" who="S0018">take your eye off them</u>
<u n="148" who="S0033">you you with all kinds of work there always ends up being the one kind of person who seems very incompetent at the job <pause dur="short"/> and you keep have to cover for them and I hated that over there so much cos I was working so hard over there <pause dur="short"/> there was one guy who was meant to be running like what we were doing and he was just never there but the problem was he was best friends with the boss</u>
<u n="149" who="S0018">aha <pause dur="short"/> difficult situation</u>
<u n="150" who="S0033">so I must have almost got him sacked about three times and the boss saved his bacon every time</u>
<u n="151" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="152" who="S0033">so he didn't like me very much</u>
<u n="153" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And do you speak French then?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0033">um I've gotten better at it yeah I mean the problem when I first got there was everyone wanted to learn English</u>
<u n="155" who="S0018">yes <pause dur="short"/> I've heard that too <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0033">I was in an international academy and I was one of the only coaches who knew English the rest of them were very bad disjointed English so I kinda taught everybody English and for the first six months or something didn't learn any of it myself</u>
<u n="157" who="S0018" trans="overlap">aha <pause dur="short"/> aha <pause dur="short"/> yeah were you actually <trunc>taug</trunc> was it were any of your students French or were they mostly international?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0033" trans="overlap">some of them where the funniest part about it actually was most of my kids were like <trunc>fore</trunc> like Serbia Russian something like that so they knew English as well as well it was one of the things some of them were French and wanted to learn English but I remember they lobbed me with a job erm coaching the local school kids</u>
<u n="159" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0033">so I had a bunch of six year olds who only spoke French <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> so there you go <pause dur="short"/> okay I don't know what I'm going to be doing here</u>
<u n="161" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0033">and they did that when I first got there so that was a difficult summer but it helped me out I mean having to learn the language that way is</u>
<u n="163" who="S0018">yeah good motivator <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0033" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> otherwise you've got a bunch of six year old kids just staring at you going I have no idea what you're talking about mate</u>
<u n="165" who="S0018">I did that I was erm I had a class the <trunc>th</trunc> for for one of the first classes I had for when I moved to Spain and hadn't learnt Spanish before <pause dur="short"/> I went and learnt it there while I was living there and yeah I had a group of eh six and seven year olds <pause dur="short"/> I was in an English class but yeah once they realised that I didn't speak any Spanish they really tried it on and then they realised that I was going to give it to them in English <trunc>r</trunc> regardless of the fact that I didn't speak any Spanish they were going to get it from me if they behaved badly <pause dur="short"/> in an in a language that they didn't understand but uh</u>
<u n="166" who="S0033" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0018">you can express annoyance in international language</u>
<u n="168" who="S0033">but the thing is body language  body language is  beautiful cos it works in any language</u>
<u n="169" who="S0018">yep <pause dur="short"/> it's true <pause dur="short"/>  it's true</u>
<u n="170" who="S0033">but erm yeah no I mean just I fell into tennis just because and I've been doing it ever since <pause dur="short"/> I I mean I started late <pause dur="short"/> I started late for what any any coach anybody in this country will tell you <pause dur="short"/> I started at thirteen and they all told me I'd never make it anywhere</u>
<u n="171" who="S0018">was that eh was that something your parents suggest you should do or was it something you wanted to do?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0033" trans="overlap">no It was  it was  quite strange I was a  I was a  cricket player when I was younger</u>
<u n="173" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0033">but I got a strange <trunc>in</trunc> injury to my leg and like kinda big mental block playing cricket so my dad suggested that I move to tennis <pause dur="short"/> I wanted to play football</u>
<u n="175" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0033">but we're Ozzies so he didn't really like football</u>
<u n="177" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0033">so he kinda shepherded me round that and got me into tennis and you know I I I played from I was thirteen until I was fifteen just a couple of times a week and stuff <pause dur="short"/> we ended up going er travelling quite far distances to go to squads and learn from some of the coaches <pause dur="short"/> and then when I was like fifteen I I quit school and I did <trunc>di</trunc> like distance education</u>
<u n="179" who="S0018">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0033">learning from home cos I did that in Australia anyway</u>
<u n="181" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="182" who="S0033">and erm I I did that from home so I trained eight hours a day got home and did my school work <pause dur="short"/> it just made it so much more simple because you can't get courts at night time you can't train at the times you want to after school and you're always tired after school</u>
<u n="183" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yep <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> so who schooled you was it um your parents or you had a</u>
<u n="184" who="S0033">myself</u>
<u n="185" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="186" who="S0033">it was distance education from Australia again because umm when I was living in Australia I lived on a bus <pause dur="short"/> like a tour bus and ah my mum used to teach me but they they do  they do  it quite well from Australia the the books and stuff are well written</u>
<u n="187" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh-uh <pause dur="short"/> so what were  what were  you living over there for?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0033">in Australia?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="190" who="S0033">because of my parents are Australian my whole family is Australian</u>
<u n="191" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="192" who="S0033">and I lived there till I was ten</u>
<u n="193" who="S0018">did you?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0033">mhm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0018">where you born in Britain?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0033">no</u>
<u n="197" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0033">I was born in <trunc>Austral</trunc> all my grandparents are English</u>
<u n="199" who="S0018">aha</u>
<u n="200" who="S0033">but all my other relatives are all Australian</u>
<u n="201" who="S0018">aha <pause dur="short"/> so what's your nationality?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0033">I've got both</u>
<u n="203" who="S0018">aha <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0033">I've got dual citizenship</u>
<u n="205" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="206" who="S0033">both passports</u>
<u n="207" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> But you'd say you're a British  you're a British  national as much as an Australian national or?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0033">I don't know  I don't know  I don't know if I've ever really felt at home in either place to be honest with you</u>
<u n="209" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm yeah when you live between two places it's always</u>
<u n="210" who="S0033">it's difficult because I grew up as an Ozzie I do  I do  feel Australian but I've lived a lot of my time here as well <pause dur="short"/> I lived a bit of time in France and I'd like to think I'm a bit French</u>
<u n="211" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Ooh la la <vocal desc="laugh"/> So how how come you ended up moving back to Britain?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0033">um my parents still lived here</u>
<u n="213" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0033">and when I  when I  quit my job in France I was I just needed to some stability again</u>
<u n="215" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> but why did they move over?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0033">why did they move over?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="218" who="S0033">we moved over here in 2000 cos of my dad's job because of comedy</u>
<u n="219" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0033">he wanted a different avenue to pursue</u>
<u n="221" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0018">so he went  he went  down the moving countries route and we moved over here <pause dur="short"/> a few years went past and and we bought a pub up in <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0033">mm mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0018">and that went really well and then we moved to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0033">worst decision of our lives</u>
<u n="227" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Why why did you go for <anon type="place"/> was it a researched <trunc>deci</trunc></u>
<u n="228" who="S0033" trans="overlap">because there was a <trunc>tenni</trunc> tennis centre there</u>
<u n="229" who="S0018" trans="overlap">ah okay</u>
<u n="230" who="S0033">there was a tennis centre there and we were travelling from <anon type="place"/> to there every single day and we figured hey we're living in a village we thought hey if we're living in a kind of town kind of area it can't do badly we'll just take the model that we've got here and put it in that pub down there <pause dur="short"/> died an absolute death <pause dur="short"/> oh my God it died</u>
<u n="231" who="S0018" trans="overlap">really? <vocal desc="laugh"/> What's <anon type="place"/> like?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0033">dirty</u>
<u n="233" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0033">it's just it's not a great place <pause dur="short"/> but uh it's getting better slowly <pause dur="short"/> but I mean things have been going better since my mum's like the pub's not really even a pub anymore</u>
<u n="235" who="S0018">what is it?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0033">it's like a bead shop brassiere type thing</u>
<u n="237" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0033">it's still got the beer and everything in it but because of my mum's beads and pearls she needs wall to wall in that now</u>
<u n="239" who="S0018" trans="overlap">aha <pause dur="short"/> oh wow</u>
<u n="240" who="S0033">all the women who come there love it and the guys don't mind getting dragged along because they can have a pint</u>
<u n="241" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That sounds like a winning solution</u>
<u n="242" who="S0033">so it's ah it's a good little  good little  one that one</u>
<u n="243" who="S0018">does your mum actually make up the necklaces and bracelets as well or?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0033">no we sell them wholesale</u>
<u n="245" who="S0018">ah okay</u>
<u n="246" who="S0033">we sell erm wholesale and people who either have small businesses or run shops of their own where they sell the made up stuff buy off us so <pause dur="short"/> but I mean she does fairs all over the country she's up in Scotland and God knows where selling the stuff all the time</u>
<u n="247" who="S0018">sounds like fun</u>
<u n="248" who="S0033">well it's not fun but it's something my a lot of my family's into</u>
<u n="249" who="S0018">yeah?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0033">my uncle in Australia and my cousin in America <pause dur="short"/> she had twenty-six stores at one point in America</u>
<u n="251" who="S0018" trans="overlap">blimey <pause dur="short"/> mhm <pause dur="short"/> and where are you family from in Australia cos my our family live out there as well?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0033">kind of all over the place but the majority of them are in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0018">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0033">the majority of the family live in <anon type="place"/> or off the coast on a couple of islands out there</u>
<u n="255" who="S0018">aha <pause dur="short"/> nice <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0033">so we're from out that way but there's some one of my mum's brothers lives up in <anon type="place"/> one in <anon type="place"/> erm couple I think my dad's brother lives in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0018">mhm <pause dur="short"/> mm my brother's in <anon type="place"/> over the other side</u>
<u n="258" who="S0033" trans="overlap">it's nice</u>
<u n="259" who="S0018">yeah lovely place <pause dur="short"/> and I never went to <anon type="place"/> but</u>
<u n="260" who="S0033">aw it's beautiful</u>
<u n="261" who="S0018">but went to <anon type="place"/> and the Barrier Reef and up to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0033">Sydney bores me it's like any other city in the entire world and</u>
<u n="263" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0033">just doesn't  just doesn't  do it for me <pause dur="short"/> that's why I liked Nice <pause dur="short"/> it was strange it was a very different place it wasn't like a city it was old it was very old and they kept it that way</u>
<u n="265" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yep yep Nice is lovely</u>
<u n="266" who="S0033" trans="overlap">it wasn't like they'd tried to build new buildings and tried to cram up the place it was just</u>
<u n="267" who="S0018">true but I guess it's got more history hasn't it?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0033">yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0018">it's cos the old quarter in Nice dates from quite a long time ago doesn't it?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0033" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I used to spend most of my time down there and I loved Cannes as well</u>
<u n="271" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="272" who="S0033">the promenade down there was beautiful</u>
<u n="273" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0033">ah but no I'd with me I'd never know <pause dur="short"/> never know where I'm headed me</u>
<u n="275" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0033">I'm twenty-one</u>
<u n="277" who="S0018">are you?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0033">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've a lot of life ahead of me <pause dur="short"/> I hope</u>
<u n="279" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And what are your plans? Do you think?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0033">no I have no I never have plans</u>
<u n="281" who="S0018">no?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0033">no but the one plan I had in my head is that I would like to buy a place in South France one day <pause dur="short"/> and like retire there</u>
<u n="283" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh sounds like a good plan</u>
<u n="284" who="S0033">but I would need so much money to do that <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to have to work very hard</u>
<u n="285" who="S0018">I think you might <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> You might have to coach tennis in your retirement</u>
<u n="286" who="S0033" trans="overlap">win the lottery <pause dur="short"/> no but like I mean still got the contacts over there I mean they're meant to be starting up a new Club Med <pause dur="short"/> have you ever heard of Club Med?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0018">uh-uh</u>
<u n="288" who="S0033">they're meant to be starting up a new Club Med tennis academy there</u>
<u n="289" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="290" who="S0033">in 2013 or something and</u>
<u n="291" who="S0018">isn't Club Med the kind of  kind of  a holiday you go on if you want to get drunk all the time?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0033">no I don't know if no it's it it depends <pause dur="short"/> I think there might be some of those ones but the the one of my friends is working in um Sandpiper Bay in Florida at the moment <pause dur="short"/> and erm it's it's a real tennis academy</u>
<u n="293" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="294" who="S0033">it's intense <pause dur="short"/> but at a place which is like a five star hotel with um five star golf course and everything just it's amazing and I had friends out there coaching in France who were going to people's houses and coaching and taking a hundred euros an hour</u>
<u n="295" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes wouldn't surprise me</u>
<u n="296" who="S0033">if you can live your life like that you'd be alright</u>
<u n="297" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yes definitely <pause dur="short"/> if you can get the contacts of the people who can pay that much money</u>
<u n="298" who="S0033">well you got to think realistically <pause dur="short"/> me being able to speak English it's all the ex-pat communities you want to be going to</u>
<u n="299" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="300" who="S0033">erm the people who who've moved over there in and have the money to spend on stuff like that</u>
<u n="301" who="S0018">yep <pause dur="short"/> then again I don't know what the ex-pat community is like nowadays <pause dur="short"/> I know it's in Spain it's withered considerably after the</u>
<u n="302" who="S0033">it's all in China these days</u>
<u n="303" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0033">oh all over there <pause dur="short"/> it's um it's a different place over there</u>
<u n="305" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="306" who="S0033">I went over there for like a week</u>
<u n="307" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="308" who="S0033">that was strange</u>
<u n="309" who="S0018">working or holidaying?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0033" trans="overlap">kind of yeah <pause dur="short"/> with my parents</u>
<u n="311" who="S0018">oh to find the beads</u>
<u n="312" who="S0033">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0033">but that was like six years ago was the last time I went to Australia <pause dur="short"/> haven't seen any of my family in six years</u>
<u n="315" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh-uh <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="316" who="S0033">Don't get the chance <pause dur="short"/> it's uh too expensive <pause dur="short"/> the flights over there and</u>
<u n="317" who="S0018" trans="overlap">it is <pause dur="short"/> yeah my brother  my brother  always says oh are you coming to visit me and I'm like erm</u>
<u n="318" who="S0033">I don't know it's not just that it's</u>
<u n="319" who="S0018">have I got a spare couple of thousand in a month? No</u>
<u n="320" who="S0033">it's not just  it's not just  that you know it's also the the fact that if you go to Australia with the jet lag and all that lot you don't want to be going there for a week or two weeks you want to be going for a month</u>
<u n="321" who="S0018">definitely</u>
<u n="322" who="S0033">or six weeks or something and then to get that time off work is almost impossible these days</u>
<u n="323" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah no the last time I went was I think it was two weeks and I spent the first week just feeling absolutely exhausted cause of the flight</u>
<u n="324" who="S0033">it just knocks you out cos it's it's like ten hours in front <pause dur="short"/> you know is it ten hours in front? It's almost the opposite of the clock you've gotta change your entire body clock</u>
<u n="325" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but even the just thirty hours in transit i <pause dur="short"/>e <pause dur="short"/> in you know travelling and</u>
<u n="326" who="S0033">I'm alright with that cos I just sleep as soon as the plane turns its engine on gone</u>
<u n="327" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh no no I was uh on I was travelling alone so I was had to sit next to other people who were travelling alone and I was sitting next to this huge fat smelly guy <vocal desc="laugh"/> So for want of a better word he smelt <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0033">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0018">and uh he ate really loudly and he kinda just took up so much place I was couldn't really relax on the way over</u>
<u n="330" who="S0033">I sat I solve all those problems I always get the window seat and I take an iPod with me <pause dur="short"/> stick the earphones goodnight to the world</u>
<u n="331" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You can</u>
<u n="332" who="S0033" trans="overlap">I normally put a jacket over my face or something so nobody can touch me</u>
<u n="333" who="S0018">well a friend recommended that I take a piece of string and just sit there with a piece of string <trunc>hang</trunc> hanging out of one half and just sit there looking like I'm crazy and then no-one would want to sit next to me <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="334" who="S0033">and the the the especially like the short transit flights are it's a joke <pause dur="short"/> I fall asleep when the engine turns on and I wake up when the plane hits the tarmac</u>
<u n="335" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0033">it doesn't matter if it's a two hour flight like I'll get on and go fall asleep and then boom oh well look I'm here <pause dur="short"/> quality</u>
<u n="337" who="S0018" trans="overlap">you're lucky <pause dur="short"/> very lucky <pause dur="short"/> hmm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0033">I remember the amount of flights I've caught from here and France and back no luggage whatsoever <pause dur="short"/> just walked on with a tennis racket</u>
<u n="339" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0033">being a tennis coach just walked on with a tennis racket sat down gone to sleep woken back up got off the plane and gone to work</u>
<u n="341" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/>That's a good commute <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> So I guess you didn't get to come over and visit your family much when you were living in France did you?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0033">I don't know whether it was a good thing or not</u>
<u n="343" who="S0018" trans="overlap">they go over to you? <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> did they go over to you at all?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0033">yeah yeah they came and visit me quite a lot I mean it was a good little trip for them you know <pause dur="short"/> little few cheap hotels in the area and they could just come and stay with me for a bit and</u>
<u n="345" who="S0018">I might be going to Nice at some point in the future I've got a a friend well I was friends with a family a Russian family when I was living in Barcelona I was teaching them English</u>
<u n="346" who="S0033">yeah?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0018">and erm they were from Uzbekistan And they'd moved away from Russia because they didn't he had a building construction industry uh company and he didn't want to be involved in all the corruption and scamming and that was going on <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0033" trans="overlap">with the mafia</u>
<u n="349" who="S0018">erm they moved to Barcelona to France erm Aix-En-Provence?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0033">mm</u>
<u n="351" who="S0018">and erm three years later he found his wife had been blown up in their car and she obviously died erm and then the next day he was put in prison for it <pause dur="short"/> when there was no evidence whatsoever that he'd done it he'd he'd got a witness saying that he was somewhere else and he's been battling this for the past seven years</u>
<u n="352" who="S0033">was that French police or?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0018">french police yeah <pause dur="short"/> they obviously just didn't you know they probably sniffed that it might be a mafia type crime and they just didn't want to touch it and</u>
<u n="354" who="S0033">the French police are are quite strange the way they go about things because they're very laid back about everything <pause dur="short"/> you don't see police cars driving up and down the road you don't see people patrolling you won't see them walking through the streets <pause dur="short"/> the one thing I have seen I think I was in Lyon at the time and you don't see anybody and then this guy's walking down the street I saw a SWAT van pull up about twenty guys jump out of it and just bang grab this guy throw him in the back of the van and see you later <pause dur="short"/> and I'm like wow</u>
<u n="355" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="356" who="S0033">it's either nothing or everything <unclear/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah they are <pause dur="short"/> hard full on tactics to <pause dur="short"/> when I was um I used to work in Disneyland in Paris when I was at uni and uh one summer the Americans who worked there and lived in the same residence as me decided they wanted to have a a fourth of July party <pause dur="short"/> and so it was crazy I mean it was like a university residence and there was a rock band on one of the balconies and they were chucking fireworks into the crowd below and there was a lot of people around drinking and just having fun and exactly what the French people had were gonna do for their July the fourteenth holiday but somebody phoned the police and nobody came but about an hour later the CRS you know the riot squad they arrived and they just put themselves in position with their full riot gear and like everybody was just like oh what's going on carried on drinking and they just stayed there they didn't do anything they were just waiting for something to happen</u>
<u n="358" who="S0033" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> to happen</u>
<u n="359" who="S0018">and one of the drunken American guys decided it would be a good idea to pull a moonie at them and so he just <trunc>work</trunc> went stand in front of them pulled his trousers down in front of them and they just absolutely leapt at him <pause dur="short"/> they they got the dogs on him the tear gas was going and from that <trunc>tot</trunc> that tiny action of</u>
<u n="360" who="S0033" trans="overlap">no they're just waiting for something <pause dur="short"/> give them an excuse and they'll go for it</u>
<u n="361" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but they were brutal absolutely brutal it was crazy <pause dur="short"/> then again it was a stupid thing to do to go and moon the French CRS <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0033">you can't help people when they start to drink</u>
<u n="363" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> But I guess in the place that you were the the Anatalie? What was it Sophia Anatalie</u>
<u n="364" who="S0033"><trunc>So</trunc> Sophia Antipolis</u>
<u n="365" who="S0018">that's it <pause dur="short"/> um I guess there were like private security police and</u>
<u n="366" who="S0033">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0018">stuff like that cause like in some areas like that the police don't go there cause it's such an established community</u>
<u n="368" who="S0033" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no I mean they have security guards everywhere for everything you know even at the university they've got their own personal security guards but thing was as well I was best friends with them</u>
<u n="369" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0033">I mean we had a swimming pool like exactly next to our complex and we used to go swimming in that three o'clock in the morning <pause dur="short"/> me and some guys and the security guards eh three o'clock in the morning let's go for a swim</u>
<u n="371" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0033">but um just it was it wasn't too bad it was not like they don't enforce anything but I think I only ever annoyed them once</u>
<u n="373" who="S0018">mm what did you do? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0033">I was playing like Playstation games at like two in the morning and I had my balcony window open and shouting and screaming as you do and they just come up and started going mental to me cos I was waking up the entire <vocal desc="laugh"/> camp</u>
<u n="375" who="S0018">oops <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0033">campus</u>
<u n="377" who="S0018">and you were shouting at your?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0033">yeah my friend</u>
<u n="379" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> naughty boy that's no example to set to children</u>
<u n="380" who="S0033"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it was funny though <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0018">so what's your work schedule like here?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0033">I work six days a week</u>
<u n="383" who="S0018">yeah?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0033">I have a Tuesday off which is possibly the worst day in the world to have off cos you can do nothing on a Tuesday but no I work six days a week and I'll be in for like twelve hours every day</u>
<u n="385" who="S0018">really? That's a lot of work</u>
<u n="386" who="S0033">I'm not working that much I'm just here</u>
<u n="387" who="S0018" trans="overlap">no?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0033">but the problem is cos I live so far away I can't go home I can't  I can't  really do anything I just have to sort of suck it up and try and get myself more work every time I'm down here</u>
<u n="389" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> so how does it work do they feed you clients or what?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0033">no <pause dur="short"/> I have to do it all myself</u>
<u n="391" who="S0018">and how do you go about that?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0033">talk to people <pause dur="short"/> be around as much as possible <pause dur="short"/> give out free lessons every once in a while to try and get people involved in it <pause dur="short"/> mm anything really I mean I do a lot of groups for this place</u>
<u n="393" who="S0018">uh huh <pause dur="short"/> is that organised groups that they organise for you or?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0033">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so that's all the money that they earn and I have to do that instead of like a rental fee</u>
<u n="395" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="396" who="S0033">and I so I work all those groups and you can pick a few lessons out of groups and do other stuff so it's okay that way as well</u>
<u n="397" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="398" who="S0033">but erm it's not bad <pause dur="short"/> it's not bad it's not brilliant but better than anything else I can get in this area</u>
<u n="399" who="S0018">yes it's not fantastic for work round here is it?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0033">I mean I'll never <trunc>loo</trunc> I'll never be out of a job as a tennis coach but it's it's not easy to get ahead in England as a tennis coach <pause dur="short"/> not very easy</u>
<u n="401" who="S0018" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> oh well you're not if you're not eh tied to England you could</u>
<u n="402" who="S0033">no I mean</u>
<u n="403" who="S0018">consider going other places</u>
<u n="404" who="S0033">no I mean I'm just I'm I'm seeing what with my other businesses and stuff I'm seeing how that pans out really <pause dur="short"/> they kick off at me makes it worthwhile staying here if they don't I can be gone tomorrow</u>
<u n="405" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> well then asleep on an airplane <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0033" trans="overlap">and get <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> asleep on an <trunc>airothan</trunc> airplane with nothing packed but my tennis rackets and my guitar and I'll be alright</u>
<u n="407" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> where would you like to end up apart from retired in the South of France? Where would you like to work?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0033">oh Florida I could go there for a couple of years see my sister and work over there it'd be mental over there</u>
<u n="409" who="S0018">that would be cool</u>
<u n="410" who="S0033">and Dubai I wouldn't mind visiting there for a bit <pause dur="short"/> be a bit crazy with laws though</u>
<u n="411" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0033">not to to sure I'm keen on their laws</u>
<u n="413" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You'd be like yeah I live in England in a pub they'd be like what? Cut his hands off <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0033">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but ah or in Australia <pause dur="short"/> I mean I've got all my family there I could go live with them and work over there but the thing is even there tax and everything has been hiked up over the past couple of years</u>
<u n="415" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0033">it's killing the country as well over there</u>
<u n="417" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> and what's your sister doing in Florida then? What's she studying?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0033">um American university is strange</u>
<u n="419" who="S0018">yeah?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0033">they study like everything</u>
<u n="421" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0033">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you don't major until like your last two years or something</u>
<u n="423" who="S0018">oh really?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0033">so she's there for four years and for the first two years you know you study everything <pause dur="short"/> you do maths English <trunc>whate</trunc> you've gotta choose like a bunch of classes to go to and you've gotta fill it up to fifteen credits so each class amounts to a different amount of credits so</u>
<u n="425" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mhm <pause dur="short"/> and what's she thinking of majoring in?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0033">she wants to do fashion design</u>
<u n="427" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="428" who="S0033" trans="overlap">Don't ask me why but she wants to do it <pause dur="short"/> but erm she can only stay in Tampa for two years cos it's a junior college</u>
<u n="429" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="430" who="S0033">because she <trunc>fin</trunc> she quit school after GCSEs and didn't do A-Levels</u>
<u n="431" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mhm <pause dur="short"/> aha</u>
<u n="432" who="S0033">Cos of tennis <pause dur="short"/> she couldn't go straight into university <pause dur="short"/> they're very very very um tight on their laws on who can go to where and what <pause dur="short"/> like her tennis standard puts her in a division one school in America but she has to go to junior college for two years first and complete that before she can move onto the last two years at a division one school</u>
<u n="433" who="S0018">oh right and will she do that in America do you think? Will she be allowed to?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0033" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0018">hey</u>
<u n="436" who="S0033">she'll move she'll <trunc>mo</trunc> I mean she's got the highest they do it on grade point average GPA</u>
<u n="437" who="S0018">oh yeah yep</u>
<u n="438" who="S0033">she's got the highest GPA out of any athlete in her school</u>
<u n="439" who="S0018">oh fantastic</u>
<u n="440" who="S0033">so I think she got something ridiculous like a five point two which I think is the highest you can get <pause dur="short"/> she got straight As in everything basically</u>
<u n="441" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="442" who="S0033">feel quite proud of her for that to be honest with you</u>
<u n="443" who="S0018">what's she studying at the moment then? All the?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0033">uh she's doing mathematics and psychology English history <pause dur="short"/> I think she's doing American history or something I don't know <pause dur="short"/> a bunch of other things I can't remember</u>
<u n="445" who="S0018">and is she enjoying the the culture?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0033">yeah she seems to be enjoying <pause dur="short"/> I think it's just it's a tough life as an athlete cos all you do is study and train</u>
<u n="447" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0033">study train and compete <pause dur="short"/> if you enjoy the life you can get along with it I mean I was offered it so many times but I knew that when I  when I quit tennis and I was like a model professional and I was playing I was  I was  doing eight hours a day didn't drink ate healthily never went out just kept myself good and then when I quit tennis I just went off the rails</u>
<u n="449" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0033">I just went well from one  from one  like extreme to the other just absolutely went off <pause dur="short"/> took me a while to get back from there to be honest with you</u>
<u n="451" who="S0018">really? <vocal desc="laugh"/> how long and how bad did you get?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0033">oh it was bad</u>
<u n="453" who="S0018">you've not been deported that's a good sign <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0033" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was  it was it was  bad especially when I was in France <pause dur="short"/> couple of bad relationships along the way and I was off</u>
<u n="455" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0033">erm but uh no it was  it was  but uh I got  I got  myself back and uh I just knew I could never go to school I know I never enjoyed it</u>
<u n="457" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="458" who="S0033">never enjoyed studying</u>
<u n="459" who="S0018">I don't enjoy studying either no</u>
<u n="460" who="S0033">for me I enjoy working <pause dur="short"/> very much <pause dur="short"/> I enjoy working and I enjoy doing stuff <pause dur="short"/> I mean I have one day off a week now because I know my body needs the rest</u>
<u n="461" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="462" who="S0033">Seven days a week just kills me but even the one day off a week yesterday just didn't know what to do with myself just pacing up and down the house cause it was raining outside and I had nothing to do</u>
<u n="463" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="464" who="S0033">I just it drives me insane <pause dur="short"/> I can't deal with it I love just working or having something to do even when I'm here and I've got a couple of hours off I'll help somebody</u>
<u n="465" who="S0018">aww</u>
<u n="466" who="S0033">I'll be like <trunc>wha</trunc> <trunc>wha</trunc> what are you <trunc>do</trunc> what do you need doing? Give me something to do</u>
<u n="467" who="S0018" trans="overlap">that's very nice <pause dur="short"/> and what classes have you got today?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0033">erm I've got a lesson at three a private individual lesson at four another individual then I've got a group of red kids which is like five to eight year olds <pause dur="short"/> six to <trunc>sev</trunc> uh five till six six to seven is a group of orange which is like eight to nine <pause dur="short"/> then I do a drill session at seven which is just anybody adults and then uh I think I'm doing the tennis social tonight</u>
<u n="469" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mhm <pause dur="short"/> ooh lovely <pause dur="short"/> what's that involve?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0033" trans="overlap">means I have to stand around and tell people what court to go and play each other on</u>
<u n="471" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Did you come to the Rackets' Dinner or whatever it was?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0033">yeah I was singing in that</u>
<u n="473" who="S0018">you were singing?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0033" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they keep  they keep  hiring me <pause dur="short"/> they figured out that I sing and they just they hire me at every opportunity</u>
<u n="475" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0033">they've realised I'm like a very cheap alternative to anybody else that they can find</u>
<u n="477" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> You should bill them properly <pause dur="short"/> surely?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0033">we work out things for</u>
<u n="479" who="S0018">and how did that go? How was the dinner-dance?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0033">so <pause dur="short"/> it was good <pause dur="short"/> it was good but uh decided to do something a little different see normally I play guitar and we just kind of do covers and all that sort of stuff but erm when I went to dinner-dance I decided I was going to do more of a sort of like a jazzy Michael Buble Sinatra tribute act type thing so it was  it was uh kinda new ground for me</u>
<u n="481" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> aha and how did that go the new ground?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0033">everyone else seemed to like it <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>di</trunc> wasn't too impressed myself but <pause dur="short"/> I think it needed a bit of work</u>
<u n="483" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Was that you were singing and playing the guitar?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0033" trans="overlap">no no I wasn't playing guitar</u>
<u n="485" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="486" who="S0033">it was just to like backing tracks and stuff just</u>
<u n="487" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="488" who="S0033">Cos unfortunately I can't find anybody in this area who can play instruments to make a band</u>
<u n="489" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="490" who="S0033">but um I got an agent at the moment he keeps getting me gigs all round the country</u>
<u n="491" who="S0018">oh really?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0033">yeah</u>
<u n="493" who="S0018">what playing to backing tracks or?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0033" trans="overlap">no playing like guitar</u>
<u n="495" who="S0018">and what kind of stuff do you play when you play your guitar?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0033" trans="overlap">everything</u>
<u n="497" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="498" who="S0033">just about everything and anything <pause dur="short"/> people go can you play this and I go yeah yeah I can <pause dur="short"/> I've got a memory which is really strange <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what I did yesterday but I can remember about three hundred songs</u>
<u n="499" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0033">always had a memory that's it just remembers music more than anything <pause dur="short"/> well I grew up with it <pause dur="short"/> my mum was a singer in a band featuring</u>
<u n="501" who="S0018">mhm?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0033">my dad a comedian so it's just entertainment my whole life</u>
<u n="503" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you're an entertainer <pause dur="short"/> so what yeah where does he  where does he  do his gigs and stuff?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0033">all over the country still</u>
<u n="505" who="S0018">yeah?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0033">I mean he could be on telly and doing a lot of that sort of stuff but he doesn't want to <pause dur="short"/> he's sixty-four now he still headlines corporate gigs and he's sixty-four he's like the oldest comedian on tour at the moment</u>
<u n="507" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0033" trans="overlap">on the  on the  circuit</u>
<u n="509" who="S0018">what kind of sense of humour has he got?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0033">erm <pause dur="short"/> I don't think he would want pasted as blue but it's very it's kind of political I suppose</u>
<u n="511" who="S0018">uh-uh</u>
<u n="512" who="S0033">he's had to change it a lot because a lot of it applied to Australia</u>
<u n="513" who="S0018">uh-uh</u>
<u n="514" who="S0033">I think  I think  he might refer to himself as an anarchist <pause dur="short"/> maybe a bit like that I don't know but</u>
<u n="515" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0033">um comedy's changed over the last decade <pause dur="short"/> it's stand-up comedy is just sketches these days it's all storytelling and personal experiences and stuff that you can relate to much like music is these days as well <pause dur="short"/> it's not so much one-liners and pub jokes any more</u>
<u n="517" who="S0018">has he been <trunc>ad</trunc>  has he been  able to adapt to that easily?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0033">yeah I mean he was doing it all along anyway really <pause dur="short"/> he's he's been through a few changes in his sort of comedy over the time he's been doing it but I mean he's been doing it what forty years now or something <pause dur="short"/> he knows the the scene inside out</u>
<u n="519" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="520" who="S0033">but he hates it these days he only does it for the money</u>
<u n="521" who="S0018">aww <pause dur="short"/> does he do it with musical accompaniment too?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0033" trans="overlap">he used to <pause dur="short"/> I mean my my dad in Australia he was  he was  that big you know like Reading and Leeds festivals and stuff?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0018">aha</u>
<u n="524" who="S0033">he used to headline the equivalent in Australia He was huge</u>
<u n="525" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mhm <pause dur="short"/> oh brilliant <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0033">seriously <pause dur="short"/> we we spent we'd spend the whole year on tour cos you but he'd be booked out the whole year we'd just travel from place to place  to place  for all these gigs <pause dur="short"/> and he'd do it with a guy <pause dur="short"/> some guy would play guitar and sing <pause dur="short"/> so it was kinda uh a cabaret I suppose type show <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="527" who="S0018">and when he gets home from work is he really serious <vocal desc="laugh"/>? Or does he continue cracking jokes all the time?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0033">ah he doesn't crack jokes but he's not really serious he's just a he's a business man dad is <pause dur="short"/> what everything's always about <pause dur="short"/> where to go from here</u>
<u n="529" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="530" who="S0033">just unfortunately he's not a very good investor <pause dur="short"/> he ah spends the money when he has it <pause dur="short"/> he likes to live</u>
<u n="531" who="S0018" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> oh well live for the moment <pause dur="short"/> it's not a bad philosophy</u>
<u n="532" who="S0033">it's not a bad philosophy but I mean he's been a millionaire twice in his life the unfortunate part is he's been broke three times</u>
<u n="533" who="S0018">oh no <vocal desc="laugh"/> What he's been a millionaire off his success on the comedy circuit?</u>
<u n="534" who="S0033">mhm</u>
<u n="535" who="S0018">oh wow</u>
<u n="536" who="S0033">he was huge <pause dur="short"/> t-shirts</u>
<u n="537" who="S0018">uh-uh</u>
<u n="538" who="S0033">videos CDs the lot</u>
<u n="539" who="S0018">but did he enjoy his millions that's the important question?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0033">I've no idea cos it wasn't while I was around <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0018">aww <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> You missed that</u>
<u n="542" who="S0033">I missed that part</u>
<u n="543" who="S0018">shame</u>
<u n="544" who="S0033">I mean when I was younger we were quite well off  when I was younger we were quite well off  but one of the reasons we moved to England was we lost everything over there</u>
<u n="545" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0033">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's why we needed a change</u>
<u n="547" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> why was that was there some kind of financial crisis?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0033">nah <pause dur="short"/> agent</u>
<u n="549" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="550" who="S0033">can't trust them</u>
<u n="551" who="S0018">as far as you can throw them <pause dur="short"/> and has he been doing it himself then over here has he been promoting himself?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0033" trans="overlap">yeah he's he's got a couple of agents over here but he just he doesn't do it that big and he doesn't want to go that big anymore he just  he just  sort of mills along these days</u>
<u n="553" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="554" who="S0033">but I mean both my parents just don't know how to relax <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> work</u>
<u n="555" who="S0018" trans="overlap">really? Oh what a shame <pause dur="short"/> you would have thought that they'd have got that down to pat by now</u>
<u n="556" who="S0033" trans="overlap">yeah like seven seven days a week just as much as they can working</u>
<u n="557" who="S0018">then again Mr who says he works six days a week and then uh <vocal desc="laugh"/> doesn't know how to relax on his day off</u>
<u n="558" who="S0033" trans="overlap">I think uh  I think  I got that from my parents to be honest with you</u>
<u n="559" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="560" who="S0033">wish I'd parents who knew how to relax a little bit <pause dur="short"/> I mean I get home and end up cleaning the entire house cleaning the car cleaning everything and just uh it's still only like twelve and I'm going what can I do now?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0018">aww <pause dur="short"/> hmm yes I guess when you're a tennis coach the last thing you want to do on your day off is go and play <vocal desc="laugh"/> tennis</u>
<u n="562" who="S0033" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the worst thing with me is like since I quit tennis and um when I quit tennis I still stayed in the gym quite a bit and uh but then for some reason I just stopped completely <pause dur="short"/> and uh since then I don't I mean I work for David Lloyd and I've been in the gym twice in two years <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I mean that's bad  that's bad  I've used the pool maybe three times <pause dur="short"/> I've used the gym twice and I work in this place six days a week</u>
<u n="563" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh but you get <pause dur="short"/> you get free access don't you?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0033" trans="overlap">yep <pause dur="short"/> I just don't touch any of it <pause dur="short"/> I've never been to a class here I've never done anything here <pause dur="short"/> because <trunc>th</trunc> the thing is I mean I run around the court all day</u>
<u n="565" who="S0018" trans="overlap">no oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="566" who="S0033">I run around the court all day and <trunc>th</trunc> the last thing I want to do at the end of the day is go and run some more to be honest with you</u>
<u n="567" who="S0018">true</u>
<u n="568" who="S0033">but the things is I'm not as fit as I used to be so <unclear/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0018" trans="overlap">hmm</u>
<u n="570" who="S0033">get's me down a little bit but then again I'm just too lazy to get myself in the gym</u>
<u n="571" who="S0018">get one of the personal trainers on your case</u>
<u n="572" who="S0033"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Might try and trade off for tennis lessons</u>
<u n="573" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="574" who="S0033">I'll teach you how to play tennis if you get me fit again</u>
<u n="575" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well they'll probably just say just carry the kettle bells around the court when you're training <vocal desc="laugh"/> So what time did you arrive this morning then if you're leaving so late tonight?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0033">uh started at quarter to nine this morning</u>
<u n="577" who="S0018">in the morning?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0033">and I finish at ten</u>
<u n="579" who="S0018">oh my life</u>
<u n="580" who="S0033">then it takes me an hour to get home so I'll be back at eleven</u>
<u n="581" who="S0018">God And uh but have you got did you have like a lesson early this morning or something?</u>
<u n="582" who="S0033">I had a lesson at quarter to nine and then uh a lesson at ten and then nothing till two then this and then I'm on court three till ten now</u>
<u n="583" who="S0018">blimey</u>
<u n="584" who="S0033">and that's a solid seven hours on court</u>
<u n="585" who="S0018" trans="overlap">that is solid isn't it? Do you is there anywhere you can take a nap round here?</u>
<u n="586" who="S0033">not really <pause dur="short"/> I've got my car out back</u>
<u n="587" who="S0018">aww <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="588" who="S0033">it serves alright sometimes <pause dur="short"/> I used to have a big Vauxhall Vivaro van and I honest to God had a double bed mattress in the back of it</u>
<u n="589" who="S0018" trans="overlap">aha <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0033">so when I was driving that around I used to just whenever I had a couple of hours off I'd jump in the back of that fall asleep and wake up again and go back to work</u>
<u n="591" who="S0018">it's a good idea <pause dur="short"/> but why don't you I mean what do you do with your time off if you've got if you had nothing for what three four hours?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0033">nothing</u>
<u n="593" who="S0018">and don't you like go in the spa or go for a swim?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0033" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> it's too much effort</u>
<u n="595" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="596" who="S0033">I just go and sit down somewhere</u>
<u n="597" who="S0018">you go and sit down somewhere</u>
<u n="598" who="S0033">I go and sit down somewhere and do some work doing something</u>
<u n="599" who="S0018">and do they feed you here?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0033">no</u>
<u n="601" who="S0018">you have to bring your own stuff? Do you get a discount?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0033">uh very minimal</u>
<u n="603" who="S0018">yeah?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0033">fifteen per cent or something</u>
<u n="605" who="S0018">that's a shame</u>
<u n="606" who="S0033">with these prices it's not even worth it</u>
<u n="607" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah true <pause dur="short"/> mm aw you should take advantage of your time and the free time you have and the cos they've got some fantastic um installations haven't they like swimming pools and</u>
<u n="608" who="S0033">hey if it was sunny outside I would've been outside sunbathing that's what I would have been doing</u>
<u n="609" who="S0018">mm well</u>
<u n="610" who="S0033" trans="overlap">the weather has just decided to give it one again</u>
<u n="611" who="S0018">what a shame eh? Last week it was gorgeous I got sunburn sitting out there for forty-five minutes <pause dur="short"/> and uh when do they open the swimming pool?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0033" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's meant to be open now</u>
<u n="613" who="S0018">oh is it? Yeah just now that the weather's getting crappy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="614" who="S0033" trans="overlap">it's meant to open first of April but uh I don't know what's going on with it <pause dur="short"/> but yeah interesting to anybody listening to this because my accent changes every five minutes</u>
<u n="615" who="S0018">it does <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="616" who="S0033">I've no idea why <pause dur="short"/> it's cos I I travelled the country playing tennis <pause dur="short"/> I got friends from all over the place and I used to spend weeks and weeks in Wales and up North and then down South and Bristol and then London and</u>
<u n="617" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yep <pause dur="short"/> oh really? mm <trunc>you</trunc> you're a linguistic nomad</u>
<u n="618" who="S0033">I think so <pause dur="short"/> my accent tends to change sometimes I sound like I'm from up North sometimes I sound like I'm Welsh</u>
<u n="619" who="S0018">sometimes you have got a Brummie twang</u>
<u n="620" who="S0033">I've been told  I've been told  that like that like I sound like like I'm from the West Country at one point <pause dur="short"/> I'm like I definitely do not sound like that</u>
<u n="621" who="S0018" trans="overlap">it's true yeah sometimes <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0033">it's just such a strange accent</u>
<u n="623" who="S0018">and uh I thought maybe there was <trunc>som</trunc> something Eastern European going on at some point</u>
<u n="624" who="S0033">there probably is I pick up  I pick up  things without knowing it <pause dur="short"/> think that's got a lot to do with my music and stuff though</u>
<u n="625" who="S0018">yeah having a musical ear is that's very</u>
<u n="626" who="S0033" trans="overlap">makes me sound like a mongrel in my accent</u>
<u n="627" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> woof woof <pause dur="short"/> okay right well you have to go teach soon don't you?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0033">yeah</u>
<u n="629" who="S0018">so I'll let you go</u>
</body>
</text>
