<text id="SJWU">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:28:19</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-23</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0482 S0483</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Life, family, work</topics>
		<activity>Talking while cooking.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0482">
				<exactage>37</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Guildford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Post Doc Researcher, Health Pyschologist</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Rudimentary; French -- almost  conversational</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0483">
				<exactage>37</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Bromsgrove</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Assessment Manager (Education)</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Rudimentary; German -- Rudimentary; Spanish -- Rudimentary</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0482">right</u>
<u n="2" who="S0483">yeah looking at the erm the space station I'll show you it's just on this bit here erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah he's tweeted saying that er <pause dur="short"/> you can see the snowstorm from space where is it? it is the</u>
<u n="3" who="S0482" trans="overlap">who the Brit?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0483" trans="overlap">the the man</u>
<u n="5" who="S0482" trans="overlap">the British astronaut</u>
<u n="6" who="S0483">I don't know if he's British but he's a man in space <pause dur="short"/> it's Scott Kelly <pause dur="short"/> see?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0482">yeah that's pretty snowy <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm not a meteorologist</u>
<u n="8" who="S0483">yeah well <pause dur="short"/> yep very snowy <pause dur="short"/> so what did you think of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house then?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0482">yeah I loved it</u>
<u n="10" who="S0483">it's really erm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0482" trans="overlap">really cool yeah <pause dur="long"/> I liked their erm <pause dur="short"/> er their <pause dur="short"/> what do you call it? entertaining room <pause dur="short"/> function room</u>
<u n="12" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah it was gorgeous <pause dur="short"/> I imagine I imagine it could get quite got in the summer they'll have to erm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0482" trans="overlap">did you see they had erm <pause dur="short"/> er concertina doors?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0483">no I didn't</u>
<u n="15" who="S0482" trans="overlap">for the whole yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0483" trans="overlap">oh really? oh wow no I didn't spot that oh well that is going to be special then isn't it?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0483">I mean actually you know with the erm <pause dur="short"/> with the all the Velux's open and the doors open it won't get so hot will it? but I mean you know</u>
<u n="19" who="S0482" trans="overlap">no I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did say he thought it would get <pause dur="short"/> hot</u>
<u n="20" who="S0483">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0482" trans="overlap">when he when they went to see it first I think in the summer he said it was very hot but</u>
<u n="22" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0482">they haven't you know the blinds and the Velux's weren't there</u>
<u n="24" who="S0483">yeah <pause dur="short"/> particularly if you sort of I know I don't know if it was me I'd certainly have a few more plants in that room because it's</u>
<u n="25" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0483">you know</u>
<u n="27" who="S0482">yeah but they're not terribly planty</u>
<u n="28" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I don't think they are terribly plenty no</u>
<u n="29" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0483">no definitely not cor no lovely yeah very <pause dur="short"/> very countrysidey</u>
<u n="31" who="S0482">yeah it was and and it's a really nice <pause dur="short"/> feel of being out in the country and</u>
<u n="32" who="S0483">yeah <pause dur="long"/> mm it was nice so what are we having? what are you cooking?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0482">Thai chicken curry</u>
<u n="34" who="S0483">chicken curry I thought you said fish?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0482">Thai fish curry</u>
<u n="36" who="S0483">Thai fish curry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0482">who said to put chicken <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> excellent and er <pause dur="short"/> beer <pause dur="short"/> gin and tonic? <pause dur="short"/> wine?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0482">all the above erm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0483" trans="overlap">which do you prefer?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0482">I don't know maybe a beer it's sort of appropriate it always feels appropriate with a er <pause dur="short"/> thai curry</u>
<u n="42" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> consider it done oh</u>
<u n="43" who="S0482">it's also a bit it's a bit more cost effective</u>
<u n="44" who="S0483">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> do you want it in a glass?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0482">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh right I see okay</u>
<u n="46" who="S0483" trans="overlap">well if we could share shall we share this first one <pause dur="short"/> thus keeping it fairly cold and then share the second one</u>
<u n="47" who="S0482">okay</u>
<u n="48" who="S0483">right where's the little glasses?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0482">the Chinese think of everything</u>
<u n="50" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0482">but we're not Chinese <pause dur="short"/> we must have forgotten something then</u>
<u n="52" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0482">it's a Goon Show thing</u>
<u n="54" who="S0483">is it?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0482">I wouldn't expect you to appreciate it</u>
<u n="56" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no no well I wasn't middle middle class upbringing was it?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0482">yes you did</u>
<u n="58" who="S0483">didn't</u>
<u n="59" who="S0482">yep</u>
<u n="60" who="S0483">alright well I extra extra top middle class if you're gonna be watching things like the fricking Goon Show</u>
<u n="61" who="S0482">firstly it's a radio show so you don't watch it</u>
<u n="62" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0482">secondly I'm I'm sorry that appreciating good comedy means your upper middle class</u>
<u n="64" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah right</u>
<u n="65" who="S0482">just uncultured</u>
<u n="66" who="S0483">we were watching we were we were watching lower class comedy like Some Mothers Do Ave Em <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0482" trans="overlap">that's what uncultured people say <pause dur="short"/> yeah we watched some of that as well</u>
<u n="68" who="S0483">mm <pause dur="short"/> did you? I can't see your parents watching that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0482">yeah my mum did a bit</u>
<u n="70" who="S0483">did she?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0482">yeah well I mean I've seen it <pause dur="short"/> so somebody must have put it on</u>
<u n="72" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0482">I I hated it</u>
<u n="74" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0482">er it's the worst kind of comedy</u>
<u n="76" who="S0483">I thought it was quiet funny</u>
<u n="77" who="S0482">no okay I mean that that was a bit harsh there were</u>
<u n="78" who="S0483">the one with the er the one with you know scene the scene with the roller boots</u>
<u n="79" who="S0482" trans="overlap">do you want some of the extra bits?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0483">can't beat that</u>
<u n="81" who="S0482">mm don't know that one <pause dur="short"/> it just <pause dur="short"/> I don't like</u>
<u n="82" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I get it gets <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I can't remember it's <trunc>so</trunc>something to do with he's on a <trunc>p</trunc>pair of roller boots or roller skates or something he gets <trunc>ha</trunc>holds onto the back of a van or something goes under a lorry</u>
<u n="83" who="S0482">I just don't like the kind of calamity comedy whatever you know like oh no he's done it it's all going wrong and then the catchphrases come out and <pause dur="short"/> I just sort of think mm you know</u>
<u n="84" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah no it's it's crap <pause dur="short"/> it's crap</u>
<u n="85" who="S0482" trans="overlap">catchphrase stuff it can be it can be good but</u>
<u n="86" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0482">I think the catchphrase itself has to start off being <vocal desc="cough"/> <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="88" who="S0483">you're saying that ooh Betty was not the best catchphrase in the world?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0482">he had a few didn't he? <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0483">I think it was mainly ooh Betty</u>
<u n="91" who="S0482">was it?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0483">and a few you know</u>
<u n="93" who="S0482">what were the yeah what were his other catch?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I don't remember any more I think that was it</u>
<u n="95" who="S0482">and who came up with that one? ooh Betty</u>
<u n="96" who="S0483">well it's his wife's name</u>
<u n="97" who="S0482">no I <vocal desc="laugh"/> I know but it's not it's <pause dur="short"/> it's not very erm diverse is it? well <pause dur="short"/> you can use it in lots of different ways in different scenarios and it and it be grow as a kind of containing catchphrase</u>
<u n="98" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> well you know it wasn't a sophisticated comedy was it?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0482">no <pause dur="short"/> not really <pause dur="short"/> I like The Goon Show</u>
<u n="100" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh my god <pause dur="long"/> so how many er hours burn time do you think I've got from those logs that I've er? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0482">I'd say you're up to about fifteen minutes</u>
<u n="102" who="S0483">no <pause dur="short"/> no I'm sure a bit longer than that</u>
<u n="103" who="S0482" trans="overlap">that log is a big</u>
<u n="104" who="S0483" trans="overlap">surely that would last us the evening?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0482">no</u>
<u n="106" who="S0483">really? not even me big log?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0482">no <pause dur="short"/> we worked out apparently if you were going to have fires occasionally</u>
<u n="108" who="S0483">yep <pause dur="short"/> yep yep</u>
<u n="109" who="S0482">for a year you'd need about four metres squared area of wood</u>
<u n="110" who="S0483">erm <pause dur="short"/> you say we worked it out who worked this out?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0482" trans="overlap">so imagine <pause dur="short"/> imagine <pause dur="short"/> well I say we er the guy who wrote that book I read said that and er and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I</u>
<u n="112" who="S0483" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay so four <trunc>s</trunc> four square metres</u>
<u n="113" who="S0482">yes so</u>
<u n="114" who="S0483" trans="overlap">hang on so hang on a minute hang on a minute hang on a minute hang on a minute oh so is that so is that two by two cubed?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0482" trans="overlap">so if you imagine two <pause dur="short"/> no it's two <trunc>cub</trunc> well I don't know</u>
<u n="116" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0482">four sorry four cube metres sorry my wrong <pause dur="short"/> four cubic metres</u>
<u n="118" who="S0483" trans="overlap">four cube metres so is that a two by two by two?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0482">yeah two by two by two so imagine like a pokey bedroom two metres by two metres</u>
<u n="120" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah full of wood</u>
<u n="121" who="S0482" trans="overlap">full of wood <pause dur="short"/> that's for occasional</u>
<u n="122" who="S0483" trans="overlap">and that can gives us what? well how many yeah but how many is occasional fires?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0482" trans="overlap">if you do every night</u>
<u n="124" who="S0483">mm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0482">pretty much</u>
<u n="126" who="S0483">no no no no no never mind that you've got to define occasional fire so <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0482">I I don't know</u>
<u n="128" who="S0483">I know I know but I mean basically you can knock out kind of March to October say</u>
<u n="129" who="S0482">he said like on chilly summer evenings</u>
<u n="130" who="S0483">you won't have a frigging fire on chilly summer evening that's ridiculous</u>
<u n="131" who="S0482">no actually no that was for using it every day</u>
<u n="132" who="S0483" trans="overlap">well anyway <trunc>li</trunc>well listen</u>
<u n="133" who="S0482">between between that between four and nine</u>
<u n="134" who="S0483">no I don't think we you know <pause dur="short"/> we'd probably be talking</u>
<u n="135" who="S0482" trans="overlap">but I think for us <pause dur="short"/> I think for us more more like on the lower end of that maybe three</u>
<u n="136" who="S0483">I don't think we'll be using it in the summer</u>
<u n="137" who="S0482">no I know that was the occasional use</u>
<u n="138" who="S0483">well no but I mean occasional use to me would probably be about twenty a year</u>
<u n="139" who="S0482">oh that really is occasional</u>
<u n="140" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0482">I'd imagine er yeah <pause dur="short"/> a hundred a year every every three days <pause dur="short"/> every day <unclear/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0483" trans="overlap">a hundred a year is mental we'd never have that many</u>
<u n="143" who="S0482">well er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they have it every day at the moment</u>
<u n="144" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah well they they're yeah but it's still a novelty for them and they could probably heat the house a bit better with it cheaper than electricity or whatever <pause dur="short"/> but you know that's not happening and they're living you know and they're at home more <pause dur="short"/> we're too busy fannying around looking after kids and things so we're not going to be sat in front of the fire are we?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0482" trans="overlap">are we? <pause dur="short"/> where are we if we're not at home in the evening?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0483">no I know but what I'm <pause dur="short"/> we're not gonna have them that much so all I'm saying is that log might do us</u>
<u n="147" who="S0482" trans="overlap">yes I know no okay <pause dur="short"/> that one log the rotten log that you picked up from the</u>
<u n="148" who="S0483" trans="overlap">look that will do an evening</u>
<u n="149" who="S0482" trans="overlap">it's not going to burn very well anyway even when it's dry</u>
<u n="150" who="S0483">it will if it's rotten it'll burn nicely</u>
<u n="151" who="S0482">yeah but if you think about it when something rots it loses a lot of its <pause dur="short"/> er stuff</u>
<u n="152" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah but it's dry it's nice and dry</u>
<u n="153" who="S0482">it's not dry</u>
<u n="154" who="S0483">it will be</u>
<u n="155" who="S0482">oh it will be yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0483">yeah and then it'll go up nice</u>
<u n="157" who="S0482">yeah it'll go up quick and nice</u>
<u n="158" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0482">we'll get five minutes <pause dur="short"/> of of nice flames and then <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> we need more wood</u>
<u n="160" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> do we have to get a wood basket?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0482">yep</u>
<u n="162" who="S0483">mm <pause dur="short"/> where are we going to put that? that's gonna put dirt everywhere</u>
<u n="163" who="S0482">erm I'm afraid <pause dur="short"/> that's what comes with a fire</u>
<u n="164" who="S0483">ah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0482">but erm I do think basically what we should do is we should chuck out our wood base</u>
<u n="166" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0482">erm work out roughly how much space we have</u>
<u n="168" who="S0483">yeah quite a bit there yeah a lot there yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0482" trans="overlap">clear it try and and then obviously we'll just stack it up</u>
<u n="170" who="S0483" trans="overlap">oh no we've got a lot of space there</u>
<u n="171" who="S0482" trans="overlap">erm I think it'll be really good a really good lot of storage that's right out the back door</u>
<u n="172" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah we've got a lot of space there yeah yeah we've got a lot got a lot of space there and we could put one out the front we could put one out the front as well</u>
<u n="173" who="S0482" trans="overlap">it would make it look a lot better there as well</u>
<u n="174" who="S0483">yeah but we can put one out the front</u>
<u n="175" who="S0482">oh I don't know our neighbour might</u>
<u n="176" who="S0483">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0482">walk off with it</u>
<u n="178" who="S0483">yeah you're not kidding he would as well <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> ah cool <pause dur="short"/> that's good news yeah erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying about putting some decking in maybe and I just said whatever you do don't paint it</u>
<u n="179" who="S0482">yeah difficult to treat decking isn't it?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0483">yeah no it's just difficult to treat decking <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>what</trunc> well I do well I don't know I mean it'll need to be treated it'll need to be stained or something but I assume that lasts a lot better than paint <pause dur="short"/> cos that's what most people do so</u>
<u n="181" who="S0482">why didn't we do that? oh we needed to paint it cos <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0483" trans="overlap">well well we had to paint it cos it all got flaky paint on it <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh but yeah cos they've got all that space to the side of the erm <pause dur="short"/> lounge</u>
<u n="183" who="S0482">yeah that's it's a big-sized plot</u>
<u n="184" who="S0483">yeah yeah it is</u>
<u n="185" who="S0482">I liked it I thought I thought I definitely would have built the house closer to the road</u>
<u n="186" who="S0483">yeah yeah you don't need a big drive</u>
<u n="187" who="S0482" trans="overlap">you don't need all that big garden</u>
<u n="188" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no no no no no you don't</u>
<u n="189" who="S0482">it's the front garden really</u>
<u n="190" who="S0483">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it's nice you know nice and manageable and easy</u>
<u n="191" who="S0482">yeah I need some lime</u>
<u n="192" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I like I like that got shedloads of limes have we got limes</u>
<u n="193" who="S0482">and a lot of fruit</u>
<u n="194" who="S0483">yeah they need using up though</u>
<u n="195" who="S0482">interesting definition of shed loads</u>
<u n="196" who="S0483">well it is three is a lot <pause dur="short"/> you only get four in a bag so</u>
<u n="197" who="S0482">if you're er if there's three people in a boat and you're dying of scurvy then three limes is probably a life-saver but</u>
<u n="198" who="S0483">mm mm wouldn't have thought so I think you might need more</u>
<u n="199" who="S0482" trans="overlap">although the problem is not scurvy probably doesn't matter does it?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0483">don't know</u>
<u n="201" who="S0482">or does it reverse?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0483">er no I think you can reverse it</u>
<u n="203" who="S0482">well I mean you can reverse it cos it's a dish condition you can treat it</u>
<u n="204" who="S0483">well no er <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0482">er what am I in here for?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0483">er? limes onion <pause dur="short"/> fish</u>
<u n="207" who="S0482">yeah that's all in here oh and er sauce</u>
<u n="208" who="S0483">what are we erm having with it rice?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0482"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0483">oh</u>
<u n="211" who="S0482">well we don't have any noodles do we? <pause dur="short"/> do we? <pause dur="short"/> I don't think we have <unclear>any left</unclear></u>
<u n="212" who="S0483" trans="overlap">well it's more that I'm going to have to get up and cook it</u>
<u n="213" who="S0482">so we need some wine oh no no no no</u>
<u n="214" who="S0483" trans="overlap">er yeah what wine? <pause dur="short"/> white presumably?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0482">yeah but we were gonna go for another beer</u>
<u n="216" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0482">erm <pause dur="short"/> nope no noodles</u>
<u n="218" who="S0483">while you're on your feet go and get another beer</u>
<u n="219" who="S0482">indeed</u>
<u n="220" who="S0483">I really liked their little bistro set that was really cute for breakfast</u>
<u n="221" who="S0482">yeah it was nice that they had their pictures of Greece above it</u>
<u n="222" who="S0483">did they? <pause dur="short"/> ah yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0482" trans="overlap">they had those picture up</u>
<u n="224" who="S0483" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0482">it was nice</u>
<u n="226" who="S0483">no it was really sweet</u>
<u n="227" who="S0482">I really really liked their house I thought wow I would have <pause dur="short"/> I think it's the sort of house we would have gone wow this is really nice</u>
<u n="228" who="S0483">yeah yeah yeah yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="229" who="S0482">it erm I think they've made a really good move</u>
<u n="230" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0482">I never saw the upstairs in their old house actually <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0483" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> no no I I I I think I sort of glanced into <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s room and things but no I haven't really sort of fully had a a good look erm yeah no it's just really nice really nice</u>
<u n="233" who="S0482">yes</u>
<u n="234" who="S0483">really nice <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0482">let's move this over here <pause dur="short"/> let's start cooking</u>
<u n="236" who="S0483"><trunc>d</trunc>do you reckon is it going to pick up well on there? <pause dur="long"/> I think it's not ideal making all this noise</u>
<u n="237" who="S0482">no <pause dur="short"/> excuse me</u>
<u n="238" who="S0483">oh er <pause dur="short"/> erm should we ring your mum at some point and tell her about coming down in a few weeks?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0483">cool</u>
<u n="241" who="S0482">I think that'd be nice</u>
<u n="242" who="S0483">yeah absolutely no I'll do that and</u>
<u n="243" who="S0482">glad to hear the timing will be good</u>
<u n="244" who="S0483">yeah yep yep <pause dur="short"/> sounds <pause dur="short"/> sounds good <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it works for us really we'll we'll erm we'll see what the traffic's like on that Friday</u>
<u n="245" who="S0482"><unclear/> to alert on erm <pause dur="short"/> coconut milk <pause dur="short"/> we've only got one</u>
<u n="246" who="S0483">only got one coconut milk</u>
<u n="247" who="S0482">oh no no no we do yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0483">oh <trunc>sh</trunc> oh er oh but I'm going to Aldi next week shall we start doing me an Aldi list</u>
<u n="249" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0483"><trunc>co</trunc>coconut milk being er <pause dur="short"/> high up there</u>
<u n="251" who="S0482">full fat or half fat?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0483">don't mind</u>
<u n="253" who="S0482">full fat</u>
<u n="254" who="S0483">right</u>
<u n="255" who="S0482">given that it's fish <pause dur="short"/> no fat from fish</u>
<u n="256" who="S0483">erm <vocal desc="yawn"/> erm but yeah if I can get some bits from Aldi and I can get some more of that lager and some more erm coconut milk</u>
<u n="257" who="S0482">okay dokey</u>
<u n="258" who="S0483">we're happy with that coconut milk aren't we?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0482">which one?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0483">that one well is that? is it?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0482" trans="overlap">yeah the erm it's good</u>
<u n="262" who="S0483">I wonder how much it is</u>
<u n="263" who="S0482">it's like about eighty P</u>
<u n="264" who="S0483">is it?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0482">so it's really cheap</u>
<u n="266" who="S0483">we ought to buy big then won't we?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0482">yeah I'd buy buy like twelve or something</u>
<u n="268" who="S0483">well may as well buy a year's supply <vocal desc="laugh"/> how long does it last for?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0482">I suspect quite a while I think a tin lasts for a while <pause dur="short"/> erm twenty <trunc>s</trunc> July twenty-seventeen</u>
<u n="270" who="S0483">there you go we'll get an apocalypse an apocalypse level of coconut milk</u>
<u n="271" who="S0482">absolutely</u>
<u n="272" who="S0483">fifty-two <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> one a week</u>
<u n="273" who="S0482" trans="overlap"><unclear/> don't go crazy</u>
<u n="274" who="S0483">we could get through one a week</u>
<u n="275" who="S0482">one a week fifty-two</u>
<u n="276" who="S0483">well actually no this is about it's about half a week so we need twenty-five to get us through a year</u>
<u n="277" who="S0482">get twenty-five then</u>
<u n="278" who="S0483">I will I'll get twenty I'll get twenty</u>
<u n="279" who="S0482" trans="overlap">a years' supply sort of thing you win in a competition</u>
<u n="280" who="S0483">a years' supply of coconut milk</u>
<u n="281" who="S0482">yes twenty-five cans that would be a really</u>
<u n="282" who="S0483">well that's it like grandad got his years' supply of whisky but I don't know how much it was but he got through it I three months so I mean it was obviously not really a years' supply</u>
<u n="283" who="S0482" trans="overlap">did he?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0482">you'd you'd think you'd think it would have to be based on like they just keep giving it to you for a whole year until</u>
<u n="286" who="S0483">yeah well they can't what if they get a proper alky? it's not responsible is it? mind you back then</u>
<u n="287" who="S0482" trans="overlap">well then that person has a</u>
<u n="288" who="S0483">but I'd have thought what would you <trunc>si</trunc> what would you think would be a years' supply of whisky?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0482" trans="overlap">I mean a years' supply of a ten-year-old would be well none you know they wouldn't drink it</u>
<u n="290" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0482">so what's official a years' supply?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0483">a <trunc>whisk</trunc> yeah but a years' supply of whisky what is that? <pause dur="short"/> three bottles?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0482">twelve bottles?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0483">no it can't be you can't be</u>
<u n="295" who="S0482">a bottle a month? <pause dur="short"/> that's what? a quarter of a bottle a</u>
<u n="296" who="S0483">yeah I suppose yeah twelve bottles then</u>
<u n="297" who="S0482">quarter of a bottle a week is what</u>
<u n="298" who="S0483">god</u>
<u n="299" who="S0482">er seven what how is it a litre a standard or is it seven fifty?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0483" trans="overlap">er no it's seven fifty</u>
<u n="301" who="S0482">so then you know <pause dur="short"/> that's only about two hundred mil a week</u>
<u n="302" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah I suppose</u>
<u n="303" who="S0482">which is like four doubles a week</u>
<u n="304" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no it's not much at all <pause dur="short"/> so twelve bottles and he got through that in three months <pause dur="short"/> wasn't an alky <pause dur="short"/> I don't think he drank anything other than whisky I don't know if I saw him drinking wine or anything</u>
<u n="305" who="S0482" trans="overlap">well that's the other thing isn't it? it would last us a while cos we don't really</u>
<u n="306" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah that's your tipple yeah yeah yeah yeah that's your tipple <pause dur="short"/> tipple of choice</u>
<u n="307" who="S0482">tipple of choice</u>
<u n="308" who="S0483">I guess it probably it's about the only thing he could taste as well <pause dur="short"/> must have been a bit of a taste trip for him maybe</u>
<u n="309" who="S0482">why did he have a taste problem?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0483">couldn't taste anything</u>
<u n="311" who="S0482">oh really</u>
<u n="312" who="S0483">couldn't smell anything couldn't smell lost his sense of smell in the war got some sort of</u>
<u n="313" who="S0482">from an injury?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0483">no no no from erm I think it was like a bug you know <pause dur="short"/> like the sort of thing you pick up like dysentery or whatever don't think it was dysentery but</u>
<u n="315" who="S0482" trans="overlap">bloody hell really?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0483">yeah <pause dur="short"/> whatever it was knocked his er</u>
<u n="317" who="S0482" trans="overlap">you'd really you really only appreciate what you have when you've <trunc>li</trunc> when you lose it don't you?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0483">well</u>
<u n="319" who="S0482">sense of smell's one of those things you probably just I remember when I lost my sense of smell for a couple of weeks it was really weird</u>
<u n="320" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah it was rubbish yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0482">it it but it was just I mean I I think <pause dur="short"/> I remember thinking to myself what if this is it you know</u>
<u n="322" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0482">like they don't they don't come back but it wasn't it wasn't a massive one</u>
<u n="324" who="S0483">no</u>
<u n="325" who="S0482">I sort of thought that would be a pain but oh well</u>
<u n="326" who="S0483">it would be a pain I mean put it like this it would be life would be cheaper cos you wouldn't you you you wouldn't bother with wine</u>
<u n="327" who="S0482" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> but remember I got taste from my tongue and I noticed that one more even just in the short period</u>
<u n="328" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I'm just saying like you wouldn't need to go out for dinner ever <pause dur="short"/> you wouldn't drink any nice wine or anything any more cos you wouldn't be able to taste it <pause dur="short"/> you'd be able to eat quite healthily cos you do you know what I mean like er</u>
<u n="329" who="S0482" trans="overlap">it's not like acid levels it's not that</u>
<u n="330" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no I mean like for for me I'd just eat lots of fruit and veg cos I wouldn't be able to taste <pause dur="short"/> it'd be proper healthy</u>
<u n="331" who="S0482" trans="overlap">it would be a shame wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0483">it it would be a shame I wouldn't need chocolate any more I'd be the healthiest person ever</u>
<u n="333" who="S0482" trans="overlap">I don't know now you see because no you see cos you still get that reward from chocolate even if you don't taste it</u>
<u n="334" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no you're not gonna bother no no no</u>
<u n="335" who="S0482" trans="overlap">no you do yeah you would</u>
<u n="336" who="S0483">no no no</u>
<u n="337" who="S0482">okay just <pause dur="short"/> smokers don't care about the taste of cigarettes particularly</u>
<u n="338" who="S0483">no I know but the reward you get from chocolate is nowhere near the level of reward you get from having a fag</u>
<u n="339" who="S0482" trans="overlap">no but you can get a little bit of a like after a meal it makes you feel right even if you've not tasted it</u>
<u n="340" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no no bullshit no if you can't taste it it's worthless</u>
<u n="341" who="S0482">oh no</u>
<u n="342" who="S0483">no and it doesn't and and in fact it <pause dur="short"/> case in point I never do it when I've got a cold if I have a if I have a if I have a segment of Dairy Milk and I can't taste it I quit I don't even bother keeping going</u>
<u n="343" who="S0482">what do you?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0483" trans="overlap">what's the point? there's no there's no reward?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0482" trans="overlap">well that okay but I could taste it on my tongue but I suppose maybe your grandad had lost his tongue taste</u>
<u n="346" who="S0483" trans="overlap">mm no no basically the only things he could really properly taste were stem ginger</u>
<u n="347" who="S0482">talking of which</u>
<u n="348" who="S0483">uhu yeah ginger</u>
<u n="349" who="S0482" trans="overlap">we don't have any do we?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0483">yeah we've got loads of ginger</u>
<u n="351" who="S0482">is that?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0483">yeah <pause dur="short"/> been there for months</u>
<u n="353" who="S0482">is it?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0483">yeah it's sprouting</u>
<u n="355" who="S0482">where?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0483">down <pause dur="short"/> down down</u>
<u n="357" who="S0482">down down</u>
<u n="358" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0482">kneel down <pause dur="short"/> okay brilliant you should have told me</u>
<u n="360" who="S0483">do you think we can grow it?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0482">what? I don't think we need to it's doing it by all by itself</u>
<u n="362" who="S0483" trans="overlap">no but like I wonder if you can grow ginger or whether you need erm <pause dur="short"/> well don't kill that bit I know does it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0482" trans="overlap">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> well it grows underground <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's like a it's a root oh</u>
<u n="364" who="S0483" trans="overlap">a root <pause dur="short"/> don't hurt it's root though</u>
<u n="365" who="S0482">oh I'm not I'm just trying to cut around it <pause dur="short"/> like the</u>
<u n="366" who="S0483" trans="overlap">what? <pause dur="short"/> what? <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc>yeah <pause dur="short"/> well you've killed that other bit now you'd better do that bit as well</u>
<u n="367" who="S0482">what bit?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0483">I know well you've just flapped this flap that's not gonna do it any good is it? <pause dur="short"/> do you think we should grow it? <pause dur="short"/> where are we gonna put it?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0482">erm I dunno</u>
<u n="370" who="S0483">it looks very keen to grow and it was growing in the dark</u>
<u n="371" who="S0482">yeah well</u>
<u n="372" who="S0483">I suppose it just grows through the ground yeah I know but I've never had it grown before but then we've never kept it that long before</u>
<u n="373" who="S0482" trans="overlap">you're you're definitely not gonna be team botanist in an apocalypse movie</u>
<u n="374" who="S0483" trans="overlap">what? <pause dur="short"/> fucking no more botany than you</u>
<u n="375" who="S0482">I know but well clearly you possibly don't</u>
<u n="376" who="S0483">I think I do I beg to differ</u>
<u n="377" who="S0482">well you only just worked out that the reason why it sprouts in the dark is because it's when you're underground it's dark</u>
<u n="378" who="S0483">yeah alright I know you chuck potatoes in the dark as well but</u>
<u n="379" who="S0482">oh I see now you're just showing off</u>
<u n="380" who="S0483">mm</u>
<u n="381" who="S0482">put all the ginger in</u>
<u n="382" who="S0483" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> this is good <pause dur="short"/> this looks good</u>
<u n="383" who="S0482"><unclear>what</unclear> looks good?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0483">well it's food <pause dur="short"/> it smells nice</u>
<u n="385" who="S0482">it's just done in <pause dur="short"/> possibly for <unclear/> family <unclear/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0483">ah sorry yeah I've bought loads more leeks again they're just on such good value at the moment</u>
<u n="387" who="S0482">it's fine leeks good <pause dur="short"/> I like I think they make a better base for a Thai meal than onions actually that's why I went for loads <unclear/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0483">I don't know you I don't think you can beat an onion</u>
<u n="389" who="S0482">well I regret cutting off a very big piece of ginger</u>
<u n="390" who="S0483" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ginger's very good for you though good for colds</u>
<u n="391" who="S0482">it's one of those things that people always say I'm sure it's right but</u>
<u n="392" who="S0483">it's gotta be good for colds everyone says it</u>
<u n="393" who="S0482">everyone says it's good for you</u>
<u n="394" who="S0483">yeah <pause dur="short"/> fact</u>
<u n="395" who="S0482">what are we watching tonight?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0483">don't know</u>
<u n="397" who="S0482">I think probably not House of Cards</u>
<u n="398" who="S0483">no</u>
<u n="399" who="S0482">we're on a new disc now <pause dur="short"/> erm they've seen literally everyone I didn't I didn't even realise they those guys had Netflix</u>
<u n="400" who="S0483" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0482">I know but lots of things are popular and people don't get round to watching them <pause dur="short"/> I'm just you know I never expect to be that behind on things but we we you know we really missed the boat on his one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0483">it doesn't matter we've got it now</u>
<u n="403" who="S0482" trans="overlap">I know it doesn't matter I know <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> erm potentially got time <pause dur="short"/> bit of Zelda yeah</u>
<u n="404" who="S0482">we should have done Scarlet's Sword</u>
<u n="405" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0482" trans="overlap">I know but how much did we played it in the last <pause dur="short"/> three weeks</u>
<u n="407" who="S0483" trans="overlap">I know well because you've been working every no you've been working <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> if we'd have had every evening free then we would've done it</u>
<u n="408" who="S0482">yes <pause dur="short"/> agree</u>
<u n="409" who="S0483">yes</u>
<u n="410" who="S0482"><unclear/> have it <unclear/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0483">we have we have we have</u>
<u n="412" who="S0482" trans="overlap">no we haven't</u>
<u n="413" who="S0483">we pretty much have <pause dur="short"/> we have <pause dur="short"/> when do you need me to do the rice?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0482">now?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0483">ah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="416" who="S0482">hey look it looks like a little aerial it looks like a a wi-fi card for a PC <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0483">open the <unclear/> immediately</u>
<u n="418" who="S0482">Alaskan pollock</u>
<u n="419" who="S0483">I'll ask him?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0482">Alaskan</u>
<u n="421" who="S0483">I'll ask him?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0482">Alaskan</u>
<u n="423" who="S0483">do you mean Alaskan?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0482">no it's without skin <pause dur="short"/> alaskan</u>
<u n="425" who="S0483">Alaskan</u>
<u n="426" who="S0482"><vocal desc="laugh"/> great ingredients fish a hundred per cent brilliant <pause dur="short"/> that's what we like we don't like our fish anything less than a hundred per cent fish <pause dur="long"/> I've caught pollock before</u>
<u n="427" who="S0483">have you?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0482">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the biggest fish I've ever caught has been a pollock</u>
<u n="429" who="S0483">well how big was it?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0482">don't laugh</u>
<u n="431" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh yes</u>
<u n="432" who="S0482">it was about four and a half pounds</u>
<u n="433" who="S0483">oh that's ridiculous</u>
<u n="434" who="S0482">it was alright</u>
<u n="435" who="S0483">I've caught</u>
<u n="436" who="S0482">I was little it was about half the size of me</u>
<u n="437" who="S0483" trans="overlap">ah that's little I've caught bream in a canal that was four and a half pounds</u>
<u n="438" who="S0482">alright</u>
<u n="439" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> is that seriously the biggest fish you've ever caught?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0482">yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0483">god</u>
<u n="442" who="S0482">well <pause dur="short"/> I think <trunc>s</trunc> well it's I don't know</u>
<u n="443" who="S0483">hi my name's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> extreme fishermen biologist <pause dur="short"/> biggest fish I've even caught four and a half pounds</u>
<u n="444" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0482">well look <pause dur="short"/> let's find something that's four and a half pounds and we'll see how heavy it is</u>
<u n="446" who="S0483" trans="overlap">well it's four bags of sugar</u>
<u n="447" who="S0482">phwoar</u>
<u n="448" who="S0483">phwoar <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="449" who="S0482">pull that out of the sea when you're about eight</u>
<u n="450" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0482">thing is a lot of the fishing that I've done has been sort of fishing <pause dur="short"/> for small <pause dur="short"/> fish</u>
<u n="452" who="S0483"><vocal desc="laugh"/> for small insignificant fish yeah?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0482">yeah like you know? <pause dur="short"/> caught you know <pause dur="short"/> sea trout but they've been quite small</u>
<u n="454" who="S0483">I've never seen you catch a fish that's <pause dur="short"/> anything bigger than teeny</u>
<u n="455" who="S0482">I know that's because of the lengths I fish in</u>
<u n="456" who="S0483">mm <pause dur="short"/> did we catch anything when we went fishing in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0482">I no</u>
<u n="458" who="S0483" trans="overlap">it was three nibbles or something wasn't it?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0482" trans="overlap">I'll tell you what I did get yeah I got a couple of nibbles and a couple of risers and erm <pause dur="short"/> there were just anglers who were sat there with beers out like from about nine o'clock in the morning</u>
<u n="460" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="461" who="S0482">I did I did better than them <pause dur="short"/> cos they got nothing but they were they were just sitting there with ropes or whatever and I was fly fishing <pause dur="short"/> yeah they said they hadn't got any er bites at all and I did definitely got a few bites</u>
<u n="462" who="S0483" trans="overlap">maybe it was just not quite the right time of year <pause dur="short"/> it was frigging cold</u>
<u n="463" who="S0482">it was nice weather though</u>
<u n="464" who="S0483">yeah but it was so cold at night</u>
<u n="465" who="S0482">well the conditions weren't great I mean you don't want to go fishing when it's <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="466" who="S0483" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="yawn"/> sunny and still</u>
<u n="467" who="S0482">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> light rain or something like that</u>
<u n="468" who="S0483">I don't know</u>
<u n="469" who="S0482">will improve things</u>
<u n="470" who="S0483">maybe that's what we should do as our as our old age pensioners we should do fishing that could be an activity for us</u>
<u n="471" who="S0482">sounds good <pause dur="short"/> walking and fishing</u>
<u n="472" who="S0483">walking and fishing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0482">nothing better than that <pause dur="short"/> wouldn't get better than that</u>
<u n="474" who="S0483">it would be it could get better than that if we weren't doing it in the UK</u>
<u n="475" who="S0482">if you end up at a pub at the end of the day</u>
<u n="476" who="S0483">but we were walking fishing somewhere warm</u>
<u n="477" who="S0482">yeah but then</u>
<u n="478" who="S0483" trans="overlap">now you're talking</u>
<u n="479" who="S0482">the thing is <pause dur="short"/> the countryside in the UK is beautiful partly because it's not that warm and it rains a lot</u>
<u n="480" who="S0483" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah but the countryside in other places is also beautiful</u>
<u n="481" who="S0482">yeah in some other places but <pause dur="short"/> like where?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0483">the continent</u>
<u n="483" who="S0482"><trunc>So</trunc> South Island New Zealand <trunc>Sou</trunc>South Island South Island New Zealand</u>
<u n="484" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0482">beautiful but not that warm</u>
<u n="486" who="S0483">yeah I was thinking maybe Sweden <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> when it's warm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0482" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> sweden when it's warm?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0483">mm</u>
<u n="489" who="S0482">what about the UK when it's warm?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0483">yeah but it's not always reliably warm is it? whereas I think Sweden gets many weeks of very hot weather <pause dur="short"/> according to my books <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0482">I don't know depends what you mean</u>
<u n="492" who="S0483">well they get they get proper hot weather there they get like you know <pause dur="short"/> like forty degrees <pause dur="short"/> hot</u>
<u n="493" who="S0482">do they?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0483">er I think so</u>
<u n="495" who="S0482" trans="overlap">well I <trunc>mea</trunc> I'm sure it has been that warm there but I don't think that's their typical weather</u>
<u n="496" who="S0483" trans="overlap">well they get they get no they get proper no no well no no I think every every year they get proper summer holiday weather</u>
<u n="497" who="S0482">do they?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0483">yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0482"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0483">I think so <pause dur="long"/> what are the tomatoes for?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0482">I quite like them in a curry</u>
<u n="502" who="S0483">yeah that's fine I'm just wondering what they're doing hanging out on that plate?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0482">well they're they're not gonna go they're not quite in yet</u>
<u n="504" who="S0483">right okay</u>
<u n="505" who="S0482">so they they're like they're the kind of the skins keep them oops <pause dur="short"/> the skins keep them tapped but you know they're sort of melt and go all gooey in the middle and then but then in a curry they're quite nice</u>
<u n="506" who="S0483" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I understand I I understand cooking a tomato I'm just surprised they haven't gone in yet</u>
<u n="507" who="S0482" trans="overlap">ooh that looks a bit <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> <foreign lang="fre">sacré bleu</foreign> <pause dur="short"/> oops <pause dur="short"/> he's a bit keen <pause dur="short"/> how's the wine going?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0483">badly very badly have we got some in the fridge? you're on your feet you have a look</u>
<u n="509" who="S0482">have we got some in the fridge?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0483">no there's a white in the open in the fridge</u>
<u n="511" who="S0482">oh <pause dur="short"/> thought I'd better not let that <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah we do <pause dur="short"/> we do indeed</u>
<u n="512" who="S0483">ah dear <pause dur="short"/> we've done the <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0482">so I'm on my own turn this off <pause dur="short"/> oh I can do it from here</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
