<text id="SJXU">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:02</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Films, piracy, TV shows</topics>
		<activity>ANON and ANON chatting</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0115">uh yeah so your favourite film is it uh uh <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's it's got Doris Day in as well hasn't it?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0037">I like a bit of Doris <pause dur="short"/> um I like Calamity Jane but that's mainly sentimental reasons like</u>
<u n="3" who="S0115">ye ha</u>
<u n="4" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> it reminds us of like going to my nana and granddad's and <trunc>l</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> actually cos you know my mam doesn't really like films and neither did her mam but my dad's mam loves films like</u>
<u n="5" who="S0115">yeah you've definitely got that from from that</u>
<u n="6" who="S0037">she likes</u>
<u n="7" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you mean like uh culturally speaking</u>
<u n="8" who="S0037">like E</u>
<u n="9" who="S0115">you've picked up the meme of watching films</u>
<u n="10" who="S0037">well I mean I I don't I'm not a big film lover I don't go to the cinema</u>
<u n="11" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I don't know if you I don't know if it's genetic I don't know if you've inherited the film loving gene or if it's a culture</u>
<u n="12" who="S0037">no but I mean I I don't go to the cinema very often for example and and I don't own any films <pause dur="short"/> I don't own any  I don't own any  DVDs or any films and that but but I do quite like them and</u>
<u n="13" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well I've got a few mainly just cos I I got I don't spending loads of money on it so I'd rather have sort of like recordings and yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I didn't even do that <pause dur="short"/> I didn't even <pause dur="short"/> like I've never had a video player or a <pause dur="short"/> is that my <trunc>D</trunc>? No that's your DVD player <pause dur="short"/> I've never even had one like I've never</u>
<u n="15" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0037">but I do quite like them and I uh watch them if they're on the telly and stuff <pause dur="short"/> but um <vocal desc="yawn"/> excuse me yeah <pause dur="short"/> I like Calamity Jane <trunc>c</trunc> for <trunc>c</trunc> sentimental reasons same with like a lot of those other films like that like Back To The Future and my nana used to have</u>
<u n="17" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I really love Back To The Future it's one my favourites yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0037">my nana used to have like a little cabinet and she would like <pause dur="short"/> like when we were younger cos obviously there's a bit of a gap between me and like me and Tom and then our other cousins <pause dur="short"/> so we had like a bit where we were like the only kids if you know what I mean and like <pause dur="short"/> so when we were younger there would be like crayons and stuff in there but then as we got older it was like uh The Land Before Time <pause dur="short"/> back To The Future</u>
<u n="19" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh Land Before Time</u>
<u n="20" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> like um <pause dur="short"/> she used to tape them during the week and then we would go over at the weekend and watch them <pause dur="short"/> and like um uh Batteries Not Included</u>
<u n="21" who="S0115">that was <trunc>y</trunc> that was on TV recently that that's that's a good one that is <pause dur="short"/> very very sort of Spielbergy isn't it very like?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0037" trans="overlap">uh ET <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> gremlins um</u>
<u n="23" who="S0115">oh well that's a Spielberg that is isn't it?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0037" trans="overlap">little Shop Of Horrors like</u>
<u n="25" who="S0115">oh yeah that that's a lot uh</u>
<u n="26" who="S0037">um Ghostbusters Ghostbusters Two my personal favourite</u>
<u n="27" who="S0115" trans="overlap">A lot of eighties eighties things <pause dur="short"/> the Little Shop Of Horrors is good actually because it's a musical isn't it it's a bit of a cult one actually that isn't it?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0037">Ghostbusters Two</u>
<u n="29" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="30" who="S0037">and Ghostbusters obviously <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> so she was pretty good like <pause dur="short"/> she was pretty</u>
<u n="31" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Igon Spengler</u>
<u n="32" who="S0037">bit of Igon Spengler <pause dur="short"/> she was pretty good at like um you know getting all those and like we saw loads of those kinda kids' films Goonies and um</u>
<u n="33" who="S0115">oh yeah yeah yeah that's a  that's a  good one like <vocal desc="laugh"/> But they did they were a bit</u>
<u n="34" who="S0037">captain Hook</u>
<u n="35" who="S0115">they did  they did  them sort of bad jokes about that  about that  fat kid didn't they who used to get into like roll <pause dur="short"/> I think he's  I think he's  died of a <trunc>hear</trunc> I think he's died of a heart attack though</u>
<u n="36" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> truffle shuffle <pause dur="short"/> oh has he?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0115"><unclear/> I dunno</u>
<u n="38" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and like um <pause dur="short"/> yeah <trunc>ca</trunc></u>
<u n="39" who="S0115">he may oh I just like I was thinking because of his sort of size like</u>
<u n="40" who="S0037">yeah but he was only a bairn then though</u>
<u n="41" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that wasn't  that wasn't  sustainable</u>
<u n="42" who="S0037">um Captain Hook</u>
<u n="43" who="S0115">I know it was uh that made  that made  like the truffle shuffle even like worse to sort of laugh at like</u>
<u n="44" who="S0037">I know</u>
<u n="45" who="S0115">you can't laugh at child</u>
<u n="46" who="S0037">obesity</u>
<u n="47" who="S0115">obesity can you?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0037">well it's not his fault really is it it's his parents <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="49" who="S0115">that's what I'm gonna say</u>
<u n="50" who="S0037">yeah and Captain Hook</u>
<u n="51" who="S0115">oh that was really uh <trunc>Ho</trunc> it's called Hook</u>
<u n="52" who="S0037">yeah you know what I mean</u>
<u n="53" who="S0115">that's <trunc>i</trunc> lot of <trunc>s</trunc> lot of eighties a lot of sort of Spielberg <unclear/> as well</u>
<u n="54" who="S0037">so <pause dur="short"/> my nana like recorded all of those and she had them in this little cabinet like this little <pause dur="short"/> in fact I think they've still got it</u>
<u n="55" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well we've got something similar I mean I've got all my videos</u>
<u n="56" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but it had like a door and she used it like much like you have <pause dur="short"/> like <trunc>r</trunc> had uh like written them in her handwriting on the side of the film</u>
<u n="57" who="S0115">oh yeah like I've got I mean double play like eight hours  eight hours  like so you can get four films on one tape</u>
<u n="58" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah my nana did yeah yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0115">two hours each</u>
<u n="60" who="S0037">um and I used to like you know really used to like sort of The Neverending Story and</u>
<u n="61" who="S0115">oh yeah I never watched that actually the um</u>
<u n="62" who="S0037">land Before Time</u>
<u n="63" who="S0115">never watched it but <pause dur="short"/> land Before Time yeah cos we we actually got to see that at school uh there was like a</u>
<u n="64" who="S0037" trans="overlap">watership Down and</u>
<u n="65" who="S0115">there was a trip at school like to the cinema</u>
<u n="66" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0115">um and I I was excited cos my parents didn't take me to the cinema and I'd never been to the cinema before</u>
<u n="68" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh really? No mine didn't really</u>
<u n="69" who="S0115">uh so I'd never been to the cinema before like not not ever and I don't think and</u>
<u n="70" who="S0037">I remember <trunc>go</trunc></u>
<u n="71" who="S0115" trans="overlap">think that was my first ever trip uh that the school took <pause dur="short"/> but like there was two groups of us and like the older ones</u>
<u n="72" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0115">like got to see like like a PG rated film</u>
<u n="74" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0115">um and the younger um including me went to see a U rated film which happened to be Land Before Time</u>
<u n="76" who="S0037">oh that's a good one</u>
<u n="77" who="S0115">I think but but I think actually that was the better of the two like the the PG one was called Mac And Me</u>
<u n="78" who="S0037">oh right</u>
<u n="79" who="S0115">uh this would've been like nineteen eighty-nine or nineteen ninety</u>
<u n="80" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0115">nineteen eighty or ninety-two or something but uh yeah I think we  I think we  did better to get</u>
<u n="82" who="S0037">land Before Time was a good one</u>
<u n="83" who="S0115" trans="overlap">wait wait a minute no it was it would be younger than oh I can't remember</u>
<u n="84" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="85" who="S0115">I've really really bad memory of my uh childhood to be honest uh</u>
<u n="86" who="S0037">well it was a long time ago way</u>
<u n="87" who="S0115">it's just black it's just blacked out like</u>
<u n="88" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="89" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> it's there's too <trunc>m</trunc> too many things that uh I don't wanna remember</u>
<u n="90" who="S0037">I remember my nana and granddad my nana and granddad took us to the pictures once and like me and my nana wanted to see one film and my granddad and our Tom wanted to see another film so we went to see different ones and I remember thinking that was really like really good because like usually it would just be like with my dad or with my mam so you couldn't split it up and like I'd have to sit through like</u>
<u n="91" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0037">transformer</u>
<u n="93" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Steven Steven Seagal oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0037">but like me and my nana went to see Little Women and my nana was like it's amazing and I was like</u>
<u n="95" who="S0115">what is that?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0037">little Women? Come on</u>
<u n="97" who="S0115">what is that?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0037">it's a book like you've read the have you maybe you haven't it's more of a girls' book</u>
<u n="99" who="S0115">it sounds to me like I think of uh big men is more up my street than little women</u>
<u n="100" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe big men is right up your street <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0115">I think uh if if something was called Little Women I would would suspect that it might be like a romantic comedy or something</u>
<u n="102" who="S0037">yeah it is a bit floppy</u>
<u n="103" who="S0115">um no but I I don't romantic comedies</u>
<u n="104" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's one of those classics though</u>
<u n="105" who="S0115">I think we were talking about them a couple of days ago actually</u>
<u n="106" who="S0037">yeah Bridget Jones</u>
<u n="107" who="S0115">you're you you <trunc>th</trunc> you don't like um <pause dur="short"/> you don't like them do you?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no but I mean</u>
<u n="109" who="S0115">is that what Little Women is? What's it about?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0037">well it's a story about some <trunc>r</trunc> like four sisters <pause dur="short"/> and the Dad's gone off to the American civil war</u>
<u n="111" who="S0115">alright <pause dur="short"/> fight the carpet-baggers <pause dur="short"/> what side was he on?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0037">uh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> but they like do various things like <pause dur="short"/> there's like one of them who wants to be a writer and she goes off to the city to be a writer and then <pause dur="short"/> oh there's a man who lives next door and he likes them but they don't like him oh but just just</u>
<u n="113" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh I think I'm gonna find myself uh slipping slipping into</u>
<u n="114" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's like a  it's like a  Jane <trunc>Auste</trunc> no no no that's the end of the story <pause dur="short"/> it's like a Jane Austen-esque but not as exciting I suppose</u>
<u n="115" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Oh right</u>
<u n="116" who="S0037">but anyway it's um <pause dur="short"/> went to see that and <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I didn't go to the cinema very much <pause dur="short"/> didn't really</u>
<u n="117" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I went uh I went for a bit like I got <trunc>b</trunc> uh taken got taken by my parents a bit when uh when I was in like</u>
<u n="118" who="S0037">I went on a like a date once to the cinema</u>
<u n="119" who="S0115">ha ha</u>
<u n="120" who="S0037">and I remember thinking it was the stupidest place to go because like</u>
<u n="121" who="S0115">well <pause dur="short"/> yeah it is yeah it's <trunc>i</trunc> it's one of the probably most common like child child date destinations innit?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's so bad and stupid <pause dur="short"/> but I was like fifteen or whatever <pause dur="short"/> and I went to see you know Liar Liar with Jim Carey</u>
<u n="123" who="S0115">yeah yeah that's a  that's a  sort of typical</u>
<u n="124" who="S0037" trans="overlap">was quite a good film actually</u>
<u n="125" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0037">but it's just like <pause dur="short"/> well it's totally pointless <pause dur="short"/> you may as well just sit on your own for an <trunc>ho</trunc> two hours <pause dur="short"/> it is entirely pointless</u>
<u n="127" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but it is a bit silly actually isn't it cos you basically just sit next to each other</u>
<u n="128" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you should never go to the cinema with anyone that you like because there's no point <pause dur="short"/> it's like you can <trunc>ha</trunc> you can't speak to them you can't see them <pause dur="short"/> if you whisper something to them everyone else gets pissed off</u>
<u n="129" who="S0115" trans="overlap">people do though don't they they always go looking for like</u>
<u n="130" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like when we watch films I'm always like hey <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so is that the guy that's done this that's done that? or What's happened then? What's happened now? Like you can't do any of that at the cinema cos you piss everyone else off</u>
<u n="131" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No I think my favourite way to watch a film would be yeah to like to be able to talk through it and like pause it and like</u>
<u n="132" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> rewind it yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> let's watch this bit <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah definitely let's watch this bit again like <pause dur="short"/> and uh and in that bar I was talking about like you know my favourite  my favourite  bar in the world you know the the</u>
<u n="134" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah in Berlin</u>
<u n="135" who="S0115">there was next to it was a room called that they called the Multikulti <trunc>Rau</trunc> Room</u>
<u n="136" who="S0037">right</u>
<u n="137" who="S0115">and they would put they <trunc>l</trunc> they would screen films and you can do exactly that like</u>
<u n="138" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0115">it not only is the best bar in the world but also has like</u>
<u n="140" who="S0037">best cinema in the world</u>
<u n="141" who="S0115">like a <trunc>ver</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> a good cinema where you could sort of <pause dur="short"/> I think the best for me like it's all about like the best the best bar the best cinema is about like you can do what you want with it you know like</u>
<u n="142" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I've quite</u>
<u n="143" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's about  it's about  allowing people to do <pause dur="short"/> it's about giving people the <trunc>op</trunc> the power and opportunity to do what they want</u>
<u n="144" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0115">and uh and a lot of that doesn't happen in uh in bars and cinemas like you're kind of stuck in like</u>
<u n="146" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no that's true</u>
<u n="147" who="S0115">yeah with a cinema you're kind of stuck there aren't you?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Cos like <pause dur="short"/> and like you know going to the loo is due you know in two hours it's natural that you would wanna at least pop to the loo once <pause dur="short"/> and like that's why it's sort of</u>
<u n="149" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I mean it it's if your mates you would wanna get you and your mates uh quite a few of them and then just watch a <trunc>s</trunc> a film like that you know in in one of your houses like and that's the sort of thing</u>
<u n="150" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0115">problem is like there's a bit of an incentive to yeah getting talking about economics again but uh there's a bit of an incentive in the economy to to to against that you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0115">what is at? Fifteen? Have we done fifteen?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0037">nine</u>
<u n="155" who="S0115">oh <pause dur="short"/> uh there's a bit of an incentive against doing things yourself at home um and in favour of spending more money <trunc>bec</trunc> because of the need for for more  for more  growth and more money in the economy so that like maybe people like the kinds of bars I was talking about they're not <trunc>parti</trunc> not particularly profitable</u>
<u n="156" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no no</u>
<u n="157" who="S0115">in terms of the economy</u>
<u n="158" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="159" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> and a lot of that the bar thing would have an element of cash-in-hand-ness about it and I think it did <pause dur="short"/> you know you when when you were saying you'd keep some of the profits <trunc>f</trunc> for yourself like  the <trunc>c</trunc>  = the <trunc>c</trunc> the cinema screening thing that I was talking about was like that was free so there was no money in that so that economically speaking they you know the government might wanna  might wanna  <trunc>di</trunc> dissuade people from doing that</u>
<u n="160" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0115">from spending their time without spending money you know what I mean</u>
<u n="162" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0115">uh and also in the bar yeah I think you would take the money for the beers and you were allowed to keep a certain share of the profit and clearly that clearly that's cash in hand like I think you're not you're you're unlikely to uh I think</u>
<u n="164" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah pay tax on that and everything</u>
<u n="165" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I I <trunc>t</trunc> I I'm not  I'm not  sure but I I imagine that you would collect all the money up and then like</u>
<u n="166" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0115">I think you would <pause dur="short"/> no I <trunc>do</trunc> I don't know actually I I suppose it's it's it would surely possibly be illegal to uh</u>
<u n="168" who="S0037">well I don't know</u>
<u n="169" who="S0115">to uh I just felt like it was like</u>
<u n="170" who="S0037">maybe if it's a private institution like maybe it's</u>
<u n="171" who="S0115">not taxed <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="172" who="S0037">something separate but I dunno</u>
<u n="173" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> no not I'm not sure about that actually I I guess they would have to write  they would have to write  everything down and therefore they could be liable for tax on that but but yeah was it it was a  it was a  <trunc>s</trunc> it was a uni</u>
<u n="174" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0115">bar so</u>
<u n="176" who="S0037">well it's probably subsidized anyway</u>
<u n="177" who="S0115">it may have some kind of yeah it may have <pause dur="short"/> so yeah no I don't think it was  it was  cash in hand like as much as I said but but I think it would've would've been subsidized yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah dodgy yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0115">but I was talking about um you see how like economics is you know like all this sort of profit is great on the one hand but on the other hand like some of the better things sometimes the better things are</u>
<u n="180" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0115">are not are <trunc>f</trunc> you know best things are free aren't they you know sometimes</u>
<u n="182" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think I tend to do most of my</u>
<u n="183" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like uh <pause dur="short"/> you know you would <trunc>re</trunc> record there's a problem like you record a film and then you just</u>
<u n="184" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0115">pass it like you copy it you video it and you pass it round you're your friends and that</u>
<u n="186" who="S0037" trans="overlap">pass it round yeah <pause dur="short"/> I tend to do most</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that's bad for the economy cos then they're not spending money on that film are they?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="189" who="S0115">you know what I mean so it's it's a bit of a there's a bit of a <trunc>coll</trunc> collision <trunc>coll</trunc> conflict between um</u>
<u n="190" who="S0037">I tend to do most of my film watching at um Christmas like <pause dur="short"/> tend to not really watch that many films not not recent films</u>
<u n="191" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah well we we're very lucky to have we're we're lucky to have like you know your your dad's fondness of DVDs and he buys all these <trunc>DVD</trunc> or he gets them from <trunc>ch</trunc> on quite cheap doesn't he because he sort of temporarily gets them or something?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but he buys <pause dur="short"/> no but <pause dur="short"/> he buys them ex-rental so</u>
<u n="193" who="S0115">I see yeah so he gets them quite cheap doesn't he?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like he goes to like you know Blockbuster or whatever?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0115">I've heard of it</u>
<u n="196" who="S0037">and um you know they have like you know they rent out DVDs and well everything um games and that as well but they they rent out like DVDs and stuff and um so once they've been rented out for however long</u>
<u n="197" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0037">then you can just buy them for like two quid or something <pause dur="short"/> because obviously they've been like played loads of times but well like my dad says like doesn't really matter how many times they've been played <pause dur="short"/> you know it's a DVD isn't it like? It doesn't run out after a hundred plays like</u>
<u n="199" who="S0115">yeah I mean</u>
<u n="200" who="S0037">they can't sell if it's if it doesn't work you know</u>
<u n="201" who="S0115">you know like that uh brings me onto actually uh the Pirate Party a bit actually cos uh</u>
<u n="202" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> actually</u>
<u n="203" who="S0115">it's it's quite big news in Europe in German and like Europe but <trunc>no</trunc> no one yeah I've never heard the <pause dur="short"/> I've never heard them mentioned in England really like</u>
<u n="204" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I've never really heard much about it like <pause dur="short"/> you keep talking about it and like</u>
<u n="205" who="S0115">but they're quite they've won like a they've won something in um in Germany like the Pirate Party</u>
<u n="206" who="S0037">so what are their values like? Pieces of eight?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I think they they don't really have any values apart from that you should be able to like</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037">plunder?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0115">it's to do with getting films like <trunc>pir</trunc> it's to do with pirated um</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037">piracy?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115">it's to do with like <trunc>int</trunc> internet piracy particularly like films and and music I think and and they they believe that like films should be <trunc>sh</trunc> should be freely shared after a certain amount of time or something</u>
<u n="212" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Piraty?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115">so they're perhaps have a certain they have an anti-copyright uh agenda <pause dur="short"/> um which I find</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but you can't get in like you can't win like something based on just one narrow</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115">well no they don't just have one uh I mean essentially they're they're I think there's an element of like um you know an a <trunc>s</trunc> a marginal anti-capitalism or some kind of centre-left</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115">vibe there that they have as well <pause dur="short"/> although I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> they they're sort of <pause dur="short"/> I don't know actually like <pause dur="short"/> I think they've got a strong like <trunc>libe</trunc> liberal you know libertarian sort of feel about them like that they wouldn't want to <pause dur="short"/> uh to be honest I don't know <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> um but I know that they were</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037">Cos you can't surely base like a political party on just one like fairly narrow um</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115">yes you can uh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0037">well like BNP IE other <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> But uh you you <trunc>ca</trunc> you can if people vote for you <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>pe</trunc> if there's a market if people  if people  will vote for a narrow one-issue party then then that's what's gonna happen like and uh if if obviously</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115">UKIP is the  is the  sort of the typically might be described as one one issue</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037">oh I hate all those</u>
<u n="225" who="S0115">one issue party um uh <pause dur="short"/> it's it's many they're just</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no because and not sticking up for UKIP cos to be fair I think they're absolute donkeys but</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115">I'll stick up for the British Empire</u>
<u n="228" who="S0037">no but they have like they <trunc>th</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> what I'm saying is though that their their spread of um values is a tiny bit wider than just piracy <pause dur="short"/> cos like UK independence or whatever the crazy</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115">oh is there any more of that down there?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> whatever the crazy uh sorry um whatever the crazy thing is that they're after</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0037">um it's slightly wider than piracy isn't it?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> yeah no no they they have other things as well like they they have like <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> oh but I I don't know I just knew that they that it was like a new movement coming out as a result of the the there is a bit of a problem isn't there in the the economy that that it's becoming very easy to to freely transfer any information so that would include any movie or theatre or or music or</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> share things yeah <pause dur="short"/> well what there was that young lad who was extradited to the US wasn't he? He had like a film sharing thing</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115">I don't know I don't</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037">he was a student he was from Sheffield I think</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115">oh right <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe</u>
<u n="238" who="S0037">and he was <pause dur="short"/> I can't exactly remember all the ins and outs of it but</u>
<u n="239" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they they had a thing in <anon type="place"/> didn't they they had in <anon type="place"/> they had like a  like a  peer-to-peer um</u>
<event desc="phone rings"/>
<u n="240" who="S0037">oh</u>
<u n="241" who="S0115">A peer-to-peer program that um you know some programmers that uh</u>
<u n="242" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh it's yours</u>
<u n="243" who="S0115">uh could well be my uh</u>
<u n="244" who="S0037">your mum?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0115">my mum couldn't it?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0037">shall I have a look?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0115">or it could be O2 even though I've told them to stop texting me</u>
<u n="248" who="S0037">it's from your mum <pause dur="short"/> shall I read it to you?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0115">uh as long as it's as long as there's <trunc>n</trunc> no swearing</u>
<u n="250" who="S0037">okay <pause dur="short"/> Hi Matt</u>
<u n="251" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0037">how are you? Have you been able to get out in the lovely sunshine today? We've had a four mile walk along the canal at <anon type="place"/> where you had an interview for bar work a few years ago</u>
<u n="253" who="S0115">yeah um I remember that yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0037">it was lovely <pause dur="short"/> the new dog enables us to walk much more briskly than we have <pause dur="short"/> some text missing</u>
<u n="255" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh I forgot yeah the the dog's died I forgot <pause dur="short"/> it's uh it is sad</u>
<u n="256" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I said about</u>
<u n="257" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it is sad it's always sad when uh when a dog dies but uh</u>
<u n="258" who="S0037" trans="overlap">of course</u>
<u n="259" who="S0115">but you know this new one uh the <trunc>Ja</trunc> the Jack Russell</u>
<u n="260" who="S0037">it's not a jack russell</u>
<u n="261" who="S0115">well it's similar to a jack russell</u>
<u n="262" who="S0037">it's a patterjack</u>
<u n="263" who="S0115">it's similar to jack russell isn't it?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0037">Patterdale terrier and a jack russell crossed apparently</u>
<u n="265" who="S0115">oh alright yeah <pause dur="short"/> so it's half a Jack Russell</u>
<u n="266" who="S0037">how do I even know this it's your mum's dog?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0115">I don't know you know I didn't  I didn't  even</u>
<u n="268" who="S0037">and I've got the <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="269" who="S0115">we could ask actually I can send a text back um</u>
<u n="270" who="S0037">we haven't got the rest of the end of the message</u>
<u n="271" who="S0115">is it asking exactly uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think I'd like to get a jack russell</u>
<u n="272" who="S0037">I like quite like the spaniels</u>
<u n="273" who="S0115">and a cat</u>
<u n="274" who="S0037">well I can't get a cat I'm allergic to cat</u>
<u n="275" who="S0115">yeah but I reckon we should just get it on a trial basis</u>
<u n="276" who="S0037">I don't think you can do that with a cat it's not a blooming</u>
<u n="277" who="S0115" trans="overlap">sort of like a <trunc>thir</trunc> thirty day trial <pause dur="short"/> it's not software?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="279" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no well <pause dur="short"/> could have a free trial</u>
<u n="280" who="S0037">I do have a cat allergy which</u>
<u n="281" who="S0115">yeah I was just <pause dur="short"/> I'm sorry</u>
<u n="282" who="S0037">we seem to have somehow forgotten</u>
<u n="283" who="S0115">I thought it was like a general allergy</u>
<u n="284" who="S0037">mainly cats</u>
<u n="285" who="S0115">you've got a lot of <pause dur="short"/> you've got the plant allergies but you grow plants don't you?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0037">I haven't got a plant allergy Matt</u>
<u n="287" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's the stupidest</u>
<u n="289" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you have you're allergic to some plants</u>
<u n="290" who="S0037" trans="overlap">am I? Am I allergic to plants? No no</u>
<u n="291" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> aren't you? You got tested <pause dur="short"/> you're allergic to leaves</u>
<u n="292" who="S0037">I'm allergic to some mould <pause dur="short"/> look <trunc>th</trunc> when they test you for allergies they test you for like two hundred things <pause dur="short"/> they put scratches on your back and they rub all sorts of crap on you <pause dur="short"/> and yes I am uh mildly allergic to some some weird mould in autumn leaves that doesn't mean I'm allergic to plants</u>
<u n="293" who="S0115">sorry I thought you had a like a pollen thing <pause dur="short"/> no?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0037">no I don't really  I don't really  have hay fever very badly no <pause dur="short"/> sometimes</u>
<u n="295" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I've probably  I've probably  got it worse than you actually</u>
<u n="296" who="S0037">sometimes it tickles but not very <pause dur="short"/> no not really <pause dur="short"/> it hasn't really</u>
<u n="297" who="S0115">my dad had hay fever or he said he did</u>
<u n="298" who="S0037">it doesn't really bother us <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>m</trunc> people in my family get it very badly but I think I've um I sort of have it less a lot less</u>
<u n="299" who="S0115">it's a bit mellow for Kerrang this is isn't it?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0037">I know I was thinking that actually I wonder if it's some</u>
<u n="301" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no don't turn it over it they'll probably  they'll probably  get better</u>
<u n="302" who="S0037">no no I just wondered what what was on <pause dur="short"/> oh it's the unsigned thing</u>
<u n="303" who="S0115">the the overlord of Alex Baker the overlord of upcoming and under the radar music <pause dur="short"/> Uh</u>
<u n="304" who="S0037">so it's</u>
<u n="305" who="S0115">he's the overlord but he's under the radar</u>
<u n="306" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well it's better than Loz Guest <pause dur="short"/> he's terrible <pause dur="short"/> he's like So you're um a musician</u>
<u n="307" who="S0115" trans="overlap">slander <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um</u>
<u n="308" who="S0037">so</u>
<u n="309" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> So <pause dur="short"/> no but he's he's just he's very lazy isn't he?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he's so bad <pause dur="short"/> oh he's terrible <pause dur="short"/> it's like doing an interview with someone you'd never met like without it ever being known that you had to give an interview <pause dur="short"/> but actually he's job's an interviewer <pause dur="short"/> it's like imagine if you just walked into a room and someone was like oh can you interview this person? you'd be like oh hi so tell me about yourself <pause dur="short"/> Essentially that's what he's like every time even though that's his job</u>
<u n="311" who="S0115">meh <pause dur="short"/> hm you never finished uh the Tin Drum did you?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0037">huh? Um</u>
<u n="313" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you never finished reading the Tin Drum?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0037">um has it still got a bookmark in? Yes</u>
<u n="315" who="S0115">I don't think you've finished it</u>
<u n="316" who="S0037">I haven't no <pause dur="short"/> I forgot about it <pause dur="short"/> we moved house</u>
<u n="317" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Ay?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0037">we moved house when I was in the middle of reading it <pause dur="short"/> and then I forgot about it</u>
<u n="319" who="S0115">really?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0115">oh <pause dur="short"/> well um yeah you should uh take it up again</u>
<u n="322" who="S0037">should do I wonder what the bookmark's in</u>
<u n="323" who="S0115">was it like Cat And Mouse then?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0037">huh?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0115">you <trunc>re</trunc> you read all of Cat And Mouse</u>
<u n="326" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I've read Cat And Mouse</u>
<u n="327" who="S0115">it's a tough book to read isn't it?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0037">yeah it uh a bit weird <pause dur="short"/> um but I should  I should  finish it <pause dur="short"/> I'm only about a quarter of the way through <pause dur="short"/> that's a good point I'll need that <pause dur="short"/> I've read a lot of books instead though like <pause dur="short"/> I've read a lot of <pause dur="short"/> started to read try and read a lot of the classics that I hadn't read</u>
<u n="329" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0037">Jane Eyre Pride And Prejudice Wuthering Heights <pause dur="short"/> You know I'd never <pause dur="short"/> it's bad to get to like twenty-eight and not to have read those</u>
<u n="331" who="S0115">sorry what yeah I was  I was  getting you know looking at this sandwich which could be the tastiest tuna sandwich of all time</u>
<u n="332" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it is really nice but have it's like I thought it was uh it tasted a bit</u>
<u n="333" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no no I'm not  I'm not  ready to taste it I'm just sort of  sort of  feeling it a bit</u>
<u n="334" who="S0037" trans="overlap">why? Are you not? How can you not be hungry? I was quite hungry</u>
<u n="335" who="S0115">no well I will be minute I will be in a while</u>
<u n="336" who="S0037" trans="overlap">see if the rest of your message has arrived <pause dur="short"/> no it hasn't</u>
<u n="337" who="S0115">got loads of rocket so it's gonna give it a</u>
<u n="338" who="S0037">it's nice I like I'll I might grow some rocket <pause dur="short"/> I think actually that's on my list</u>
<u n="339" who="S0115">Ray Winston was wanted to make a a <trunc>g</trunc> um Tin Drum</u>
<u n="340" who="S0037">what?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0115">I think they should make a film of Tin Drum <pause dur="short"/> well they already have made a film but they should make a another film I <trunc>rem</trunc> I just <trunc>rem</trunc></u>
<u n="342" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh we're missing  we're missing  Homeland but I've read the Wikipedia page so</u>
<u n="343" who="S0115">you've read the Wikipedia page? No no you've spoilt it man</u>
<u n="344" who="S0037">no but you see you didn't wanna <trunc>wa</trunc> you said you didn't watch it anymore</u>
<u n="345" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I don't really like it though <pause dur="short"/> I it's in  it's in  the way of something else uh something more important like Benidorm</u>
<u n="346" who="S0037">yeah it is actually what are we doing we should've watched</u>
<u n="347" who="S0115" trans="overlap">we're missing Benidorm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but Benidorm's on the plus one though that's the good thing we can watch it at ten</u>
<u n="349" who="S0115" trans="overlap">ah yeah well we'll we'll watch it on the <trunc>p</trunc> we'll watch it at ten yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0037">I'll just see <pause dur="short"/> I'll just check um <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I I just thought</u>
<u n="351" who="S0115">it's alright <pause dur="short"/> it got positive reviews</u>
<u n="352" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I didn't know <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know if I could commit to like  to like  ten more episodes of Homeland I was getting a bit bored of it anyway</u>
<u n="353" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I think I don't think I don't <trunc>fanc</trunc></u>
<u n="354" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but I like the story</u>
<u n="355" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I don't fancy having to watch like like whole series of it you know like American twenty-two episode series</u>
<u n="356" who="S0037">but I like the  I like the  um <pause dur="short"/> I like the story though <pause dur="short"/> you know even towards the end</u>
<u n="357" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I felt it <trunc>con</trunc> included I felt like a bit of turning into a bit of you know granddad but I you know like I felt it included a little bit too much sex</u>
<u n="358" who="S0037">it did it was quite explicit but like not very much</u>
<u n="359" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh to the extent that you you can't <pause dur="short"/> no I'm not I'm not a  I'm not a  granddad about about sex on the TV</u>
<u n="360" who="S0037">mhm</u>
<u n="361" who="S0115">but uh I felt that in that in the show it wasn't relevant to terrorism and espionage</u>
<u n="362" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I I think some bits were <pause dur="short"/> like I think like the bits like where he you know like stuff with his wife where it was shown that he wasn't adjusted to being home</u>
<u n="363" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah yeah if it's  if it's if it's  part of the story you know yeah just a total granddad aren't I uh?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like I think some of those bits <pause dur="short"/> you're a bit granddaddy <pause dur="short"/> no no no by no means like</u>
<u n="365" who="S0115" trans="overlap">if it's  if it's  part of the uh</u>
<u n="366" who="S0037">but there was bits where like it was you know it was by what happened it was quite obvious that he hadn't <trunc>adjust</trunc> he hadn't adjusted to like to being at home um <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's right over there now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="368" who="S0037">it's like the same colour as the carpet <trunc>l</trunc> uh back a bit</u>
<u n="369" who="S0115">oh yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> so there were some bits where it was like quite obvious that it was it did say something about the story but there were other bits where it was just like yeah right like a bit gratuitous</u>
<u n="371" who="S0115">A lot gratuitous</u>
<u n="372" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so anyway</u>
<u n="373" who="S0115" trans="overlap">anyway that's not even  that's not even  apart from the granddad aspect uh</u>
<u n="374" who="S0037">but yeah so I I thought like</u>
<u n="375" who="S0115">it's kinda implausible I think</u>
<u n="376" who="S0037">I'd really like stopped myself from watching all the rest</u>
<u n="377" who="S0115">but the interesting thing is that</u>
<u n="378" who="S0037" trans="overlap">uh sorry what stopped myself from</u>
<u n="379" who="S0115">the interesting thing is it was originally um Israeli and it it had like a it came from an Israeli series that they'd already made</u>
<u n="380" who="S0037">oh really?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0115">I thought I told you</u>
<u n="382" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="383" who="S0115">I think I did</u>
<u n="384" who="S0037">I read the Wikipedia page and I didn't even get that</u>
<u n="385" who="S0115">but it says it right at the beginning</u>
<u n="386" who="S0037">must've skimmed that bit</u>
<u n="387" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's the the the Israeli title means something like um um it it it doesn't mean it's not called that in in in Hebrew it's called like another word</u>
<u n="388" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what Homeland?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0115" trans="overlap">not called Homeland it's not called the Hebrew word for Homeland <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="390" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0115">it's it's called like <trunc>Abdu</trunc> Abducted or something</u>
<u n="392" who="S0037">ah crap I didn't put that washing in <pause dur="short"/> have I got?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0115">well d'you have to?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0037">I think it's like my work things</u>
<u n="395" who="S0115">oh no that's cool but you really should've seen to that earlier shouldn't you?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0037">I'm such an idiot</u>
<u n="397" who="S0115">no I'll bring <trunc>thi</trunc> I'll bring this</u>
<u n="398" who="S0037">there's only a few things</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="399" who="S0037">think it's my work things <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> is there anything?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0115">so it's like an essential wash?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0037">no well sort of <pause dur="short"/> is there anything you want washing?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0115">um I think I'm alright</u>
<u n="403" who="S0037">did you wash these by the way in the end?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0115">I did actually I hand washed them</u>
<u n="405" who="S0037">and uh have they done better?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0115">A little bit <pause dur="short"/> they're less fluffy</u>
<u n="407" who="S0037">okay</u>
<u n="408" who="S0115">um I hand washed them because I didn't wanna <trunc>u</trunc> I was worried that they'd run a lot so I couldn't put them in</u>
<u n="409" who="S0037">oh but if you put them in with darks like everything in there's dark</u>
<u n="410" who="S0115">well I thought  I thought  of that but just the way that it  that it  worked it like there wasn't  there wasn't  any <pause dur="short"/> the the dark wash had like colours in it you know and I don't want</u>
<u n="411" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah yeah bits of fluff <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0115">like like uh pinks or something I didn't want that to get all</u>
<u n="413" who="S0037">is there any of these that you want washing? What about this Guiness shirt?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0115">I think it's alright <pause dur="short"/> I think my stuff's alright I've <trunc>w</trunc> I washed  I washed  it all already</u>
<u n="415" who="S0037">what about this?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0115">no they're they're they're <pause dur="short"/> I mean if you think that <vocal desc="laugh"/> they need the</u>
<u n="417" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no unless you</u>
<u n="418" who="S0115">no I think I'm my stuff's alright <pause dur="short"/> I've uh I've washed all my stuff</u>
<u n="419" who="S0037">well I'll wash this</u>
<u n="420" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="421" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I should've done it before <pause dur="short"/> like I meant to do it while we were in here just um making tea but I forgot</u>
<u n="422" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0037">sorry</u>
<u n="424" who="S0115">oh yeah so I was gonna talk about the <vocal desc="laugh"/> Passover actually</u>
<u n="425" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="426" who="S0115">uh it's gonna I suppose we were talking about Easter and the Passover but uh kind of</u>
<u n="427" who="S0037">you is it is there something you wanted to do at <trunc>East</trunc> like you know like cos I'm off for a few days is there something you fancy doing or?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> uh you</u>
<u n="429" who="S0037">it's alright if there's not I mean we could just hang around and</u>
<u n="430" who="S0115" trans="overlap">something active uh</u>
<u n="431" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0115">we could go on a trip to Ely</u>
<u n="433" who="S0037">that might be nice mightn't it? I've not been</u>
<u n="434" who="S0115">I thought about it anyway um</u>
<u n="435" who="S0037">we'll have to look at the buses cos I think there might be like a <trunc>Sun</trunc> Sunday</u>
<u n="436" who="S0115" trans="overlap">or <trunc>Grant</trunc> Grantchester whatever it's called</u>
<u n="437" who="S0037">yeah like a bike ride? A picnic?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0115">possibly yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0037">that might be nice</u>
<u n="440" who="S0115">sounds uh interesting <pause dur="short"/> there</u>
<u n="441" who="S0037">ooh smell that</u>
<u n="442" who="S0115">there's some wine or whatever still</u>
<u n="443" who="S0037">it smells like something</u>
<u n="444" who="S0115">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's like um <pause dur="short"/> well it's partly a bit like  a bit like  toilet toilet uh fresheners as <trunc>w</trunc> a bit</u>
<u n="445" who="S0037">smells like something that I know but I can't think what it is</u>
<u n="446" who="S0115">yeah yeah I know that smell from somewhere</u>
<u n="447" who="S0037">I do <pause dur="short"/> ah it's so annoying <pause dur="short"/> hang on I'll just put this on</u>
<u n="448" who="S0115">quite like sniffing this thing</u>
<u n="449" who="S0037">ay?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0115">calpol</u>
<u n="451" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="452" who="S0115">yeah it's <trunc>Cal</trunc> it's cough medicine</u>
<u n="453" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="454" who="S0115">it is</u>
<u n="455" who="S0037">it's a perfume I used to have or something</u>
<u n="456" who="S0115">oh right <pause dur="short"/> no it's well to me it smells like cough medicine</u>
<u n="457" who="S0037">whoa <pause dur="short"/> I'm having a fight with this washing</u>
<u n="458" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is it's it's like pink Calpol <pause dur="short"/> did you ever have pink Calpol?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it does smell a bit Calpol-y <pause dur="short"/> it smells like that perfume I used to like</u>
<u n="460" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it has that smell like <pause dur="short"/> what is it? Is it jojoba oil <pause dur="short"/> it's jojoba <pause dur="short"/> like the world's a funny place innit where you can have fabric conditioner that's flavoured with jojoba oil <pause dur="short"/> how did they even think of flavouring a fabric <trunc>con</trunc></u>
<u n="461" who="S0037" trans="overlap">can you get that to <trunc>s</trunc> like</u>
<u n="462" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><trunc>S</trunc> stop being broken? You have to  you have to  turn the knob all the way</u>
<u n="463" who="S0037">yeah I know I know</u>
<u n="464" who="S0115">it's a dial actually not a knob but it has to turn all the way around all sixteen clicks to the  to the to the  number twenty-nine</u>
<u n="465" who="S0037" trans="overlap">do you? Is that the answer?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0115">think it's just <pause dur="short"/> well that's just like <pause dur="short"/> I'm not an  I'm not an  engineer but I guess that like if you do it sort of slowly then it goes like</u>
<u n="467" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is that really what how you do it?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0115">but sometimes it gets it it gets itself in a</u>
<u n="469" who="S0037">it gets itself in a tizzy all the time <pause dur="short"/> I've I've put it on for one thing</u>
<u n="470" who="S0115" trans="overlap">fix it two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen <pause dur="short"/> ah it's it's stuck on its um <pause dur="short"/> it should go to thirty when I pressed it <pause dur="short"/> it's gone to sixty <unclear/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0037">hooray <vocal desc="laugh"/> That's what it did for me</u>
<u n="472" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it did it  it did it  before I'm gonna have to uh turn it  turn it  off and on at the switch <pause dur="short"/> ah it's terrible <pause dur="short"/> we should ring the man</u>
<u n="473" who="S0115">I was gonna ring him about the leaky uh shower actually</u>
<u n="474" who="S0037" trans="overlap">shower <pause dur="short"/> I think that's under control a bit now though</u>
<u n="475" who="S0115">yeah it's got better <pause dur="short"/> I was worried that there was an an internal leak and uh <pause dur="short"/> well I've turned it turned him off</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="476" who="S0037">suppose we have  we have  been here for two years like things do start to sort of go wrong a bit and</u>
<u n="477" who="S0115">something doing that <event desc="sound of washing machine gurgling"/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0037">I don't want it on <trunc>fif</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> what was it on?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0115">fifteen <vocal desc="laugh"/> I did it too fast maybe</u>
<u n="480" who="S0037" trans="overlap">minutes?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0115">yeah I think I did it too fast <pause dur="short"/> well we'll just turn it off and on and</u>
</body>
</text>
