<text id="SK3B">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:30:21</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-05</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0041 S0084</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Relationships, TV, monarchy</topics>
		<activity>Friends eating dinner, chatting.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T11</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0041">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Conference and Events Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0084">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lewisham, London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Production Controller</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0041">tread water <pause dur="short"/> that's fine <pause dur="short"/> I can do that</u>
<u n="2" who="S0084">so you just have to tread water for twenty minutes?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0041">swim for twenty minutes and then tread water for three</u>
<u n="4" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="5" who="S0041">that's easy <pause dur="short"/> so basically the issue here is the long distance running and the sit-ups</u>
<u n="6" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="7" who="S0041">and the fact that <vocal desc="laugh"/> I've got to knock another two minutes off my time</u>
<u n="8" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so really when do you so by the time you go and do your fitness in five weeks you need to be running at thirteen minutes?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> I need to be running at about fourteen <pause dur="short"/> but my fitness won't be in five weeks <pause dur="short"/> it'll be a minimum of six weeks <pause dur="short"/> very very minimum</u>
<u n="10" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="11" who="S0041">from now <pause dur="short"/> so I've got six weeks <pause dur="short"/> I've already been training for six weeks</u>
<u n="12" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0041">so just six seven weeks</u>
<u n="14" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's definitely feasible</u>
<u n="15" who="S0041">I could I <trunc>de</trunc> I reckon I could lose a minute in six weeks</u>
<u n="16" who="S0084">absolutely <pause dur="short"/> it's definitely feasible</u>
<u n="17" who="S0041">imagine if I'd not started doing this in January?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh man</u>
<u n="19" who="S0041">can you imagine if right now oh it's getting a bit closer I've passed my recruit test I should start training now?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I mean it's amazing how quickly your body copes with things like that <pause dur="short"/> you'd have to be training every day though wouldn't you</u>
<u n="21" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0084">you'd have to go every single day</u>
<u n="23" who="S0041">and your legs'd think your probably legs'd just fall off</u>
<u n="24" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's</u>
<u n="25" who="S0041">you'd just wake up one morning and you'd be legless <pause dur="short"/> not the good way</u>
<u n="26" who="S0084">legless <pause dur="short"/> and your heart might explode</u>
<u n="27" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> that's also an option</u>
<u n="28" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's a tough one <pause dur="short"/> well I mean it'll be worth it in the long run <pause dur="short"/> I suppose that's the idea about pushing yourself so much <pause dur="short"/> presumably that's why people do it <pause dur="short"/> I would <unclear/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0041">I've just sent <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a message but it didn't save <pause dur="short"/> that's annoying <pause dur="short"/> I hope it went</u>
<u n="30" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> is he misbehaving?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0041">I hope so <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I just said um <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> should be okay I think <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="32" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh <pause dur="short"/> bugger <pause dur="short"/> it's cold</u>
<u n="33" who="S0041">freezing <pause dur="short"/> yep <pause dur="short"/> fact <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> to be honest I train most days during the week <pause dur="short"/> managed to get my run down to five O five</u>
<u n="34" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> let me know if you're free one daytime</u>
<u n="36" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0041">basically that's it <pause dur="short"/> I'm not  I'm not  being the person that he can easily see as an afterthought when he's got a a bit of spare time during the week <pause dur="short"/> he can fuck off</u>
<u n="38" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">love you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="41" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0041">love you</u>
<u n="43" who="S0084">hm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so sod that</u>
<u n="45" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="46" who="S0041">fuck that for a game of soldiers <pause dur="short"/> and if he wants to spend his weekends travelling to <anon type="place"/> then go for it <pause dur="short"/> cos by the sounds of it</u>
<u n="47" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/> But then I put another wristband <unclear/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0041">this girl's a massive limp lettuce</u>
<u n="49" who="S0084">yep <pause dur="short"/> oh definitely</u>
<u n="50" who="S0041">she's twenty-six and she's still working at uni <pause dur="short"/> well fucking great <pause dur="short"/> and I tell you what <pause dur="short"/> if he has a a nice easy life with her then fantastic <pause dur="short"/> five years time he's gonna be bored to fuck</u>
<u n="51" who="S0084">I was gonna say</u>
<u n="52" who="S0041">and he won't have achieved anything</u>
<u n="53" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not gonna be <trunc>g</trunc> it doesn't sound like it's anything that's gonna be going anywhere <pause dur="short"/> like in the short-term it's probably quite the appeal is that it's different to what he had with you</u>
<u n="54" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0084">but that's nothing that's gonna keep him there and interested long-term</u>
<u n="56" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> definitely not</u>
<u n="57" who="S0084">and if she were living here it might be a very different story</u>
<u n="58" who="S0041">I bet if she was living here he'd get bored of her very quickly</u>
<u n="59" who="S0084">I can definitely say that's true</u>
<u n="60" who="S0041">like it's all lovely now cos she's <trunc>g</trunc> they're <trunc>ba</trunc> he goes there and he <trunc>t</trunc> she takes him to gigs</u>
<u n="61" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0041">Cos she gets to go at the student union</u>
<u n="63" who="S0084">oh nice</u>
<u n="64" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so they went to see <anon type="place"/> and somebody else or something</u>
<u n="65" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="66" who="S0041">either way <pause dur="short"/> if she'd not got that privilege do you think she'd be buying him tickets to see stuff? No I don't think so</u>
<u n="67" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0041">and do you think he he'd be so excited to go there? No <pause dur="short"/> probably not</u>
<u n="69" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0041">so</u>
<u n="71" who="S0084">oh huh <pause dur="short"/> she's blackmailing him</u>
<u n="72" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> blackmailing him and then he's gonna feel sorry for her cos she's so fat</u>
<u n="73" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and and boring</u>
<u n="74" who="S0041">and which makes me <trunc>s</trunc> do you know I hate  I hate saying that I hate  saying that cos that's one thing that I always think that if you're gonna insult someone don't go for the below the belt shot</u>
<u n="75" who="S0084"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0041">have the fat comment <pause dur="short"/> but it makes me feel better right now <pause dur="short"/> so huh <pause dur="short"/> whilst she can't actually physically hear it then</u>
<u n="77" who="S0084">well I mean and</u>
<u n="78" who="S0041">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't know it then</u>
<u n="79" who="S0084">and the anger isn't directed at her <pause dur="short"/> like er your frustration is that he's interested in someone like her <pause dur="short"/> but your anger isn't at her <pause dur="short"/> it's at him</u>
<u n="80" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0084">for being a douchebag <pause dur="short"/> because she is er by the by and totally inconsequential</u>
<u n="82" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0084">and</u>
<u n="84" who="S0041">and at least she's not hot</u>
<u n="85" who="S0084">she's not <pause dur="short"/> it'd be much worse</u>
<u n="86" who="S0041">can you imagine if he walked <trunc>r</trunc> walked round with a stunner on his arm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0084">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I have this conversation all the time</u>
<u n="88" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="89" who="S0084">all the time <pause dur="short"/> because of my two serious ex-boyfriends <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and the first um serious boyfriend <pause dur="short"/> he ended up with someone who was a complete troll <pause dur="short"/> who I detested and who I knew <pause dur="short"/> and I knew he was after her <trunc>w</trunc> when we were together <pause dur="short"/> and I broke up with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> it ended quite badly <pause dur="short"/> and he got together with this</u>
<u n="90" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="91" who="S0084">girl who is fat and horrible <pause dur="short"/> and I just hated her</u>
<u n="92" who="S0041">huh</u>
<u n="93" who="S0084">absolutely detested each other at college <pause dur="short"/> she is a complete cowbag <pause dur="short"/> and er just <trunc>sl</trunc> slept her way through our group of friends <pause dur="short"/> like she was just known as the group bike <pause dur="short"/> basically everyone had shagged her <pause dur="short"/> and um and she just really like a <trunc>m</trunc> massive knob <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? Like no one had any time for her <pause dur="short"/> he got together with her and then they moved in together <pause dur="short"/> and they were together for about four years I think</u>
<u n="94" who="S0041">huh</u>
<u n="95" who="S0084">but they broke up last year</u>
<u n="96" who="S0041">Good</u>
<u n="97" who="S0084">and I said well at least she's a hound</u>
<u n="98" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0084">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said no no no no because it's a reflection on you <pause dur="short"/> like you'd want</u>
<u n="100" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0084">you'd want them to go for someone hot because then it means that they find hot women what you perceive to be hot attractive</u>
<u n="102" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0084">and therefore you know that you're hot <pause dur="short"/> cos then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> obviously bit of a dickhead at the time but got together with this girl <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> who was I consider to be very attractive <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> big boobs <pause dur="short"/> um pretty face <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> could cook <pause dur="short"/> is quite homely</u>
<u n="104" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0084">all these types of things <pause dur="short"/> and I always used to compare myself to her <pause dur="short"/> but I  but I  knew we were very different <pause dur="short"/> but she is hot <pause dur="short"/> she's what I would <trunc>c</trunc> consider to be quite attractive <pause dur="short"/> and er typically his type <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> brunette <pause dur="short"/> quite curvy <pause dur="short"/> and that had got boobs <pause dur="short"/> and I  and I  knew that he that'd be his type <pause dur="short"/> so it's quite hard <pause dur="short"/> like I think I don't wanna think of <trunc>hi</trunc> of anyone that I've been with to be with someone hotter than me <pause dur="short"/> cos you don't wanna think they're comparing you <pause dur="short"/> but at the same time</u>
<u n="106" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0084">like you don't wanna think that their taste is munters</u>
<u n="108" who="S0041">well that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> do you know this'll</u>
<u n="109" who="S0084">so</u>
<u n="110" who="S0041">make me sound awful but I kind of thought well apart from Tom who's gonna be biased because it's his girlfriend's friend</u>
<u n="111" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0041">and he must still think it anyway <pause dur="short"/> is that I don't want him introducing this fatty to his friends who you know has you know similar length hair to me similar colour <pause dur="short"/> I'm not a small person <pause dur="short"/> you know I don't want them to think oh well er he obviously goes for you know chubby blondes</u>
<u n="113" who="S0084">you're completely different though <pause dur="short"/> you look completely different <pause dur="short"/> you've got  you've got  a completely different style haven't you <pause dur="short"/> like she <trunc>d</trunc> she doesn't wear er high heels from what you were saying <pause dur="short"/> like she's not feminine at all</u>
<u n="114" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="115" who="S0084">whereas you very much are <pause dur="short"/> like if they met her they would see that she's completely different to you</u>
<u n="116" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0084">I mean obviously all girls have a similar look in the sense that they've all got boobs and a vajayjay</u>
<u n="118" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0084">do you know what I mean? Like I don't think they would compare the two of you <pause dur="short"/> and I <trunc>th</trunc> maybe that's as I say part of the appeal</u>
<u n="120" who="S0041">freaking hope not <pause dur="short"/> that's partially why I wanted to see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> I know it sounds awful and it makes me sound really shallow <pause dur="short"/> but I just wanted to do a bit of parading</u>
<u n="121" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0041">Cos last time he saw me <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>h</trunc> how big were? I was  I was  the same weight but a very different size <pause dur="short"/> I was like how I was when I moved in here</u>
<u n="123" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> your body shape</u>
<u n="124" who="S0041">so I wanted</u>
<u n="125" who="S0084">your body shape has changed a lot hasn't it <pause dur="short"/> you know I mean have you seen that?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0041">I wanted to parade</u>
<u n="127" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="129" who="S0084">no it has <pause dur="short"/> it really has <pause dur="short"/> you look completely different</u>
<u n="130" who="S0041">I can see my waist more now <pause dur="short"/> my waist's longer</u>
<u n="131" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> no you have changed shape <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="132" who="S0041">I wanted to parade</u>
<u n="133" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0041">so that there was no comparison between us</u>
<u n="135" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0041">at all <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0041">which makes me sound shallow but I don't care <pause dur="short"/> I still wanted to do it</u>
<u n="139" who="S0084">well at this point you know it's huh there's no rule book <pause dur="short"/> there's nothing to say you can or can't do this <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="140" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0084">you're sort of making it up as you go along <pause dur="short"/> because invariably people don't stay friends with their exes for this very reason <pause dur="short"/> cos it's very difficult <pause dur="short"/> very painful</u>
<u n="142" who="S0041">and seeing as if you do say something you don't get a reply</u>
<u n="143" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0041">I'm just sending a message saying has <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gone road or rogue or did you actually get that message? Cos it's not going to my save er items sent items</u>
<u n="145" who="S0084"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> taking control of the situation has now decided that you will not text <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>anymore</u>
<u n="146" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s probably got my best interests at heart to be fair</u>
<u n="147" who="S0084">he absolutely has  he absolutely has  We had a word with each other <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> thank God Monday's over</u>
<u n="148" who="S0041">oh thank God for that</u>
<u n="149" who="S0084">I spoke to Nicky <pause dur="short"/> sent me the world's longest message in the world <pause dur="short"/> and I also looked at my bank balance and cried</u>
<u n="150" who="S0041">oh don't</u>
<u n="151" who="S0084">so Friday she's er she wants to go out <trunc>Mon</trunc> er hang on wait what? She wants to go out Friday <pause dur="short"/> I basically said have you recovered from the death knell? What day do you wanna go out? Blahdy blah blah whatever <pause dur="short"/> says yes recovered now thanks <pause dur="short"/> now just counting the weeks <pause dur="short"/> ten weeks she's got left in her ridiculous job and try and save every penny <pause dur="short"/> she's only got ten weeks</u>
<u n="152" who="S0041">shit</u>
<u n="153" who="S0084">she said without much success so far <pause dur="short"/> so I dunno how that's going <pause dur="short"/> she said I don't think anyone else is free on the Friday but maybe we could go anyway <pause dur="short"/> she said make up for weeks not going out <pause dur="short"/> but really I can't do both</u>
<u n="154" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0084">both the Friday and Saturday <pause dur="short"/> especially because she then says was thinking <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> you know <anon type="place"/>r <pause dur="short"/> café Rouge <pause dur="short"/> or <anon type="place"/> for meal on Saturday evening <pause dur="short"/> which would be lovely but would be expensive</u>
<u n="156" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0084">then a cocktail or two after <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> does loads of different mojitos which and it is really nice <pause dur="short"/> at the moment it's me you <vocal desc="laugh"/> obviously</u>
<u n="158" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="159" who="S0084"><unclear/> naturally and <unclear/> that weird DJ guy</u>
<u n="160" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0084">and Dom boyfriend <pause dur="short"/> bring anyone you like as long as you let me know so I can book <pause dur="short"/> was looking for offers on the internet but seems to be hardly any for weekends <pause dur="short"/> sad face <pause dur="short"/> cry cry <pause dur="short"/> cry cry <pause dur="short"/> so if you're up for it</u>
<u n="162" who="S0041">jeebus</u>
<u n="163" who="S0084">you'd be very welcome to come on the Saturday <pause dur="short"/> cos I think even the Friday sounds like an absolute steal</u>
<u n="164" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0084">I feel like because it was Friday I might go wild and totally</u>
<u n="166" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0084">enjoy myself</u>
<u n="168" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="169" who="S0084">and then I've got  I've got  to go out on Saturday</u>
<u n="170" who="S0041">whilst I would love to I think my bank balance is gonna have to say no</u>
<u n="171" who="S0084">well if it were me I wouldn't go</u>
<u n="172" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I could <trunc>str</trunc> I think I could stretch it then be fucked for the rest of the month <pause dur="short"/> and I always do this <pause dur="short"/> and I think it's okay</u>
<u n="173" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0041">it's not okay <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0084">it's not okay <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0041">some guy that I was talking to on the internet um wanted me to go to a gig in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="178" who="S0041">this weekend</u>
<u n="179" who="S0084">as a first date?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0041">as a first date <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0084">quite a long drive isn't it</u>
<u n="182" who="S0041">isn't it</u>
<u n="183" who="S0084"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0041">that's what I said <pause dur="short"/> I was like um pretty long drive <pause dur="short"/> I mean luckily for you I know my way cos I used to commute to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0041">so by the by doesn't seem that far to me <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="187" who="S0084">it's only and it's only two roads isn't it <pause dur="short"/> which is quite nice <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I said but either way you know it's at night and</u>
<u n="189" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0041">I could get lost</u>
<u n="191" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0041">with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0084">he might kill you <pause dur="short"/> is he a squaddie? Is that why he's <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's full of squaddies</u>
<u n="196" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0084">it's <trunc>rea</trunc> have you been out in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="199" who="S0084">it's really rough</u>
<u n="200" who="S0041">is it?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0084"><unclear/> did her MA at <anon type="place"/> University so I went <pause dur="short"/> and I was in <anon type="place"/> at the time <pause dur="short"/> I remember forty-five minutes away from each other <pause dur="short"/> it was brilliant <pause dur="short"/> and er we used to when I used to go and visit her we used to go out in the student union because the town was so rough</u>
<u n="202" who="S0041">huh</u>
<u n="203" who="S0084">you would not go</u>
<u n="204" who="S0041">oh God</u>
<u n="205" who="S0084">it was fucking scary <pause dur="short"/> like people get beaten up</u>
<u n="206" who="S0041">right <pause dur="short"/> I'll get the name of where it is and will will will report back</u>
<u n="207" who="S0084">oh what was it called? There was a really awful awful club like sort of similar to <unclear/> but worse</u>
<u n="208" who="S0041">I'll get I'm gonna get the name <pause dur="short"/> cos if you hear it you might  you might  recognize it</u>
<u n="209" who="S0084">I'm gonna and I'm gonna say do not go cos you'll die</u>
<u n="210" who="S0041">shit</u>
<u n="211" who="S0084">although if it's  if it's  a gig it's probably just a pub or something</u>
<u n="212" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0084">and it'd be cheap <pause dur="short"/> super cheap</u>
<u n="214" who="S0041">oh I won't be paying for it <pause dur="short"/> he's paying for everything</u>
<u n="215" who="S0084">fine <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> then it's just petrol isn't it</u>
<u n="216" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0084">but whenever I go and see Rob it's not  it's not  that far <pause dur="short"/> takes about</u>
<u n="218" who="S0041">it's about fifteen pounds I think in diesel</u>
<u n="219" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0041">about fifteen quid <pause dur="short"/> fifteen <trunc>tw</trunc> you put twenty in to be safe</u>
<u n="221" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> put twenty in</u>
<u n="222" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it's only I'd quite like to do it as a bit of an adventure</u>
<u n="223" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0041">be nice to get out of the house <pause dur="short"/> and wouldn't cost me that much</u>
<u n="225" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0041">Cos it'd be twenty quid for the weekend</u>
<u n="227" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0041">Cos he'd pay for drinks and tickets and everything <pause dur="short"/> but um</u>
<u n="229" who="S0084">is it anyone we'd have heard of? The gig</u>
<u n="230" who="S0041">er I don't I think it's a local band <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't</u>
<u n="231" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="232" who="S0041">I did I said what type of music is it? And he said er</u>
<u n="233" who="S0084">death metal</u>
<u n="234" who="S0041">rock pop</u>
<u n="235" who="S0084">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> right</u>
<u n="236" who="S0041">I was like mm <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="237" who="S0084">er could be a bit</u>
<u n="238" who="S0041">in my head that's along the the lines of like Blink 182 <pause dur="short"/> cos I don't really</u>
<u n="239" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0041">not very good with music genres at all</u>
<u n="241" who="S0084">well rock pop covers like a multitude of sins doesn't it</u>
<u n="242" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0084">could literally be anything</u>
<u n="244" who="S0041">could like be Arctic Monkeys</u>
<u n="245" who="S0084">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's probably like Red Hot Chili Pepper type indie stuff isn't it</u>
<u n="246" who="S0041">oh that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0084">who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0041">my dad</u>
<u n="249" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="250" who="S0041">I'll ring him ask him to</u>
<u n="251" who="S0084">daddykins</u>
<u n="252" who="S0041">ring me back later</u>
<u n="253" who="S0084">he'll understand <pause dur="short"/> daddy will understand this</u>
<u n="254" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0084">I was going around to my dad's for supper but I just couldn't get out of bed</u>
<u n="256" who="S0041">I want dinner <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what I want though</u>
<u n="257" who="S0084">perhaps soup <pause dur="short"/> soup and crackers</u>
<u n="258" who="S0041">soup and crackers</u>
<u n="259" who="S0084">I ate at lunchtime cos I had the suppliers in</u>
<u n="260" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="261" who="S0084">I had what did I have? Er well there wasn't very exciting menu actually <pause dur="short"/> it's typical <pause dur="short"/> the day that we get dinner paid for us <pause dur="short"/> I had bacon steak <pause dur="short"/> which was quite thick <pause dur="short"/> wIth an egg on the top <pause dur="short"/> and um new potatoes and cabbage</u>
<u n="262" who="S0041">tu tu tu</u>
<u n="263" who="S0084">was really nice</u>
<u n="264" who="S0041">tu tu <pause dur="short"/> I had salad <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0084">bleurgh</u>
<u n="266" who="S0041">bleurgh <pause dur="short"/> and some egg whites</u>
<u n="267" who="S0084">that's really boring</u>
<u n="268" who="S0041">I mean the salad did have some peppers in and some olives</u>
<u n="269" who="S0084">urgh <pause dur="short"/> sounds really boring</u>
<u n="270" who="S0041">and a tiny bit of coleslaw <pause dur="short"/> cos I don't know if they make it with full fat mayo <pause dur="short"/> so I couldn't bring myself to eat it <pause dur="short"/> but I just did my lettuce leaves over it so they weren't</u>
<u n="271" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0041">dry <pause dur="short"/> that's how sad it is</u>
<u n="273" who="S0084">oh dear</u>
<u n="274" who="S0041">and a sausage for breakfast</u>
<u n="275" who="S0084">that's not very um very filling</u>
<u n="276" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> and a apple <pause dur="short"/> I had apple</u>
<u n="277" who="S0084">that isn't filling at all</u>
<u n="278" who="S0041">so I'm quite hungry now <pause dur="short"/> I quite wanna hit the pasta</u>
<u n="279" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> do it</u>
<u n="280" who="S0041">I think I might have a bit of spaghetti bolognese</u>
<u n="281" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0041">that's wise</u>
<u n="283" who="S0084">sounds like a an absolute winner <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> Definitely</u>
<u n="284" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> and then tomorrow I need to make soup <unclear/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0084">oh boring</u>
<u n="286" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="287" who="S0084"><unclear/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0041">I think I might do dahl instead <pause dur="short"/> which is basically lentil soup isn't it <pause dur="short"/> spicy lentil soup</u>
<u n="289" who="S0084">spicy <pause dur="short"/> yep</u>
<u n="290" who="S0041">oh and I forgot my went <trunc>f</trunc> to the gym forgot my conditioner</u>
<u n="291" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> so your hair's gone all dry then</u>
<u n="292" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0041">and picked up shampoo instead</u>
<u n="294" who="S0084">so your hair's gonna be dry</u>
<u n="295" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">knock knock</u>
<u n="296" who="S0084">hiya</u>
<u n="297" who="S0041">hello</u>
<u n="298" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> coming over</u>
<u n="299" who="S0084">right <unclear/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0041">do you want me to put more clothes on?</u>
<u n="301" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">no <pause dur="short"/> I'm just</u>
<u n="302" who="S0041">okay</u>
<u n="303" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I like to sort of not pay attention to her <pause dur="short"/> if you know what I mean</u>
<u n="304" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="305" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">not be mean <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="306" who="S0041">you'd like us not to pay attention to her</u>
<u n="307" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah <pause dur="short"/> if you know what I mean</u>
<u n="308" who="S0041">fine</u>
<u n="309" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">but not being mean about it <pause dur="short"/> you know what I was saying to you yesterday <pause dur="short"/> at her coming over and things</u>
<u n="310" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="311" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">I feel a bit uncomfortable with everything that's gone on <pause dur="short"/> cos she doesn't know that any of you guys know that anything's gone on at all</u>
<u n="312" who="S0041">fine</u>
<u n="313" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0084">oh that's absolutely fine <pause dur="short"/> of course <pause dur="short"/> course</u>
<u n="315" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">can you just play a blank? Phew</u>
<u n="316" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> hi</u>
<u n="317" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0084">yep</u>
<u n="319" who="S0041">end of story</u>
<u n="320" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0084">absolutely</u>
<u n="322" who="S0041">done</u>
<u n="323" who="S0084">sounds fine</u>
<u n="324" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">marvellous <pause dur="short"/> right I'm gonna have a quick fag</u>
<u n="325" who="S0041"><vocal desc="misc"/> Er about an hour ago <unclear/> that they hadn't actually managed to <unclear/> hadn't spoken <pause dur="short"/> and he said <unclear/> and he saw that she'd been texting <unclear/> oh change of plan tonight wink wink smiley face <pause dur="short"/> and he was really angry <pause dur="short"/> and he was like it's okay I trust her <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> fucking get him to understand what the fuck's going on <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> he just loves it <pause dur="short"/> he just loves the drama doesn't he</u>
<u n="326" who="S0084"><unclear/> dream</u>
<u n="327" who="S0041"><unclear/> dream</u>
<u n="328" who="S0084">I can't believe my feet today with the bug bites <pause dur="short"/> feel these</u>
<u n="329" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="330" who="S0084">just cannot cannot stop scratching</u>
<u n="331" who="S0041">oh God <pause dur="short"/> you're gonna rip your  rip your  skin off</u>
<u n="332" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> that feels so nice <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> what are you supposed to put on scratches? I need <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="333" who="S0041">sudacrem <pause dur="short"/> oo or like</u>
<u n="334" who="S0084">I've got <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="335" who="S0041">germoline or something or</u>
<u n="336" who="S0084">I've got Sudacrem somewhere</u>
<u n="337" who="S0041">I hang on a second <pause dur="short"/> let me have a look in my bag of tricks and see what I can find</u>
<u n="338" who="S0084">consult the drawer of goodness</u>
<u n="339" who="S0041"><vocal desc="cough"/> What do we have  what do we have? I do have <unclear/> what are you? Antiseptic liquid</u>
<u n="340" who="S0084">um <pause dur="short"/> is that what you do? Is that not for cuts?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0041">er</u>
<u n="342" who="S0084">I mean it's not that I I'm ungrateful <pause dur="short"/> I just don't wanna put anything on it that's gonna make it go mental</u>
<u n="343" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0084">huh</u>
<u n="345" who="S0041">um <unclear/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0084">um um</u>
<u n="347" who="S0041"><unclear/> though probably not this <pause dur="short"/> but if you wanna Google</u>
<u n="348" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0041">streptosil <pause dur="short"/> it's er it's Spanish <pause dur="short"/> so I'm guessing it was bought for bites</u>
<u n="350" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Streptosil <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="351" who="S0041">so what does it say?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0084">I'm a bit scared by it <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> I think this is probably why you're not supposed to throw away the box</u>
<u n="353" who="S0041">this is a box that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum made up <pause dur="short"/> that's actually Italian not Spanish</u>
<u n="354" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0041">so I'm guessing she bought that for for bites</u>
<u n="356" who="S0084">aw</u>
<u n="357" who="S0041">but um it doesn't say</u>
<u n="358" who="S0084">streptosil <pause dur="short"/> strep strep is something to do with bacteria isn't it <pause dur="short"/> like strep is the bacteria you get in your throat when you've got tonsilitis</u>
<u n="359" who="S0041">is it?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0084">and Strepsils are things that you take when you've got a sore throat <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know where that cream comes into the equation</u>
<u n="361" who="S0041">tut ff</u>
<u n="362" who="S0084">can you not translate?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="364" who="S0084">are they hard words? Difficult Italian words</u>
<u n="365" who="S0041">something superficial infections</u>
<u n="366" who="S0084">yes <pause dur="short"/> it's not I don't know they're not infected</u>
<u n="367" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="368" who="S0084">I just don't wanna scratch them <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna have to go to bed with oven mitts on my hands</u>
<u n="369" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> I mean if you want me to help you tape those bad boys up I can totally get on that</u>
<u n="370" who="S0084">might be necessary <pause dur="short"/> cos I did wake up scratching my feet this morning</u>
<u n="371" who="S0041">right <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="372" who="S0084"><vocal desc="cough"/> I just don't wanna scratch my face in the night and look like the Elephant Man in the morning</u>
<u n="373" who="S0041">oven mitts a go go?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0084">might have to be <pause dur="short"/> it's like <unclear/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0084">my um you know my boss is going to New York?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> I do</u>
<u n="378" who="S0084">bitch <pause dur="short"/> but not bitch <pause dur="short"/> I'm just very jealous</u>
<u n="379" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="380" who="S0084">um <pause dur="short"/> she got an e-mail from her new team <pause dur="short"/> um just some general bollocks <pause dur="short"/> work bollocks</u>
<u n="381" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0084">Don't really wanna go into cos it's boring but but they were using like er sweet and awesome <pause dur="short"/> we've got like this awesome contact and we've got like um this really good deal with these subscription for photos <pause dur="short"/> and then she just put sweet at the end <pause dur="short"/> it's so funny <pause dur="short"/> so she's gonna become she'll come back and talking like a real New Yorker</u>
<u n="383" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know where I've got that from you know <pause dur="short"/> I say awesome all the time <pause dur="short"/> and I have to stop myself from saying it</u>
<u n="384" who="S0084">awesome</u>
<u n="385" who="S0041">but I don't know when the frig I picked it up <pause dur="short"/> but I've said it for about seven years</u>
<u n="386" who="S0084">well I wonder if it's just just culture <pause dur="short"/> you know like we'll watch TV like American TV shows and <trunc>Austral</trunc> Australian like awesome and sweet they say a lot in New Zealand <pause dur="short"/> everything's sweet</u>
<u n="387" who="S0041">do they?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0084">bro  sweet bro  Oh that's sweet bro <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> um so I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I er my mum <trunc>tol</trunc> told me that when I was <trunc>s</trunc> five or six I used to watch Neighbours a lot <pause dur="short"/> obviously didn't we all Neighbours and Home and Away <pause dur="short"/> and um my accent changed <pause dur="short"/> like my <trunc>a</trunc></u>
<u n="389" who="S0041">really?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I would pick up an Australian accent and so my intonation would change <pause dur="short"/> and you know how Australians always go up at the end of every sentence? So everything they say sounds like a question</u>
<u n="391" who="S0041">sounds like a question</u>
<u n="392" who="S0084">so I was doing that all the time <pause dur="short"/> and my mum was like for fuck's sake</u>
<u n="393" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0084">just shut up <pause dur="short"/> so um she did put a ban on Neighbours for a while <pause dur="short"/> and I was devastated <pause dur="short"/> so it's quite funny like when you go to er America now they think that you sound Australian <pause dur="short"/> like they think British</u>
<u n="395" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0084">people sound Australian</u>
<u n="397" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0084">because they're retards</u>
<u n="399" who="S0041">they think anybody with a southern accent sounds Australian</u>
<u n="400" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's weird <pause dur="short"/> I guess maybe it's not any different to um like an English person and a Scottish person <pause dur="short"/> but then if you think that you can tell the difference between a New York accent and a southern accent</u>
<u n="401" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="402" who="S0084">can't you</u>
<u n="403" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="404" who="S0084">especially if it's like an Italian American New York</u>
<u n="405" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0084">accent</u>
<u n="407" who="S0041">York <unclear/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0084">York</u>
<u n="409" who="S0041">New York</u>
<u n="410" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="411" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I find it very frustrating that they can't  they can't  tell the difference between a <trunc>s</trunc> Newcastle accent and mine</u>
<u n="412" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0041">my accent and Newcastle accent</u>
<u n="414" who="S0084">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="415" who="S0041">completely the same thing <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well I guess yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean it</u>
<u n="417" who="S0041">it's</u>
<u n="418" who="S0084">you can <trunc>te</trunc> obviously we can tell that there's a difference <pause dur="short"/> but it's it's not like a southern and a  and a  northern accent <pause dur="short"/> I mean I know your accent and and a Geordie accent is completely different</u>
<u n="419" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="420" who="S0084">if you think that if you were someone who knew that people from the south say last and people from the north say last</u>
<u n="421" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0084">and I think they just lump you all in together <pause dur="short"/> no matter that you all sound completely different</u>
<u n="423" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="424" who="S0084"><shift new="singing"/><unclear/><shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="425" who="S0041">so so are they friends again now then or what?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0084">who who even knows? I mean er it changes well not even within the hour <pause dur="short"/> like less than an hour <pause dur="short"/> it's less than hour ago <pause dur="short"/> just before you got home</u>
<u n="427" who="S0041">this is crazy shit man</u>
<u n="428" who="S0084">well he's a glutton for punishment <pause dur="short"/> because she'll only say oh I don't know what we I want</u>
<u n="429" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="430" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> you've gotta give me time <pause dur="short"/> well why's she coming over here then? She can't keep saying I've gotta have my space and then texting <unclear/> day and come over</u>
<u n="431" who="S0041">I know this and you know this <pause dur="short"/> but it turns out that'd be too sensible</u>
<u n="432" who="S0084">she's a fucking loon</u>
<u n="433" who="S0041">actual Looney Tune</u>
<u n="434" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="435" who="S0041">I think I need a bit of spice in this</u>
<u n="436" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> spicy <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0041">spicy <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="438" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> nommy <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I definitely need some sort of pudding in my life <pause dur="short"/> maybe maybe a hot chocolate</u>
<u n="439" who="S0041">or chocolate Horlicks <pause dur="short"/> it's not as chocolatey as hot chocolate</u>
<u n="440" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> I actually avoided biscuits today though <pause dur="short"/> and I didn't have pudding <pause dur="short"/> cos we had <trunc>s</trunc> obviously a pre-dinner and I didn't have I was gonna have a hot chocolate <pause dur="short"/> cos they make did I tell you they make the hot chocolate with buttons? Chocolate buttons <pause dur="short"/> man alive <pause dur="short"/> it's the most amazing thing you've ever tasted in your life <pause dur="short"/> button like giant chocolate buttons <pause dur="short"/> they melt them down <pause dur="short"/> that's why you can only get it it's like the like a really small window of time that you can get it <pause dur="short"/> because they don't melt very quickly <pause dur="short"/> cos they're just cos they're retards <pause dur="short"/> they don't do it</u>
<u n="441" who="S0041">and then burn</u>
<u n="442" who="S0084">just put it on early</u>
<u n="443" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0084">so and they never make enough <pause dur="short"/> so you've gotta be there between like quarter to ten and half past ten <pause dur="short"/> if you get in that optimum window you can get a nice hot chocolate <pause dur="short"/> so they melt all the chocolate down from chocolate buttons <pause dur="short"/> and they scoop it <pause dur="short"/> they ladle it into a cup <pause dur="short"/> then they put hot milk and they ladle like</u>
<u n="445" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="446" who="S0084">some more chocolate in the top <pause dur="short"/> it's the most decadent thing <pause dur="short"/> it's like Belgian chocolate <pause dur="short"/> it's amazing</u>
<u n="447" who="S0041">oh I really want in my life right now</u>
<u n="448" who="S0084">it costs about one pound fifty <pause dur="short"/> which considering coffee like a large coffee would cost you ninety-two P</u>
<u n="449" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0084">it's not that you know</u>
<u n="451" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="452" who="S0084">and it's more expensive than coffee but if you were to get that in Costa</u>
<u n="453" who="S0041">it'd be like a fiver</u>
<u n="454" who="S0084">it'd be like a fiver <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I could've get one of those but I didn't <pause dur="short"/> dinner biscuit</u>
<u n="455" who="S0041">that is very restrained of you</u>
<u n="456" who="S0084">but there are definitely gonna be cakes in the office tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> cakey</u>
<u n="457" who="S0041"><unclear/> you resisted so far <pause dur="short"/> I think you're doing pretty well</u>
<u n="458" who="S0084">and I'm definitely gonna go to the gym tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> cos Daniel has said that he's free tomorrow afternoon</u>
<u n="459" who="S0041">oo <pause dur="short"/> that'll be good then</u>
<u n="460" who="S0084">Danny <pause dur="short"/> Danny Boy</u>
<u n="461" who="S0041">the pipes the pipes are calling</u>
<u n="462" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> Boy</u>
<u n="463" who="S0041">that'd be good</u>
<u n="464" who="S0084">what's that one is it Peter Kay? Stand-up where he sings Danny Boy</u>
<u n="465" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="466" who="S0084">with the helium</u>
<u n="467" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0084">the first time I watched that I was absolutely crying with laughter <pause dur="short"/> and I guess because it's like observational comedy isn't it <pause dur="short"/> everything he says you're like yeah I well I call it the big light <pause dur="short"/> put the big light on</u>
<u n="469" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0084">everybody calls it that <pause dur="short"/> it's funny isn't it</u>
<u n="471" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I used to love Peter Kay <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's a bit samey now <pause dur="short"/> cos he's not released anything new for a while</u>
<u n="472" who="S0084">no exactly</u>
<u n="473" who="S0041">but um</u>
<u n="474" who="S0084">and it</u>
<u n="475" who="S0041">but certainly when it first came out it was like my favourite</u>
<u n="476" who="S0084">and everyone was repeating it <pause dur="short"/> like cheese cake</u>
<u n="477" who="S0041">cake <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0084">A cake with a cheese <pause dur="short"/> I like it when he used to talk about his nanna who's in the retirement home <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And he'd go round and she'd say guess who's died?</u>
<u n="479" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="480" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've gotta guess</u>
<u n="481" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="482" who="S0041">guess who's died <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It's really funny <pause dur="short"/> I only saw her in the supermarket last week and she looked fine</u>
<u n="484" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0084">and she was run over by a bus</u>
<u n="486" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0084">what did you expect? The grim reaper walking along behind her <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> put that down love <pause dur="short"/> won't be needing now</u>
<u n="488" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0041"><unclear/> needing that where you're going</u>
<u n="490" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0084">he does an impression of her standing there doesn't he <pause dur="short"/> like as if the bus is coming towards her</u>
<u n="492" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0041">I just</u>
<u n="494" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="495" who="S0041">I like it when he's talking about the <vocal desc="laugh"/> the tea cup and he's like <vocal desc="laugh"/> fucking Rich Teas</u>
<u n="496" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="497" who="S0041">Rich Teas <unclear/></u>
<u n="498" who="S0084">again</u>
<u n="499" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0041">you drop it in <pause dur="short"/> it's like slow motion</u>
<u n="501" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0041">mum <unclear/> me biscuit's fallen in <unclear/></u>
<u n="503" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0041">too late <pause dur="short"/> no you're too late</u>
<u n="505" who="S0084">oh it's so funny</u>
<u n="506" who="S0041">hobnobs like the SAS</u>
<u n="507" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0041">SAS of biscuits</u>
<u n="509" who="S0084">dunk me again</u>
<u n="510" who="S0041">dunk me again</u>
<u n="511" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="512" who="S0084">so good</u>
<u n="513" who="S0041">it's so funny</u>
<u n="514" who="S0084">I like when he's in the cab at the beginning and the <unclear/></u>
<u n="515" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="516" who="S0084">and he picks her up in a cab doesn't he</u>
<u n="517" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="518" who="S0084">mr B Mr B's cabs <pause dur="short"/> and she gives him the credit card <pause dur="short"/> he's like where do you want me to swipe that?</u>
<u n="519" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="520" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> I miss Pete Kay</u>
<u n="521" who="S0084">comedy gold <pause dur="short"/> I mean I must have watched Phoenix Nights I dunno how many times</u>
<u n="522" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="523" who="S0084">hundreds <pause dur="short"/> dan had them on DVD and we used to whenever we used to come home from the pub late we used to put them on <pause dur="short"/> giggle like school kids <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> Oh <pause dur="short"/> what is this?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="525" who="S0084"><unclear/> wallet</u>
<u n="526" who="S0041">it's free</u>
<u n="527" who="S0084">it's free</u>
<u n="528" who="S0041">it's free money</u>
<u n="529" who="S0084">it's er well <pause dur="short"/> lovely <pause dur="short"/> oh River Island <pause dur="short"/> english <unclear/></u>
<u n="530" who="S0041">I dunno about you but as far as I can see that's free money</u>
<u n="531" who="S0084">well I would've said so <pause dur="short"/> mates rates card from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> whatever that is <pause dur="short"/> oh that's that really shit bar isn't it at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0041">oh yeah</u>
<u n="533" who="S0084">that I never see anyone in <pause dur="short"/> huh urgh condom</u>
<u n="534" who="S0041">huh urgh</u>
<u n="535" who="S0084">condomy <pause dur="short"/> well at least he's being safe <pause dur="short"/> what are the skinny photos doing in here?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0041">er <pause dur="short"/> what's his face crazy horse wanted to see what I looked like when I was younger</u>
<u n="537" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Crazy horse</u>
<u n="538" who="S0041">he doesn't know I call him crazy horse but I quite wanna tell him</u>
<u n="539" who="S0084">it's a very appropriate name <pause dur="short"/> because he's crazy <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> Keep getting e-mails from the people that I used to volunteer for <pause dur="short"/> jimmy's the night shelter <pause dur="short"/> and I just don't wanna go back <pause dur="short"/> I'm I'm a bit scared <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="540" who="S0041">how long were you volunteering there for?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0084">A few months</u>
<u n="542" who="S0041">what made you do this?</u>
<u n="543" who="S0084">um <pause dur="short"/> dunno <pause dur="short"/> just thought I was investigating volunteering possibilities in the city and there aren't really an awful lot <pause dur="short"/> like I thought oh you could like go and read to kids in school and stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> but can't really do that <pause dur="short"/> um although our our company give you seven hours a year so like one day a year to go and <trunc>s</trunc> spend a day volunteering <pause dur="short"/> doing something <pause dur="short"/> like you can have</u>
<u n="544" who="S0041">wow</u>
<u n="545" who="S0084">you can basically choose what you wanna do <pause dur="short"/> um but it'd be quite nice if you could do it more often <pause dur="short"/> um but like my our operations boss <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> whose birthday it was last week she's gonna do a project with the Romsey Mill</u>
<u n="546" who="S0041">oh yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0084">all the um teenage girls they're gonna um they're gonna take photos and make um a magazine front cover <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can</u>
<u n="548" who="S0041">wow</u>
<u n="549" who="S0084">take her Mac and take along like all the software programs that we use like InDesign and put the photos in there <pause dur="short"/> and mock up a spread or a front cover for a magazine <pause dur="short"/> they can you know they can do whatever they like <pause dur="short"/> and then bring it into the <trunc>w</trunc> into the office and print them out <pause dur="short"/> cos we've got a super duper whizzy lovely one printer <pause dur="short"/> um and they can actually keep copies <pause dur="short"/> so she said she's gonna volunteer and do that <pause dur="short"/> cos they're one of  they're one of  our registered charities <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="550" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="551" who="S0084">it's quite a good idea <pause dur="short"/> but I think</u>
<u n="552" who="S0041">that is a nice thing to do</u>
<u n="553" who="S0084">the thing about <anon type="place"/> is you have to like if you get the nightshift you have to sleep on the sofa there overnight with them</u>
<u n="554" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0084">kind of a bit freaky <pause dur="short"/> like you either there's three shifts <pause dur="short"/> either you do the breakfast shift <pause dur="short"/> so you go in at like half six and go and make breakfast for everybody <pause dur="short"/> there's <trunc>twe</trunc> if it's full there's twenty people like sleeping there at any one time <pause dur="short"/> like <unclear/></u>
<u n="556" who="S0041">twenty people?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0084">like homeless people <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> they've got eighteen beds for blokes and two beds for women <pause dur="short"/> which at the time I was like <trunc>wh</trunc> why is that? And they were saying well predominantly it's you find there's more men on the streets than women</u>
<u n="558" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="559" who="S0084">and they they put it down to like the break up of the home <pause dur="short"/> um they're saying like you know if a husband and wife break up and they've got kids like it'll always pretty much be expected that the man will move out</u>
<u n="560" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="561" who="S0084">and if he has a bit of a break down of like <trunc>s</trunc> events spiral out of control <pause dur="short"/> like he might get a bit depressed <pause dur="short"/> he might not be able to go into work <pause dur="short"/> he might lose his job <pause dur="short"/> and then he hasn't got any money <pause dur="short"/> and all of a sudden <pause dur="short"/> he's too proud to ask for help</u>
<u n="562" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0084">before you know it it's like a really slippery slope <pause dur="short"/> and then once you're on the streets you can't get another job cos you haven't got an address and you don't ask for help <pause dur="short"/> I think women are much more um able to do that <pause dur="short"/> so you do just and actually when she said that I thought well yeah no you do mainly see men don't you</u>
<u n="564" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="565" who="S0084">you don't see a lot of women <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I dunno <pause dur="short"/> it's hard</u>
<u n="566" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I I think it would freak me out too much</u>
<u n="567" who="S0084">I think the idea of it's probably worse than it actually  it actually  is like</u>
<u n="568" who="S0041">I'd just be scared of people that are on drugs</u>
<u n="569" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> although I mean obviously they've got very strict rules <pause dur="short"/> if they found out that anybody brought it onto the the site they'd be out instantly</u>
<u n="570" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0084">but um yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean you just don't know <pause dur="short"/> and if you</u>
<u n="572" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's my only problem <pause dur="short"/> the drug thing</u>
<u n="573" who="S0084">if you sleep there you've gotta sleep on the sofa <pause dur="short"/> which is out in the open <pause dur="short"/> like the er dormitory block on the side <pause dur="short"/> um but to get out and cross the room to the toilets they've gotta come into your space <pause dur="short"/> and there's always night people there <pause dur="short"/> like there's always <trunc>sta</trunc> cos you're a volunteer but there are extra paid staff <pause dur="short"/> and there's always someone sat in their little office <pause dur="short"/> but it's locked <pause dur="short"/> and it's got like bulletproof glass <pause dur="short"/> and they're they're behind the screen <pause dur="short"/> and I think God if anything</u>
<u n="574" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so people behind the screen</u>
<u n="575" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="576" who="S0041">and I've got to be in with them all</u>
<u n="577" who="S0084">with the crazies</u>
<u n="578" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I'm sure they're not all crazy <pause dur="short"/> but the risk of sleeping anywhere with a group of strangers</u>
<u n="579" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="580" who="S0041">never mind homeless people <pause dur="short"/> doesn't matter who they are</u>
<u n="581" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="582" who="S0041">you know <pause dur="short"/> freaks me out</u>
<u n="583" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is hard <pause dur="short"/> cos you do sort of you get to a point where you think well I wanna  I wanna  do something <pause dur="short"/> I wanna give something back <pause dur="short"/> but it's finding the right thing</u>
<u n="584" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="585" who="S0084">you know you can't sort of volunteer in a shop because you work</u>
<u n="586" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0084">and you don't have time to do that <pause dur="short"/> so it's sort of finding other ways of doing it <pause dur="short"/> and then I was gonna volunteer for the St John's Ambulance but I realized too squeamish</u>
<u n="588" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that would've been great <pause dur="short"/> but yeah be <trunc>ve</trunc> I'd be sick so</u>
<u n="589" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I would literally just pass out <pause dur="short"/> and then they'd need another paramedic for me</u>
<u n="590" who="S0041">bit of an issue</u>
<u n="591" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="592" who="S0041">I actually watched um a programme recently and basically a bit like Brits Abroad but</u>
<u n="593" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="594" who="S0041">brits going to festivals and getting too drunk</u>
<u n="595" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="596" who="S0041">and how they got hurt you know smashing their feet in into stuff and</u>
<u n="597" who="S0084"><vocal desc="yawn"/> Oh God</u>
<u n="598" who="S0041">just basically being general alcoholics</u>
<u n="599" who="S0084">Good <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="600" who="S0041">and all the people from St John's Ambulance that kind of volunteered did this every year</u>
<u n="601" who="S0084">God</u>
<u n="602" who="S0041">like they they spent their summers picking up drunkards</u>
<u n="603" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="604" who="S0041">literally picking up drunkards <pause dur="short"/> they were getting vomited on</u>
<u n="605" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="606" who="S0041">like they were getting people that were like shouting cos they were drunk <pause dur="short"/> I mean they were getting people that were genuinely actually just got trampled in the</u>
<u n="607" who="S0084">oh God</u>
<u n="608" who="S0041">in the herd</u>
<u n="609" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="610" who="S0041">I just I was watching it and they were like well you know they'll get more out of this than coming to the show itself</u>
<u n="611" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> what's what</u>
<u n="612" who="S0041">generous thing to do</u>
<u n="613" who="S0084">what people like that do is amazing isn't it really <pause dur="short"/> I think of all the times <vocal desc="laugh"/> all the times</u>
<u n="614" who="S0041">every time</u>
<u n="615" who="S0084">the occasional times that I would get really smashed at when I was at uni and you know they they were always there  they were always there  outside the student union every night just to make sure everyone was okay <pause dur="short"/> and <unclear/> and they'd come in and look after you if you were feeling a bit dodgy and you know <pause dur="short"/> it was nice that they did that</u>
<u n="616" who="S0041">do you wanna try the <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="617" who="S0084">um <pause dur="short"/> shall I?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0041">do you want to have a smell of it and see what <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="619" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just a little sniffedy doo dah</u>
<u n="620" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">how are you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> anyway by the way?</u>
<u n="621" who="S0041">Good <pause dur="short"/> thank you</u>
<u n="622" who="S0084">thank you</u>
<u n="623" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">jolly good good good good good goody good good good</u>
<u n="624" who="S0084"><unclear/> nutritiously delicious?</u>
<u n="625" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="626" who="S0084">why's it nutritiously delicious? Cos it's oats?</u>
<u n="627" who="S0041">full of vitamins</u>
<u n="628" who="S0084">huh <pause dur="short"/> is it actually full of vitamins?</u>
<u n="629" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="630" who="S0084">is it actually actually a source of calcium? <trunc>Vi</trunc> oh</u>
<u n="631" who="S0041">I think I might've made a bit too much here to be fair</u>
<u n="632" who="S0084">get it down you <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="633" who="S0041">but you know I can always have a rest and come back to it later can't I</u>
<u n="634" who="S0084">does smell nice <pause dur="short"/> mm that's better</u>
<u n="635" who="S0041">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's better <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="636" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="637" who="S0041">it's like it's warm and malty and chocolatey and</u>
<u n="638" who="S0084">what do I do with it? Four teaspoons</u>
<u n="639" who="S0041">just put four teaspoons and then milk</u>
<u n="640" who="S0084">little bit of milk <pause dur="short"/> ah man</u>
<u n="641" who="S0041">little bit of milk</u>
<u n="642" who="S0084">still haven't bought milk <pause dur="short"/> can I pinch a bit of yours?</u>
<u n="643" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> course you can</u>
<u n="644" who="S0084">thanks mate <pause dur="short"/> I promise I'll buy milk tomorrow</u>
<u n="645" who="S0041">you might as well just use it cos er it'll just go out of date <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> er if that milk does go out of date <pause dur="short"/> don't really know but</u>
<u n="646" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="647" who="S0041">May already be out of date and I'm secretly poisoning you <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="648" who="S0084">until one of us dies</u>
<u n="649" who="S0041">until one of us keels over <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> achy legs</u>
<u n="650" who="S0084">that's from a film actually isn't it <pause dur="short"/> is there a film where someone says that?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0041">until one of us dies?</u>
<u n="652" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> it's in Blackadder <pause dur="short"/> did you ever watch Blackadder?</u>
<u n="653" who="S0041">mm mm</u>
<u n="654" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> when I was growing up my mum had mum and dad were really into Blackadder <pause dur="short"/> but they had the fourth series <pause dur="short"/> so you know like each series is a different period of time</u>
<u n="655" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="656" who="S0084">dunno if you've ever watched <trunc>Blacka</trunc> Blackadder <pause dur="short"/> yeah so it's just</u>
<u n="657" who="S0041">I saw the one with Queen Victoria in</u>
<u n="658" who="S0084">er</u>
<u n="659" who="S0041">I've seen a couple of those <pause dur="short"/> is that it?</u>
<u n="660" who="S0084">Elizabeth <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> queen Elizabeth is <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="661" who="S0041">oh sorry <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0084">um so that's the second series <pause dur="short"/> queenie <pause dur="short"/> um <vocal desc="cough"/> and then the third series is the Regency <pause dur="short"/> so it's like sort of turn of the century <pause dur="short"/> nineteen hundreds <pause dur="short"/> um and then oh no earlier than that <pause dur="short"/> later than that? Was Regency before Victoria? No it must have been <trunc>af</trunc> God my history's terrible</u>
<u n="663" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="664" who="S0084">anyway it's <trunc>re</trunc> it's Regency <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>whene</trunc> whenever that was <pause dur="short"/> I'm not quite sure <pause dur="short"/> um but they're wearing  they're wearing  tights <pause dur="short"/> so I'm gonna say it was pre-Victorian <pause dur="short"/> which means it would've been like the eighteen</u>
<u n="665" who="S0041">that's really annoying me now <pause dur="short"/> I really wanna know</u>
<u n="666" who="S0084">eighteen forties or something <pause dur="short"/> let me go and get my phone and I'll be able to tell you madame</u>
<u n="667" who="S0041">need some water <pause dur="short"/> be able to google that up</u>
<u n="668" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="669" who="S0041">I mean I'd get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but I googled too much today on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0084"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="671" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="672" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> voicemail voicemail</u>
<u n="673" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="674" who="S0084">right <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> blackadder <pause dur="short"/> so the third <pause dur="short"/> the third season is Regency <pause dur="short"/> we will determine when that actually was</u>
<u n="675" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="676" who="S0084">um <pause dur="short"/> and the fourth season is the First World War <pause dur="short"/> so in the trenches <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="677" who="S0041">oh right <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="678" who="S0084">they all play <trunc>diff</trunc> they all play the same titled character <pause dur="short"/> so they're always there's always um Rowan Atkinson plays Blackadder <pause dur="short"/> there's always um</u>
<u n="679" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then they do</u>
<u n="680" who="S0084">Tony Robinson who plays Baldrick</u>
<u n="681" who="S0041">extras as well</u>
<u n="682" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="683" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="684" who="S0084">and they do extras <pause dur="short"/> and it's usually the same sort of people <pause dur="short"/> and um in the huh in the fourth series Blackadder plays um er an officer <pause dur="short"/> um because he's educated <pause dur="short"/> er Hugh Laurie plays George <pause dur="short"/> who's also an officer <pause dur="short"/> he's out just out of <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> but he's only an officer because he <trunc>w</trunc> he's from the middle classes <pause dur="short"/> but he's thick as two um</u>
<u n="685" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="686" who="S0084">short planks <pause dur="short"/> he's really really stupid <pause dur="short"/> it's really funny <pause dur="short"/> and he gets on well with Baldrick <pause dur="short"/> who's lower working class <pause dur="short"/> who's just like the the squaddie <pause dur="short"/> the cannon fodder</u>
<u n="687" who="S0041">is that the one that was on Time Team?</u>
<u n="688" who="S0084">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="689" who="S0041">got it</u>
<u n="690" who="S0084">Tony Robinson <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so <vocal desc="laugh"/> he's like er they play I spy <vocal desc="laugh"/> and um he's going like I spy something beginning with R <pause dur="short"/> and then it's <trunc>B</trunc> Baldrick the stupid one and Blackadder <pause dur="short"/> and he's like motorbike</u>
<u n="691" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="692" who="S0084">and <vocal desc="laugh"/> and Blackadder's like what? He's like oh motorbike starts with a <event desc="sound of motorbike"/></u>
<u n="693" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="694" who="S0084">no no the letter <pause dur="short"/> it starts with the letter <pause dur="short"/> breakfast</u>
<u n="695" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="696" who="S0084">what? My breakfast always starts with a letter <pause dur="short"/> then I have a little boiled egg <pause dur="short"/> and he's like right come here <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> He says please get this before one of us dies</u>
<u n="697" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="698" who="S0084">it's so funny</u>
<u n="699" who="S0041">that's really good</u>
<u n="700" who="S0084">I really  I really  would recommend it <pause dur="short"/> I mean the thing is actually it's quite sad because the fourth series is the last series <pause dur="short"/> and obviously it's set in the trenches <pause dur="short"/> and it's all very funny like darkly comic</u>
<u n="701" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="702" who="S0084">and the last episode in the every episode they're basically trying to find a way of getting out of being in the trenches <pause dur="short"/> like that's the idea in every episode <pause dur="short"/> I think there's eight <pause dur="short"/> blackadder's trying to find a way to get out <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't wanna die <pause dur="short"/> he really</u>
<u n="703" who="S0041">right</u>
<u n="704" who="S0084">wants to live quite badly <pause dur="short"/> doesn't wanna go over the top <pause dur="short"/> certainly doesn't wanna go out into no man's land <pause dur="short"/> certainly doesn't wanna get shot <pause dur="short"/> so in every episode he's trying to find a way out <pause dur="short"/> until the last episode <pause dur="short"/> and he thinks he's done it <pause dur="short"/> he thinks he's found a way out by acting mad <pause dur="short"/> but then he realizes it's it's it's not gonna work <pause dur="short"/> he's gonna have to go over the top <pause dur="short"/> and er and they do and they blow all their whistles and they go over the top <pause dur="short"/> and then you just see like footage of the men like coming over the top of the trenches <pause dur="short"/> and it's all in slow motion <pause dur="short"/> I don't really like slow motion but it's really powerful <pause dur="short"/> it's really poignant <pause dur="short"/> and um</u>
<u n="705" who="S0041">do you know I might have seen somebody talk about this on the TV before</u>
<u n="706" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="707" who="S0041">and then play that clip</u>
<u n="708" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it's <trunc>re</trunc> it really brings tears to your eyes <pause dur="short"/> but obviously because it all just makes it so real <pause dur="short"/> because you knew that they were doing that <pause dur="short"/> boys were coming out of the trench into the cannons <pause dur="short"/> and then you know millions died in these fields <pause dur="short"/> and er they play like slow music over the <trunc>t</trunc> they play the theme tune but really slowly</u>
<u n="709" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="710" who="S0084">and er then then it all just fades</u>
<u n="711" who="S0041">I have heard it before</u>
<u n="712" who="S0084">into the poppy fields <pause dur="short"/> so which is what it is now <pause dur="short"/> and oh my God it kills you</u>
<u n="713" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="714" who="S0084">because er I think because up to that point you don't  you don't  see it coming <pause dur="short"/> like the first time you watch it you think oh it's really funny  it's really funny  They're gonna get out <pause dur="short"/> of course they're gonna get out  they're gonna get out</u>
<u n="715" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="716" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> and they don't</u>
<u n="717" who="S0041">I think it was a programme about black humour I watched</u>
<u n="718" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="719" who="S0041">Cos it had things about Mighty Boosh in it as well <pause dur="short"/> there was quite a few little things</u>
<u n="720" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="721" who="S0041">but that's something I never got into <pause dur="short"/> blackadder or Monty Python</u>
<u n="722" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean it is very very strange <pause dur="short"/> very daft <pause dur="short"/> I suppose <pause dur="short"/> but um it's worth  it's worth  a watch because I just think it's so clever <pause dur="short"/> it's so well done <pause dur="short"/> um that I think anyone should watch it really</u>
<u n="723" who="S0041">like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> made me watch the Monthy Python film once</u>
<u n="724" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="725" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> and I didn't really get it <pause dur="short"/> like I didn't find it funny at all <pause dur="short"/> whereas daft humour we're talking Drop Dead Fred and Bottom</u>
<u n="726" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="727" who="S0041">with Rik Mayall <pause dur="short"/> I find hilarious</u>
<u n="728" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="729" who="S0041">I don't understand where I missed the train</u>
<u n="730" who="S0084">well I don't I mean it's just  it's just  people's um humour isn't it <pause dur="short"/> you know it's</u>
<u n="731" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="732" who="S0084">you're not  you're not  gonna have it all not everyone's gonna have the same sense of humour</u>
<u n="733" who="S0041">well it's <trunc>abou</trunc> it's the same type of comedy isn't it <pause dur="short"/> same type</u>
<u n="734" who="S0084">um</u>
<u n="735" who="S0041">of silly <pause dur="short"/> thirty-year-old boy toilet humour</u>
<u n="736" who="S0084">you yeah well that's that's what you like <pause dur="short"/> I mean the black humour obviously is is quite different I think <pause dur="short"/> cos it's like I think the Mighty Boosh draws from that <pause dur="short"/> that sort of silly silly humour <pause dur="short"/> but it's also so off the wall <pause dur="short"/> so obscure <pause dur="short"/> so abstract <pause dur="short"/> like it's it's sort of pushing those boundaries I think <pause dur="short"/> and now that he's done that stupid like</u>
<u n="737" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="738" who="S0084">luxury Comedy I think you know</u>
<u n="739" who="S0041">what was that?</u>
<u n="740" who="S0084">you're just being a twat now <pause dur="short"/> no one  no one  gives a fuck about you <pause dur="short"/> okay Regency era was eighteen eleven to eighteen twenty <pause dur="short"/> so it was pre-Victoria</u>
<u n="741" who="S0041">well done you</u>
<u n="742" who="S0084">well <pause dur="short"/> so it was turn of the century <pause dur="short"/> just not the nineteenth <trunc>centu</trunc> no it was the nineteenth century not the twentieth century <pause dur="short"/> actually I might've said that <pause dur="short"/> but yeah basically my my history is sort of earlier and then later</u>
<u n="743" who="S0041">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> I've none <pause dur="short"/> I have literally Egypt <pause dur="short"/> tudors <pause dur="short"/> romans</u>
<u n="744" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="745" who="S0041">little bit of Elizabeth <pause dur="short"/> victorians</u>
<u n="746" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="747" who="S0041">little bit of Victorians</u>
<u n="748" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="749" who="S0041">and that's about it <pause dur="short"/> that's literally my entire history <pause dur="short"/> no world wars <pause dur="short"/> no cold war <pause dur="short"/> no civil war <pause dur="short"/> no <trunc>n</trunc> nothing</u>
<u n="750" who="S0084">I think it's probably the stuff that you learn at school though isn't it <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? Like you probably don't go into that much detail of the cold war till <trunc>lat</trunc> until you do your GCSEs <pause dur="short"/> and if you haven't chosen to do history</u>
<u n="751" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="752" who="S0084">then you wouldn't <pause dur="short"/> you probably wouldn't study it</u>
<u n="753" who="S0041">and I moved schools as well so</u>
<u n="754" who="S0084">there's probably gaps there</u>
<u n="755" who="S0041">I completely missed like they were studying the Aztecs in the secondary school <pause dur="short"/> whereas I was studying like er dunno Tudors or something <pause dur="short"/> and as I moved</u>
<u n="756" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="757" who="S0041">they were studying Tudors again</u>
<u n="758" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="759" who="S0041">so I I got two lots of the same thing</u>
<u n="760" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="761" who="S0041">and missed like two years of history</u>
<u n="762" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="763" who="S0041">out of the four that I did so</u>
<u n="764" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="765" who="S0041">really bad</u>
<u n="766" who="S0084">that's that's the danger with the curriculum <pause dur="short"/> that you know it is open to um an interpretation at each of the schools that you're at so</u>
<u n="767" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="768" who="S0084">so yeah that is quite hard</u>
<u n="769" who="S0041">like what happened after Victorians?</u>
<u n="770" who="S0084">oh that</u>
<u n="771" who="S0041">what was here after that? Cos as far as I'm concerned that was the end of it</u>
<u n="772" who="S0084">well no no well er</u>
<u n="773" who="S0041">victorians there's us</u>
<u n="774" who="S0084">well Victoria died in nineteen O one didn't she <pause dur="short"/> and then you had Edward <pause dur="short"/> but Edward <trunc>eb</trunc> abdicated <pause dur="short"/> so you had  you had  George her son <pause dur="short"/> she had fourteen kids or something ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> obviously cos they had all <trunc>ch</trunc> all the children <pause dur="short"/> they had a lot of</u>
<u n="775" who="S0041">all the children</u>
<u n="776" who="S0084">a lot of children that died <pause dur="short"/> but they had um it was George <pause dur="short"/> you know The King's Speech?</u>
<u n="777" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="778" who="S0084">it was George the fifth after Victoria</u>
<u n="779" who="S0041">so that's him?</u>
<u n="780" who="S0084">well no he's the one who came after <pause dur="short"/> he's George the sixth <pause dur="short"/> he's the Queen's dad <pause dur="short"/> so George the fifth was the was his dad in the film <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> michael Gambon <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>re</trunc> he was really mean to him</u>
<u n="781" who="S0041">oh yeah</u>
<u n="782" who="S0084">why can't you speak? It was George the fifth <pause dur="short"/> who was Victoria's son presumably <pause dur="short"/> um then it and er he died <pause dur="short"/> and it was Edward <pause dur="short"/> edward <trunc>wa</trunc> <trunc>th</trunc> although that wasn't his name <pause dur="short"/> his name was Robert <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="783" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="784" who="S0084">his name was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and he was supposed to be king <pause dur="short"/> he would've been Edward the eighth <pause dur="short"/> and in fact he was <pause dur="short"/> and he was in love with Wallace Simpson <pause dur="short"/> the American who was divorced <pause dur="short"/> and everyone said she's an old soak <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="785" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="786" who="S0084">he didn't wanna give her up <pause dur="short"/> er but she could never be a queen</u>
<u n="787" who="S0041">I heard a bit about that</u>
<u n="788" who="S0084">cos she was divorced <pause dur="short"/> so he abdicated <pause dur="short"/> er and then there hadn't</u>
<u n="789" who="S0041">for her?</u>
<u n="790" who="S0084">for her <pause dur="short"/> and there hadn't been an abdication in decades <pause dur="short"/> hundreds of years <pause dur="short"/> so he abdicated <pause dur="short"/> and George the sixth</u>
<u n="791" who="S0041">so hang on</u>
<u n="792" who="S0084">took the throne</u>
<u n="793" who="S0041">so there was the Queen Victoria</u>
<u n="794" who="S0084">yep</u>
<u n="795" who="S0041">she had all the kids</u>
<u n="796" who="S0084">she had all the kids</u>
<u n="797" who="S0041">and one</u>
<u n="798" who="S0084">George the fifth</u>
<u n="799" who="S0041">one of those kids</u>
<u n="800" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> second eldest <pause dur="short"/> cos I think the eldest son died <pause dur="short"/> and then but the thing is they're all called Albert and George <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? Like it's impossible</u>
<u n="801" who="S0041">it's not helpful is it</u>
<u n="802" who="S0084">and they're not even their real names <pause dur="short"/> they're their king names <pause dur="short"/> so like</u>
<u n="803" who="S0041">Great</u>
<u n="804" who="S0084">Edward was called</u>
<u n="805" who="S0041">so actually all the kings have king names as well as their real names?</u>
<u n="806" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="807" who="S0041">oh great <pause dur="short"/> so that's helpful</u>
<u n="808" who="S0084">so that's really good <pause dur="short"/> so yeah Edward is <trunc>orig</trunc> it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and George the sixth was the Queen's dad <pause dur="short"/> who was The King's Speech speech issue</u>
<u n="809" who="S0041">so you're going to Victoria <pause dur="short"/> to her child second in line</u>
<u n="810" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="811" who="S0041">to he is Queen's speech's dad</u>
<u n="812" who="S0084">queen's speech's dad <pause dur="short"/> king's Speech's dad <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="813" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="814" who="S0084">so basically</u>
<u n="815" who="S0041">oh it's not a big gap then?</u>
<u n="816" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> cos if you think that was <trunc>twen</trunc> er the the that was twentieth century <pause dur="short"/> cos Victoria died nineteen O one <pause dur="short"/> I think Edward was</u>
<u n="817" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="818" who="S0084">um crowned nineteen thirties <pause dur="short"/> no he was cos it was during the war wasn't it <pause dur="short"/> it happened during the war <pause dur="short"/> second World War <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="819" who="S0041">I only know that one of them was fourteen</u>
<u n="820" who="S0084">or just before</u>
<u n="821" who="S0041">so the first one was fourteen wasn't it? Nineteen fourteen</u>
<u n="822" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="823" who="S0041">that's the only date I know</u>
<u n="824" who="S0084">of the wars?</u>
<u n="825" who="S0041">of all the wars</u>
<u n="826" who="S0084">of all the wars</u>
<u n="827" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> I really don't know anything <pause dur="short"/> do you know? This is how bad my history is</u>
<u n="828" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="829" who="S0041">I was working in a pub in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> the roughest place in the world ever</u>
<u n="830" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="831" who="S0041">full of yokels that would lob pint pots at each other's faces <pause dur="short"/> it was that rough <pause dur="short"/> and they were talking and like it went over my head <pause dur="short"/> that is how bad <pause dur="short"/> yobs</u>
<u n="832" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="833" who="S0041">yobs <pause dur="short"/> old men yobs that will never go anywhere other than <anon type="place"/> ever in their whole lives <pause dur="short"/> and never want to <pause dur="short"/> and most of them don't have jobs</u>
<u n="834" who="S0084">yep</u>
<u n="835" who="S0041">knew more than me <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know what the Gestapo was</u>
<u n="836" who="S0084">you didn't know what the Gestapo was? Right</u>
<u n="837" who="S0041">and I was twenty twenty-one</u>
<u n="838" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="839" who="S0041">how do you miss that in your life? I don't know</u>
<u n="840" who="S0084">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> but but I mean particularly because it's not that long ago <pause dur="short"/> like we've got living relatives</u>
<u n="841" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="842" who="S0084">who would've experienced that</u>
<u n="843" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="844" who="S0084">still so</u>
<u n="845" who="S0041">and I didn't even know that <pause dur="short"/> because my relatives didn't <pause dur="short"/> my my grandma and grandad did <pause dur="short"/> but they both died</u>
<u n="846" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="847" who="S0041">I mean my grandma died when I was like three</u>
<u n="848" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="849" who="S0041">never met my grandad <pause dur="short"/> but on the other side my mum my mum's <trunc>par</trunc> my dad's parents</u>
<u n="850" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="851" who="S0041">he was in the RAF <pause dur="short"/> so they were in Cyprus</u>
<u n="852" who="S0084">oh right <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="853" who="S0041">so all those stories you get fed <pause dur="short"/> I never had any</u>
<u n="854" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="855" who="S0041">I never had any contact with any of it at all <pause dur="short"/> apart from we have a cutting of my grandma</u>
<u n="856" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="857" who="S0041">from the newspaper <pause dur="short"/> cos she was one of the first ten women to cross the Rhine <pause dur="short"/> when the allies broke through into Germany</u>
<u n="858" who="S0084">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> you did say that <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's quite cool</u>
<u n="859" who="S0041">that's the only thing I've ever known <pause dur="short"/> and at the time I didn't really know what the Rhine was <pause dur="short"/> or what the hell they were talking about <pause dur="short"/> or how serious it was</u>
<u n="860" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="861" who="S0041">until <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s grandma last year was telling me stories about the air raids and the bomb shelters and things</u>
<u n="862" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="863" who="S0041">when she came to visit <pause dur="short"/> and I couldn't believe it <pause dur="short"/> I've never had anybody give me that information before</u>
<u n="864" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="865" who="S0041">I was gobsmacked <pause dur="short"/> I didn't think anybody alive now knew that</u>
<u n="866" who="S0084">bloody hell</u>
<u n="867" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I didn't think anybody alive now on the planet would have memories of air raids and going to the bomb shelter <pause dur="short"/> and rationings</u>
<u n="868" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="869" who="S0041">and</u>
<u n="870" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="871" who="S0041">like cos I just I never ever learnt about it <pause dur="short"/> never</u>
<u n="872" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="873" who="S0041">not once <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="874" who="S0084">that's mad</u>
<u n="875" who="S0041">so I didn't have a clue what the frig the Gestapo was</u>
<u n="876" who="S0084">but did did you not do that er cos I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> cos I did history all the way through into university <pause dur="short"/> so I can't remember where I learnt what <pause dur="short"/> but did you not do modern history? So anything from you know nineteen forty-five I think is when they actually class modern history <pause dur="short"/> but anything you know in the nineteen hundreds <pause dur="short"/> did you not do any of that in secondary school? Or not really? I'm trying to find you a list of the monarchs here <pause dur="short"/> I am listening</u>
<u n="877" who="S0041">they um they did it in the second school I went to in year eight</u>
<u n="878" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="879" who="S0041">in the first school I went to they did it in year nine <pause dur="short"/> so I missed that <pause dur="short"/> cos I moved the school <pause dur="short"/> moved into the new school halfway through the year <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> So I missed the first half of the year</u>
<u n="880" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="881" who="S0041">when they were studying this type of thing</u>
<u n="882" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="883" who="S0041">the second half of the year basically I got the shit end of it <pause dur="short"/> of something to do with the fallow field idea of the crops</u>
<u n="884" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="885" who="S0041">and farmers <pause dur="short"/> and what the women did <pause dur="short"/> and making stuff in the factories <pause dur="short"/> that's all I got</u>
<u n="886" who="S0084">right</u>
<u n="887" who="S0041">which you know is no help to anyone <pause dur="short"/> and then for some reason that all that whole idea of all this stuff is moshed in with Oliver Cromwell</u>
<u n="888" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="889" who="S0041">what the frig did he do? Cos all I know now this is how <trunc>w</trunc> bad my history is</u>
<u n="890" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="891" who="S0041"><vocal desc="cough"/> All got moshed together from fallow field crap</u>
<u n="892" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> don't need to worry about that</u>
<u n="893" who="S0041">which is no is not use nor ornament to anybody in the world ever</u>
<u n="894" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="895" who="S0041">to Oliver Cromwell and the person who invented the loom <pause dur="short"/> looms and working the cotton mill</u>
<u n="896" who="S0084">that well all of that is er by the by <pause dur="short"/> like when we did the Peasants' Revolt <pause dur="short"/> it just <trunc>sor</trunc></u>
<u n="897" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="898" who="S0084">I could see a light coming out of the person's window <pause dur="short"/> they've got a flashlight for some reason <pause dur="short"/> that second window that's lit up</u>
<u n="899" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="900" who="S0084">you know so there's that someone like a shadow in the window</u>
<u n="901" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="902" who="S0084">they've got a torch</u>
<u n="903" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> it's the  it's the  light on the roof <pause dur="short"/> but he was stood up so his head blocked it</u>
<u n="904" who="S0084">do you think? Cos he definitely had something in his hand</u>
<u n="905" who="S0041">did he?</u>
<u n="906" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um I got it wrong <pause dur="short"/> after Victoria it was her son Edward the seventh who took over <pause dur="short"/> so that was nineteen O one <pause dur="short"/> then George the fifth <pause dur="short"/> edward the eighth <pause dur="short"/> george the sixth <pause dur="short"/> and now Queenie <pause dur="short"/> our Queenie <pause dur="short"/> which is Windsor <pause dur="short"/> but annoyingly on this you gotta do it in two bits for some reason <pause dur="short"/> like I can't jump back a <trunc>sectio</trunc> it's in sections essentially <pause dur="short"/> jump back a section please <pause dur="short"/> fine <pause dur="short"/> so basically</u>
<u n="907" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> should I grab <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="908" who="S0084">where's Cromwell?</u>
<u n="909" who="S0041">so I don't even know what the hell he did <pause dur="short"/> or where he came into it <pause dur="short"/> don't know who the frig he is</u>
<u n="910" who="S0084">well he sort of led the revolution against the monarchy</u>
<u n="911" who="S0041">for the peasants?</u>
<u n="912" who="S0084">er <pause dur="short"/> well for everyone really <pause dur="short"/> peasants' Revolt <trunc>ca</trunc> was much earlier</u>
<u n="913" who="S0041">um</u>
<u n="914" who="S0084">back a section <pause dur="short"/> come on</u>
<u n="915" who="S0041">when did the cake thing happen? Where the hell's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="916" who="S0084">cake?</u>
<u n="917" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">dunno but I'm bricking it</u>
<u n="918" who="S0041">er <pause dur="short"/> little bit?</u>
<u n="919" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="920" who="S0041">Don't worry though</u>
<u n="921" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">she's on road</u>
<u n="922" who="S0041">Don't worry <pause dur="short"/> you'll be fine</u>
<u n="923" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="924" who="S0041">you'll be fine</u>
<u n="925" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="926" who="S0041"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="927" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="928" who="S0041">so who's the person that met let them eat cake? Was that <trunc>Victor</trunc> was that Elizabeth?</u>
<u n="929" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No <pause dur="short"/> no that's um Marie Antoinette <pause dur="short"/> but she never said it</u>
<u n="930" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> she never said it?</u>
<u n="931" who="S0084">she never said it</u>
<u n="932" who="S0041">so it was a complete lie</u>
<u n="933" who="S0084">it was a complete lie</u>
<u n="934" who="S0041">Good</u>
<u n="935" who="S0084">I mean she was a massive ball bag <pause dur="short"/> er it's the French Revolution as opposed to our revolution</u>
<u n="936" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="937" who="S0084">which I did when I was at college <pause dur="short"/> nothing to do with us</u>
<u n="938" who="S0041">nothing to do with us</u>
<u n="939" who="S0084">not</u>
<u n="940" who="S0041">the <trunc>ki</trunc> the cake was French</u>
<u n="941" who="S0084">it was a French thing <pause dur="short"/> basically her and Louis the sixteenth <pause dur="short"/> he was mental <pause dur="short"/> properly mental <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="942" who="S0041">had had syphilis and stuff?</u>
<u n="943" who="S0084">had syphilis <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="944" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="945" who="S0084">and was a very young king <pause dur="short"/> and so didn't really understand <pause dur="short"/> he had a beautiful wife <pause dur="short"/> marie Antoinette <pause dur="short"/> and wanted to keep her happy <pause dur="short"/> so he she wanted more and more ridiculous things <pause dur="short"/> like she wanted a wig that had a ship in it <pause dur="short"/> and a house in like a <trunc>to</trunc> a dolls' house in the wig <pause dur="short"/> and he bought a he but he all he wanted to do was play on his train set <pause dur="short"/> love him</u>
<u n="946" who="S0041">how old was he?</u>
<u n="947" who="S0084">oh like well for his whole life <pause dur="short"/> but he when he was</u>
<u n="948" who="S0041">oh right <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="949" who="S0084">king he was like fourteen</u>
<u n="950" who="S0041">oh right <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="951" who="S0084">and then he just</u>
<u n="952" who="S0041">it just didn't get any older</u>
<u n="953" who="S0084"><unclear/> he just</u>
<u n="954" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="955" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he just</u>
<u n="956" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just got crazy with the syphilis</u>
<u n="957" who="S0084"><trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> stayed there</u>
<u n="958" who="S0041">and</u>
<u n="959" who="S0084">so as the  as the  people were starving he would do ridiculous things like throw a banquet just for the rich people because then they could say that <trunc>h</trunc> that he was having a lovely time <pause dur="short"/> and he was and they were decadent <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously in those days they thought they were ordained by God <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="960" who="S0041">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="961" who="S0084">it was that their given right to be on the throne <pause dur="short"/> therefore everyone should adore them</u>
<u n="962" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> look at us</u>
<u n="963" who="S0084">people are starving in the streets <pause dur="short"/> and they're having a banquet <pause dur="short"/> so you can imagine why the French had a revolution <pause dur="short"/> and er that's when they invented the guillotine <pause dur="short"/> and they chopped everybody's heads off <pause dur="short"/> louis the sixteenth was quite fat by this stage <pause dur="short"/> one chop of the guillotine wasn't enough</u>
<u n="964" who="S0041">huh <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="965" who="S0084">two chops of the guillotine <pause dur="short"/> like his head was hanging off <pause dur="short"/> this is why I studied the French Revolution at college <pause dur="short"/> it was so gory <pause dur="short"/> it was amazing <pause dur="short"/> there was there's so much good stuff <pause dur="short"/> like every time you learnt something new there was like a threat from here and some guy got stabbed to death in his bath by an old lover who stormed in and <pause dur="short"/> and he  and he  had</u>
<u n="966" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="967" who="S0084">leprosy <pause dur="short"/> and bits of him kept falling off</u>
<u n="968" who="S0041"><event desc="sound of clapping"/></u>
<u n="969" who="S0084">it was so</u>
<u n="970" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> I wish I'd have done this</u>
<u n="971" who="S0084">it was so good <pause dur="short"/> and our our history teacher was so animated <pause dur="short"/> he was like a tiny little man <pause dur="short"/> he was like quite</u>
<u n="972" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="973" who="S0084">a bit like a rat <pause dur="short"/> but quite quite like loveable rat <pause dur="short"/> and he used to he was was just really engaging <pause dur="short"/> he made everything really interesting <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="974" who="S0041">we had the world's boringest history teachers known to man ever</u>
<u n="975" who="S0084">well you see that will do it <pause dur="short"/> that'll kill it <pause dur="short"/> absolutely <pause dur="short"/> but <trunc>hi</trunc></u>
<u n="976" who="S0041">they're just</u>
<u n="977" who="S0084">history itself is really interesting I think <pause dur="short"/> it just you've gotta have a have someone who makes it interesting for you</u>
<u n="978" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="979" who="S0084">I think</u>
<u n="980" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's why I remember the Tudors <pause dur="short"/> cos we had a really animated teacher in year seven <pause dur="short"/> and I still don't remember the order of the wives or anything <pause dur="short"/> but I know more about it than anything else <pause dur="short"/> which considering how little my knowledge is in other areas clearly isn't that much but</u>
<u n="981" who="S0084">well <pause dur="short"/> I think there's a lot of stuff that is just not relevant</u>
<u n="982" who="S0041"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="983" who="S0084">like the Peasants' Revolt in like thirteen twenty</u>
<u n="984" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="985" who="S0084">who the hell gives a fuck <pause dur="short"/> doesn't mean a thing</u>
<u n="986" who="S0041">but when you're a kid you don't know which one's important</u>
<u n="987" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="988" who="S0041">and you just absorb which one you enjoyed being taught the most I suppose</u>
<u n="989" who="S0084">absolutely</u>
<u n="990" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sent me a message back by the way</u>
<u n="991" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="992" who="S0041">he said lol <pause dur="short"/> I got it <pause dur="short"/> oh well <pause dur="short"/> let me know when you see her <pause dur="short"/> and send her my love</u>
<u n="993" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="994" who="S0041">fifteen O five <pause dur="short"/> that's brilliant <pause dur="short"/> well done you <pause dur="short"/> sure <pause dur="short"/> will do <pause dur="short"/> as in let</u>
<u n="995" who="S0084">that's a sure will do let him let you know when he's free?</u>
<u n="996" who="S0041">for a day <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> by the way may I add onto this that I got my little birthday cake um which I was</u>
<u n="997" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="998" who="S0041">gonna take to the hotel</u>
<u n="999" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0041">and put a little candle in <pause dur="short"/> just to be nice</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> and I cos I was working the wedding I forgot it <pause dur="short"/> and left it there</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0041">so in the hotel room whatever and we wake up and have champagne breakfast even though it's the day before his actual birthday <pause dur="short"/> and I was like oh you know um I got you a little birthday cake <pause dur="short"/> but obviously I forgot it <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0041">we'll have it another time <pause dur="short"/> you can come and collect it at some point <pause dur="short"/> or you know we can have cake for tea instead one day <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> he was like yeah okay I I'm a bit busy this week <pause dur="short"/> and he was cos he's been doing exhibitions and stuff in London <pause dur="short"/> blah blah <pause dur="short"/> I was like fine <pause dur="short"/> and he said oh and yeah I'm busy at the weekend <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna see the frigger</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> fatty</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0041">fine <pause dur="short"/> fatty <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> so I was like oh that's okay <pause dur="short"/> just let me know when you're free one one evening or whatever and you can come and collect it and we'll have cake then</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0041">Cos by that time you'll have eaten granny's cake and it'll be cake number two time</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so as far as he's concerned I'm sat on birthday cake and a birthday card <pause dur="short"/> which I am <pause dur="short"/> it's just not in the house <pause dur="short"/> it's at work like but</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's somewhere <pause dur="short"/> it's accessible <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's a weirdo</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0084">this is  this is we  we know this <pause dur="short"/> do you want to learn about the I mean what are they? Are they Viking kings at this point? Wessex <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0041">what the hell's Wessex?</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0084">Wessex? Um <pause dur="short"/> that's when isn't that when the <trunc>sa</trunc> the um</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0084">er what do you call it? The Saxons once they'd yeah Alfred the Great <pause dur="short"/> the list of English monarchs begins with Offa of Mercia <pause dur="short"/> who was dominant in the late eighth century <pause dur="short"/> although his power did not <trunc>exten</trunc> extend to Northumbria <pause dur="short"/> that's when the country was divided and they all had clans <pause dur="short"/> so that's when you have got Wessex and Essex or Northumberland <pause dur="short"/> like all the tribes the Saxon tribes had their own county</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0041">right</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0084">so there there wasn't like a king of a united England <pause dur="short"/> which is why the first one is this Offa</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0041">how long ago is this?</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0084">well this is the eighth century <pause dur="short"/> so this is <trunc>ei</trunc> er</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0041">oh right <pause dur="short"/> so we're going really far back now</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0084">yeah <trunc>th</trunc> yeah no he was er this was nine nine twenty-seven <pause dur="short"/> so over a thousand years ago</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0041">shabs <pause dur="short"/> that's forever ago</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's <trunc>qui</trunc> quite a long time ago <pause dur="short"/> so that was the first king</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0041">aren't Romans near that time?</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0084">romans were before this</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0041">romans were before that?</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> romans were about eight <trunc>hu</trunc> eight hundred years before this</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0041">okay</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0084">so in that time we've had Saxons <pause dur="short"/> vikings <pause dur="short"/> normans <pause dur="short"/> anyone you like really</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0041">saxons <pause dur="short"/> vikings <pause dur="short"/> normans <pause dur="short"/> yep <pause dur="short"/> I really wanted to learn about the Normans</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0084">so the German the French and the Norwegians</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0041">I really wanted to learn about them <pause dur="short"/> something to do with my my friend used to tell me about their burial stuff <pause dur="short"/> and they believed really crazy witch type stuff</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0084">I suppose they all do <pause dur="short"/> well the Vikings used to bury you alive in your ship didn't they</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0041">alive?</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1040" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1041" who="S0041">er</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0084">they thought it</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0041">it's your time to go now</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1045" who="S0041">um just about to have my tea <pause dur="short"/> no no</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> basically</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0041">get yourself in your ship <pause dur="short"/> you're off</u>
<u n="1048" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1049" who="S0084">it's time for you to go now <pause dur="short"/> you've reached the grand old age of twenty-five</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It's your day</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0084">you won't be alive much longer anyway</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Rolling a dice</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0041">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s today</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Enjoy <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="1056" who="S0041">fancy a funeral anybody?</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0084">wilfric <pause dur="short"/> or whatever they were called</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0041">guess who's dead? No one</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Guess who's dead</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Let's kill one</u>
<u n="1061" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1062" who="S0084">it's your time <pause dur="short"/> they were all called Ethel weren't they <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> ethelred <pause dur="short"/> ethelbald</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1064" who="S0084">Ethelwulf</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0041">Ethel is a man?</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0084">Ethel <pause dur="short"/> ethelwulf</u>
<u n="1067" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1068" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0084">Egbert <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1070" who="S0041">humperdinck</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0084">that's er</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0041">nearly</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0084">then Alfred the Great <pause dur="short"/> edward the Elder <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> anyway anyway anyway <pause dur="short"/> so basically this has probably got Cromwell on here <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so after the Tudors</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0084">then you had the Stuarts <pause dur="short"/> which was Elizabeth the first</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> completely missed that</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> so Elizabeth the first was the first Stuart</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0084">but I dunno why <pause dur="short"/> because she never got married <pause dur="short"/> I dunno how she's classed as the first Stuart <pause dur="short"/> but it must be something to do with her line from the Boleyn line <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously she's Anna Boleyn's daughter</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0084">so it must be something to do with where she comes from <pause dur="short"/> as opposed to <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously her dad is Henry the eighth <pause dur="short"/> and he was a Tudor</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0084">so why she's a Stuart I don't know <pause dur="short"/> but at that point after her James the <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="1084" who="S0041">Anne Boleyn's German?</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0084">huh? She's Stuart</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0041">Anne Boleyn</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0084">Anne Boleyn</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0041">oh Berlin <pause dur="short"/> that's where I was going with that</u>
<u n="1089" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1090" who="S0084">she's not German <pause dur="short"/> well I mean er she might be <pause dur="short"/> think I dunno  I dunno  if she's German</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0041">okay <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> I'm with it now <pause dur="short"/> I'm with it</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0084">yep <pause dur="short"/> so then you had all the Jameses <pause dur="short"/> so you had Elizabeth the first <pause dur="short"/> then</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0084">James the first <pause dur="short"/> who came after <pause dur="short"/> who was</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0084">some descendant of Mary <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously Mary at that point had gone mental</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0041">did he not last very long?</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0084">he didn't last very long either <pause dur="short"/> and he <trunc>w</trunc> he tried to unite Scotland as well</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oo yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0084">he was James the sixth of Scotland but James the first of England</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0084">it's all a bit confusing</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0041">is that Robin Hood?</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0084">that's not Robin Hood</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0041">do you think that's?</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> damn it</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0084">that's definitely not Robin Hood <pause dur="short"/> then there was his son <pause dur="short"/> which is Charles the first <pause dur="short"/> now he was the one who was beheaded <pause dur="short"/> he was because he was a complete despot and then he dismissed Parliament <pause dur="short"/> and he just wanted to run the country himself <pause dur="short"/> and so all of you lot can fuck off</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0041">right</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0084">I'm the king <pause dur="short"/> you will do what I say</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0084">and people went</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0041">and everyone said no</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0084">that's very interesting <pause dur="short"/> goodbye <pause dur="short"/> give us your head</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0041">God says this</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so then he went <pause dur="short"/> they chopped his head off <pause dur="short"/> they had a trial that wasn't really a trial <pause dur="short"/> chopped his head off <pause dur="short"/> and buried him <pause dur="short"/> oliver Cromwell became oh I always want to say mother superior <pause dur="short"/> it's not mother superior</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1118" who="S0084">it's something  it's something  like that <pause dur="short"/> he was essentially he he essentially ran the country <pause dur="short"/> and but he was a  he was a  Puritan</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0041">right</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0084">like to the point where I think he used to flagellate self-<trunc>flage</trunc></u>
<u n="1121" who="S0041">puritan?</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0084">um <pause dur="short"/> tut <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> it's a type of Anglican er Christianity <pause dur="short"/> so it's not  it's not  from the Pope <pause dur="short"/> it's not Catholic <pause dur="short"/> it's far more right than than that <pause dur="short"/> like it's really you can't there's certain food that you can't eat <pause dur="short"/> you can't do certain things on the Sabbath day <pause dur="short"/> like it's it's religion to the extreme</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0041">to the extreme</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so he so the people got really annoyed with him <pause dur="short"/> cos they're like you're you're also maybe a bit mental as well <pause dur="short"/> so goodbye to you <pause dur="short"/> and then at the same time Charles the first who had his head beheaded his son was had had to flee when he was a boy <pause dur="short"/> and he'd been hiding out in Scotland</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0041">right</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0084">his son came back <pause dur="short"/> claimed the throne <pause dur="short"/> dug his dad up with his missing <vocal desc="laugh"/> head</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0041">what?</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> had and then had a ceremony for him and then reburied him <pause dur="short"/> and he chopped and he dug up do you know who he dug up? He dug up Oliver Cromwell <pause dur="short"/> chopped his head off when he was dead and put it on a spike um outside the palace <pause dur="short"/> as a fuck you <pause dur="short"/> because that's what they did</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0084">to Charles the first</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0084">all pretty gruesome <pause dur="short"/> then you had um James the second <pause dur="short"/> who was Charles's son <pause dur="short"/> and then it becomes a bit weird <pause dur="short"/> and you get these people from um Holland <pause dur="short"/> william and Mary and Anne and some other degenerates <pause dur="short"/> that's all about the seventeen hundreds</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0041">I don't know anything about those lot</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0084">I don't really know anything about that lot either <pause dur="short"/> how do I? Right so that takes you up to seventeen hundreds <pause dur="short"/> now we need the second list <pause dur="short"/> timeline <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> so at that point then you've got all the Georges <pause dur="short"/> which is the Hanover line <pause dur="short"/> which is this <trunc>ho</trunc> Dutch line <pause dur="short"/> then then the Germans come into it <pause dur="short"/> cos they all start having they they're all <trunc>int</trunc> intermarry</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0041">right</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0084">this is all the bit that I don't really know <pause dur="short"/> so you've got all the Georges <pause dur="short"/> another William <pause dur="short"/> and then it's Victoria <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> Um and then yeah <pause dur="short"/> so she dies nineteen O one <pause dur="short"/> then it's Edward the seventh <pause dur="short"/> for <trunc>qu</trunc> <trunc>qu</trunc> quite a long time according to this <pause dur="short"/> oh maybe about oh no no not a long time <pause dur="short"/> is that ten years then? Oh that's ten years <pause dur="short"/> so in nineteen thirty-nine possibly Edward the eighth er George so what do you think that means then? Like when does George the fifth come in? And when does Edward the eighth? Cos George the fifth is obviously Edward the eighth's dad</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0084">it's weird isn't it <pause dur="short"/> george the fifth must've come in at the end of Edward the eighth's reign er</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0084">seventh's reign</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0084">but not for very long</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> at all <pause dur="short"/> how strange</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0084">he must've died straight away</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0041">shabs</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0084">and then George the sixth served for a long time <pause dur="short"/> oh no he didn't <pause dur="short"/> where's George the sixth gone?</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0041">there</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0084">oh right <pause dur="short"/> so he was from</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0041">he's from nineteen fifty</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> six years then <pause dur="short"/> cos the Queen came in <pause dur="short"/> oh no two years <pause dur="short"/> nineteen fifty-two <pause dur="short"/> cos it's her Diamond Jubilee isn't it <pause dur="short"/> seventy years this year <pause dur="short"/> sixty years this year</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0041">so why's it saying?</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0084">seventy years this year</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0041">this this is lying to us</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0084">Cos I thought he was um crowned in the forties <pause dur="short"/> cos it was during the war <pause dur="short"/> and everyone was kicking off</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0041">I have no frigging idea</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0084">I don't think it was the fifties <pause dur="short"/> I think it was the forties <pause dur="short"/> I think that's wrong</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0041">think they're lying to us?</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0084">it might be the scale <pause dur="short"/> maybe that's why it looks wrong <pause dur="short"/> or we're just reading it wrong <pause dur="short"/> cos basic ah okay <pause dur="short"/> the name is at the end</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0041">name is at the end of the bar</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0084">so George the fifth is the bar above <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0041">got it</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0084">we get it <pause dur="short"/> so that bottom bar is Elizabeth <pause dur="short"/> that bar  that bar  there is George the sixth</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0041">George the sixth</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0084">so it was</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0041">that tiny little line</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0084">looks like nine nineteen thirty-eight maybe nineteen thirty-nine to nineteen fifty-two</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0084">Cos it's isn't it Queenie's is it seventy years?</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0041">I have no idea</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0084">sixty years? Cos it was fifty-two she was crowned <pause dur="short"/> so it must be sixty years mustn't it</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0041">jeebus <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0084">so there you go</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0041"><trunc>Fee</trunc> feel like I've learned</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0084">sort of in one ear and out the other isn't it <pause dur="short"/> cos you just forget <pause dur="short"/> cos they're all called George and William</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1178" who="S0084">how the hell are you supposed to know?</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0041">there's a few Victoria's thrown in</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0084"><trunc>F</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0041">A couple of Annes</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0084">couple of Annes</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0041">and Lizzy <pause dur="short"/> that's it</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0084">it's intense</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0041">my dad just text me <pause dur="short"/> and my phone's so</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0084">uh</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0041">shit I don't know if it sent</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0084">daddy <pause dur="short"/> daddy Cool <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1189" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>d</trunc> I just don't know dad <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> I just don't know <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> I really want chocolate now</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0084">get Horlicks</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0041">all the chocolate</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0084">that was really nice <pause dur="short"/> thank you</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's good isn't it <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> just before bed</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0041">I <trunc>d</trunc> I was so busy learning I didn't even get to spy her <pause dur="short"/> tut oh</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0041">my perfect shot as well</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0084">yeah you ninny</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0041">oh huh</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0084">should go and borrow a</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0041">back brush?</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0084">back <trunc>br</trunc> oh</u>
<u n="1203" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1204" who="S0084">huh <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="1205" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1206" who="S0084">oh you're a <unclear/> person</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Did you enjoy that? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1208" who="S0084">oh no</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1210" who="S0084">now I've got mental images of her upstairs now</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1212" who="S0084">plaiting it</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh my God</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0084">oh urgh</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0041">that's sick</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0084">man alive <pause dur="short"/> you're wrong in the head</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1218" who="S0084">urgh</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> I need to get rid of this <pause dur="short"/> I've got such an itchy nose</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0084">um <pause dur="short"/> does that mean someone's talking about you? Or you're <trunc>te</trunc> telling lies?</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0041">I'm gonna get angry</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0084">you're gonna get angry</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0084">because your nose is really itchy</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0041">well that's what I always say <pause dur="short"/> course I'm gonna get angry <pause dur="short"/> my frigging nose is itchy</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ridiculous behaviour</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0041">feel a bit coldy</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I do <pause dur="short"/> I think cos I just er couldn't get warm today <pause dur="short"/> baltic isn't it</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1230" who="S0084">like even though they said it was three degrees <pause dur="short"/> it feels like it's much colder <pause dur="short"/> it might've been the wind</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0041">three degrees?</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but considering it was twelve over the weekend <pause dur="short"/> like it is that means that it is a lot colder</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0041">uh</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0041">I feel a bit like snotted up</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0084">aw <pause dur="short"/> the death <pause dur="short"/> not the death man</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0041">not the death</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0041">uh</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0084">I wonder if I can get out of dinner with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> cos she didn't come to my dinner did she <pause dur="short"/> that's a good point <pause dur="short"/> some something about the bus or something</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> I think you can pretty much get away with it <pause dur="short"/> can't you just join her for cocktails later?</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0084">well that's what I'm thinking <pause dur="short"/> week before pay day</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0041">oo yeah</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0084">I'll check the old bank balance again tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1245" who="S0041"><vocal desc="whistle"/> Oh the that funny thing happened again again today <pause dur="short"/> so I go in the gym <pause dur="short"/> there's two blokes in there</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> one of them's got a a frigging hot bod</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0084">really?</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0041">er <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> really hot bod <pause dur="short"/> but he must've been about thirty-five but his face wasn't as hot as his bod</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0041">it it was hot enough</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0041">it was  it was  doable</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0041">but he was like he was foreign <pause dur="short"/> so I think they were Flemish <pause dur="short"/> I could <trunc>te</trunc> I could hear their accent</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0084">oh right</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> it they were  they were  either Dutch or Flemish <pause dur="short"/> cos it wasn't German but it wasn't French</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> and they were chattering away <pause dur="short"/> and as I walked in he was you know trying to catch my eye</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0041">and he's doing all these silly stretches and he's doing his ab ab bit on the floor <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0041">grr <pause dur="short"/> and I was just sat there laughing to myself <pause dur="short"/> thinking right any minute  any minute  now when I start getting sweaty and red</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1265" who="S0041"><unclear/> that</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1267" who="S0041">and then I got on the treadmill and I don't know what they were saying <pause dur="short"/> but they were talking between them and then the older guy <unclear/> about forty odd got on the treadmill next to me <pause dur="short"/> and I saw him looking at what I was doing</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0041">and telling the other guy</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0084">ah</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> and then putting his treadmill to match mine</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0041">which was a bit weird</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0084">were you going quite fast?</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> and he kept up for a little while</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0041">and then he slowed down a bit <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> and then he kept up again <pause dur="short"/> and then at the end when I sprinted it he didn't keep up <pause dur="short"/> but he carried on like but he stayed on the treadmill for longer when I got off</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it was really funny <pause dur="short"/> cos you could see like once I got off <pause dur="short"/> cos I get a bit excited if I win  if I win  the <vocal desc="laugh"/> treadmill</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0084">win <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1283" who="S0041">I get really excited <pause dur="short"/> I'm like yes <pause dur="short"/> hah <pause dur="short"/> take that treadmill</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0084">nice</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0041">and because I can barely breath at the time obviously saying that virtually wipes me out</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1287" who="S0041">um</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0084">that's a nice feeling though</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0084">especially if you're looking at them and you would consider them to be quite fit</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> but apparently if you run outside it builds your fitness up really quickly</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0084">oh really?</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0084">it's more difficult <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos it's a rough different terrain isn't it</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0041"><unclear/> get on it</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0041">what I need to do is put <trunc>m</trunc> some tunage on the iPod</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0041">that will help</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0084">something that actually motivates you</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0041"><unclear/> that cack <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> pretends to call music</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Is it really bad?</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> actual cack</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> gromit</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0041">I notice from his message that he wasn't kind of I maybe will have some time free at some point <pause dur="short"/> he's just like yeah I'll let you know</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cheers Jord</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0084">you bell-end</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0041">you're fucking fantastic you are</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0084">oh my God <pause dur="short"/> right today it was four degrees <pause dur="short"/> feels like minus one <pause dur="short"/> I was gonna say er there's no way that it feels like four degrees out there <pause dur="short"/> that's intense isn't it <pause dur="short"/> that</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0041">what does it say for tomorrow?</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0084">that's cos of the wind <pause dur="short"/> seven degrees <pause dur="short"/> feels like six <pause dur="short"/> it's not gonna be too bad</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0041">oh I can get on board a bit more with that <unclear/></u>
<u n="1314" who="S0084">but that's sorry love</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0041">I was just gonna say I did nearly die of face ache on the way to work this morning it was that cold</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0084">it's just my lungs <pause dur="short"/> it's such a worry <pause dur="short"/> like just cos I had bronchitis as a kid and I think you know it's so dangerous when you've had the flu that I don't really wanna go out in it really <pause dur="short"/> so um but Wednesday it's gonna rain <pause dur="short"/> so tomorrow's fucking rain <pause dur="short"/> tomorrow's gonna be</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0041">basically get the cycling out of the way tomorrow even if you freeze <pause dur="short"/> cos you're not cycling on Wednesday</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> though you are definitely not not according to this <pause dur="short"/> heavy rain shower <pause dur="short"/> but Thursday sunny intervals <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not gonna get above six degrees for the rest of the week</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0041">oh fantastic</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0084">but at least that's better than bloody minus one</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh um not helping at all with the lack of pay but um Azendi in town</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0084">oo</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0041">has got a massive fifty percent sale on</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0084">ff <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0041">it's closing down <pause dur="short"/> and the jewellery's really cheap</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0084">is it?</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> um <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and er tut Jane at work have been going in every lunchtime and coming out with bits <pause dur="short"/> because it's so cheap</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0084">oh my God</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0041">it's actually properly fifty percent off everything <pause dur="short"/> the shop's shutting down <pause dur="short"/> and I don't know why they can't transfer the stock</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0041">but apparently they can't <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0084">well</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0041">everything's gotta go</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0041">so I'm gonna pop in and see if there's anything that Kate would like</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0041">seeing as I missed her birthday last month <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0084">oh no</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0084">sounds a bit dangerous <pause dur="short"/> but awesome <pause dur="short"/> at the same time</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I figure if it's not buying for me then it's allowed</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's definitely true</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0041">but um I told you about the the mess up with the the girl and the bedrooms and the wedding didn't I</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0084">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0041">and how I thought <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> couldn't do anything and then Chris did it</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0041">well today <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> found the reservations in the system</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0084">oh really?</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0084">and what did he say? Did he kick off?</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0041">he said what's this? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> proper kicked off <pause dur="short"/> um cos apparently Chris has got them <unclear/> and stuff based on <unclear/> selling things</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0041">he's put them under different rate codes and stuff <pause dur="short"/> and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gets in trouble for the bookings being incorrect or I don't really get it <pause dur="short"/> but anyway he was like you know I'm really pissed off about this <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> it's like I said something and you both just <unclear/> no that's not acceptable as an answer and just went behind my back <pause dur="short"/> I felt like saying yeah I did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0041">for the sake of your revenue that you're harping on at</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0041">for a hundred quid</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0041">you would've given you would've ruined the woman's best day of life</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0084">absolutely</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0041">get it into perspective</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0084">and from a business perspective lost four grand</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0084">do you know what I mean? If she'd walked away <pause dur="short"/> if she'd absolute cos er she was on the edge</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0084">she was frazzled <pause dur="short"/> if she'd kicked off surely Robin would've just said right fine well</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0084">you know as we can't keep this booking</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0041">and also <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sneeze"/></u>
<u n="1370" who="S0084">bless you</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0041"><vocal desc="sneeze"/></u>
<u n="1372" who="S0084">bless you</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> didn't take into consideration that muggins here is gonna be there on her wedding day</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0041">and should one tiny little thing go wrong</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0041">it's gonna be me that gets it in the neck <pause dur="short"/> and there's gonna be tears and tantrums and stamping and</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0084">absolutely</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0041">God knows what for the sake of what? A hundred quid</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's nothing <pause dur="short"/> and it's er I mean if you'd actually er if Robin had er had to be brought into it he would've agreed with you <pause dur="short"/> surely</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0041">he would <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so basically I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got the gist of the story <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously she wasn't there <pause dur="short"/> but um <vocal desc="cough"/> you know he started kicking off <pause dur="short"/> and I just said look <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that's not obviously that's not what I intended but I think</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0041">the best thing in this situation for you to do is talk to <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="1384" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0041">he overheard me talking and basically saved my bacon <pause dur="short"/> and you know if it's stepping on toes then I don't know what to say other than speak to him <pause dur="short"/> it will all they're all in wrong <pause dur="short"/> I said well to be honest I don't know how to correct them <pause dur="short"/> or if they are in wrong <pause dur="short"/> cos I haven't got a clue <pause dur="short"/> you know it's not something that's part of my job <pause dur="short"/> and if <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> has put something in wrong that pisses you off I suggest you talk to him</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0041">and he was like but you know I came back from my lunch and you could've even told me <pause dur="short"/> you couldn't have even said to me that oh by the way we've sorted it and we've done this</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0041">I thought no I couldn't cos er you would've if if you wanted to do that</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0041">or if you had any intention of it you could've done it before then when I asked you in the first place</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> bell-end</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0041">so er I mean in the end Eve actually had to say <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I think you should kind of bring extract yourself from this conversation now <pause dur="short"/> even in front of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> cos I think you're not gonna get anywhere <pause dur="short"/> you know it's best if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just take it with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> and I just thought oh my God <pause dur="short"/> for the sake of a hundred quid</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0084">oh it's just massive egos isn't it <pause dur="short"/> essentially that's all it is <pause dur="short"/> his ego's</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0084">been bruised</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0084">he wants to think that he's running the show</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0084">and at the end of the day and he probably he he knows he's been caught out <pause dur="short"/> he knows that you know that he could've given you a better deal</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0084">he could've actually been a bit more helpful other than <unclear/> can do</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0041">well seeing how extreme that situation was</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0041">and he didn't do anything about it</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0084">in any business you've gotta make a call haven't you <pause dur="short"/> like a huh a <trunc>l</trunc> a less extreme version a less extreme example when I worked at Waterstones for example <pause dur="short"/> it'd be our policy not to do any returns outside of the twenty-eight day um exchange period or <pause dur="short"/> someone came in and were really kicking off <pause dur="short"/> just for the sake of what? A few quid? You'd just be like right fine <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> whatever <pause dur="short"/> do whatever you want <pause dur="short"/> of course we'll do you an exchange <pause dur="short"/> you think cos you wanna keep your customers happy <pause dur="short"/> you <trunc>wa</trunc> you know you particularly something like a wedding <pause dur="short"/> and they're spending</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0084">so much money <pause dur="short"/> and he's just think what is the matter with you? Like why are you so tight about this?</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it's like he's it's coming out of his own pocket</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's er <trunc>co</trunc> it's just like he's he's read the rule book and he's taking it literally</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0084">like there's no sort of grey area with him</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0041">but he bends it for he bends it <pause dur="short"/> all the time <pause dur="short"/> just not on this occasion <pause dur="short"/> like there's been times when basically we take a group booking it's contracted <pause dur="short"/> they're liable for bedrooms even if they don't take them</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0041">which with us on conference he's really strict with <pause dur="short"/> but I overheard him to Sarah earlier today</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0041">and she had a group booking the twenty rooms and they took one</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0041">and they didn't charge cos they're a corporate client that they didn't wanna piss off <pause dur="short"/> and I was like well er wedding woman that I don't wanna piss off cos I don't fancy getting that in the face next week thanks</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely <pause dur="short"/> so is it just that he's not being helpful towards you do you think? Is it personal?</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0041">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> it wouldn't surprise me <pause dur="short"/> after all the other things that have gone on</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0041">but God knows <pause dur="short"/> but basically <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> had said as he did it <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> knew that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was being a knob</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0041">and Simon and I both knew <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was being a knob <pause dur="short"/> which is why we both kind of just kept it quiet and just said agreed for <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> to do it <pause dur="short"/> I knew when he was doing it it was wrong</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0041">um but he said basically <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is very strict on what bedroom rates he offers <pause dur="short"/> however there's a new kind of scheme coming into play <unclear/> next week which is being trialed <pause dur="short"/> which basically will take that power away from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1428" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0041">on conference bookings <pause dur="short"/> so they'll they'll give us a framework which basically says if the total booking is worth say one grand two grand three grand four grand then the the minimum acceptable bedroom rate is <trunc>l</trunc> like lower and lower as the price of the booking gets higher</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0041">which makes sense</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely <unclear/> deal</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0041">and obviously for a four grand booking</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the difference between a one six four rate and a one thirty rate is thirty-four pounds</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0041">it's not gonna break the bank</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0041">you know <pause dur="short"/> we charge them sixteen pound for breakfast and it doesn't cost us that <pause dur="short"/> so really twenty quid a booking <pause dur="short"/> four grand</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0041">three bedrooms <pause dur="short"/> it's <trunc>n</trunc> it's a no-brainer <pause dur="short"/> plus the F and B spend that they're gonna spend on foods and drinks and everything else while they're here <pause dur="short"/> it's just it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0084">you charge sixteen pounds for breakfast?</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0041">sixteen pound fifty</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0084">I would literally go in there with my handbag</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0084">just like that</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1448" who="S0084">I'd presume they were charging for the day</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0084">all my food <pause dur="short"/> this is for everything</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0084">stand there making sandwiches for the day</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'd do it</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0084">wow</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> sixteen pound fifty</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0084">I bet it's nice though <pause dur="short"/> is it nice?</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's really good</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0041">really good <pause dur="short"/> and you can even if you want to choose you can <trunc>ma</trunc> choose your own omelette and tell the chef <pause dur="short"/> er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has this big hot plate and he'll put like smoked salmon or whatever in it</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0041">whatever you want <pause dur="short"/> or he'll make you crepes <pause dur="short"/> or</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0084">yum</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0041">and then full English <pause dur="short"/> full continental <pause dur="short"/> fresh fruit <pause dur="short"/> yoghurts <pause dur="short"/> there's literally everything you could possibly want</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that sounds lovely <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> tut <pause dur="short"/> when how did we leave things about the hotel in Belfast? Did we leave it that you were gonna <trunc>e</trunc> e-mail somebody? Or did we book it?</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0041">we can just book it</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0084">did we</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0041">we haven't booked it</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0084">we didn't book it did we?</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0041">we can book it though <pause dur="short"/> the rate won't change</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0084">it won't change?</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0084">okay <pause dur="short"/> well we can just book it whenever then</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0084">can't we <pause dur="short"/> just need to <unclear/> those rooms</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0041">I was gonna book it on pay day <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0084">oh then yeah let's do that <unclear/></u>
<u n="1477" who="S0041">they um they won't sell out between now and</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0084">May</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0041">now and pay day <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0084">okay</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0041">well I was gonna say between now and like the first of April</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0084">is that when you get paid? What month are we in?</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0041">get paid on the twenty-eighth <pause dur="short"/> march</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that sounds perfect</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0084">that sounds perfect <pause dur="short"/>  on pay day</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what's happening with my bike</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0041">you not heard anything back yet?</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> they're ordering the parts <pause dur="short"/> they said they were gonna arrive today or tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> so I suppose it will be tomorrow or Wednesday that I can collect it <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="sound of snoring"/></u>
<u n="1491" who="S0041">urgh</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0084">it's just such bad timing <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> said we'd do the Salon Rouge night out</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0041">oh yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0084">and but that's next weekend so that's the day before pay day <pause dur="short"/> cos we get paid on the Monday</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0084">it's a Saturday <pause dur="short"/> and I don't huh in our I like her but I don't like all of the people that we used to work with <pause dur="short"/> and I've seen them all quite recently <pause dur="short"/> whereas <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hasn't seen them for years <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously she's only just moved back <pause dur="short"/> so um um comparatively <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> so part of me's like</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0084">maybe I'll just jack that in <pause dur="short"/> but it's it's one of those things you think could be really fun</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0084">like get dressed up in your pantaloons and dance about <pause dur="short"/> so I'll take a view on it next week</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0084">I think</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0084">and see</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0041">that's sounds wise</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0084"><unclear/> what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s gonna wear</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0041">frigging <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's turned into a bitch at work has booked in her thirtieth at work in September</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0084">her thirtieth?</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0041">party <pause dur="short"/> she's gonna have it in the hotel</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0084">is that cos she gets <trunc>dis</trunc> a really good discount? <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="1511" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> probably</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0084">fine <pause dur="short"/> cos you wouldn't choose</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0084">to have it where you work surely? No</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0084">must get a good discount</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0041">but she's got a twin sister <pause dur="short"/> so I think they wanted to do a big bash</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0041">and as far as hiring a place out goes they're gonna get that for next to nothing</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0084"><vocal desc="yawn"/> Was she <unclear/> expecting to be there in September then?</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0041">oh no <pause dur="short"/> I didn't get an invite</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> her <pause dur="short"/> she's expecting to be there?</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0041">ah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> she will <pause dur="short"/> she won't go anywhere <pause dur="short"/> she's er quite chuffed</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0084">oh so she's onto a bit of a winner now isn't she <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0084">Will be quite a good salary for doing very little</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> from the sounds of things</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0041">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> Uh</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> is it My Big Fat Gypsy Wedding tonight?</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0041">oh is it?</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0084">when did we book the flights? Did we book them on a Tuesday? Wasn't it <trunc>la</trunc> oh no <trunc>w</trunc> no it's only fucking Monday today</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0041">oh is it? Oh</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0084">bollocks</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0084">I thought it was Tuesday <pause dur="short"/> just for a moment there</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0041">damn it</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0041">so is is <trunc>Esse</trunc> made in Essex on today then? When's that on?</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0084">Wednesday</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0041">oh <pause dur="short"/> so there's nothing on today?</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0084">Don't know <pause dur="short"/> eastenders <pause dur="short"/> missed that</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0041">uh</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0084">going to have a look <pause dur="short"/> bedfordshire o'clock</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0041">I I feel like it's about eleven o'clock at night you know</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0041">that's it bloody <vocal desc="yawn"/> getting up early this morning <pause dur="short"/> and then my hair feels awful <pause dur="short"/> and I was gonna get in and lather it in conditioner that I could rinse out in the morning <pause dur="short"/> but I just</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0084">oh</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0041">can't be bothered</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0084"><vocal desc="yawn"/> Sounds fine</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0041">can't actually be arsed</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> I should have a shower now but I probably just have one in the morning instead</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0041">you see I'm really bad if I leave it till the morning I'll literally get up</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0084">mhm</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0041">and then not get in the shower <pause dur="short"/> like as in I'll wake up to get in the shower</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0041">and then I'll get up and I won't actually make it to the shower</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's really difficult</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0041">I'm so so bad <pause dur="short"/> I'd rather have the extra twenty minutes in bed</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0084">I know <pause dur="short"/> cos that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> cos you've gotta set your alarm extra early</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> and I just snooze and snooze  and snooze  snooze snooze snooze <pause dur="short"/> and I think shit actually <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos I'm really er crap at working out times</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0041">like actually <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you've fucked it now <pause dur="short"/> get your clothes and you're out</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> bus</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0084">bus bus</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0041">so I'll have to get in the night before <pause dur="short"/> I mean luckily I didn't know people sweated in their sleep until recently</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0084"><vocal desc="yawn"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1569" who="S0041">didn't know that you know</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0084">I remember you saying <pause dur="short"/> somewhere</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0041">I still don't really understand it <pause dur="short"/> if I'm honest</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0084">um</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0041">um</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0084">I dunno whether it's just naturally your body raises its temperature <pause dur="short"/> or <trunc>w</trunc> or whether it's because you're wriggling around <pause dur="short"/> or or what it is <pause dur="short"/> cos when you're um</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0041">I'm freezing all night long <pause dur="short"/> if I  if I</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0084">no I'm I'm a radiator</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0041">accidentally like turn over or hit my head or something or you know</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0041">just <trunc>tr</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> stir in the night and wake up I'm freezing</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> god no once I'm asleep I'm an absolute radiator</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0084">kick the covers off <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh and I always wake up in a tangle of bedding cos I'm a <trunc>s</trunc> such a wriggler <pause dur="short"/> and I'm always in a completely different position unless I'm sleeping in a hovel with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="1583" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0084">take note</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0084">um <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I always  I always  get really hot in the night <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0041">just don't get it <pause dur="short"/> in fact I woke up about two weekends ago two or three weekends ago really hot <pause dur="short"/> but I'd been out the night before and the radiator was on full blast <pause dur="short"/> and it was</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0084">ah <pause dur="short"/> that'll do it <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0041">about six about seven or eight o'clock <pause dur="short"/> got up</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0041">woke up <pause dur="short"/> turned it down <pause dur="short"/> slept again till <trunc>t</trunc> one <pause dur="short"/> till one</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0084">Cos have you had those days where you're you're really hungover and you start your period? That is an absolute killer <pause dur="short"/> cos you feel like you wanna kill yourself <pause dur="short"/> cos er when you're you start your period your body is raises the temperature</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0084">by one degree <pause dur="short"/> and when you're hungover your body is raised temperature</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0041">still don't notice it that bad</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0084">oh it's so so so bad <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> just a pain</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I still don't notice it that bad <pause dur="short"/> actually that's a lie <pause dur="short"/> when I was in the hotel <pause dur="short"/> which was er sod's law</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0041">for some reason my <trunc>d</trunc> period decided to wanted to be a week late</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0041">thanks</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> I was <trunc>ho</trunc> really hot in the hotel hotel room and Jord wasn't <pause dur="short"/> so that's probably it <pause dur="short"/> but I still not I still wasn't hot enough to sweat</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's a bit weird</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0084">when I was reading the reviews of the place that I've booked in Brighton <pause dur="short"/> they were saying oh the rooms are too hot <pause dur="short"/> we had to crack the window open <pause dur="short"/> I was like oh I would just love that</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1610" who="S0084">just like cook myself in the night</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0041">Cook me  cook me  with fresh air blowing</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'd never complain about that</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I can't believe how cheap you found it</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0084">well yeah it's probably gonna be a like a total bedsit</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0084"><vocal desc="yawn"/> But it's fine <pause dur="short"/> I'm literally gonna put</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0041">place to put your head for the night isn't it</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0084">just gonna put my head down <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0041">definitely</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0084">not a problem <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I'll see some friends on the Sunday morning <pause dur="short"/> and we check out about eleven I think</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0041">nice</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0084">it's fine <pause dur="short"/> they don't do breakfast <pause dur="short"/> but that's not a problem <pause dur="short"/> cos you eat so much and you drink so much at a wedding don't you</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0084">you know <pause dur="short"/> like full the next day</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0041">I er did I tell you I put my holiday in?</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0084">for the wedding?</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> good <pause dur="short"/> no you didn't tell me that</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0041">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like oh well you should put that in before you booked the flight you know <pause dur="short"/> and I was like well yeah I know but to be honest I'd already checked to see if no one had got the dates <pause dur="short"/> so I already knew <pause dur="short"/> and even if you'd have said no cos there was a reason that I couldn't take it <pause dur="short"/> for <trunc>ha</trunc> the amount the flights were we just booked it round then</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely <pause dur="short"/> yeah we did get quite a bargain</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0084">I still haven't tut um spoken to Coleen about laying the groundwork for the fact that we're not staying at the hotel</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0084">but I think she'll understand to be honest <pause dur="short"/> I think she'll be absolutely fine <pause dur="short"/> because we can't afford seventy pound hotel rooms when you can get a nine pound hotel room</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's no comparison is there</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0084">not in a month where everyone's getting married</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> all the world <pause dur="short"/> all the marriages</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0084">all the marriages <pause dur="short"/> all the birthdays in March <pause dur="short"/> all the weddings in April</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0041">huh</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0084">and then just generally loathing life</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0084">in May <pause dur="short"/> and June</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0041">and June <pause dur="short"/> that's why I was thinking I'd rather wait a bit for my birthday actually</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0041">and like do it when it's nice and hot in July or something daft <pause dur="short"/> but then I thought the other problem is that it's a university town <pause dur="short"/> all the students'll go</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0084">students will go where?</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0041">from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1648" who="S0084">oh right <pause dur="short"/> so you think</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0041">go home</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0084">it'll be empty?</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0084">I think it's quite um there's quite a few town townfolk who often go there as well</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0041">it's</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0084">depends where you wanna go <pause dur="short"/> I think my I was talking to my colleague today <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and er her fella's from <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and she was saying like the nightlife there's really really good</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0084">it's quite quite a lot of sort of trendy bars and alternatives</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> rung me yesterday actually <pause dur="short"/> and I missed it <pause dur="short"/> and I text her saying can't believe I missed your call <pause dur="short"/> really wanna talk to you</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0084"><vocal desc="yawn"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0041">um <pause dur="short"/> but so I'll ask her <pause dur="short"/> see what she thinks <pause dur="short"/> cos I'd prefer to leave it till yeah probably beginning of July really</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0084">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean we could obviously do something small</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0041">kind of break up time time away</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0041">Cos if we're going in what? Mid mid-May</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0084">to er <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0041">be nice to maybe wait till like mid end June <pause dur="short"/> maybe pay day in June</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0041">would be a nice time</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0084">spread it out <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0041">Cos it's a nice</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0041">like a nice gap <pause dur="short"/> whereas if we go out the last week in April <pause dur="short"/> which is my birthday</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0041">then it's only a couple of <trunc>weeke</trunc> weekends till <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1676" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0041">and it'll I'd rather something that I'm looking forward to like <anon type="place"/> be on its own <pause dur="short"/> and something I look forward to like birthday be on its own</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0041">Cos you see the other thing then is it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday on the twentieth of June</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0084">oh perfect <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0041">so could go and see her for my birthday</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0041">as well <pause dur="short"/> so do a joint thing <pause dur="short"/> I just need to talk to her I suppose</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0084">just pick up <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and call her <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="1685" who="S0041">find out what the haps is</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0084"><vocal desc="yawn"/> Hip hop happening</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0041"><vocal desc="yawn"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0084">oh that sounds like a a pretty good idea <pause dur="short"/> cos May's gonna be a bit of a right-off because of the weddings and</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0084">I've got this I've got a book course um training course in London twenty-fourth and twenty-fifth of May <pause dur="short"/> which is quite cool <pause dur="short"/> I'm quite looking forward to that</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0084">so that's the end of May <pause dur="short"/> and then you know it's the Diamond Jubilee isn't it on so they've you know normally have</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0084">two bank holidays in May <pause dur="short"/> so the May second May bank holiday's now June</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0084">so I think it said the fourth and fifth <pause dur="short"/> bank holiday <pause dur="short"/> so I've taken the rest of that week off</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0084">so you get</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0041">I think I did that</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0041">I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> I need to work it out <pause dur="short"/> but I think I did that</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0084">so I always we always joke in the office that you can get like three <trunc>f</trunc> like eleven for the price of three <pause dur="short"/> so you get like eleven days off but only use three days holiday <pause dur="short"/> so I've got that week <pause dur="short"/> but I haven't booked anything else after that until December <pause dur="short"/> cos I've booked that week off before Christmas</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0084">so that I can just chill out <pause dur="short"/> and then I finish my <unclear/></u>
<u n="1705" who="S0041">do me a favour actually <pause dur="short"/> when you get to work have a look at those three dates for the you know three days for the seven</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0041">and text me up so I can make sure I've booked the right ones</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0041">I think I <trunc>th</trunc> I think I did do it <pause dur="short"/> I'm so rubbish at remembering <pause dur="short"/> so rubbish <pause dur="short"/> cos remember I did the same last year when they got married</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0084">yeah</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0041">that was a cushy deal wasn't it</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0084">that was pretty sweet <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I didn't do it <pause dur="short"/> because everybody else got there first</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0041">uh</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0084">and somebody has to stay in the office <pause dur="short"/> but it was brilliant because everybody was out <pause dur="short"/> so even if you had to work there was no work</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0041">nice <pause dur="short"/> like it</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0084">like a lot of our suppliers already are saying like oh that piece of work falls during the Olympics <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> well we can't really guarantee any dates over the Olympics <pause dur="short"/> and I was like er so what you're saying is the office is gonna <trunc>clo</trunc> like this audio recording studio is gonna close for two weeks at the Olympics <pause dur="short"/> um I don't remember reading that there are any bank holidays in that time <pause dur="short"/> I E you should be fucking working</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0084">and he said oh no there's no bank holidays <pause dur="short"/> but you know it happens once in a lifetime and I can't guarantee that I can get people to work <pause dur="short"/> and blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> and I was like well if you want the work</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0041">then you'd better guarantee that people are working</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0084">then you'd <trunc>bette</trunc> better sort it because I need this by this date <pause dur="short"/> and that means you working over those two weeks <pause dur="short"/> and he was like yeah I'm sure we'll be fine</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0084">see it's really unprofessional to say to your  to your  client</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0041">boss</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0084">yeah um</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0041">which is what it is <pause dur="short"/> because</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we're his client</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0041">you're paying him</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> for him to say to us oh I dunno if I can work in those two weeks</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0084">bye</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0041">cheers</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> bye bye now</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0041">see you later then <pause dur="short"/> bye <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> nice <pause dur="short"/> nice guy</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> nice <pause dur="short"/> I have to go and put my head on a pillow</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm gonna do that too</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0084"><vocal desc="misc"/> It's very quiet upstairs <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> shagalagging</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0041">if I hear any shagalagging there's gonna be issues</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0084">shoes on the ceiling</u>
<u n="1739" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1740" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> some shoes on the ceiling <pause dur="short"/> maybe that's what those marks are on my ceiling</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0084">probs</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0041">why did we not think of this?</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0084">whoever was in there before</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0041">automatically</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0084">then you would wouldn't you <pause dur="short"/> if you heard <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> shagging <pause dur="short"/> as you know all too well</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0041">yep yep <pause dur="short"/> bad bad</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0084">I wonder what they're doing now <pause dur="short"/> not those two</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0084">um we can well imagine what they're doing <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1750" who="S0041">God knows <pause dur="short"/> did <trunc>c</trunc> did you hear <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> saying that she text him?</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0084">no</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0041">she text him the other day <pause dur="short"/> maybe yesterday or the day before</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0084">mm <pause dur="short"/> just checking in? Or?</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0041">no I think she said are you do you still smoke?</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="1756" who="S0041">and I don't know if she was gonna pop round and have a cigarette with him</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0084">that's a bit of a weird question</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0084">maybe it's the her her way of opening up communication channels</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>h</trunc> and he didn't reply</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0084">what?</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was like what do you mean? He said well she's burnt her bridges with me her br br <pause dur="short"/> and I was like you're gonna regret that</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0084">yeah <pause dur="short"/> absolutely <pause dur="short"/> oh she's my sister <pause dur="short"/> oh really?</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0084">what the hell? Why won't you reply? That's obviously her coming and trying isn't it <pause dur="short"/> like trying to make amends</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> I just thought I'm not wasting my breath</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> well we tried</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0084">and I was getting really angry that night after he'd been drinking <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0084">he was saying ridiculous things <pause dur="short"/> like er oh I love her like a sister <pause dur="short"/> I love her unconditionally <pause dur="short"/> but she's dead to me</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0041">but yeah</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0084"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1774" who="S0041">I'd stamp on her face if I saw her</u>
<u n="1775" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1776" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> very weird</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0084">oh <pause dur="short"/> she's probably really lonely</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I bet she is</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0084">she hasn't got anybody <pause dur="short"/> cos even when she was here and she was hating us at least that's like some sort of emotion</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1781" who="S0084">she's not got anything <pause dur="short"/> she's only got him</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> She can't even have anyone to hate</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0084">no <pause dur="short"/> she's not got anything <pause dur="short"/> she's well apart from him <pause dur="short"/> she probably hates him <pause dur="short"/> cos er</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0084">he's a massive peni</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0041">if she doesn't hate him by now then she's got issues</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0084">I think she probably does hate him</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0041">do you think she's still engaged to him?</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0084"><vocal desc="yawn"/> Oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos she's a bit silly <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>thi</trunc> well <trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> she probably feels a bit isolated doesn't she <pause dur="short"/> if her family have walked away <pause dur="short"/> and the few friends that she</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1791" who="S0084">had have walked away <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna fall asleep standing up if I don't go to bed</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0084">mm</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1795" who="S0084">Monday's just <trunc>to</trunc></u>
</body>
</text>
