<text id="SK7X">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:15:17</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0024 S0144</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's parents' house, Norfolk</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Cooking, kids, Walmart, oil</topics>
		<activity>Couple chat and cook.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T20</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0024">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>28</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0144">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Norwich, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0024">erm yes three onions cos we're trying to cook enough for tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> we're gonna cook a massive <pause dur="short"/> is that enough carrots for a massive one? <unclear/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0144" trans="overlap">alright well I can I get rid of these onions because I've run out of space?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0024">well no I'm not ready</u>
<u n="4" who="S0144">well can I put them on this one then?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0024">you've got a tiny board <pause dur="short"/> it's tiny</u>
<u n="6" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> well I thought that was the one you gave me</u>
<u n="7" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="8" who="S0144">that was</u>
<u n="9" who="S0024">oh <pause dur="short"/> I didn't really give you one <pause dur="short"/> that was like left there from <pause dur="short"/> wasn't tidied away from last time</u>
<u n="10" who="S0144" trans="overlap">what's this then? It wasn't used to chop up a chicken or anything was it?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't think so <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="12" who="S0144">okay</u>
<u n="13" who="S0024">oh I'm getting very confused with what <pause dur="short"/> what's this? Oh this was my pasta one <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0144">can I put this on?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> oh well I'm not ready <pause dur="short"/> hang on <pause dur="short"/> that will be alright <pause dur="short"/> I'll erm I'll just get the butter and the oil</u>
<u n="16" who="S0144">mm mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0024">butter and oil</u>
<u n="18" who="S0144">okay</u>
<u n="19" who="S0024">right <pause dur="short"/> so is there anything else we need to do before we go tomorrow?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0144">well I need to charge the camera erm <pause dur="short"/> don't know <pause dur="short"/> I need to phone everyone to make sure it's okay</u>
<u n="21" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said it's okay so that will be <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it should be fine with my mum because I mean I don't think she's left the house in about three months anyway so she's not going anywhere</u>
<u n="23" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh I switched the wrong one on <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know but whether she'll be well enough <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="24" who="S0144">yeah if she's well enough I don't know <pause dur="short"/> but I'm sure she'd like to see us even if it's for a couple of hours</u>
<u n="25" who="S0024">yep</u>
<u n="26" who="S0144">but that is a long way to drive for a couple of hours</u>
<u n="27" who="S0024">yeah but it needs to be</u>
<u n="28" who="S0144">you're talking six hours</u>
<u n="29" who="S0024">yeah but it needs to be done <pause dur="short"/> but we need to go <pause dur="short"/> well I'd love to go and see her</u>
<u n="30" who="S0144">yeah yeah it would be great</u>
<u n="31" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I'd love it</u>
<u n="32" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I mean even if she isn't well enough there's plenty of other stuff to go and do round there isn't there? Okay</u>
<u n="33" who="S0024" trans="overlap">we've been in <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> we've been in England far too long to not go and see her</u>
<u n="34" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0024">you know <pause dur="short"/> I know she</u>
<u n="36" who="S0144">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0024">why does she have to live so far away? We'd go and visit her all the time if she lived a bit closer</u>
<u n="38" who="S0144">well <pause dur="short"/> it was her choice wasn't it?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0024">car</u>
<u n="40" who="S0144">yep <pause dur="short"/> hmm <pause dur="short"/> yeah did you see er Discovery Channel's that Bear Grylls <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh that's what <pause dur="short"/> why did they?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0144">er I don't know <pause dur="short"/> something to do with his contract <pause dur="short"/> no he was probably asking for money or something</u>
<u n="43" who="S0024"><unclear/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0144">you know what people are like <pause dur="short"/> bit of greedy <pause dur="short"/> or maybe the Discovery Channel wanted to start making him do stuff he didn't want to do</u>
<u n="45" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> probably <pause dur="short"/> probably <pause dur="short"/> poor bloke <pause dur="short"/> he's quite I I like him <pause dur="short"/> very adventurous</u>
<u n="46" who="S0144" trans="overlap">he seems alright actually <pause dur="short"/> he does seem down to earth doesn't he?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I want to learn all of that stuff <pause dur="short"/> they do some</u>
<u n="48" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I'd love to learn all that <pause dur="short"/> that would be brilliant</u>
<u n="49" who="S0024">have you heard about the new forest schools?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="51" who="S0024">they've got <pause dur="short"/> they've started them in different places of the UK where the kids <trunc>ac</trunc> oh it's a sore point I think because it's mainly the kids who are having difficulties</u>
<u n="52" who="S0144">right</u>
<u n="53" who="S0024">they're getting to go and live and stay in the forest cos it improves their behaviour because they're learning life skills in the forest</u>
<u n="54" who="S0144">okay so it's like you're behaving like a complete bastard <pause dur="short"/> let's send you on holiday  as a  as a punishment</u>
<u n="55" who="S0024" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> well no <pause dur="short"/> but  it's part of the school  it's part of the school <pause dur="short"/> they do it every month but they've every week or every month or something a class goes out to the forest and learn</u>
<u n="56" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah but what's the incentive to be a a good kid these days?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0024" trans="overlap">Good kid <pause dur="short"/> yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> but they they reckon they are learning quite a lot of stuff from it</u>
<u n="58" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah I'm sure they are</u>
<u n="59" who="S0024">and they're becoming better behaved but you do wonder about the good kids</u>
<u n="60" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="61" who="S0024" trans="overlap">maybe they're doing the good kids as well</u>
<u n="62" who="S0144">well they don't you see it on <pause dur="short"/> well you see it on TV all the time <pause dur="short"/> you know they're doing up a boat or they they get I don't know they go on a orienteering thing or or whatever <pause dur="short"/> and it's always these kids that are you know got these behavioural problems and I can understand they come from bad</u>
<u n="63" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> do you want to do it over here?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0144">A lot of them come from bad environments</u>
<u n="65" who="S0024">do it over here</u>
<u n="66" who="S0144">but I don't think you can have a society that operates that way</u>
<u n="67" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't understand the how they always <trunc>re</trunc> well they don't reward they try and better the behaviour by giving them nice things don't they <pause dur="short"/> but that it is rewarding</u>
<u n="68" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah which is essentially rewarding bad behaviour</u>
<u n="69" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0144">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I think they should reward good kids and so the other kids say look <pause dur="short"/> look at that kid <pause dur="short"/> he's getting all this stuff <pause dur="short"/> what's wrong with that onion?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0024">oh it's just doubled up in the middle I think</u>
<u n="72" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0144">it's a proper country onion that one</u>
<u n="75" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0144">it's got two heads</u>
<u n="77" who="S0024">yeah I think it should change soon with the</u>
<u n="78" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0024">they do do good <pause dur="short"/> they do try and do good people as well <unclear/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="81" who="S0024">I think it mostly on the news you get to hear  about the  about the bad kids more</u>
<u n="82" who="S0144">maybe</u>
<u n="83" who="S0024" trans="overlap">Don't you? I'm going to have to chop this in half <pause dur="short"/> it might make you cry <pause dur="short"/> here <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> it looks like a pickled onion</u>
<u n="84" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no that that is a pickled onion</u>
<u n="85" who="S0024">oh it smells like a pickled onion</u>
<u n="86" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> I'm not eating that</u>
<u n="87" who="S0024">oh what happened to that?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0144">have we got any more?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0144">hmm <pause dur="short"/> why do onions make you cry? What is it that travels like from air particle to air particle and gets into your eyes?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0024">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> er if you do that</u>
<u n="92" who="S0144">why?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I've got to be quick</u>
<u n="94" who="S0144">why is it when you put a metal spoon in your mouth it stops it?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0024">do you want it? Do you need a metal spoon?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0024">that will do because I need it now <pause dur="short"/> I got to get the</u>
<u n="98" who="S0144">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> what is it?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0024">I have no idea <pause dur="short"/> well it's just the</u>
<u n="100" who="S0144">I'm going to google it</u>
<u n="101" who="S0024">what right now?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0144">well no when we've <pause dur="short"/> later</u>
<u n="103" who="S0024">after dinner? I'm still getting used to this electric cooker <pause dur="short"/> so who's going to take over from Bear Grylls then?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0144">I don't know they'll just get some other bloke won't they? Plenty of them about</u>
<u n="105" who="S0024">I always thought we'd be quite good at that <pause dur="short"/> oh well I always wanted to be in the a photographer <pause dur="short"/> a wildlife photographer or outdoor <pause dur="short"/> oh look the fire's still burnt <pause dur="short"/> that's burning quite high <pause dur="short"/> is that supposed to be doing that?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0144">no that's just smoking <pause dur="short"/> that's okay</u>
<u n="107" who="S0024">really?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0024">okay <pause dur="short"/> did you chop me another onion?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0144">erm no I need to go and get one <pause dur="short"/> where are they?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0024">they're just in the bottom  of the  of the larder <pause dur="short"/> just in the bottom there <pause dur="short"/> I thought there was <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> eyes</u>
<u n="112" who="S0144" trans="overlap">did I tell you about that erm programme I watched last night on RT?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0024" trans="overlap">excuse me <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> was it some girl a girl was doing a new programme <pause dur="short"/> a financial programme or something?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it was brilliant <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="115" who="S0024">no?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0144">no that was something else</u>
<u n="117" who="S0024">oh <pause dur="short"/> no then</u>
<u n="118" who="S0144">no I was watching this erm <pause dur="short"/> it was just an interview</u>
<u n="119" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="120" who="S0144">and they were interviewing the guy from er it was like the vice president or vice chairman of er Walmart</u>
<u n="121" who="S0024">oh yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0144">and it's a Russian guy cos Walmart actually went over to Russia er to try and get in their market</u>
<u n="123" who="S0024" trans="overlap">they're an American company aren't they?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they went to Russia to try and get in and I don't know the Russian government put up loads of obstacles kind of prevented them doing it</u>
<u n="125" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0144">but when Walmart kind of erm went back and admitted defeat they took with them this guy who was the head of one Russia's like biggest supermarket chains and him and put him in place of their you know vice chairman</u>
<u n="127" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="128" who="S0144">and er</u>
<u n="129" who="S0024" trans="overlap">so what does that mean? Is it owned? Who's it owned? What he's directing?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0144">well he's the I don't know he's the chairman <pause dur="short"/> he's I don't know he's making all the big decisions and stuff <pause dur="short"/> I think basically he's he's <trunc>sho</trunc> he's going to show them how to get into the Russian market because</u>
<u n="131" who="S0024">oh what he's just now taking over?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0144">yeah it was quite recently I think <pause dur="short"/> because I mean that's going to make billions for them <pause dur="short"/> and he was saying that Walmart is so big <pause dur="short"/> it's the <pause dur="short"/> do you know it's the biggest company in the world? It's bigger than Coca Cola <pause dur="short"/> it's bigger than</u>
<u n="133" who="S0024" trans="overlap">is it bigger than Tesco?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it's bigger <pause dur="short"/> no it's much bigger than Tesco <pause dur="short"/> bigger than Shell <pause dur="short"/> BP <pause dur="short"/> Microsoft</u>
<u n="135" who="S0024">really?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0024">what all the computer companies?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0144">yep <pause dur="short"/> bigger than anything</u>
<u n="139" who="S0024">how?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0144">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> cos it's not really <pause dur="short"/> you just associate it with America don't you?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0144">but it's not</u>
<u n="143" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah but</u>
<u n="144" who="S0144">he was saying that if you took like all of their earnings over a year</u>
<u n="145" who="S0024">you've got such a little chopping board</u>
<u n="146" who="S0144">I know this is all going everywhere</u>
<u n="147" who="S0024" trans="overlap">it's all falling off <pause dur="short"/> why don't you use the big one?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0144">well <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0024" trans="overlap">took all their earnings for the year</u>
<u n="150" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it would be if you compared it countries GDP it would be the seventeenth er wealthiest country in the world</u>
<u n="151" who="S0024">what? What?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0024">it can't be a country <pause dur="short"/> it's not a country</u>
<u n="154" who="S0144">no but the the amount of money they they take in</u>
<u n="155" who="S0024">what it's bigger than a bank?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0024">what it has higher income than than any well say like that oh I've forgotten the name of that New York bank</u>
<u n="158" who="S0144">what JP Morgan? Goldman Sachs?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0024">no way</u>
<u n="160" who="S0144">I don't know actually if they included banks in that <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> no they probably did because lots of these banks are running at loss anyway with all the derivatives</u>
<u n="161" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> do you think that was <trunc>en</trunc> enough garlic?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0144" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's enough garlic</u>
<u n="163" who="S0024">how much garlic did you do?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0144">I only did one <trunc>clo</trunc> oh shall I do another one?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0024">yeah I think so because</u>
<u n="166" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well it's your mum and dad don't like garlic though do they</u>
<u n="167" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no but I'm trying to cook loads for tomorrow</u>
<u n="168" who="S0144" trans="overlap">are you trying to get them hooked on it?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0024">huh?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0144">yep <pause dur="short"/> wean them on and before they before you know it</u>
<u n="171" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I'm <unclear/> They'll be eating garlic every day <pause dur="short"/> they'll miss it</u>
<u n="172" who="S0144">oh I hope so <pause dur="short"/> they'll be like oh this tastes a bit bland <pause dur="short"/> it's cos it hasn't got garlic</u>
<u n="173" who="S0024">so what was he doing on this programme? What Walmart man? Just saying?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no just having an interview <pause dur="short"/> this guy was giving him quite a hard time because well <trunc>R</trunc> RT you know it's Russian</u>
<u n="175" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0144">and he he was almost talking to him like he was a traitor for leaving Russia <pause dur="short"/> it was quite <trunc>fu</trunc></u>
<u n="177" who="S0024">and going to an American company</u>
<u n="178" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah to go go in to America <pause dur="short"/> it was quite <pause dur="short"/> it was really good <pause dur="short"/> I love that programme <pause dur="short"/> it's the best <pause dur="short"/> well I love the channel <pause dur="short"/> it's the best</u>
<u n="179" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well what <trunc>pro</trunc> what programme? Was just the news channel <pause dur="short"/> news erm programme on there?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0144">yeah it was just this <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think every week he interviews like someone different and</u>
<u n="181" who="S0024">who?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0144">I don't know just this Russian bloke <pause dur="short"/> and he was quite an eccentric interviewer as well <pause dur="short"/> he his</u>
<u n="183" who="S0024">it's not the Cross Talk one?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0144">no it's not Cross Talk <pause dur="short"/> no he was quite intense <pause dur="short"/> and he was always you know he wasn't sitting there all calm and collective like I don't know like a David Dimbleby kind of character <pause dur="short"/> he was he was fidgeting in his seat and he was <pause dur="short"/> I don't know he would really say something like snide like to get the other person under the radar</u>
<u n="185" who="S0024">hmm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0144">it was it was quite funny</u>
<u n="187" who="S0024">hmm</u>
<u n="188" who="S0144">I'd quite happily watch that channel all day really</u>
<u n="189" who="S0024">well it is the best the best one for picking up bits and bobs isn't it?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0144">yeah and they've got some good documentaries on there as well</u>
<u n="191" who="S0024">is that done?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0024">ready? So I'm going to cook this and then I I'm going to have to cook the meat separately I think because I'm cook</u>
<u n="194" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0024">I'm trying to cook like a big massive <pause dur="short"/> is that fine enough?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0144">that's fine enough innit?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0024" trans="overlap">can you cook it <pause dur="short"/> cut it</u>
<u n="198" who="S0144">you like it so fine <pause dur="short"/> I like it a little bit <pause dur="short"/> a little bit of a bite to it</u>
<u n="199" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I usually squish it</u>
<u n="200" who="S0144">what? Put salt on it?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0024">yeah because we used to do that for like garlic bread <pause dur="short"/> when you make garlic bread</u>
<u n="202" who="S0144">yeah well it's</u>
<u n="203" who="S0024" trans="overlap">just like really squish it up</u>
<u n="204" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah that's different isn't it? I mean that one <pause dur="short"/> that's fine</u>
<u n="205" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I suppose <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> thank you <pause dur="short"/> right what's next?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0144">er</u>
<u n="207" who="S0024">erm <pause dur="short"/> I think we'll we've got the tomatoes <pause dur="short"/> we've got the peppers <pause dur="short"/> just erm steak now</u>
<u n="208" who="S0144">mm mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0024">er <pause dur="short"/> can you put the water on the pasta? Let's boil that <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's got to be done haven't they? We'll try a carrot</u>
<u n="210" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> mm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> can you get the water from the kettle?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0144">yep <pause dur="short"/> yeah I watched this other documentary on it as well <pause dur="short"/> they were erm <pause dur="short"/> they were following</u>
<u n="213" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yep <pause dur="short"/> can you stick it on there?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they were in Nigeria <pause dur="short"/> erm there's not enough water in this</u>
<u n="215" who="S0024">huh? Oh well yeah we'll have to fill up again quickly <pause dur="short"/> no no no <pause dur="short"/> oh dear <pause dur="short"/> that will be alright won't it?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0144">just about I think</u>
<u n="217" who="S0024">is there any more left in the kettle no? That's it</u>
<u n="218" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> that's it</u>
<u n="219" who="S0024">and I've lost my lid <pause dur="short"/> oh here it is <pause dur="short"/> right let's get that on <pause dur="short"/> boil</u>
<u n="220" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah they were in Nigeria and I think it was at Shell or BP <pause dur="short"/> just off the coast they've got all these erm oil rigs</u>
<u n="221" who="S0024">yeah?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0144">and they run the pipelines obviously to the shore cos it's pretty close</u>
<u n="223" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0144">and there's all these shanty villages like right there on the shore and there are these big pipelines going through the village that people literally have to step over and drive over on their motorbikes</u>
<u n="225" who="S0024">what?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0144">if they're lucky enough to have a motorbike</u>
<u n="227" who="S0024" trans="overlap">what they haven't? They're just sticking out?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0144">huh? Yeah cos there's this huge <unclear/> <event desc="sound of banging"/> erm they go and they run through the village <pause dur="short"/> and the village is so poor that they haven't got any electric themselves</u>
<u n="229" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0144">are you alright?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> it's all burning</u>
<u n="232" who="S0144">why is it burning?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0024">hang on <pause dur="short"/> I've just got to do this quickly that's all <pause dur="short"/> I'm listening</u>
<u n="234" who="S0144">yeah and yeah they're so poor that none of them have got electric and yet they've got all of this er can't remember if it's gas or oil <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> just running through the the little village</u>
<u n="235" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0144">and then it goes through the village into the jungle where there's some like vents in the pipes</u>
</body>
</text>
