<text id="SK82">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:46:49</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0282 S0292 S0293</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>At the Cox family house</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>life in the services as a woman, local history, studying, clothes</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about the services, uniforms and university</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring,  anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T13</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0282">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Stratford-upon-Avon</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>self employed</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0292">
				<exactage>81</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>80_89</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Southsea, Hampshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>29</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired WRAF officer</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0293">
				<exactage>21</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Guildford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>21</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>unemployed</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>German -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0292">you'd never know it might be pure</u>
<u n="2" who="S0293">so you learned German as well then in fact?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0292">erm no I mean I picked it up but I didn't learn it no no no no but of course I was working within as a volunteer for the British Council in my off duty times and it was basically English</u>
<u n="4" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="5" who="S0292">and sadly in my sessions for the foreign <unclear/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0293">did you do singing as well at that time?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0292">no I'd given up singing at that time I picked it up again <unclear/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0292">really anything I love it</u>
<u n="10" who="S0293">did you always plan to have a short stint in the Air Force <unclear/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0292">no I I didn't think plan for anything <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was all luck all the way through</u>
<u n="12" who="S0293">you had to be able to be married</u>
<u n="13" who="S0292">no no no I had my last year erm married living off camp we had our first house no that was earlier but by the time that I'd come along erm you could be married</u>
<u n="14" who="S0293">so you didn't want to continue then?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0292">well I'd come <unclear/> actually yes erm if I'd gone on I and I would have had to have signed on for another three years as it were because our initial commissions were for eighteen years erm you could leave before that of course but I'd come to that stage and I'd met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and erm he hadn't quite proposed but I knew that it was coming and erm I really did want to sign on for the next two years</u>
<u n="16" who="S0282">oh but it would be so easy to get out if all you had to do was get married</u>
<u n="17" who="S0292">yes yes I mean</u>
<u n="18" who="S0293">you don't need to get married you just have to finish</u>
<u n="19" who="S0292">you'd have to become pregnant then you would have to <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0282">oh yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0292">not now of course I disapprove very strongly of that because if you're a young mother in the Air Force or in any services and you have a child a baby you cannot put the service first and therefore your if you rush off because you've got a baby your colleagues are carrying the weight and I think that's quite wrong they used to have a rule that you couldn't join if you had children under fifteen and I thought that was fair after that they can fend for themselves but until that time we felt that erm careers should come secondary to the child</u>
<u n="22" who="S0282">mm it's difficult with the men really</u>
<u n="23" who="S0292">yes I think it's just so hard it's just not fair but I mean the norm now is that they can be pregnant in the service and keep on with their career and have babies</u>
<u n="24" who="S0282">I don't I it's that there will probably be quite a lot of litigation involved in trying to police that kind of <unclear/> these days because if a if a soldier or an airman erm males who's male can have children then you couldn't possibly say that a woman couldn't</u>
<u n="25" who="S0292">that's right</u>
<u n="26" who="S0293">because they're <unclear/> legislation and etcetera etcetera</u>
<u n="27" who="S0292">that's right it's just that for a baby certainly I would have thought mother was essential <unclear/> we know very well that in America they have the most because I remember one of the women who was captured in the Iraq in the Kuwait war had a baby</u>
<u n="28" who="S0282">but then I suppose I I suppose that erm there's probably more peace time enough jobs and are based in this country of administrative nature that that if you have a child you could be you know sort of confined to duty at some base either here or in Germany or <unclear/> that you wouldn't have to be</u>
<u n="29" who="S0292">no but again it could mean again that your male colleagues are taking an unfair portion of work to be done it's different</u>
<u n="30" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="31" who="S0293">see <unclear/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0292">yes he was made redundant and uh luckily erm he was a <unclear/> part time jobs in the museum erm in the <unclear/> and the orchestra so he was very <unclear/> which was lovely</u>
<u n="33" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0292">yes he did he loved it</u>
<u n="35" who="S0282">and were you interested in history before that or did he get you involved in the local historical society?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0292">I suppose I was vaguely interested in that we had parents who loved taking us to erm I mean not <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but who erm not in the war but later on erm we were expected to go around the old stately home with them and this type of thing but not serious history no I wouldn't say that I'm a serious historian now I just learnt enough to go as a volunteer <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0293">you <unclear/> don't you?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0292">uhu that's the thing I study really history that is different I mean you can't study art as you know without doing a certain amount of historical background to fit the movements and the people into their social setting</u>
<u n="39" who="S0282">I mean if you're interested in art <unclear/> their life and who they knew and who they hung out with and where they lived and so then you're in a historical place without really realizing it</u>
<u n="40" who="S0292">yeah that's absolutely right absolutely right</u>
<u n="41" who="S0282">and who do they know which other artists were they friends with</u>
<u n="42" who="S0292">that's right and who influenced them</u>
<u n="43" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0292">yes yes that's right</u>
<u n="45" who="S0282">there was an article in the paper yesterday about erm the link between Houston Freud and Francis Bacon and I hadn't I hadn't really realized that they were connected to each other</u>
<u n="46" who="S0292">oh yes yes it's important</u>
<u n="47" who="S0282">and there's one particular painting which is which was erm Bacon taking a painting of Freud's and elaborating on it and</u>
<u n="48" who="S0292">oh</u>
<u n="49" who="S0282">it being a self-portrait but he it was a self-portrait but incorporating Freud's erm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0292">oh</u>
<u n="51" who="S0282">um sort of style and the particular thing that he had done</u>
<u n="52" who="S0292">yes</u>
<u n="53" who="S0282">so and I thought oh that that's that could explain why sometimes I get a bit confused about which of the two I'm looking at</u>
<u n="54" who="S0292">oh yes</u>
<u n="55" who="S0282">I know that's a terribly heathen thing to admit</u>
<u n="56" who="S0292">no no well certainly I <unclear/> painted the other but I couldn't remember which ones now</u>
<u n="57" who="S0282">yeah but so you did know <unclear/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0292">yes yes yes it was enjoyable</u>
<u n="59" who="S0282">is that through a local charity or local historical society?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0292">no that's through the museum</u>
<u n="61" who="S0282">through the museum?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0292">hmm we're most of us are friends of the museum and some some of that group are also town guides there's erm a local history courses that run and after two years those who that are they can become town guides if they wish</u>
<u n="63" who="S0282">yeah new patch</u>
<u n="64" who="S0292">no</u>
<u n="65" who="S0293">oh</u>
<u n="66" who="S0292">no they're not from the village so they're not quite perhaps as well trained as if <unclear/> but</u>
<u n="67" who="S0282">well were as widely trained you had to do a whole camp</u>
<u n="68" who="S0292">yes</u>
<u n="69" who="S0293"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dad's a Blue Badge guide</u>
<u n="70" who="S0282">yeah he studied for quite a while</u>
<u n="71" who="S0292">who is?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0293"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s father</u>
<u n="73" who="S0282">my father yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0292">oh really?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0293">yes</u>
<u n="77" who="S0282">in the West Midlands</u>
<u n="78" who="S0292">yes well I know and they have to take exams</u>
<u n="79" who="S0282">yes he did take exams</u>
<u n="80" who="S0292">but I mean that doesn't happen with they were asked I understand suggested they should become Blue Badge guides but they all ran away from the study and the things yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0293">I think it was <unclear/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0292">oh did she?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0293">but they were all obsessed most of the <unclear/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0292">mm mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0282">so you spent yesterday underground then?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0292">oh only two hours</u>
<u n="88" who="S0282">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0292">erm it's it's enough in there too because erm in the mid to late twentieth century I'm not quite sure of the date erm it was used as a tourist information centre and then fortunately therefore they put down paving it had been a mud floor and when it was a mud floor it was the right kind of floor and it absorbed the dampness</u>
<u n="90" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="91" who="S0292">as soon as they put down the paving erm we we were having a problem of damp in the underground so you have now a dehumidifier going the whole time we were in there because there's nothing to absorb the damp</u>
<u n="92" who="S0293"><unclear/> isn't it a problem</u>
<u n="93" who="S0292">what?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0282">did you get lots of people visiting?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0292">yes we always do on heritage day but I was surprised at the number in that two hours was it a hundred and fifty I think so it's non-stop they pour in and you rush around saying do you want any information? are you going to look? can I help? and they all cluster around and some of them are very interested in our so called ninety-nine percent <unclear/> medieval synagogue erm down the high street if it is erm a synagogue it will be the oldest in England</u>
<u n="96" who="S0282">wow</u>
<u n="97" who="S0292">we've had the experts from America and Israel and erm <unclear/> Hebrew I think it is in Bristol but no documentary everything about it was discovered about twenty years ago seems to link with the synagogue and they even found in one of the columns in a niche the perfect silver coin dated twelve seventy and the Jews were thrown out of Gilford in twelve seventy-five</u>
<u n="98" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="99" who="S0292">and one of the pretexts as you well know erm for the massacre and throwing the Jews out was that it was said they shaved the edges of the silver coin and amassed the shavings and here was a perfect silver coin deliberately stuck into a niche and then this was had been partially demolished so it's not full height it was full of rubble when it was discovered it had to be refilled but at least all the work has been done on it and recently this person I was mentioning that did her doctorate on the immigrant tower she is a wonderful historian and she went to erm Germany for a big historian's conference and met some German erm <trunc>hi</trunc>historians and archaeologists there and she was talking about our so called erm synagogue and they said oh that sounds an exact copy of one we have up in north Germany so that was rather pleasing to hear</u>
<u n="100" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0292">so we're not sure it might be something else but it has three sides of it have a stone shelf seat running around it which ours certainly hasn't because that was built as a shop so it is interesting great excitement to hit the world news</u>
<u n="102" who="S0282">yeah <unclear/> why was it why was there another <unclear/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0292">why because um that was presumably the norm and we know there were probably well we know we have signs of at least six of the erm high streets still and erm we believe there were twelve and in fact the so called <unclear>Primpt Restaurant</unclear> underneath the Angel Hotel is in fact an <unclear>under croft</unclear> really erm much ought to whereas ours hasn't been um and ours was built between twelve fifty and thirteen hundred roughly about then and erm we know it was built as a shop and we've brought sides of the original stairs down just a little bit and we have the original window and an original beautiful arched little doorway which lead led we think to erm a spiral staircase but it's that's been ruined and there's just <trunc>someth</trunc> a thing about it which suggests to the experts that it was or was intended to be a <trunc>spi</trunc> spiral staircase which if so then would have led up to <trunc>sh</trunc> the house above</u>
<u n="104" who="S0282">oh and was the street leveller in those days? it must have been</u>
<u n="105" who="S0292">yes not an awful lot because you see a high street is a hill</u>
<u n="106" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0292">so I suspect that when the storms came it would remove some of the rubbish onto the bottom of the hill so I don't think you got quite the build-up that you get in other towns which are more level</u>
<u n="108" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0292">I suppose the difference is about <pause dur="long"/> eighteen inches</u>
<u n="110" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0292">and I think sometimes it's much steeper isn't it? but I'm no expert I really don't know</u>
<u n="112" who="S0282">no I don't know <unclear/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0293"><unclear/> barbarians</u>
<u n="114" who="S0292">mm gosh how exciting barbarians</u>
<u n="115" who="S0282">or was it erm was it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we were going to <unclear/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0282">right no oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0282">no well I had <unclear/> I got I went and applied for the scholarship when I was a teenager to go and join they were sponsoring a young person to join a dig</u>
<u n="120" who="S0292">oh</u>
<u n="121" who="S0282">and I went to <anon type="place"/> to interview but there was somebody who was gonna go off and study archaeology at university so they gave it to her</u>
<u n="122" who="S0292">oh yes I did some digging and I was it was very lucky really I it was when I was stationed in <anon type="place"/> and got involved and our archaeologist was of all people <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> before he went on <unclear/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0282">wow</u>
<u n="124" who="S0292">so we went and had an interesting short time in <unclear/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0292">in the services your interests were always <vocal desc="laugh"/> a short time and then you were off I was put in my place because there were these leather jacketed you would have thought <unclear/> cycling on their motorbikes all in studded leather but they could tell me far more about the angry Saxons and cemetery digging than I could ever have known <vocal desc="laugh"/> and it was a good lesson <unclear/> from the outside</u>
<u n="127" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0293">did you find it quite odd being surrounded by men all the time? did you not miss women sometimes?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0292">erm sometimes I can remember one very funny occasion when I was in Kenya and I was dress making standing gravely on the dining room table as the men <vocal desc="laugh"/> some of the men <vocal desc="laugh"/> who lived in the mess were doing my hems for me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0282">it must have been good explaining I'm trying to get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to do that <unclear/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0292"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0282">it's lots of chaos</u>
<u n="133" who="S0292">yes of course yes it could be and it was lonely when you were most senior because of course you can't really erm however friendly you were with your staff</u>
<u n="134" who="S0293"><unclear/> so who how <unclear/> friends at some point</u>
<u n="135" who="S0292">actually because of my career I don't have very many because I spent so much time doing rather strange <unclear/> jobs but I was nothing to do with the WRAF which suited me because I was never keen on welfare and erm so I supposed the ones I knew best was when I was in charge of the WRAF officer training at our joint <unclear/> and I had four wonderful flight lieutenants or flight commanders who were very experienced and I was an absolute erm beginner really cos I had a background in intelligence jobs and erm they kept me on the straight and narrow we had a lot of fun</u>
<u n="136" who="S0293">uhu what did you do in Kenya?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0292">oh I was erm signals edge and codes and cyphers there they thought they would put a WRAF section into Kenya and though I had already served in Egypt for a few months and we were thrown out and went to Cypress where we had <unclear/> terrorism they thought they'd put WRAF to Kenya so I was sent down as the vanguard to be you know base the signals edge and cyphers officer with the idea that I'd be there to open up when when we came this was <unclear/> terrorism erm but erm that never happened</u>
<u n="138" who="S0293">why did they send young women there? was that the natural course of business or</u>
<u n="139" who="S0292">I don't know I really don't know I mean I was a fairly junior officer I was only twenty-three at the time and and erm you know so I don't think I knew the rationale you're just told you're going down which was exciting and erm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0293">that was remember in Egypt that time was that the <unclear/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0292">no that was I did <unclear/> when I was in <unclear/> and <unclear/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0282"><unclear/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0292">it's funny look how young you were at the time I mean <unclear/> was what fifty-six and I was in charge of the cypher office in <anon type="place"/> which dealt not only with the Air Force erm erm codes and cyphers but with the government erm British government erm and I used to deal with stuff then that only the governor of the colony and the two most senior RAF officers were allowed to see I used to have to walk myself away from my stuff and at twenty-three and the governor used to send his car oh I did love it no no number plate just a silver crown you know got big headed with such</u>
<u n="144" who="S0282">so who would you who would be your reporting officer if there was just you in your</u>
<u n="145" who="S0292">well we were a headquarters and so erm there were people in the headquarters and there was somebody I think in front of the in charge of the signal centre we must have been some of it's rather vague it's awful</u>
<u n="146" who="S0282">erm erm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0292">you're talking about the fifties</u>
<u n="148" who="S0282">yes yes gosh so erm so we're looking backwards and you um you regretted that you couldn't go to university and you always wanted to do it in the end think actually you know what this was as good as going to university all that I proved myself anyway and that you know through the Russian and through that</u>
<u n="149" who="S0292">I I suppose so really yes I don't regret it now because I so loved my career in the Air Force</u>
<u n="150" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0292">which presumably wouldn't have happened</u>
<u n="152" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="153" who="S0292">and I wouldn't have been to these exciting places and so I'm a great believer that universities are essential really for an interesting career and I remember one of the most effective officers I knew a natural leader a wonderful person and how she got in I don't know quite rightly she wouldn't even have those days of course she didn't even have that but she was an absolute wow as a leader as a officer and erm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0282">so somebody must have spotted her talent then</u>
<u n="155" who="S0292">yes they yes yes that's right thank goodness</u>
<u n="156" who="S0282">absolutely</u>
<u n="157" who="S0292">yes there was an opening she ended up as a kind of personal assistant to erm dear erm Princess Ann as the Duchess of <unclear/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0282">oh really</u>
<u n="159" who="S0292">Duchess of <unclear/> was the head of the <unclear/> Air Force of the WAF</u>
<u n="160" who="S0282">oh I see I see</u>
<u n="161" who="S0292">no I'm sure that's quite enough</u>
<u n="162" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0282">it's it would be handy if we could get to you know the nearest <unclear/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0293">I missed the last I missed the last exciting bit about <unclear/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0292"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0293">I guess you get you didn't wear out your own clothes did you in the Forces <unclear/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0282">do you want another ten minutes? cos then it takes us to three quarters of an hour</u>
<u n="168" who="S0292">right okay I suppose that's true really I wore a uniform during the day</u>
<u n="169" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0292">but they were very expensive clothes</u>
<u n="171" who="S0293">oh you had to buy them?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0292">oh yes</u>
<u n="173" who="S0293">oh I thought you got them free</u>
<u n="174" who="S0292">oh no I mean not even the I don't think even the other ranks they were issued at first they probably were had to buy replacements maybe not but right from the beginning we had to buy</u>
<u n="175" who="S0293">oh no I thought you might of at least got free uniforms</u>
<u n="176" who="S0292">oh no I mean that's that's part of being an officer I mean that's why many male officers couldn't take the degrees very different then sorry not degrees erm commissions in the guards</u>
<u n="177" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="178" who="S0292">because they needed such a private income to compete with the social life and</u>
<u n="179" who="S0282">I suppose there were times when you had to bring your own horse wasn't there?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0292">yes yes but erm that that probably doesn't apply now I'm sure it doesn't apply now because things that very much more democratic even in the guards although I suspect there's still required a certain kind of person but no no you bought your own uniforms and they were jolly expensive <pause dur="short"/>I I was very lucky when you're a little officer cadet you erm fairly on in the course you erm all the major military tailors arrive and you're expected to go around and choose one who will start making your uniform in the hope that you will eventually graduate and erm they had Moss Brothers and Gaves and <unclear/> I think it is isn't it <unclear/> I can't remember now oh <unclear/> I think and all the rest and erm there was a just a little man standing quietly by himself and nobody was getting up to him so I thought oh poor thing so I went up to him and we got chatting and oh yes yes he'd happily do my uniform and it turned out that again I I was lucky in the Air Force I had chosen the people erm person that did all the most senior officers in every kind of <vocal desc="laugh"/> field and guards officers and things and he said to me would you like a red lining which was technically not really allowed oh yes I said so I always had a bright red silk lining in my uniform <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0282">what what did you wear when you got married?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0292">erm oh a <trunc>con</trunc>conventional wedding dress</u>
<u n="183" who="S0282">oh you did?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0292">oh yes</u>
<u n="185" who="S0293">and your husband was he was he in his</u>
<u n="186" who="S0292">he was just in the morning suit yes</u>
<u n="187" who="S0282">oh okay</u>
<u n="188" who="S0292">because he was a <unclear/> officer he wasn't full time Army</u>
<u n="189" who="S0282">gosh</u>
<u n="190" who="S0292"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0293">did you have to clean those uniforms? because there wasn't dry cleaning was there?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0292">oh yes we've always had dry cleaning</u>
<u n="193" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0292">I don't really know but certainly they were always dry cleaned</u>
<u n="195" who="S0282">they used to damp them with something you used to damp them with ammonia or something</u>
<u n="196" who="S0292">oh dab it off at one time but no they have to go occasionally to dry clean</u>
<u n="197" who="S0293"><unclear/> wool they must have got very smelly</u>
<u n="198" who="S0292">ah well on the <trunc>ho</trunc> well it depends where you are in Germany yes it was the blues but it was in the Middle East it was what they called khaki drill it wasn't drill for women it was the khaki</u>
<u n="199" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0292">erm yes I mean I always had <unclear/> and things so I didn't wash them</u>
<u n="201" who="S0293"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0282">what's it like <unclear/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0292">I know it seems unreal now very <unclear/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0282">no but you you do um you still have you don't wash the <unclear/> in the forces now it it gets laundered I mean when my brother was in the Navy they had they had an laundry department started by Chinese people</u>
<u n="205" who="S0292">that's right</u>
<u n="206" who="S0282">so you sent all your stuff to them and they boil washed everything so it didn't last very long</u>
<u n="207" who="S0293">why?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0282">because it sort of disintegrates itself after they've boil washed a certain number of times they start falling apart the seams fall apart</u>
<u n="209" who="S0292">wow</u>
<u n="210" who="S0282">you wouldn't have if they were wearing a white t-shirt they would have to come out the same shade of white you can't possibly have people you know in different shades of white because it's <unclear/> washed it</u>
<u n="211" who="S0292">yes</u>
<u n="212" who="S0282">and the right amount of <unclear/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0293">that's that they do with the leotards right before um exams</u>
<u n="215" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="216" who="S0293">they have a set of leotards for exams and they wash them all together so that everyone's the same colour so they fade all the same time time</u>
<u n="217" who="S0292">how interesting</u>
<u n="218" who="S0293">they obviously do that for shows as well</u>
<u n="219" who="S0292">yes I didn't know that</u>
<u n="220" who="S0282">but if you look at a cohort of school children who are all started out on day with the same uniform and you look at them six months later</u>
<u n="221" who="S0292">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0282">there will be the ones that are faded out and washed <unclear/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0293">well it seems that <unclear/> they're they're permanent no that's gonna be with you know for the rest of your school career <vocal desc="laugh"/> there's not much I can do about that</u>
<u n="224" who="S0292">yeah there is something that's meant to remove ink</u>
<u n="225" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0292">really? oh oh</u>
<u n="227" who="S0293">and she's not a very bright child</u>
<u n="228" who="S0282"><unclear/> students</u>
<u n="229" who="S0292">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0282">it's like waiting on classes</u>
<u n="231" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0292"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0282">perhaps she'll she'll become studious by looking studious</u>
<u n="235" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0282">I'm sure there's management theories as to <unclear/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0293">she's absolutely appalled by <unclear/> they're supposed to do philosophy and <trunc>economi</trunc> er philosophy and ethics</u>
<u n="238" who="S0292">mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0293">and they're not supposed to do Christianity but she's got the most</u>
<u n="240" who="S0292">oh</u>
<u n="241" who="S0293">evangelical church <vocal desc="laugh"/> teacher who's making her do all this Christian stuff which drives her absolutely bonkers</u>
<u n="242" who="S0292">really?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0293">cos she can't bear being told what you know what to believe or what to think or whatever</u>
<u n="244" who="S0292">mm mm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0293">I see her point though you do think actually in a school these days it'd be pretty hard to teach a hard-line Christian line</u>
<u n="246" who="S0292">yes</u>
<u n="247" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="248" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0292">but you see with such a mixed</u>
<u n="250" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0292">I'm surprised I mean er I think it</u>
<u n="252" who="S0293">I'm sure they're not supposed to I'm er sure it's supposed to be multi-religious</u>
<u n="253" who="S0282">I didn't think they were supposed to either</u>
<u n="254" who="S0293">no not in school</u>
<u n="255" who="S0292">I I wouldn't have thought so I mean I don't approve of them <trunc>m</trunc><trunc>m</trunc>missing out morning assembly but if they've er got to miss out morning assembly the to teach hard-line Christianity</u>
<u n="256" who="S0293">it's really a bit <unclear/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0292">it's really strange by all means erm I mean I think they should learn something about Christianity</u>
<u n="258" who="S0293">well they ought <trunc>l</trunc> ought to learn about all the main religions really oughtn't they?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0292">yes</u>
<u n="260" who="S0293">but they certainly shouldn't have one line only</u>
<u n="261" who="S0292">I think that's er valuable or not</u>
<u n="262" who="S0282">well we had a RE teacher who was a Catholic and she wasn't allowed to teach RE we had to do other things in the RE class because <trunc>sh</trunc></u>
<u n="263" who="S0292">really?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0282">she wasn't permitted <trunc>t</trunc>to to to talk to us about religion because she</u>
<u n="265" who="S0293">but how can she be an RE teacher then?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0282">cos <trunc>sh</trunc> mm?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0293">how can she be an RE teacher?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0282">because well it was because RE wasn't an exam subject or anything it was just something you had to do as part of curriculum so you had a lesson a week</u>
<u n="269" who="S0293">yeah but how can she be an RE teacher if she couldn't <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0282">well no because it it was kind of who was left over for period six on a Friday?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0292">mm</u>
<u n="272" who="S0282">after you've allocated all the other things so she'd got the short straw because there was only her available to do RE that term I suppose</u>
<u n="273" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0282">otherwise I can't it must've been her availability in that time slot cos we had quite a small school or it was four hundred people so the so the curriculum thing has always been terribly troubled</u>
<u n="275" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="276" who="S0282">because you were trying to sort of you know sort of make sure that the teachers got spread across</u>
<u n="277" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="278" who="S0282">everything that they needed to do so you got all <trunc>e</trunc> whoever got the short straw got to do RE</u>
<u n="279" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0282">it's not like my dad who got an O-level in RE</u>
<u n="281" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0282">he yes when</u>
<u n="283" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="284" who="S0282">he <unclear/> <trunc>abs</trunc>absolutely has no interest in religion at all we wonder how he did it</u>
<u n="285" who="S0293">mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0292">I don't think we even we in our age took exams <trunc>R</trunc>our in er religious we took we had to take so many papers as you know for er in the old school <unclear/> and you had to pass so many at er a credit level to to to matriculate which officially gave you the right to go into university erm but of course nobody ever did go in with matric but officially that was the entrance er er</u>
<u n="287" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0292">oh yes you get er credits in <trunc>Fr</trunc> er or as I say French but possibly it was any foreign language erm English which was grammar and literature and everything maths I can't can't remember what the other two were</u>
<u n="289" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">geography?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0292">maybe it was er <trunc>s</trunc> I think</u>
<u n="291" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0292">it was geography I certainly did geography and got credit but whether that was whether er they I I <trunc>d</trunc> I suppose yes cos they did lay down all five maybe one was a science subject I wouldn't be surprised physics or chemistry or something I don't remember</u>
<u n="293" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="294" who="S0292">but</u>
<u n="295" who="S0282">or general science?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0293">no we didn't have general science in those days we did physics and chemistry mm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0293"><unclear/> no we did <trunc>g</trunc> we did <unclear/> cos that was how on earth did people have uniforms during the war? bearing in mind there was so little material around school uniforms how did they do it?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0292">well I can remember that our school uniform the summer school uniform the high school was the most ridiculous it was a pale cream dress plain pale cream</u>
<u n="299" who="S0293">oh</u>
<u n="300" who="S0292">and my mother managed somebody gave her er a parachute that had faded</u>
<u n="301" who="S0293">oh you could have any material pale cream?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0292">yes and she made my school uniforms out of parachute silk</u>
<u n="303" who="S0293">but how on earth would you do what what about the winter uniforms? did you have to wear blue <trunc>s</trunc> er you could all just wear wear blue skirts?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0292">we er</u>
<u n="305" who="S0293">you had to make a skirt?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0292">we had to wear <trunc>na</trunc> well we wore gym slips and erm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0293">were were they all the same or did you make them yourself?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0292">oh no no they were <trunc>m</trunc> I mean they must be quite complex to make the old gym slips you know with the great wide pleats down</u>
<u n="309" who="S0282"><unclear/><unclear>oh right yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="310" who="S0293">no no I know that but how on earth did they have the <unclear/> to do it?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0292">I don't know</u>
<u n="312" who="S0293">it was <unclear/></u>
<u n="313" who="S0292">I suspect</u>
<u n="314" who="S0282">perhaps it was the same people who made the uniforms for the soldiers and things <unclear/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0292">it was probably second hand I don't know I don't remember let me see how old were I was it still war time when I went up to the?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0293">er the only reason I ask is cos I know my mother</u>
<u n="317" who="S0292">eleven</u>
<u n="318" who="S0293">only had her</u>
<u n="319" who="S0292">eleven</u>
<u n="320" who="S0293">one set of clothes so I <trunc>kn</trunc>I know that you know at certain times in the war</u>
<u n="321" who="S0292">yes ah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0293">erm</u>
<u n="323" who="S0292">well mm now er I was eleven when when I went up to the high school so that would be forty-four so it was still war time</u>
<u n="324" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0292">but somehow we had gym slips I don't ask</u>
<u n="326" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0292">don't know how maybe there were special dispensations for the first <trunc>s</trunc>school uniform</u>
<u n="328" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="329" who="S0292">and then later I remember in the sixth year we were allowed skirts navy blue skirts</u>
<u n="330" who="S0282">perhaps that's where I don't know about your school but we always had an official supplier of our school uniform</u>
<u n="331" who="S0292">yes yes</u>
<u n="332" who="S0282">and you could only get your school uniform from official school suppliers</u>
<u n="333" who="S0292">that's right</u>
<u n="334" who="S0282">so perhaps it started in the war where certain manufacturers because they were making uniforms were allowed to have access to</u>
<u n="335" who="S0293">I know do you know the coupons to get them are <unclear/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0282">but not everything was on coupons</u>
<u n="337" who="S0293">oh I see <unclear/> that's why she always wore <unclear/> that would make sense</u>
<u n="338" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="339" who="S0293">she always <unclear/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0292">yes yes and of course my mother was very good at making sewing</u>
<u n="341" who="S0282">yeah I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0292">yes that's right so we were never short of clothes and bless her she even kept rabbits and we eat the rabbits and she learned how to deal with the rabbit fur and made gloves</u>
<u n="343" who="S0282">oh wow oh my word that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0292">yes she was <trunc>ama</trunc></u>
<u n="345" who="S0282"><unclear/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0293">she was amazing but then women of that age were incredibly <trunc>inn</trunc>innovative and tough</u>
<u n="347" who="S0282">yeah take sleeves out put new sleeves in turn turn the collar</u>
<u n="348" who="S0292">mm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0293">I did that <unclear/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0292">really yes yes</u>
<u n="351" who="S0293">at least <unclear/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0282">but then we always had we always had recycled as well I mean in our school there was a huge market in second hand blazers and gabardines and</u>
<u n="353" who="S0293">I never I never knew <unclear/></u>
<u n="354" who="S0292">see we didn't have that in erm in that erm I mean most schools now have second hand little departments at the beginning of the school year don't they</u>
<u n="355" who="S0282">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0293">but nothing like that no that would have been considered very odd because I'm so much older than you</u>
<u n="357" who="S0282">well no I had a second my my blazer was a second hand</u>
<u n="358" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0292">and of course it was I remember my mother getting very upset it was so funny I was dancing erm in the dancing troupe at the age of I should think ten or eleven no it was the time of the invasion so I was perhaps twelve and erm we were in a typical little ballet school and doing things like <shift new="singing"/> don't sit under the apple tree with anyone else but me <shift new="normal"/> well they gave a great concert for all the troops that they were mainly all marines in <unclear>Isney</unclear> in Portsmouth and I've often thought since these poor men who were doomed though they possibly didn't know that at that very moment were due to go across and <trunc>in</trunc> invade and instead of having glamorous women they had <vocal desc="laugh"/> ten year olds <vocal desc="laugh"/> always made me laugh and I had a new pair of socks for the erm stage white little socks and I lost one and I remember my mother was very angry and I presume <unclear/> question of clothing coupons and things</u>
<u n="360" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="361" who="S0293">it must be so stressful <unclear/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0292">awful <unclear/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0282">well I was only allowed one pair of tights I think I must have <unclear/> I can't imagine</u>
<u n="364" who="S0292">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="365" who="S0282">I used to go around ladders all over that's why I had to get a job in Woolworths I had to lie about my age and get a job in Woolworths because a pair of tights was twenty-five p my pocket money was twenty-five p so it was either get a new pair of tights every week and nothing else or else you know find the income to get a new pair of tights</u>
<u n="366" who="S0292">mm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0282">and we use to complain like mad at school and say it's really not fair the school should have to pay for our tights because look the desks look at which the desks are doing</u>
<u n="368" who="S0292">yes</u>
<u n="369" who="S0282">to which the answer was well go back to socks then if you feel like that</u>
<u n="370" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0292">I am trying to think of course we didn't have tights because they weren't around then I'm just trying to think</u>
<u n="372" who="S0282">you must have had socks</u>
<u n="373" who="S0292">I think we must of had socks</u>
<u n="374" who="S0282"><unclear/> pictures of my mum she had socks</u>
<u n="375" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0292">yes</u>
<u n="377" who="S0282">vile socks fawn socks or grey socks</u>
<u n="378" who="S0292">I can't remember</u>
<u n="379" who="S0282">white socks in summer</u>
<u n="380" who="S0293">we had um brown knickers and we had to wear knickers underneath them</u>
<u n="381" who="S0292">goodness me</u>
<u n="382" who="S0282">two pairs of knickers</u>
<u n="383" who="S0292">oh yeah we had to navy blue passion killers remember for gym</u>
<u n="384" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0293">we used to go around having said that we still used to prance around in our best of knickers cos at state school that's what you do we had red knickers at state school</u>
<u n="386" who="S0292">oh</u>
<u n="387" who="S0293">my junior school</u>
<u n="388" who="S0292">goodness</u>
<u n="389" who="S0282">we had really really big really new very big big big navy blue pants</u>
<u n="390" who="S0292">yes right down to <unclear/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0293">I still think there should be a uniform now but there you go</u>
<u n="392" who="S0292"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0282">well especially if you roll your pants up and get a glimpse of the knickers underneath that would soon to cramp their style <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0293">oh heaven knows what they would do</u>
<u n="395" who="S0282">but my mother was I remember my mother not having enough money and deciding to make my school skirt from a piece of material that was nearly nearly the same as the school because I wore purple</u>
<u n="396" who="S0292">goodness</u>
<u n="397" who="S0293">my</u>
<u n="398" who="S0282">yeah and <unclear/> our blazer was turquoise purple and yellow stripes</u>
<u n="399" who="S0292">my goodness it must have been <unclear/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0282">I know and with matching tie</u>
<u n="401" who="S0292">yes</u>
<u n="402" who="S0282">yeah so my mother made this skirt out of a piece of material that was nearly nearly that colour and we had this big quadrant in the middle of our school with a piece of grass in it and I was walking I think I was walking across the grass in the direction of the head mistress and the deputy head mistress and I could see them looking at me as I went across and I was trying to veer away and kind of duck into the science hall</u>
<u n="403" who="S0292">oh</u>
<u n="404" who="S0282">and they went eh eh and called me over and then they said that's not the proper school skirt they said you're to go home until you get a proper school skirt</u>
<u n="405" who="S0292">oh</u>
<u n="406" who="S0282">so I got sent home and my mother was so furious but they wouldn't of course they wouldn't have it you had to have a proper school skirt so that was that</u>
<u n="407" who="S0292">mm</u>
<u n="408" who="S0293">we had shades of purple and the shades of</u>
<u n="409" who="S0282">did you?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0293">purple were a big issue because we had <unclear/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0282">nine? well we were allowed to have we were allowed to make our own in the sixth form as a special treat</u>
<u n="412" who="S0292">goodness</u>
<u n="413" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0282">but that was quite</u>
<u n="415" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="416" who="S0292">yes</u>
<u n="417" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0282">oh no no no I would do I would have been up to here with <unclear/> my uncles <unclear/> the only way to have what you wanted was to was to erm was to make it yourself</u>
<u n="419" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="420" who="S0282">the only way to get you had to so in the sixth form and then my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who was beautiful and just beautiful and erm and her mother had her summer dresses made by a seamstress so she was not only beautiful but she had the most gorgeous shirt dresses you know that were absolutely cut to her and and and skimmed her body so she looked even more gorgeous and the rest of were frumping around in something that we'd made ourselves which kind of fitted in most places but kind of didn't</u>
<u n="421" who="S0292">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0282">out of the three <unclear/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0292">and was she envied?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0282">oh erm yes you were just invisible when you were next to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because she was so beautiful every boy in town wanted to get up <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so you <unclear/> with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and erm she would be writing someone's name in her</u>
<u n="425" who="S0293">what did she end up doing then?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0282">she ended ah no well she blotted her copy book she ended up as a physiotherapist and as soon as she said she wanted to be a physiotherapist my school just wrote her off because it wasn't academic enough</u>
<u n="427" who="S0292">oh</u>
<u n="428" who="S0282">and they just ignored her and erm and then in fact she actually died when she was twenty-five of breast cancer</u>
<u n="429" who="S0292">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="430" who="S0282">I know leaving two small children so</u>
<u n="431" who="S0292">isn't life unfair</u>
<u n="432" who="S0282">I know that was bitter but my mother of course protecting her daughter I didn't find out my mother didn't tell me she died she thought I would be too upset</u>
<u n="433" who="S0292">oh</u>
<u n="434" who="S0282">so when I sort of said oh whatever happened to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know she's like oh well she's dead</u>
<u n="435" who="S0293"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0282">what <vocal desc="laugh"/> since when? oh I don't know ten years fifteen years <vocal desc="laugh"/> something like that</u>
<u n="437" who="S0292">oh</u>
<u n="438" who="S0282">oh thanks very much for telling me</u>
<u n="439" who="S0292">my goodness yes</u>
<u n="440" who="S0282">but erm but no she was absolutely beautiful every boy in <anon type="place"/> wanted to go out with her and every week she had a different <unclear/> so one week it would be she was writing someone's name on in her rough book and then the next week it would be rubbed out with pencil and somebody else's name would go</u>
<u n="441" who="S0292">uhu</u>
<u n="442" who="S0282">you know but</u>
<u n="443" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0282">and then every time</u>
<u n="445" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0292">oh yes yes</u>
<u n="447" who="S0293"><unclear/> very strange person</u>
<u n="448" who="S0292">it's interesting isn't it because he's not</u>
<u n="449" who="S0293">it's the voice</u>
<u n="450" who="S0292">yes</u>
<u n="451" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="452" who="S0292">I can believe that yes yes well I think voices are one of the sexiest things about a person</u>
<u n="453" who="S0293">oh without any doubt</u>
<u n="454" who="S0282">does he</u>
<u n="455" who="S0292">I think it's the voice that I would always fall for</u>
<u n="456" who="S0293">oh me too absolutely</u>
<u n="457" who="S0292">yes</u>
<u n="458" who="S0293">in fact people with horrible voices as <unclear>Ray Charlotte</unclear> said I'm not racist I'm voiceist</u>
<u n="459" who="S0292">yes</u>
<u n="460" who="S0282">if people have horrible voices I don't like them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0292">but it's and he does I suppose have a certain I don't know there is something about him which is attractive albeit he's not physically</u>
<u n="462" who="S0282"><unclear/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0292">attractive</u>
<u n="464" who="S0282"><unclear/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0292">yes yes that's a nice sort isn't it? I I don't know I've never heard it of a man</u>
<u n="466" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0292">but there's really no reason why not</u>
<u n="468" who="S0282">no <unclear/> as well <unclear/> he's he played a villain and he had his hair all sort of stuck down</u>
<u n="469" who="S0292">mm</u>
<u n="470" who="S0282">and he was just so ugly but there was something really mesmerizing</u>
<u n="471" who="S0292">mm</u>
<u n="472" who="S0282">so I said oh there's something about him</u>
<u n="473" who="S0292">who <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="474" who="S0282">no erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0292">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0293">I have these great attractions to people I don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0292">oh this wasn't television this was film oh yes he was a wonderful French</u>
<u n="479" who="S0282">the Virginian when I was ten I thought he was great</u>
<u n="480" who="S0292">yes I remember the vaguely I don't think I ever watched it but erm</u>
<u n="481" who="S0282">he was in what's the that film Pollyanna</u>
<u n="482" who="S0293">was he?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0282">yeah he was in that I went like oh my god it's the it's the Virginian</u>
<u n="484" who="S0292">mind you most of the young men that I fell for in films later to my absolute dismay because I fell for them in my teens and early twenties have turned out to be gay and I felt it was such a blow people like erm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0282">well Cary Grant</u>
<u n="486" who="S0292">yes and all the people like that</u>
<u n="487" who="S0282">Rock Hudson</u>
<u n="488" who="S0292">oh</u>
<u n="489" who="S0282">there's another one as well</u>
<u n="490" who="S0292">there was a splendid Englishman who turned out to be gay and I thought the world of him</u>
<u n="491" who="S0282">I know</u>
<u n="492" who="S0292">yes</u>
<u n="493" who="S0282"><unclear/> wrong</u>
<u n="494" who="S0292">I know</u>
<u n="495" who="S0293">what?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0282">a female companion who you masquerades as your girlfriend so that erm presumably who Doris Day was with apparently <unclear/> people's girlfriends</u>
<u n="497" who="S0292">oh did she yes because of who she was gay yes yes that would work couldn't it?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0282">yeah so so erm they had to <trunc>manufac</trunc> well in those days the studios manufactured your social life for you there was only people like Errol Flynn who insisted on actually you know doing his own thing and going his own way and getting himself into big trouble</u>
<u n="499" who="S0292">so was he gay?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0282">no he was he was very much not gay</u>
<u n="501" who="S0292">I thought not</u>
<u n="502" who="S0282">very much gay not but erm who was the other one? erm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0292"><unclear/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0282">no no he was married</u>
<u n="505" who="S0292">I suspect he's not there was a lovely one he he's in he was English erm and he was in a wonderful film about Vienna Venice</u>
<u n="506" who="S0282">oh ah yes yes yes yes yes erm what's his face erm oh Lawrence <unclear/> was Lawrence <unclear/> oh then who is it? erm oh what's his name?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0292">wonderful actor</u>
<u n="508" who="S0282">yes Death in Venice</u>
<u n="509" who="S0292">Death in Venice</u>
<u n="510" who="S0282">erm the caretaker erm</u>
<u n="511" who="S0292">yes that's the one</u>
<u n="512" who="S0282">erm erm</u>
<u n="513" who="S0292">it's ridiculous his name is gone</u>
<u n="514" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="515" who="S0292">and he was my absolute pin-up</u>
<u n="516" who="S0282">really</u>
<u n="517" who="S0292">and I was devastated and I didn't hear about it until I was in my forties</u>
<u n="518" who="S0282">early thirties suave man</u>
<u n="519" who="S0292">yes yes</u>
<u n="520" who="S0282">end on that note <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0293"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="522" who="S0292"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
