<text id="SKCY">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:58:50</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-19</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0004 S0014 S0018</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Relocating, food, relationships, weather, education, jobs, friends, internet dating, health, religion, socialising</topics>
		<activity>Friends and flatmates talking while having lunch.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T03</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0004">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace></birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Germany</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Engineer</occupation>
				<socgrade>C2</socgrade>
				<nssec>5</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0014">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hereford, Herefordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Journalist</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0018">so you can work in London? And he can find a job in London can he?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> every yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I think the other option is we stay here and I take redundancy and then probably take a lower paid job <pause dur="short"/> but we might be happier because we're here <pause dur="short"/> but erm we haven't really talked about it like properly in terms of we need to make a decision now <pause dur="short"/> at the moment it's just kind of well er these are our options</u>
<u n="3" who="S0018">what shall we do? What shall we do?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0014" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0018">it's a difficult one though isn't it?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0014">I know <pause dur="short"/> it is like quality of life versus like money really I guess</u>
<u n="7" who="S0018" trans="overlap">exactly <pause dur="short"/> but not only I think it's the pace of life in London too</u>
<u n="8" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0018">I mean I</u>
<u n="10" who="S0014">I think if it had been ten years ago we would have both said yeah let's do it <pause dur="short"/> thank you <pause dur="short"/> cheers <pause dur="short"/> but yeah like now we're in our thirties we don't really want to make that kind of move really</u>
<u n="11" who="S0018">how I mean how far out of London can you live so that it's not actually really London living?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0014">erm it depends like basically the BBC will give me a relocation package</u>
<u n="13" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0014">so they'd help me sell my house and help finance a move <pause dur="short"/> but if I did that I'd have to live within a thirty mile radius of where I'd be working which is central London</u>
<u n="15" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="16" who="S0014">so I could say no I don't want any financial help <pause dur="short"/> I'll do it myself and then I could live wherever I wanted</u>
<u n="17" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="18" who="S0014">and then I thought well I could commute it from <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> but then I thought well I could probably do it for a couple of months <pause dur="short"/> thanks but er that would take its toll I think</u>
<u n="19" who="S0018">would you miss <anon type="place"/>? Do you actually like living here?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0014">erm well all my friends are here <pause dur="short"/> and I think it's just ideal because it's not far from my mum and dad <pause dur="short"/> they're an hour away <pause dur="short"/> my friends are all here</u>
<u n="21" who="S0018">how far is Hereford from</u>
<u n="22" who="S0014">from London?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0018">London?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0014">be over three hours</u>
<u n="25" who="S0018">oh gosh really?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0014">between three and four hours I think</u>
<u n="27" who="S0018">is it that far?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0018">oh I guess cos London's more east to the east isn't it</u>
<u n="30" who="S0014" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm this is good</u>
<u n="31" who="S0018">do you like it?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0018">it might need a bit of salt and a bit of pepper</u>
<u n="34" who="S0014">oh it's really yummy <pause dur="short"/> what have you put in it?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0018">ooh er</u>
<u n="36" who="S0014">I can taste carrot</u>
<u n="37" who="S0018">yep carrot parsnip potatoes sweet potatoes celery onion</u>
<u n="38" who="S0014">mm <pause dur="short"/> yum</u>
<u n="39" who="S0018">I think that's it</u>
<u n="40" who="S0014">I need to start making soup more</u>
<u n="41" who="S0018">but it's so easy <pause dur="short"/> honestly I me and my mum went for a coffee at about half past ten <pause dur="short"/> we got back here at twelve <pause dur="short"/> I just chop chop chopped <pause dur="short"/> whacked it in a big saucepan with some boiling water</u>
<u n="42" who="S0014">oh wow and that's it?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and twenty minutes later I just whizzed it all up</u>
<u n="44" who="S0014">God <pause dur="short"/> very easy and very healthy</u>
<u n="45" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="46" who="S0014">Cos I need to start being more healthy</u>
<u n="47" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0014">well me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went to Malta for a week</u>
<u n="49" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="50" who="S0014">and we were just like right we're not gonna worry about food or anything cos we're both prone to like putting on weight and stuff <pause dur="short"/> we just thought well we'll just eat what we want <pause dur="short"/> and I like put on like half a stone in a week <pause dur="short"/> I was devastated</u>
<u n="51" who="S0018">ah it's holiday though</u>
<u n="52" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Another benefit like now we need to rein it in <pause dur="short"/> not eat out so much</u>
<u n="53" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0018">ah well you're still going through that honeymoon period aren't you <pause dur="short"/> you probably want to go oh romantic candlelit dinners</u>
<u n="55" who="S0014">oh I've never done that</u>
<u n="56" who="S0018">no?</u>
<u n="57" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0014">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't think either of us are really that romantic really</u>
<u n="59" who="S0018">so how long was it since you dated and started to realise that you actually?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0014">it all happened really fast actually</u>
<u n="61" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0014">I'd say within three weeks we were like we were kind of talked about not moving in straight away but we were kind of like yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0018">oh wow</u>
<u n="64" who="S0014">we can see this going somewhere <pause dur="short"/> and we can see us living together and getting married and stuff <pause dur="short"/> and that was within within three weeks definitely</u>
<u n="65" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0018">and has he met the Boodhoos?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0014">mm <pause dur="short"/> even that <pause dur="short"/> within two months we'd done all the family stuff</u>
<u n="69" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="70" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0018">do your parents love him?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0014">mm they do <pause dur="short"/> they really like him</u>
<u n="73" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0014">so yeah I remember at the time everyone was going oh this is going too fast <pause dur="short"/> it's not gonna last but we were just like you know if it feels right just go with it</u>
<u n="75" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="76" who="S0014">there's no point</u>
<u n="77" who="S0018">yeah yeah yep</u>
<u n="78" who="S0014">saying oh no let's not do this cos you know it's too fast <pause dur="short"/> and it you know eight months later it's still great so</u>
<u n="79" who="S0018">well there's no little rule book is there? It's</u>
<u n="80" who="S0014">no</u>
<u n="81" who="S0018">as you say how things go naturally and</u>
<u n="82" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0018">important to go with the flow</u>
<u n="84" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0018">and where's he from?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0014">erm he's from the <anon type="place"/> originally</u>
<u n="87" who="S0018">ha <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> lovely</u>
<u n="88" who="S0014">yeah so we had a really nice like few days down there when we went to see his parents</u>
<u n="89" who="S0018">oh that's a beautiful place <pause dur="short"/> whereabouts are his parents?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0014">erm <pause dur="short"/> a place called <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> which is kind of like literally just on the as the <anon type="place"/> actually starts</u>
<u n="91" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="92" who="S0014">it's like a little village</u>
<u n="93" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0014">like you could probably walk to the  to the  actual inter-forest from there</u>
<u n="95" who="S0018">is that quite close to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0014">it's closer to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="98" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0018">yeah my dad's got a little  a little  boat down near well it's basically just opposite the Isle of White</u>
<u n="100" who="S0014">oh okay that's probably close then</u>
<u n="101" who="S0018">so he's he sees the <anon type="place"/> when he's out on his boat</u>
<u n="102" who="S0014">mm <pause dur="short"/> hmm mm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0018">when my aunt she used to erm her husband was a farmer so she used to breed horses on the farm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0014">oh wow</u>
<u n="105" who="S0018">and they used to take their horses down to the <anon type="place"/> to</u>
<u n="106" who="S0014">ah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0018">to gallop around on holiday</u>
<u n="108" who="S0014">so how are you finding it being back in England?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> alright</u>
<u n="110" who="S0014">do you miss Spain?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0018">I miss the weather</u>
<u n="112" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0018">I miss the passion</u>
<u n="114" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0018">but there's a lot of things that England has that Spain doesn't</u>
<u n="116" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it must be nice being around family and friends like and seeing them</u>
<u n="117" who="S0018">definitely</u>
<u n="118" who="S0014">all the time</u>
<u n="119" who="S0018">it is really nice <pause dur="short"/> another good thing about Spain is that it's always there</u>
<u n="120" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ha yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0018">yeah I'm trying to get in a little visit <pause dur="short"/> I need a bit of sun</u>
<u n="123" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0018">just to feel the sun like this for example this morning if it was like this every day <pause dur="short"/> it's just the light and the warmth</u>
<u n="125" who="S0014">how how did you find the winter then that must have been tough</u>
<u n="126" who="S0018">well it <trunc>w</trunc> it wasn't too bad because it has been quite a mild winter</u>
<u n="127" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0018">when I got into December I was thinking I can handle this <pause dur="short"/> I can handle this <pause dur="short"/> and then I started going to everybody oh I'm alright <pause dur="short"/> I can handle British winters <pause dur="short"/> and they were like this is not a British winter <pause dur="short"/> this is the mildest it has been for years <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0014">mm <pause dur="short"/> you should have been here the winter before <pause dur="short"/> you would not have survived</u>
<u n="130" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> But you know little by little <pause dur="short"/> see how it ends up</u>
<u n="131" who="S0014">are you still speaking Spanish much then? Or have you not spoken any for a while?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0018">no actually I've not <pause dur="short"/> well obviously because I was doing the PGCE I was teaching Spanish</u>
<u n="133" who="S0014" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0018">so I was still kind of thinking about it but I mean teaching Spanish at secondary school</u>
<u n="135" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0018">there's not much teaching or Spanish involved <pause dur="short"/> it's more like sit down <pause dur="short"/> stop trying to body slam him in the corner</u>
<u n="137" who="S0014">oh God</u>
<u n="138" who="S0018">come on sit down</u>
<u n="139" who="S0014">oh my God</u>
<u n="140" who="S0018">sit down <pause dur="short"/> am I gonna have to put you on report? Okay you in the other corner <pause dur="short"/> stop <pause dur="short"/> stop jabbing the pencil up his nose <pause dur="short"/> health and safety issues</u>
<u n="141" who="S0014"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Does does anyone want to learn?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0018">um <pause dur="short"/> there were a few kids in each class that were actually you could see they were very sparky and you could engage them</u>
<u n="143" who="S0014" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0018">but the thing is once you've engaged the kids that you know are open to it</u>
<u n="145" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0018">you've got all the ones that are playing up and have got anger management issues or</u>
<u n="147" who="S0014">God</u>
<u n="148" who="S0018">visual impairment <pause dur="short"/> or hearing impairment or</u>
<u n="149" who="S0014">that sounds really tough</u>
<u n="150" who="S0018">it is tough because you're dealing with so many variables in the one class</u>
<u n="151" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0018">that er as soon as you've engaged one of the groups you lose all the others <pause dur="short"/> and then it's like forever juggling <pause dur="short"/> and it wasn't that er I don't know I I seem to remember my classes when I was at secondary school <pause dur="short"/> because we were streamed they were a lot more homogeneous</u>
<u n="153" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0018">so it was only really a handful of naughty boys that used to distract the class</u>
<u n="155" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0018">but in the schools that I've seen and the schools that you know my colleagues were telling me it's it's not it's now it's only a handful of kids that you can actually work you know teach</u>
<u n="157" who="S0014" trans="overlap">oh God</u>
<u n="158" who="S0018">and it's the rest it's all crowd control and <pause dur="short"/> it's sole destroying <pause dur="short"/> it really is</u>
<u n="159" who="S0014">do you think you'll go back to it?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> it is my back up plan</u>
<u n="161" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0018">I mean having done the training in inner city <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's not really a microcosm of all the schools that exist</u>
<u n="163" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0018">I'm sure that there are schools that that you don't have to handle that amount of misbehaviour and <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know <pause dur="short"/> if I find a job working with adults I think I'd much prefer doing that</u>
<u n="165" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0018">and cos I'm <trunc>learn</trunc> I'm targeting like erm English Language Teaching <pause dur="short"/> publishing and</u>
<u n="167" who="S0014">oh okay</u>
<u n="168" who="S0018">that's why a lot of the jobs are coming up are in Oxford</u>
<u n="169" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0018">I think if you're targeting publishing it's Oxford Cambridge or London really</u>
<u n="171" who="S0014" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0018">erm <pause dur="short"/> so we'll see what happens <pause dur="short"/> I've just heard that I haven't got an interview for one of the jobs I went for</u>
<u n="173" who="S0014">okay</u>
<u n="174" who="S0018">but that was I think quite normal because I phoned the guy in Human Resources and asked him about this particular job that I couldn't work out whether it was in Oxford or Madrid <pause dur="short"/> and it ended up that it was in Madrid</u>
<u n="175" who="S0018" trans="overlap">but I kind of took that opportunity to just quickly tell him my experience and ask him a bit of advice</u>
<u n="176" who="S0014" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0018">and he was like look you know just because it says we require sales and marketing experience</u>
<u n="178" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0018">if there's one or two things on the requirements list that you don't have send your CV in anyway because</u>
<u n="180" who="S0014">okay</u>
<u n="181" who="S0018">you never know <pause dur="short"/> so it was one of those situations</u>
<u n="182" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0018">I didn't  I didn't  think that I think I might have got an interview had they only had like three people</u>
<u n="184" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0018">ha ha but I don't think in this day and age they only get three people</u>
<u n="186" who="S0014">no that's true <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0018">applying <pause dur="short"/> I think they get three hundred people applying for the</u>
<u n="188" who="S0014">mm <pause dur="short"/> what about teaching in sixth forms? Or do you still need to do the whole PGCE thing for that?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="190" who="S0014">do you?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0014">oh</u>
<u n="193" who="S0018">I did er teach in sixth form too because there were erm most schools nowadays have their own little sixth form</u>
<u n="194" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0018">and it was generally nicer because they were smaller classes</u>
<u n="196" who="S0014">and they wanna be there don't they I guess?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0018">they still don't wanna be there</u>
<u n="198" who="S0014">oh don't they?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0018">no no no no</u>
<u n="200" who="S0014">oh</u>
<u n="201" who="S0018">they still didn't wanna be there <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0014">God <pause dur="short"/> cos I just think once you get to sixth form</u>
<u n="203" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0014">you know it's a kind of a choice isn't it? Cos you don't have to go <pause dur="short"/> so you kind of think the people there</u>
<u n="205" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0014">want to learn</u>
<u n="207" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean there were a couple of very good students in that class <pause dur="short"/> but again it's it's such a shame that you you're distracted from the very good students by the ones who er just disrupt everything</u>
<u n="208" who="S0014" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> god</u>
<u n="209" who="S0018">it's such a shame <pause dur="short"/> it really is</u>
<u n="210" who="S0014" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0018">and of course I'm going into it off fourteen years teaching</u>
<u n="212" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0018">effectively not because I'm an effective teacher but because the <trunc>s</trunc> the students that I've had have been you know obviously there's always kids are always gonna act up a little bit aren't they but</u>
<u n="214" who="S0014">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0018">these kids were at least motivated to be there <pause dur="short"/> because you could I found a lot that my personality in the classroom would motivate them</u>
<u n="216" who="S0014">okay</u>
<u n="217" who="S0018">because if you're energetic and enthusiastic</u>
<u n="218" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="219" who="S0018">and you know you make them laugh and you get them to do the work</u>
<u n="220" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0018">and you get them to see that they can actually do it <pause dur="short"/> and all those things together motivates them to continue and motivates them to progress</u>
<u n="222" who="S0014" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0018">but if you go into a secondary school class of thirty kids who don't want to be there <pause dur="short"/> who have no idea</u>
<u n="224" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0018">why learning languages would be important <pause dur="short"/> erm if you go in there with an enthusiastic bubbly personality all positive and la la la okay how are you? Rar rar rar rar cmo estás hoy? They just sit there and think oh what is she doing?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0014"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0018">and you know make fun of the teacher <pause dur="short"/> and they've got no respect for you</u>
<u n="228" who="S0014">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0018">and then you've just started off completely on the wrong foot with them</u>
<u n="230" who="S0014">God <pause dur="short"/> cos it's difficult to know how to kind of sort of kind of take it then</u>
<u n="231" who="S0018">well you just have to be really disciplinarian and serious</u>
<u n="232" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="233" who="S0018">gage the class and maybe ease off on the whole seriousness</u>
<u n="234" who="S0014">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="235" who="S0018">oh it's just such a shame <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0014">hmm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0018">it really is <pause dur="short"/> so yeah if I don't' find anything else I'll finish the course at least</u>
<u n="238" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> would you have to start again or can you?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0018">no I'd only have to take it up from January</u>
<u n="240" who="S0014">oh that's good</u>
<u n="241" who="S0018">the stuff I've already done counts</u>
<u n="242" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0018">but I think it was a bad time for me to do it really cos I I'd just I pretty much had a year of full on intense work</u>
<u n="244" who="S0014">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0018">without without holidays and went straight from you know full on intense work in Spain to the day that I finished my job I moved back to England <pause dur="short"/> I moved all my life back to England and then the day after I moved my life back to England I started</u>
<u n="246" who="S0014">oh my God</u>
<u n="247" who="S0018">I know so I think maybe with a bit more</u>
<u n="248" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it might be easier this time then because you've had a bit of mental space as well and</u>
<u n="249" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> and the whole adapting to another culture cos</u>
<u n="250" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0018">England has changed so much since I left <pause dur="short"/> it is kind of like coming back to a foreign country in a way</u>
<u n="252" who="S0014">is it? God mm</u>
<u n="253" who="S0018">but you'll probably get that if you move to London as well</u>
<u n="254" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0018">it's like a different country <pause dur="short"/> a really different way of living <pause dur="short"/> a different rhythm</u>
<u n="256" who="S0014" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> cos I've I've gone I've lived there twice <pause dur="short"/> just like short term for work <pause dur="short"/> like the first time I I did it for eight months and the second time was for three months <pause dur="short"/> and both times there was nothing that kept me there <pause dur="short"/> I I just felt like I wanted to come back <pause dur="short"/> I just felt like I I'm earning the same money as that in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> but it's not going as far</u>
<u n="257" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0014">and I'm working longer hours <pause dur="short"/> just commuting all the time <pause dur="short"/> and I just thought I don't' really get the benefits of working here at all</u>
<u n="259" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> will they readjust your salary to London weighting?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0014">yeah they would <pause dur="short"/> though but that's only like three thousand five hundred on top <pause dur="short"/> which is still good but</u>
<u n="261" who="S0018">it doesn't reflect the</u>
<u n="262" who="S0014">it doesn't cover kind of you know tube fares and</u>
<u n="263" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0014">and all that</u>
<u n="265" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> and now the government are trying to pay people less than other places that's</u>
<u n="266" who="S0014" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's a bit crazy</u>
<u n="267" who="S0018">it is crazy <pause dur="short"/> especially when you consider that you know when you're shopping for food and when you're buying petrol</u>
<u n="268" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0018">and when you're paying the rent and pay like paying bills and stuff it's not significantly</u>
<u n="270" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0018">cheaper in the areas that they wanna pay people minimum wages</u>
<u n="272" who="S0014">yeah yeah I know</u>
<u n="273" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> it sounds really dodge <pause dur="short"/> do you want some more soup?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0014">I'm alright thanks actually</u>
<u n="275" who="S0018">there's loads left</u>
<u n="276" who="S0014">erm the other option is Salford though cos you know loads of Fiat jobs are moving up there</u>
<u n="277" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0014">so I can look into erm redeployment and and see if there's any work in Salford <pause dur="short"/> so that's another option which it's kind of maybe like a happy medium really <pause dur="short"/> it's</u>
<u n="279" who="S0018">yeah?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0014">it's a bit more like <anon type="place"/> there <pause dur="short"/> not so expensive to live <pause dur="short"/> and Matt's seen some jobs there that he wouldn't mind applying for</u>
<u n="281" who="S0018">what kind of things is he looking for?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0014">erm just charity work still <pause dur="short"/> so working within the charity sector sector doing erm research</u>
<u n="283" who="S0018">what was his PhD in?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0014">history</u>
<u n="285" who="S0018">what particular part?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0014">erm <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember now</u>
<u n="287" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0014">it was something to do with the working class sailors of Southampton in the early nineteen hundreds</u>
<u n="289" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh wow <pause dur="short"/> mm hm</u>
<u n="290" who="S0014">that was <pause dur="short"/> yeah well that was his PhD <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what he kind of specialised in though</u>
<u n="291" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0018">so in the <trunc>char</trunc> is this the first charity he's worked for?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="295" who="S0014">and he got that on the basis of erm he well actually he started off as a an advisor <pause dur="short"/> so it was just a temp job</u>
<u n="296" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0014">and then he's kind of worked himself up from there really</u>
<u n="298" who="S0018">oh super</u>
<u n="299" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0018">yeah I've heard of quite a few people who have erm got their careers out of temp jobs</u>
<u n="301" who="S0014">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="302" who="S0018">well is that something that he he went into quite early though? The temp job early in his career?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0014">erm well he's er no only about three years ago</u>
<u n="304" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="305" who="S0014">yeah so he would have been late twenties</u>
<u n="306" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh that's <trunc>ex</trunc> it's kind of exciting having options at least you know</u>
<u n="307" who="S0014">mm I guess so</u>
<u n="308" who="S0018">you've got options <unclear/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0014" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's just a bit scary because I just you know I guess <trunc>no</trunc> nothing's ever going to be easy <pause dur="short"/> I just thought you know we would have been together a year and then think about getting married and buy a house <pause dur="short"/> but actually there's so much more to think about now <pause dur="short"/> but I dunno like we're not gonna buy a house until we know where I'm gonna work and <pause dur="short"/> and we probably wouldn't be able to afford to buy I don't think</u>
<u n="310" who="S0018">really? Not even with two salaries?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0014">yeah maybe <pause dur="short"/> I still don't think we'd get erm a house as nice as we would get here</u>
<u n="312" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="313" who="S0014">like I own a four bedroom house in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> like there's <trunc>ap</trunc> there's no way I'll get er that flat in London for the same money</u>
<u n="314" who="S0018" trans="overlap">is that  is that  the one in Bearwood?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="316" who="S0018">oh okay the one that you rent out?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0014">yeah it's me and two other guys</u>
<u n="318" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="319" who="S0014">who yeah rent rooms</u>
<u n="320" who="S0018">so are you thinking of moving in together in interim</u>
<u n="321" who="S0014">mm <pause dur="short"/> in the next year I reckon <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="323" who="S0014">well I'd like to get married next year if I'm honest</u>
<u n="324" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> only cos I wanna I'd like to start a family soon</u>
<u n="326" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0014">Cos I just think I don't wanna leave it too much later <pause dur="short"/> but I wanna get married before I have kids</u>
<u n="328" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0014">which I've told him that so he knows that it has to be soon</u>
<u n="330" who="S0018">have you heard heard <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s news?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0014">no <pause dur="short"/> is she getting married? No way</u>
<u n="332" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0014">oh my God</u>
<u n="334" who="S0018">she's getting married at Christmas <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0014">that's really soon <pause dur="short"/> wow when did he propose then?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0018">erm I think when they went to India</u>
<u n="337" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0018">they were talking about having kids and and I think he <trunc>profe</trunc> proposed formally quite recently <pause dur="short"/> a couple of weeks ago or something but</u>
<u n="339" who="S0014" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> where are they gonna get married?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0018">erm up <pause dur="short"/> she did tell me <pause dur="short"/> up in the Cotswolds</u>
<u n="341" who="S0014">okay</u>
<u n="342" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think instead of having like a big huge ceremony they're going to have a a whole week in this beautiful house that they've rented in the country</u>
<u n="343" who="S0014" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0018">of just party cos it's over Christmas as well</u>
<u n="345" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0018">just getting his family cos he's French</u>
<u n="347" who="S0014">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0018">so they have to come from France <pause dur="short"/> and and her family are from all over the the British Isles and</u>
<u n="349" who="S0014">ah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0018">friends <pause dur="short"/> keep it low key</u>
<u n="351" who="S0014">I mean er they're not is there not not gong to be like a Sikh wedding or anything?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0018">there's going to be erm a registry civil wedding</u>
<u n="353" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="354" who="S0018">for the legal aspects</u>
<u n="355" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0018">and then they're gonna have a Sikh er ceremony as well so</u>
<u n="357" who="S0014" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0018">for that day he will be</u>
<u n="359" who="S0014">wow</u>
<u n="360" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0018">ah and the dress she showed me was amazing</u>
<u n="362" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="363" who="S0018">so</u>
<u n="364" who="S0014">indian style?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like pale goldy peachy erm kind of like a wrap wrap over</u>
<u n="366" who="S0014">wow</u>
<u n="367" who="S0018">over her shoulders</u>
<u n="368" who="S0014">and she's got like the right height and the right figure to carry off stuff like that</u>
<u n="369" who="S0018">she's gorgeous isn't she?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="371" who="S0018">yeah so but I'm not sure if she's wanting to spend that much money on a dress that you'll wear for one day</u>
<u n="372" who="S0014" trans="overlap">yeah yep one day</u>
<u n="373" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0018">are you sure you don't want some more soup? There's loads left</u>
<u n="376" who="S0014" trans="overlap">no I'm alright <pause dur="short"/> I might just have a bit more bread and some cheese</u>
<u n="377" who="S0018">mm go for it</u>
<u n="378" who="S0014">Cos it's really yummy that bread</u>
<u n="379" who="S0018">it is <pause dur="short"/> well this is  this is  his bread</u>
<u n="380" who="S0014">is it the same one? Oh is it?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0018">well she's marrying</u>
<u n="382" who="S0014">oh God yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0018">the guy who owns that bakery</u>
<u n="384" who="S0014">of course</u>
<u n="385" who="S0018">the little French café and</u>
<u n="386" who="S0014">oh my God</u>
<u n="387" who="S0018">so this is his bread</u>
<u n="388" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="389" who="S0018">funnily enough</u>
<u n="390" who="S0014">the last time I saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> actually <pause dur="short"/> I was sent to erm Cambridge to do a story so we met for a coffee before I went to do my interviews</u>
<u n="391" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="392" who="S0014">and it was two days before my date with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0014">Cos I was like oh yeah I've got this internet date <pause dur="short"/> I'm a bit nervous <pause dur="short"/> like I haven't spoken to her since so she probably doesn't even know that I'm actually with this guy</u>
<u n="395" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="396" who="S0018">how things happen</u>
<u n="397" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0018">and was he did you meet him quite soon after you'd erm signed up to the <trunc>app</trunc> internet site?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0014" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> this is why I recommend the site <pause dur="short"/> I joined the site on erm like the Sunday <pause dur="short"/> he messaged me on the Tuesday <pause dur="short"/> and we met on the Saturday <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't even on it a week</u>
<u n="400" who="S0018">blimey</u>
<u n="401" who="S0014">I know it was really bad</u>
<u n="402" who="S0018">was he the first date that you had off it as well?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0014">yeah first of anyone <pause dur="short"/> I I messaged loads of other guys</u>
<u n="404" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="405" who="S0014">who were potentials as well</u>
<u n="406" who="S0018"><unclear/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0014">who you know were really nice and stuff</u>
<u n="408" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0014">but erm yeah so he was the first one</u>
<u n="410" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0018">and did you put your photo up on the site then?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0018">were you not worried that people in the office would see you or?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0014">no cos I think people knew anyway that I was dating and internet dating and stuff</u>
<u n="415" who="S0018">oh right <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="416" who="S0014">so yeah it all happened really quickly</u>
<u n="417" who="S0018">and how long had he been on there previously to?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0014">he'd probably been on there a couple of months <pause dur="short"/> he's he was actually he'd been seeing someone before me <pause dur="short"/> they'd only gone on like five or six dates and then it didn't work</u>
<u n="419" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="420" who="S0014">I think he had a date with one other girl as well <pause dur="short"/> but that was just a one one date thing <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I think he he'd been on there a bit longer <pause dur="short"/> but he was saying it er that from a man's point of view actually you can be on there a long time cos girls don't tend to message <pause dur="short"/> and then you might message someone and they don't really message back</u>
<u n="421" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="422" who="S0014">Cos I think it's the other way round for women <pause dur="short"/> ha men probably come across as a bit more desperate</u>
<u n="423" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="424" who="S0014">whereas girls like to play it cool <pause dur="short"/> and I guess want the man to message don't they <pause dur="short"/> they don't really what would they do?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0018" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I kind of  I kind of  prefer to be the person in control of who I get in touch with <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="427" who="S0018">did he get in touch with you or?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0014">mm <pause dur="short"/> well what had happened was cos you can click on people's profiles and they know if you've looked at your profile <pause dur="short"/> it'll say oh these people have looked at your profiles</u>
<u n="429" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="430" who="S0014">which I didn't know anyway <pause dur="short"/> so he messaged me and went oh I I see that you checked my profile today <pause dur="short"/> not really sure what you thought but I read your profile and you seem really nice <pause dur="short"/> and I was a bit mortified cos at that point I didn't know that people could tell that you looked at their profiles</u>
<u n="431" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0014">so I guess I kind of instigated it <pause dur="short"/> but I I can't remember his profile at all</u>
<u n="433" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="434" who="S0014">hello</u>
<u n="435" who="S0018" trans="overlap">hello <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0004">hello</u>
<u n="437" who="S0018">do you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0004">er I don't think we've met have we?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0014">I don't think we've we've met? No</u>
<u n="440" who="S0018">no? Well Dan's another internet dating success</u>
<u n="441" who="S0014">oh okay</u>
<u n="442" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0004"><unclear/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0018">do you want some soup Dan?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0004">er yeah I wouldn't say no <pause dur="short"/> yeah that'd be wicked</u>
<u n="446" who="S0018">help yourself <pause dur="short"/> it's in the erm pan on the side</u>
<u n="447" who="S0014">and then there's <pause dur="short"/> is everything happy with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and stuff or?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think ooh stuff at work is a bit weird still</u>
<u n="449" who="S0014" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="450" who="S0018">it's not easy living in a situation where you don't know where you're gonna be</u>
<u n="451" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah cos she's got it as well really <pause dur="short"/> like I don't think theirs is even they either don't have a job or they do</u>
<u n="452" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="453" who="S0014">like there's they're not moving anywhere I don't think are they?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0018">so what division are you with?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0014">well I'm Asian at work but news</u>
<u n="456" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0014">so news side and programme side they're two different</u>
<u n="458" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0014">so yeah I don't <pause dur="short"/> I think Indi will be alright just cos she's worked herself up and</u>
<u n="462" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="463" who="S0014">I I think she'll be fine on the job <pause dur="short"/> yep <unclear/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0018">but isn't there talk about completely getting rid of the <anon type="place"/> side of things?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0014">no I don't <pause dur="short"/> well they haven't said that</u>
<u n="466" who="S0018">no?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0014">they're getting rid of the Leicester side of things <pause dur="short"/> that's why my job's going</u>
<u n="468" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="469" who="S0014">yeah but <anon type="place"/> as far as I know it's staying</u>
<u n="470" who="S0018">can you not work from <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="471" who="S0014">no <pause dur="short"/> I mean I could but if they're getting rid of fifty percent of the staff anyway they're not gonna give me the job <pause dur="short"/> they'll any jobs that come up will go to those people who lose their jobs I think</u>
<u n="472" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> so your job will definitely move to London</u>
<u n="473" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0018">couldn't you work out some kind of thing whereby you stay in <anon type="place"/> and you do two or three days a week in London and?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0014">possibly <pause dur="short"/> but I just think everyone will wanna do that <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>th</trunc> like basically none of my team want to move <pause dur="short"/> they're all Midlands based</u>
<u n="476" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="477" who="S0014">so if he does that for me he'll have to do it for everyone and he's not gonna do that</u>
<u n="478" who="S0018">oh what a shame</u>
<u n="479" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but yeah none of us wanna go</u>
<u n="480" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> dilemma</u>
<u n="481" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean you know it's not as bad for me <pause dur="short"/> a lot  a lot  of the people in Leicester are married with kinds and stuff <pause dur="short"/> the kids are in school</u>
<u n="482" who="S0018">yep</u>
<u n="483" who="S0014">it's a lot harder for them</u>
<u n="484" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0014">but who knows <pause dur="short"/> I need to start looking for other jobs really <pause dur="short"/> cos at the moment I'm just moaning about not wanting to go but not actually doing anything to make it better</u>
<u n="486" who="S0018">what kind of thing would you be looking for?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0014">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> I have no idea <pause dur="short"/> matt and I wanted to set up our own business of some sort</u>
<u n="488" who="S0018">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0014">erm cos we were like well if I could take the redundancy and do that <pause dur="short"/> but it's just knowing what to do</u>
<u n="490" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="491" who="S0014">erm we like the idea of opening a restaurant but hope not not as a</u>
<u n="492" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0014">like we can't cook <pause dur="short"/> we'll have to get someone else to do the cooking</u>
<u n="494" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0014">we had talked about opening a Mauritian restaurant <pause dur="short"/> that's what we wanted to do <pause dur="short"/> and then last week that Mauritian girl won MasterChef so we were like well she's gonna do that now</u>
<u n="496" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="497" who="S0014">no one's gonna come to ours</u>
<u n="498" who="S0018" trans="overlap">is it in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0014">well it'll just look like we're jumping on the bandwagon now</u>
<u n="500" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> she you could see it as erm she gave you some good publicity</u>
<u n="501" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0014">maybe</u>
<u n="503" who="S0018">people will be up for Mauritian food now</u>
<u n="504" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0018">what's it like? Mauritian food?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0014">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's kind of like this cross between I guess African cooking and Indian cooking really</u>
<u n="507" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> lovely</u>
<u n="508" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="509" who="S0018">lovely lovely</u>
<u n="510" who="S0014">A lot of fish <pause dur="short"/> that cheese is nice</u>
<u n="511" who="S0018">it is nice isn't it? How was your run then?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0004">it was good <pause dur="short"/> yeah it was</u>
<u n="513" who="S0018">beautiful day for it</u>
<u n="514" who="S0004">it's a bit chilly</u>
<u n="515" who="S0018">you might have to warm it up <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it'll be hot warm enough for you</u>
<u n="516" who="S0004">I'll give it a blast in the microwave</u>
<u n="517" who="S0018">Good idea</u>
<u n="518" who="S0014">and so we need to organise some drinks really don't we and have a night out</u>
<u n="519" who="S0018">definitely</u>
<u n="520" who="S0014">I haven't seen <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for ages</u>
<u n="521" who="S0018">that er German restaurant that you were telling her about sounded good</u>
<u n="522" who="S0014">mm <pause dur="short"/> no er Austrian</u>
<u n="523" who="S0018">oh is it Austrian</u>
<u n="524" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="525" who="S0018">that sounded really cool</u>
<u n="526" who="S0014">it's brilliant</u>
<u n="527" who="S0018">have you been there?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> basically you wouldn't even know it's there <pause dur="short"/> it's just a residential street <pause dur="short"/> and it's someone's house that they've turned into a restaurant <pause dur="short"/> and you kind of walk in and you just feel like you're in Austria <pause dur="short"/> there's people like dressed up and stuff</u>
<u n="529" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="530" who="S0014">you go down into the basement and they've turned it into a bar and you're having drinks there <pause dur="short"/> so yeah it's really good</u>
<u n="531" who="S0018">and does it look like a does it look like someone's house?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0014">from the outside</u>
<u n="533" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="534" who="S0014">and like when you're inside it like it looks like a restaurant but you can kind of tell <pause dur="short"/> well this was the living room <pause dur="short"/> this obviously was like erm a kitchen area <pause dur="short"/> and they've just kind of turned it all into a restaurant inside</u>
<u n="535" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="536" who="S0014">yeah definitely worth going</u>
<u n="537" who="S0018">because I've I've heard of these places that erm people actually set up restaurants in their own homes</u>
<u n="538" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="539" who="S0018">but on a very small scale <pause dur="short"/> so when you go round you actually feel like your</u>
<u n="540" who="S0014">I'm in someone's house</u>
<u n="541" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="542" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0018">but it just sounds a bit a little bit weird</u>
<u n="544" who="S0014">yeah once you're in there it does look like a restaurant <pause dur="short"/> I don't even know cos I didn't think he'd be allowed to do it <pause dur="short"/> they obviously got some kind of licence</u>
<u n="545" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="546" who="S0014">so if they opened a restaurant like that on a residential street</u>
<u n="547" who="S0018">what's the food like?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0014">yeah really nice <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what I had now <pause dur="short"/> erm lots of meat though</u>
<u n="549" who="S0018" trans="overlap">but not not that memorable then</u>
<u n="550" who="S0014">yeah it's kind of like meat and veg and stuff but you just get a set menu so you have to have three courses</u>
<u n="551" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="552" who="S0014">but erm yeah it's definitely I think it's just such a weird experience being in there</u>
<u n="553" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="554" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I've ever tried Austrian food</u>
<u n="555" who="S0014">where did Indi take not Indi where did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she take <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in the end?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0018">ah to a lovely little restaurant called <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="557" who="S0014">ah</u>
<u n="558" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="559" who="S0018">I think they'd er he'd been in London for two days and</u>
<u n="560" who="S0014">oh okay</u>
<u n="561" who="S0018">she was knackered and and they just got home and said oh where do you wanna go out? And they were like oh shall we just get</u>
<u n="562" who="S0014">ah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0018">Sabai Sabai to deliver <pause dur="short"/> so they got a had a Thai Thai meal</u>
<u n="564" who="S0014" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="565" who="S0018">and just chilled at home</u>
<u n="566" who="S0014">ah</u>
<u n="567" who="S0018">which is lovely cos when you're er when you're knackered</u>
<u n="568" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="569" who="S0018" trans="overlap">and you've gotta go to work the next day and you're not really in the  in the  mood for it</u>
<u n="570" who="S0014" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> ha</u>
<u n="571" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit</u>
<u n="572" who="S0014">it must be nice having them so close</u>
<u n="573" who="S0018">definitely but she's actually been ill for a bit</u>
<u n="574" who="S0014" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="575" who="S0018">she's erm did you know she had to have her wedding ring cut off?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0014">no</u>
<u n="577" who="S0018">I think erm I don't know whether it was an allergic reaction to the ring</u>
<u n="578" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0018">or whether she had a bit of eczema under it <pause dur="short"/> and it all inflamed and luckily cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad's a goldsmith</u>
<u n="580" who="S0014">oh yeah</u>
<u n="581" who="S0018">he was able to cut it off <pause dur="short"/> and her mum who's a doctor said oh just um er put some Aloe vera on it and see if it gets any better</u>
<u n="582" who="S0014" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="583" who="S0018">and they were in India and it got better I think under the sun</u>
<u n="584" who="S0014">oh okay</u>
<u n="585" who="S0018">then when they came back it just flared up again to the extent where it got completely infected <pause dur="short"/> but not just her hand <pause dur="short"/> her whole system</u>
<u n="586" who="S0014">oh God</u>
<u n="587" who="S0018">got infected <pause dur="short"/> and she was like feeling hot and cold and vomitty <pause dur="short"/> she er nauseous <pause dur="short"/> vomitty? Ha ha</u>
<u n="588" who="S0014">she was feeling vomitty</u>
<u n="589" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0004">has that happened since last weekend?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0004">or was this before?</u>
<u n="593" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> it it had happened before and she'd had to have her wedding ring cut off about two months ago</u>
<u n="594" who="S0004">shit</u>
<u n="595" who="S0018">I know <pause dur="short"/> and I think  I think  that she might be home today off work again</u>
<u n="596" who="S0014">oh God</u>
<u n="597" who="S0018">Cos she's er her little car is on her little drive <pause dur="short"/> but she had to have</u>
<u n="598" who="S0014" trans="overlap">so they still don't know what caused it then?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0018">no they don't know <pause dur="short"/> whether it was a an allergic reaction to metal in the ring or</u>
<u n="600" who="S0014" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well surely she have got it before then <pause dur="short"/> cos she's worn that for years</u>
<u n="601" who="S0018">I have no idea</u>
<u n="602" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="603" who="S0018">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't think the doctors know even</u>
<u n="604" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="605" who="S0018">but they've given her anti-inflammatories and antibiotics</u>
<u n="606" who="S0014">oh okay</u>
<u n="607" who="S0018">and steroids and</u>
<u n="608" who="S0014">and she can't wear her ring at the moment</u>
<u n="609" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="610" who="S0014">ah</u>
<u n="611" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="612" who="S0018">they had all those jokes though when they had to cut it off <pause dur="short"/> it was like she cut off my wedding ring <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="613" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="614" who="S0018">she doesn't wanna be my wifey any more</u>
<u n="615" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="616" who="S0014">that must have been quite hard for them actually with the <unclear/> having your ring cut off</u>
<u n="617" who="S0018">I know</u>
<u n="618" who="S0014">but I guess he can put it back together again somehow</u>
<u n="619" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> no he can I think it's just you know like when you get your ring when your finger gets too big and</u>
<u n="620" who="S0014" trans="overlap">oh with that <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0018">you get it enlarged or</u>
<u n="622" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0018">I think it's easily done but it's more of the <trunc>symbol</trunc> the symbolic</u>
<u n="624" who="S0014" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> oh oh</u>
<u n="625" who="S0018">so where do you want to get married? Have you  have you  actually started?</u>
<u n="626" who="S0014" trans="overlap">in in Hereford</u>
<u n="627" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="628" who="S0014">this is the other thing though because my family are Catholic <pause dur="short"/> and I really wanna get married in a Catholic church but he just refuses</u>
<u n="629" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="630" who="S0014">he doesn't want to <pause dur="short"/> and I just think if I do want to get married soon I'm probably gonna have to back down on that cos I'm not going to convince him otherwise</u>
<u n="631" who="S0018">what is it you want about a Catholic church marriage?</u>
<u n="632" who="S0014">just because I dunno it's more of childhood thing <pause dur="short"/> like I just wanted to get married in the church I've always gone to and I still go to when I go back to Hereford and stuff and</u>
<u n="633" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0014">and it's a really lovely building and it's in a really <trunc>ni</trunc> nice part of Hereford <pause dur="short"/> but then I thought actually Hereford's so beautiful <pause dur="short"/> there's so many other places we could get married that would still be as nice</u>
<u n="635" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> what's he got against the church?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0014">he just doesn't really agree with Catholicism</u>
<u n="637" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="638" who="S0014">which is fair enough <pause dur="short"/> and I just though you know I'd rather get married to him in a place we're both happy and comfortable</u>
<u n="639" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="640" who="S0014">rather than making him go through a ceremony that he just doesn't want to do</u>
<u n="641" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="642" who="S0014">but</u>
<u n="643" who="S0018">that's weird cos I'm not religious but I wouldn't actually rule out getting married in a religious institution if it was gorgeous</u>
<u n="644" who="S0014" trans="overlap">yeah well I think it's cos cos it's the Catholic church</u>
<u n="645" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="646" who="S0014">if it was Church of England I don't think he'd have as many issues <pause dur="short"/> but he just he's like oh I don't like Catholicism <pause dur="short"/> it's like a cult <pause dur="short"/> so I think it's more cos it's a Catholic church</u>
<u n="647" who="S0018">and he's okay with you being Catholic?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0014">yeah yeah he's fine with that <pause dur="short"/> but I don't think he'd want our kids to be or anything</u>
<u n="649" who="S0018" trans="overlap">are you  are you  practising?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0014">yeah not so much any more <pause dur="short"/> I used to go all the time and now it tends to be just when I'm back with my parents when I go</u>
<u n="651" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="652" who="S0014">and but when I was travelling I went quite a bit <pause dur="short"/> just cos it I dunno it was just a weird thing is you know you all these prayers you know <pause dur="short"/> like that you've said since you were a kid <pause dur="short"/> and I just felt when I was away like going somewhere you know and having that familiar <trunc>a</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> you know it was like really familiar</u>
<u n="653" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> comforting</u>
<u n="654" who="S0014">yeah it was <pause dur="short"/> so yeah it was weird and I didn't think I would kind of go to church when I was away at all <pause dur="short"/> and I did</u>
<u n="655" who="S0018" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="656" who="S0014">but it's fine <pause dur="short"/> I've kind of got over the fact now we're not gonna have a Catholic wedding</u>
<u n="657" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> are you gonna still dress in white though?</u>
<u n="658" who="S0014">yeah yeah definitely</u>
<u n="659" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="660" who="S0014">erm but as long as it's in Hereford then I don't mind</u>
<u n="661" who="S0004">can I have a soup now?</u>
<u n="662" who="S0018">yeah go for it <pause dur="short"/> sorry I should have called you down earlier <pause dur="short"/> you could have had some</u>
<u n="663" who="S0004">no I've been doing stuff upstairs <pause dur="short"/> don't worry</u>
<u n="664" who="S0018">you missed out on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s bread sorry</u>
<u n="665" who="S0004">oh</u>
<u n="666" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="667" who="S0014">do they make it all there?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ac</trunc> actually I don't know <pause dur="short"/> do you know? Cos they've got three bakeries</u>
<u n="669" who="S0004">no they make it in town somewhere</u>
<u n="670" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="671" who="S0014" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="672" who="S0004">Cos they've got a bake the well a bakery I should think <pause dur="short"/> or a shed or something where they do it</u>
<u n="673" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> a shed?</u>
<u n="674" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="675" who="S0004">I don't know how to describe it <pause dur="short"/> like a warehouse or</u>
<u n="676" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we had um I took my mum for cake</u>
<u n="677" who="S0014">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> in that place?</u>
<u n="678" who="S0018">coffee and cake <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="679" who="S0014" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="680" who="S0018">and we had a</u>
<u n="681" who="S0004">did you have a citron?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0018">no we didn't cos we had lemon meringue pie yesterday so</u>
<u n="683" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="684" who="S0018">kind of citroned out <pause dur="short"/> would you like a piece of bread?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0014">oh go on then</u>
<u n="686" who="S0018">got to finish the  bit</u>
<u n="687" who="S0014" trans="overlap">thank you</u>
<u n="688" who="S0018">and we had the apricot tart</u>
<u n="689" who="S0004">that sounds</u>
<u n="690" who="S0018">and the apple and blackberry tart</u>
<u n="691" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="692" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> so gorgeous</u>
<u n="693" who="S0014">did your mum like it?</u>
<u n="694" who="S0018">she loved it <pause dur="short"/> cos it's er the pastry is shortcrust buttery pastry</u>
<u n="695" who="S0014">ah yum</u>
<u n="696" who="S0018">and it's got a lovely custard base to it <pause dur="short"/> and then the fruit and then a glaze that</u>
<u n="697" who="S0014">ah</u>
<u n="698" who="S0018">the fruit's so tangy <pause dur="short"/> and the custard's so milky and then the pastry's so crispy</u>
<u n="699" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="700" who="S0018">they've got a place in <anon type="place"/> now haven't they?</u>
<u n="701" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="702" who="S0018">I think that might have been the original one</u>
<u n="703" who="S0014">oh okay</u>
<u n="704" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="705" who="S0004">no the original one is already</u>
<u n="706" who="S0018">oh is it?</u>
<u n="707" who="S0004">and the <anon type="place"/> one is the newest one</u>
<u n="708" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="709" who="S0014">ah so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is going to be part of that empire</u>
<u n="710" who="S0018">she is <pause dur="short"/> and they've just opened a chocolate shop</u>
<u n="711" who="S0014">oh my God <pause dur="short"/> that's dangerous</u>
<u n="712" who="S0004">what's this rubbish?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0018">I think they have both erm both him and his brother have all the different venues together <pause dur="short"/> I get the feeling</u>
<u n="714" who="S0004">the <unclear/> national chain</u>
<u n="715" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="716" who="S0004"><unclear/></u>
<u n="717" who="S0014">didn't they just meet because she used to go in with her computer and he started talking to her?</u>
<u n="718" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> well it was about two or three years ago when you remember when <trunc>the</trunc> when there was loads and loads of snow?</u>
<u n="719" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="720" who="S0018">well she was on her was to work and just stopped in for a coffee but ended up getting snowed in at the café <pause dur="short"/> well she couldn't get to work</u>
<u n="721" who="S0014">hmm mm</u>
<u n="722" who="S0018">and so she just decided to work from the caé on her laptop <pause dur="short"/> and it was that day that he he met her</u>
<u n="723" who="S0014">wow</u>
<u n="724" who="S0018">it's like would you like a coffee or a cake? Or would you like to marry me?</u>
<u n="725" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="726" who="S0014">that's a proper romantic story</u>
<u n="727" who="S0018">it is isn't it <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> met her her bloke on erm internet</u>
<u n="728" who="S0004">wow</u>
<u n="729" who="S0014">did you as well meet your other half on internet dating?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0004">I've been on three dates with this girl <pause dur="short"/> this does not classify like being my girlfriend</u>
<u n="731" who="S0014" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="732" who="S0018">no but you seem very loved up</u>
<u n="733" who="S0004">well</u>
<u n="734" who="S0018">very excited about it</u>
<u n="735" who="S0004">I am but just playing a bit coy since Saturday night so</u>
<u n="736" who="S0014">what internet site did you use?</u>
<u n="737" who="S0004">match dot com</u>
<u n="738" who="S0014">oh okay</u>
<u n="739" who="S0004">and MSF</u>
<u n="740" who="S0014">oh yeah</u>
<u n="741" who="S0004">and I had got PlentyofFish but not any more</u>
<u n="742" who="S0014">I've heard bad things about friend with fish but I don't know if it's true <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="743" who="S0004" trans="overlap">it's just it was like just really not really I didn't find it very interactive</u>
<u n="744" who="S0014">oh okay</u>
<u n="745" who="S0004">er but these other two yeah I mean I've been on another four a couple of years ago <pause dur="short"/> and then on and off like a couple of months in the spring</u>
<u n="746" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="747" who="S0004">it kind of comes in fits and starts <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="748" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="749" who="S0004"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has definitely got a girlfriend now <unclear/></u>
<u n="750" who="S0014">oh</u>
<u n="751" who="S0018" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> is that it? It's all official and everything?</u>
<u n="752" who="S0004">well <unclear/> can say that <pause dur="short"/> I'm saying it <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="753" who="S0018" trans="overlap">has he changed his Facebook status? That must be official if he's done that</u>
<u n="754" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="755" who="S0004">I don't know</u>
<u n="756" who="S0014">I haven't even done that <pause dur="short"/> I refuse to</u>
<u n="757" who="S0004">I've not  I've not  spoken to him properly since last week cos he's been erm in Paddyland all weekend</u>
<u n="758" who="S0018">he's in Ireland isn't he? When is he back</u>
<u n="759" who="S0004">he's back <pause dur="short"/> he's at work</u>
<u n="760" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="761" who="S0004">got back last night</u>
<u n="762" who="S0018">was he?</u>
<u n="763" who="S0004">yeah</u>
<u n="764" who="S0018">I didn't see him</u>
<u n="765" who="S0004">you wouldn't cos he'd have been absolutely wasted and just gone straight to bed</u>
<u n="766" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="767" who="S0004">I was texting him this morning so he's awake <pause dur="short"/> can I sit down here? Is that alright?</u>
<u n="768" who="S0018">yes of course</u>
<u n="769" who="S0014">sorry</u>
<u n="770" who="S0018">that's all my stuff there <pause dur="short"/> there you are <pause dur="short"/> make a little space <pause dur="short"/> so what you gotta do before you go to personal training?</u>
<u n="771" who="S0014">just all my washing that I just wanna do before I go to Essex tomorrow</u>
<u n="772" who="S0018">what are you going to Essex for?</u>
<u n="773" who="S0014">my best friend lives there</u>
<u n="774" who="S0018">oh right okay</u>
<u n="775" who="S0014">so cos I work the weekend <pause dur="short"/> if I work a weekend I get Monday Tuesday Wednesday off</u>
<u n="776" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="777" who="S0014">so erm yeah I'm going down there for the next couple of days</u>
<u n="778" who="S0018">oh that's a good deal</u>
<u n="779" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well you kind of need it <pause dur="short"/> cos <trunc>you</trunc> it's six till six Saturday and Sunday if you're working weekends</u>
<u n="780" who="S0018">oof</u>
<u n="781" who="S0014">so it's hardcore</u>
<u n="782" who="S0018">and did you work the weekend on the back of having worked a full week as well?</u>
<u n="783" who="S0014">erm <pause dur="short"/> so if you do a weekend you get the Friday off and the Monday Tuesday Wednesday <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I had worked but I was off on the Friday</u>
<u n="784" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="785" who="S0014">so it's okay <pause dur="short"/> it's just you're in the office on your own for like basically twenty-four hours <pause dur="short"/> and you just go crazy cos there's just no one else to talk to</u>
<u n="786" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="787" who="S0014">and by about four o'clock on the Sunday you're going out of your mind</u>
<u n="788" who="S0018">six till six <pause dur="short"/> a twenty-four hour shift?</u>
<u n="789" who="S0014">six till six Saturday then six till six Sunday</u>
<u n="790" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="791" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> a twelve hour break in between</u>
<u n="792" who="S0018">blimey <pause dur="short"/> did you come back to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="793" who="S0014">I stayed with a friend in Leicester actually</u>
<u n="794" who="S0018">that's a better idea</u>
<u n="795" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="796" who="S0004">are you BBC one as well?</u>
<u n="797" who="S0014">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> so yeah the <unclear/></u>
<u n="798" who="S0004">I'm sure I might have met you</u>
<u n="799" who="S0014">maybe</u>
<u n="800" who="S0004">I think I have</u>
<u n="801" who="S0014">were you erm I met loads of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s housemates at that curry night at</u>
<u n="802" who="S0018">yeah you were there</u>
<u n="803" who="S0014" trans="overlap">were you there?</u>
<u n="804" who="S0018">you were on a different table weren't you?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0014">no no I wasn't eating <pause dur="short"/> I just came a bit late and I came and sat with</u>
<u n="806" who="S0018">yeah you were on that table</u>
<u n="807" who="S0014">I was sitting with you</u>
<u n="808" who="S0018">did you? No</u>
<u n="809" who="S0004">I went home early that night</u>
<u n="810" who="S0014">so maybe I missed you <pause dur="short"/> cos I came as everyone was eating</u>
<u n="811" who="S0018" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="812" who="S0004">Cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was on a table with her work colleagues and we were like on a table as the post-cricket lot</u>
<u n="813" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="814" who="S0018">hmm mm</u>
<u n="815" who="S0014">no cos I wasn't with either table I just came to say hello</u>
<u n="816" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="817" who="S0004">hmm</u>
<u n="818" who="S0018">I'm sure you might have met each other on other occasions though</u>
<u n="819" who="S0004">no I do remember that now</u>
<u n="820" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="821" who="S0018">have you seen? When was the last time you saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="822" who="S0014">last week at work yeah</u>
<u n="823" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="824" who="S0004">I've not seen her since last Saturday night <pause dur="short"/> have you?</u>
<u n="825" who="S0018">I saw her on this Friday just gone <pause dur="short"/> and she cooked dinner over at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="826" who="S0014">oh okay</u>
<u n="827" who="S0018">and um</u>
<u n="828" who="S0014">he lives in <anon type="place"/> doesn't he?</u>
<u n="829" who="S0018">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="830" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="831" who="S0018">that was the night we were  we were  deejaying in the  in the  lounge <pause dur="short"/> and then all of a sudden it was five o'clock in the morning and</u>
<u n="832" who="S0004">hmm mm</u>
<u n="833" who="S0018"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> whipped out a bottle of whiskey and</u>
<u n="834" who="S0014">oh my God</u>
<u n="835" who="S0018" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="836" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="837" who="S0018">I was like okay</u>
<u n="838" who="S0014">that reminds me of the night we were at er Halloween though <pause dur="short"/> it was a summer night and we were deejaying and then all of a sudden it was five in the morning</u>
<u n="839" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="840" who="S0018">where did we go out? We were back at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <unclear/> weren't we?</u>
<u n="841" who="S0014">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="842" who="S0004">we didn't see you that night cos me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went to <anon type="place"/> no <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="843" who="S0018">which night?</u>
<u n="844" who="S0004">halloween</u>
<u n="845" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="846" who="S0014" trans="overlap">oh we didn't go there</u>
<u n="847" who="S0018">no no</u>
<u n="848" who="S0014">oh no this was a couple of years</u>
<u n="849" who="S0018">it was the year before wasn't it?</u>
<u n="850" who="S0014" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="851" who="S0018">that was when we all got dressed up</u>
<u n="852" who="S0014">and gatecrashed parties</u>
<u n="853" who="S0018">we did</u>
<u n="854" who="S0014">we we went to someone's party but I don't know who it was</u>
<u n="855" who="S0018">we went to two different parties in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="856" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then came <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="857" who="S0018">And then yeah we went to <anon type="place"/> afterwards</u>
<u n="858" who="S0014">I've just got this brilliant picture when <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> with this erm Asda value beer</u>
<u n="859" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="860" who="S0014">which she was drinking at one of the parties</u>
<u n="861" who="S0018">do you remember that guy at the at <anon type="place"/> at the bar who was just sitting there snoring?</u>
<u n="862" who="S0014">oh yeah</u>
<u n="863" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="864" who="S0018">Cos everybody was like really animated and happy and drinking and dancing <pause dur="short"/> and there was this guy in the corner who was just fast asleep through all of it</u>
<u n="865" who="S0004"><unclear/></u>
<u n="866" who="S0018">we all cheekily got our photos taken with him didn't we? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="867" who="S0014">that was a good night</u>
<u n="868" who="S0018">it was <pause dur="short"/> but the best thing about it was the three hours we spent getting ready before</u>
<u n="869" who="S0014" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="870" who="S0018">no maybe it wasn't three hours</u>
<u n="871" who="S0014">we looked we all looked really good <pause dur="short"/> we really made an effort</u>
<u n="872" who="S0018">I think we did</u>
<u n="873" who="S0014">sexy witches</u>
<u n="874" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="875" who="S0018">oh back in our youth</u>
<u n="876" who="S0014">I know</u>
<u n="877" who="S0018">it's crazy <pause dur="short"/> everyone's talking about marriage and babies and all that</u>
<u n="878" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="879" who="S0004">who do you class as everyone?</u>
<u n="880" who="S0018">everyone <pause dur="short"/> every single person on this planet <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="881" who="S0004">bet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s not</u>
<u n="882" who="S0014">she wants to</u>
<u n="883" who="S0018"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <unclear/></u>
<u n="884" who="S0014" trans="overlap">I think it's just an awkward situation isn't it</u>
<u n="885" who="S0018">no there's definitely been some discourse there</u>
<u n="886" who="S0014">oh okay</u>
<u n="887" who="S0018"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> keeps bringing up</u>
<u n="888" who="S0014">oh that's good</u>
<u n="889" who="S0018">little things as well <pause dur="short"/> I'm wondering whether</u>
<u n="890" who="S0014">mm <pause dur="short"/> she's gotta tell her parents first though</u>
<u n="891" who="S0004">yeah see isn't there some parental thing going on</u>
<u n="892" who="S0014">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="893" who="S0018">do they not know that she's getting married with him?</u>
<u n="894" who="S0014">no no <pause dur="short"/> that's the whole problem cos he's Muslim she's Sikh <pause dur="short"/> so there's all that issue</u>
<u n="895" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="896" who="S0014">so the families don't' know</u>
<u n="897" who="S0018"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s a Muslim? I didn't know that</u>
<u n="898" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well they like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="899" who="S0004">mm <pause dur="short"/> well exactly</u>
<u n="900" who="S0014"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> Hussain</u>
<u n="901" who="S0018">I knew he was Pakistani</u>
<u n="902" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="903" who="S0018">of Pakistani origin but I didn't</u>
<u n="904" who="S0014">so yeah that's why it's I think there's a few issues with</u>
<u n="905" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="906" who="S0014">that's like I think she she wants all that but</u>
<u n="907" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="908" who="S0014">she needs to tell her parents first really <pause dur="short"/> and just deal with the</u>
<u n="909" who="S0018">but her parents are lovely aren't they? Wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="910" who="S0004">yeah but they're quite old school</u>
<u n="911" who="S0014">yeah they are <pause dur="short"/> they're very traditional</u>
<u n="912" who="S0018">really? I suppose</u>
<u n="913" who="S0014">they'd want her to marry a Sikh man</u>
<u n="914" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="915" who="S0014">definitely not a Muslim</u>
<u n="916" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="917" who="S0004">mm mm</u>
<u n="918" who="S0014">no</u>
<u n="919" who="S0018" trans="overlap">I just don't agree with that kind of</u>
<u n="920" who="S0014">no</u>
<u n="921" who="S0004">but they'd let her marry an Englishman</u>
<u n="922" who="S0014">yeah they'd be more accepting over that than a Muslim</u>
<u n="923" who="S0018">well Faisal Faisal's a total Englishman really isn't he? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="924" who="S0004"><unclear/></u>
<u n="925" who="S0018"><unclear/></u>
<u n="926" who="S0014" trans="overlap">but he asked her once kind of in jest <pause dur="short"/> but he asked her What would be your Muslim name? As in are you going to convert? I think <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="927" who="S0004">God</u>
<u n="928" who="S0014">so he obviously has kind of traditional values as well</u>
<u n="929" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="930" who="S0014">so as much as you know they want it to be easy I think both of them have kind of got these I dunno religious and cultural values that</u>
<u n="931" who="S0018">what a shame</u>
<u n="932" who="S0014">I know</u>
<u n="933" who="S0018">it's all gonna go really like Romeo and Juliet on us</u>
<u n="934" who="S0004">I hope they don't both die</u>
<u n="935" who="S0014" trans="overlap">hopefully not</u>
<u n="936" who="S0018">no no hopefully not</u>
<u n="937" who="S0014">Cos you know when they lived together? Her mum and dad knew that they were living together but she they just thought he was the housemaid</u>
<u n="938" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="939" who="S0014">they didn't know they were like boyfriend girlfriend</u>
<u n="940" who="S0004">oh</u>
<u n="941" who="S0018">ooh la la</u>
<u n="942" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="943" who="S0018">blimey with <pause dur="short"/> how difficult it is</u>
<u n="944" who="S0004" trans="overlap">were they the only two in the house?</u>
<u n="945" who="S0014">pardon?</u>
<u n="946" who="S0004">were they the only two in the house?</u>
<u n="947" who="S0014">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="948" who="S0004">come on</u>
<u n="949" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="950" who="S0014">but whenever they came round <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said she made the spare room look like</u>
<u n="951" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="952" who="S0014">I mean me I'm another friend of hers erm hers and we both said your parents aren't stupid <pause dur="short"/> they'll know</u>
<u n="953" who="S0004">not some parents</u>
<u n="954" who="S0014">I don't  I don't  think they're gonna be that surprised when you tell them <pause dur="short"/> they'll probably be angry for a bit but if she loves him and wants to be with him just she'll have to deal with it</u>
<u n="955" who="S0018">but they sound  they sound  like really lovely people as well <pause dur="short"/> and not only lovely but really accepting <pause dur="short"/> and they've been through really tough kind of</u>
<u n="956" who="S0004" trans="overlap">yeah her dad picked me up from the airport last year</u>
<u n="957" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> a Sikh he he's not  he's not  a Sikh</u>
<u n="958" who="S0014" trans="overlap">but he's he's got a he has the whole turban and the beard doesn't he?</u>
<u n="959" who="S0004">who her dad?</u>
<u n="960" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="961" who="S0004">erm <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember</u>
<u n="962" who="S0014">I think he does</u>
<u n="963" who="S0004">I don't</u>
<u n="964" who="S0014">and her brother does as well <pause dur="short"/> and he's like younger than us</u>
<u n="965" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="966" who="S0004">I don't vividly remember seeing him wearing a turban but I'm sure he did</u>
<u n="967" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="968" who="S0018">are you eating peanut butter with that soup?</u>
<u n="969" who="S0014">I know I was just thinking that <pause dur="short"/> and thinking I don't know if that's gross or not</u>
<u n="970" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="971" who="S0014">how can you spoil <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s lovely soup?</u>
<u n="972" who="S0004">I'm not putting it in the same spoon <pause dur="short"/> it's going in separate mouthfuls</u>
<u n="973" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="974" who="S0018">actually I can see how it might complement the taste</u>
<u n="975" who="S0004">peanut butter just goes with everything</u>
<u n="976" who="S0018">oh it does not <pause dur="short"/> ugh <pause dur="short"/> it's cloying <pause dur="short"/> it sticks to the roof of your mouth</u>
<u n="977" who="S0004" trans="overlap">cloying?</u>
<u n="978" who="S0014">yeah it does doesn't it yeah <pause dur="short"/> isn't they a phobia for that? Like there's an actual name for people who are scared of peanut butter being stuck to the roof of their mouth</u>
<u n="979" who="S0004">peano-philia</u>
<u n="980" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="981" who="S0014">yeah maybe</u>
<u n="982" who="S0004">A peano-philiac <pause dur="short"/> peano-phobia</u>
<u n="983" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="984" who="S0004">peano <pause dur="short"/> peano</u>
<u n="985" who="S0018">do you like the soup?</u>
<u n="986" who="S0004">mm</u>
<u n="987" who="S0018">nice and fresh</u>
<u n="988" who="S0014">I'm gonna start making soup <pause dur="short"/> if it's that easy as well</u>
<u n="989" who="S0018">it is so easy honestly</u>
<u n="990" who="S0004">just lob it in and boil it and then blend it</u>
<u n="991" who="S0014">yeah and I always think it's going to be really complicated but it's not really is it?</u>
<u n="992" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yep</u>
<u n="993" who="S0004">was it onion butternut squash carrot garlic onion?</u>
<u n="994" who="S0018">no garlic even <pause dur="short"/> it's um</u>
<u n="995" who="S0004">oh</u>
<u n="996" who="S0018">potato sweet potato parsnip carrot celery and onion <pause dur="short"/> and that's it <pause dur="short"/> and water</u>
<u n="997" who="S0014">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's so healthy</u>
<u n="998" who="S0018">with a bit of black pepper <pause dur="short"/> and Voil <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I I like getting er a bit adventurous with soups <pause dur="short"/> but at the moment I'll erm I'm enjoying so much that I thought oh I just wanna cook that one</u>
<u n="999" who="S0014" trans="overlap">ha yeah</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0018">it's so nice and it's healthy</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0014">my mum does a really nice one which it probably isn't that healthy actually but it's blue cheese and potato</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0014">it's so nice</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0004">broccoli Stilton <pause dur="short"/> can't beat it</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> yum yum yum <pause dur="short"/> sounds good <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think Indi said she had a book of soups</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0014">oh okay</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0018">but erm you should have a look at</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0004">that would not surprise me</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1011" who="S0004">she's got pretty much a library in there</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0018">well <pause dur="short"/> she's got so many shelves</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0004">I know it'd be rude not to</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0018">have you seen? Her room's just walled with shelving</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0014">oh really?</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0018">do you think? Originally her family lived in this house didn't they?</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0004">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> it was a guy <pause dur="short"/> well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>  is you know he's still the landlord</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0014">oh okay</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0004">but I don't know if he lived here alone or had family or what</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0018">did he operate out of here? Like did he have a doctor's surgery here as well? Cos</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0004">there was loads of weird stuff</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0004">there was like somebody <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had this Green and Gorgeous business <pause dur="short"/> and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> even though she moved out had her erm her online sales thing registered here <pause dur="short"/> we're still getting letters <pause dur="short"/> I texted her a few weeks ago <pause dur="short"/> I was like er we're still getting letters for your business</u>
<u n="1024" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1025" who="S0004">it was like it's alright <pause dur="short"/> nothing to stress about</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0018">my parents are getting letters from these two guys <pause dur="short"/> well no for these two guys <pause dur="short"/> one of them is called <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> and the other one is called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> something or other <pause dur="short"/> and they reckon that they're they've used my parent's address for fraud purposes</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0014">no way</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0018">and they got a letter just the other day from some debt collection company saying we're coming round to collect eight-five pounds worth of unpaid fees or something and</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0014" trans="overlap">oh my God <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> shit what did they do?</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0018">well the took it they've already taken it all to the police</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0014">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> how scary</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0018">and they've got a really friendly local police officer <pause dur="short"/> it's really nice to see</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0018">community police officers actually you know interacting and</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0018">er in a nice way and helpful way <pause dur="short"/> the guy's really nice <pause dur="short"/> er so yeah I don't know to what level they're going to they're gonna investigate it</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0018">because most of it's happening on Ebay and online and</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0004">mm</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0014">mm</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0018">I guess it's difficult to track</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0018">but it's slightly disconcerting having debt collectors writing you letters saying</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0014" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0004">we used to get debt letters for ex-housemates</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0018">ha really?</u>
<u n="1047" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1048" who="S0018">do you actually phone them up and say look they don't live here any more or</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0004">well there's not much you can do <pause dur="short"/> you've got to like give the other person that letter and they've got to deregister and whatever</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0014">it's not always easy to do though like if you don't who lived here before</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0004">I know a few of them</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0014">oh okay</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0004">there's was er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> he was getting DVLA letters coming through for outstanding tax on a vehicle <pause dur="short"/> and there was like a police letter cos I think he'd sold the car but not transferred the ownership <pause dur="short"/> and they were using it for dodgy purposes</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0014">oh God</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0018">naughty naughty</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0014">well erm I used to live in  about ten years ago <pause dur="short"/> and the girl I lived with we both moved out around the same time</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0018">oh whereabouts were you then?</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0014">erm just by Pat Cabs</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0018">oh there</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0014">there erm</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0018">oh it's lovely there</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0014">so we moved out <pause dur="short"/> we both bought houses in Bearwood around the same time <pause dur="short"/> around that time she got caught speeding <pause dur="short"/> but she didn't know and all the letters started going to the old house <pause dur="short"/> we sort of knew the girl who lived there but she didn't forward them on <pause dur="short"/> and three years later the police came knocking on her door and they had a warrant for her arrest</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0004">what?</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0018">you're joking</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0014">ha it was yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos they were like we've sent you letters about you know coming to court <pause dur="short"/> you know you haven't paid the fine <pause dur="short"/> and she was like it er must have been her fault because she should have changed her address for it <pause dur="short"/> cos that's DVLA <pause dur="short"/> would it? No <pause dur="short"/> would it be DVLA?</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0004">if you change your driving licence's address</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0004">then it would automatically forward on</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0014">so she obviously hadn't done that but yeah through</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0004">I mean that's a crime in itself</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0018">is it?</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0004">you know you can get done like a grand if you don't change your driving licence address <pause dur="short"/> cos I had a go at my dad about it a while ago</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0018">that's a bit brutal isn't it</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0004">yeah but it's for the reason that people don't change addresses and then <pause dur="short"/> there was a case on the news yesterday about this guy who had multiple addresses and he was incurring all these speeding fines <pause dur="short"/> and just forwarding them round</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0014">oh my God <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1078" who="S0004">and then like transferring them from one name to another name to say that I wasn't driving such and such whereas er this address was <pause dur="short"/> and he was just like passing them around in this loop</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0014">I mean that takes so much effort <pause dur="short"/> you just think why don't you just pay it?</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0004">it was some scam <pause dur="short"/> he was making money or doing it something</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0014">oh okay</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0004">I don't know if he was offering a service where people can like sell their points to him and stuff</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0014" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> oh God</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0018">I'll buy your brains sucker</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0018">foreign exchange <pause dur="short"/> we buy <pause dur="short"/> we sell <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1088" who="S0004" trans="overlap">there was  there was  a policeman on the news yesterday morning <pause dur="short"/> and he was talking about all this whole loop of crime <pause dur="short"/> and you're like fuck <pause dur="short"/> that's some effort</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0018">I want to think me a make me something like that</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0014"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1092" who="S0018">make a  make a  million out of a loophole</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0004" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1094" who="S0018">when I've got some free time on my hands</u>
<u n="1095" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1096" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0004"><unclear/> opportunity</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0018">I'm not thinking a long term move <pause dur="short"/> you know just a get rich quick scheme</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0014" trans="overlap">quick quick cash yeah</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0004">there's a bookies round the corner</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0018">A bookies? What would I  what would I  bookie on?</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0004">I dunno whatever</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0014">horses?</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0004">become a professional gambler <pause dur="short"/> people do that</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I don't have much luck in the gambling stakes</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0014"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1107" who="S0004">gambling's not about luck though it's all about mathematical equations</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh me and numbers <pause dur="short"/> I'm better with words</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0004">oh that soup was very nice thanks</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0018">you're welcome <pause dur="short"/> ah it's time for a siesta</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0014">yeah I'm feeling a bit like that</u>
<u n="1112" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1113" who="S0004">yeah I was thinking I'll just have a nap before I go out <pause dur="short"/> I might go and have a lie down on the sofa for a minute</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0018">where are you off out to?</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0004">just going to town to get some stuff <pause dur="short"/> some bike stuff</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0018">is that your bike? Oh it's not <pause dur="short"/> yes it's still there</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0004">I just moved it cos it was a bit on the sidewalk</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0018">doesn't that get?</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0004">that's the bike that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> found outside a house in London</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0004">and it's now claimed</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0018">ha ha and it wasn't erm chained up or anything?</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0004">it was in London yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was at a <trunc>hou</trunc> an ex-housemate of his friends</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0004">and he said oh she went ages ago and nobody wants it <pause dur="short"/> so yeah just take it</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0014">oh my God <pause dur="short"/> looks like a decent bike as well</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0004">well the front  is er well the front carves your bone <pause dur="short"/> so every time you pedal it starts to <unclear/> so</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0014" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> ha</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0004">so he needs to take it off and hammer it back into shape</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0018">needs Doctor <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to sort it out</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0004">he is an engineer as well <pause dur="short"/> he can do it</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0018">hmm mm <pause dur="short"/> oh taking of <trunc>engine</trunc> er er bits of engineering</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0004">oh yeah I had a go</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0018">that</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0004">how did it come off?</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0018">I have no idea <pause dur="short"/> I think what well I do have an idea <pause dur="short"/> I opened the door and it fell out and then I saw that this had fallen on the ground <pause dur="short"/> the screw</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0004">mm</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0018">and so I picked up the screw and tried to screw it back in <pause dur="short"/> and tried to put it back in but</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0004">oh right <pause dur="short"/> well I'm just gonna botch it back in so <pause dur="short"/> it stays up <pause dur="short"/> if you push it up now</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0014">is that to go out outside or is that another room?</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0004">that's to do your horses?</u>
<u n="1142" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1143" who="S0018"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1144" who="S0004">have you got? Where's these pictures gone? Oh who moved those?</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><unclear/> What pictures?</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0004">I think Anna must have taken them down</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0018">oh no <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> apparently got rid of it before she went</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0004">why?</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0018">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> you'll have to ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> </u>
<u n="1150" who="S0004">so I was always giving <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> stick <pause dur="short"/> cos she's be I'd come in and she'd have the bottom door bottom door closed but the top door open <pause dur="short"/> and she'd be smoking a fag <pause dur="short"/> so I drew a picture of a horse like smoking a cigarette and stuck it on there</u>
<u n="1151" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1152" who="S0004">and she was wetting herself</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0014">oh that is good</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0018">like a farmyard's door</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0004">but I'd come in and that would be like closed on top of her <pause dur="short"/> and she'd be like a horse having a fag</u>
<u n="1158" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1159" who="S0018">Cos of course we've all seen horses smoking</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="1161" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1162" who="S0004">yeah <pause dur="short"/> need to give it up <pause dur="short"/> it's bad for their er bad for their health</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0014">I should probably get going now Steff</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0018">alright my love <pause dur="short"/> well it's lovely to see you</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0014">but it's really nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0018">and let's organise something like a proper night out</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0018">with all all all the peeps</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0014" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that'd be good <pause dur="short"/> but erm yeah cos like I can just stay at Matt's anyway if we do it here so</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0018">brilliant</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0014">so if we just organise the night</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0014">I don't like staying there cos it's a real boys house <pause dur="short"/> but when I'm drunk enough it's alright</u>
<u n="1174" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1175" who="S0004" trans="overlap">where is it?</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0014"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1177" who="S0018">no is it?</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0004" trans="overlap">Don't know it</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0014">do you know <anon type="place"/> where Pat Cabs is? It's kind of the road parallel to that</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0004">okay</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0018">does he live with er boy housemates?</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0014">two boys yeah</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0018">friends or?</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0014">yeah they'll all</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0004" trans="overlap">there's two boys that live here <pause dur="short"/> what are you saying?</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0014">these boys are weird though <pause dur="short"/> like they've lived in this house for ten years <pause dur="short"/> neither of them have got jobs</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0004">mm</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0014">I don't know how they're affording to stay there <pause dur="short"/> but like apart from Matt's room er the rest of the house is just horrible</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0018">how an earth do they? Maybe they're the guys in charge of this loophole thing</u>
<u n="1193" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1194" who="S0014">maybe <pause dur="short"/> I've no idea how they they've been there for ten years and those two</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0004" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Professional gamblers</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0018">is one of their  is one of their  names <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> </u>
<u n="1197" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1198" who="S0014">no <pause dur="short"/> maybe <pause dur="short"/> maybe they've got secret names as well <pause dur="short"/> erm but yeah it's fine like if if I'm <trunc>s</trunc> like Matt usually stays at mine <pause dur="short"/> but if if I am staying he'll just go he'll just completely clean the house <pause dur="short"/> and I still walk round <pause dur="short"/> I still get into the shower with my flip flops and stuff</u>
<u n="1199" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1200" who="S0018">ugh <pause dur="short"/> I'm not surprised <pause dur="short"/> like these</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0014">A proper boys house</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0018">these boys are quite these boys are probably cleaner and tidier than the girls in the house actually</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0004">yeah</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0014">so how many boys? Three boys here and three girls?</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0004">it used to be four to one <pause dur="short"/> and me as the one <pause dur="short"/> that was hard</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0018">I felt so bad for you <pause dur="short"/> especially when everyone was like oh right let's do a girly night tomorrow</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0004">yeah I thought I was gonna grow a vagina</u>
<u n="1209" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1210" who="S0018">looking over to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thinking poor <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> he's just been struck off tomorrow's social agenda <pause dur="short"/> a girly night</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0004">I'd just like go I'd just go away and do something blokey</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0014">see I live with two boys but they're gay so it's like living with girls</u>
<u n="1213" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1214" who="S0018">oh God</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0014">I've got the most testosterone in that house</u>
<u n="1216" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1217" who="S0004">Jesus</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0014">right <pause dur="short"/> oh thank you for food <pause dur="short"/> it was lovely</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0018">oh thank you for coming <pause dur="short"/> it was lovely to catch up</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0014">and I completely forgot I was being recorded the whole time which is good</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0018">oh good <pause dur="short"/> good good good <pause dur="short"/> told us all your secrets</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0014">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I don't think I swore once</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0018">didn't you? Well done</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0004">for fuck's sake <unclear/></u>
<u n="1226" who="S0018">oh Dan <pause dur="short"/> you would have to go and ruin it wouldn't you</u>
<u n="1227" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1228" who="S0018">so where do you do your personal training?</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0014">at my house</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0018">oh you've actually got</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0014">yeah</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0018">a guy who comes</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0014">A a woman <pause dur="short"/> she basically she used to work for the BBC and then she quit <pause dur="short"/> trained to be a personal trainer and erm yeah she makes loads of money now <pause dur="short"/> she trains all the footballer's wives in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1234" who="S0018">oh wow</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0014">so she's kind of got that market so</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0018">how did she do that then? How did she get</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0014">I don't know</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0018">all those contacts?</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0014">I'm not really sure <pause dur="short"/> erm but because she's ex BBC</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0014">she gives like a discount to BBC staff <pause dur="short"/> and she sometimes does like classes in the mailbox for er after work</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1243" who="S0014">so yeah she's good <pause dur="short"/> so she's actually kind of become like a a mate now so it's quite nice really</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0018">nice</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0014">um and that's how I ended up doing the half marathon last year</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0018">oh of course <pause dur="short"/> then you went to boot camp and everything didn't you?</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0014">that wasn't for that was just a Groupon thing</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0014">it was only for a few weeks <pause dur="short"/> but erm no she trained me for the half marathon <pause dur="short"/> which is good</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0018">sounds nice</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0014">I need to do something like that again cos I'm just not doing as much exercise as I was cos</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0014">when you're doing that you're just doing so much</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0018">crikey that was very impressive I have to say</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0014">yeah I'll never do it again</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0018">and is <trunc>sh</trunc> but does she work you hard? Even though she's turned into a mate</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0014" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0018">Cos that would be the danger of having a mate do it</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0014" trans="overlap">oh my God yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I'm still aching <pause dur="short"/> I have saw her on Friday <pause dur="short"/> I'm still aching today <pause dur="short"/> but yeah she probably works me harder I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="1260" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1261" who="S0018">and does she? She <trunc>work</trunc></u>
<u n="1262" who="S0014">and she she weighs me every week and if I've put on weight she's like right this isn't good enough <pause dur="short"/> I want you to write down all your food this week <pause dur="short"/> can you tell me what you've eaten and stuff?</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0014">she's good at it</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0018">that is <pause dur="short"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0014">it's good <pause dur="short"/> I I kind of need someone like that in my life really</u>
<u n="1267" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1268" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> cool</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0014">cool <pause dur="short"/> thank you very much</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0018">you're very welcome</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0014">erm tell Indi I'm sorry about the person who'll come around to her house is not  there</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0018">I know she's going to oh she'll never speak to you again</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0014" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1274" who="S0018">ever again</u>
</body>
</text>
