<text id="SKJ6">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:09:15</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-28</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0253 S0254</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>speakers' flat, Liverpool</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Museums, Parking, Work, Shopping, Weddings, Moving house, Christmas and presents, Interview for a Masters, Money, Future Plans, Pets</topics>
		<activity>Couple chatting</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0253">
				<exactage>26</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birkenhead</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Merseyside</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>26</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>English Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0254">
				<exactage>26</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birkenhead</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Merseyside</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>26</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Assistant psychologist</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0254">cos I've got an afternoon around museums and <event desc="sound of microphone"/> and I know we've done that one but I enjoyed that so that'll be nice <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="2" who="S0253">did we do that one?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0254">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we did it a while ago didn't we and then we had <anon type="place"/> in erm <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0253">weren't we heading</u>
<u n="5" who="S0254" trans="overlap">that was a really nice day</u>
<u n="6" who="S0253">weren't we heading somewhere that way <trunc>tho</trunc> that day though? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0254">you went we went to look at those erm shipping posters in the maritime museum</u>
<u n="8" who="S0253">that was a bit of a let-down that wasn't it?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0254">yeah but <vocal desc="laugh"/> the two posters that they had</u>
<u n="10" who="S0253" trans="overlap"><trunc>th</trunc>they're still there you know</u>
<u n="11" who="S0254">yeah I know I know I was I told you I was there the other day didn't I?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0253">did you actually have a look round the museum?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0254">no not really I was a bit eager to get out it's er</u>
<u n="14" who="S0253">why why do they have meetings there? is there is there conference rooms?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0254">yeah on the fourth floor there there's a café and then behind the café there's like a <pause dur="short"/> just like a large room really so there was like circle tables and then they had a projector and stuff like that</u>
<u n="16" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0254">they did lunch which was nice <pause dur="short"/> erm it's just that the people who did the course are like a private company <pause dur="short"/> so they obviously were just promoting themselves really and</u>
<u n="18" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0254">saying don't use the NHS cos they're rubbish come to us instead and obviously they were preaching to their most like ninety percent of the audience who were <pause dur="short"/> worked for the NHS</u>
<u n="20" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so it was a little bit awkward at times</u>
<u n="22" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0254">but you know free lunch cost me six quid to park there though mind</u>
<u n="24" who="S0253">that's how much it cost to park there?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0254">park there for three hours cost six pound <pause dur="short"/> have to claim it make sure I remember to claim it back</u>
<u n="26" who="S0253">in our on on <anon type="place"/> street it's four pounds or something</u>
<u n="27" who="S0254">I know it</u>
<u n="28" who="S0253" trans="overlap">they</u>
<u n="29" who="S0254">the only reason I parked there cos I <trunc>w</trunc> there was probably more intelligent places for me to park if I'd have had time to walk but I was running late anyway from and I was in <anon type="place"/> so I just thought oh I'm just gonna have to park there</u>
<u n="30" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0254">yeah so what do you want to buy?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0253">an electric toothbrush</u>
<u n="33" who="S0254">I saw I've saved the page on the thing if you want to</u>
<u n="34" who="S0253">the the Kindle?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0254">the iPad</u>
<u n="36" who="S0253">oh yeah erm I think I just wanna get this one it's the cheapest one it's got good</u>
<u n="37" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0253">Braun Oral B Vitality Precision</u>
<u n="39" who="S0254" trans="overlap">does it come with spare heads? how much are the heads? is it like a printer it's cheap to buy the actual toothbrush but the replaceable brushes are really expensive?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0253">ah they're not soft are they?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0254">I don't know but I'm just thinking is that a way they make their money? cos normally electric toothbrushes are quite expensive aren't they? does it have a buy together with oh no you <trunc>ca</trunc> <pause dur="long"/> how much are the three brush heads pack of three ten pounds is that? <pause dur="short"/> I mean that'll last ages you're supposed to change your toothbrush every six months aren't you so</u>
<u n="42" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0254">technically that would last you two years</u>
<u n="44" who="S0253">so I don't need a shaver adapter do I? or do I? I haven't got one of them</u>
<u n="45" who="S0254">I've got one of them</u>
<u n="46" who="S0253">have you? to plug stuff in?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0253">so I don't really need that set do I for the thirty-two pounds?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0254">no <pause dur="short"/> you don't even really need to buy the other brush heads</u>
<u n="50" who="S0253">just buy batteries</u>
<u n="51" who="S0254" trans="overlap">right now do you?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0253">no</u>
<u n="53" who="S0254">I would say <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0253">oh I didn't know there's so much to toothbrush toothbrushes</u>
<u n="55" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0253">I had</u>
<u n="57" who="S0254" trans="overlap">why what's that sensitive mode? daily clean mode with three D movement what?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0253">that would go around the tooth</u>
<u n="59" who="S0254">oh</u>
<u n="60" who="S0253">so I think I think my one</u>
<u n="61" who="S0254" trans="overlap">I don't like them the they scare me a bit <pause dur="short"/> like a pulsating oscillating toothbrush just</u>
<u n="62" who="S0253" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what do</u>
<u n="63" who="S0254" trans="overlap">sounds a bit scary</u>
<u n="64" who="S0253" trans="overlap">what do you want it what do you want it to do? <pause dur="long"/> polishes to remove <pause dur="short"/> surface stains</u>
<u n="65" who="S0254">I I you have to be careful with them cos someone told me I can't remember who it was that they're actually you have to be quite careful and sometimes they can be bad for your teeth cos they're a bit too</u>
<u n="66" who="S0253">aggressive</u>
<u n="67" who="S0254" trans="overlap">harsh and it takes like a layer off your teeth</u>
<u n="68" who="S0253"><trunc>s</trunc> I was talking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about the time I got my trip to the dentist</u>
<u n="69" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0253">and</u>
<u n="71" who="S0254">to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0253">I were talking about er yeah was it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yeah cos he said</u>
<u n="73" who="S0254">it is the dentist <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0253" trans="overlap">cos I couldn't remember the girl's name and his said who was it and I said and he said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0254">oh it wasn't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who was my dentist</u>
<u n="76" who="S0253">no but she was the</u>
<u n="77" who="S0254" trans="overlap">but she was in your <trunc>dent</trunc> she works in yours</u>
<u n="78" who="S0253" trans="overlap"><trunc>n</trunc> my dentist yeah cos we were just talking about that but erm he was cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying as well that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to get stains on his teeth</u>
<u n="79" who="S0254">yes cos he drank mouthwash er or he had a cup of coffee after his mouthwash</u>
<u n="80" who="S0253">so it like <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="81" who="S0254" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> told me that the other day</u>
<u n="82" who="S0253" trans="overlap">it weakens your enamel</u>
<u n="83" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0253">okay one rechargeable toothbrush so I won't be bleaching my mouth any more <pause dur="short"/> I was so scared</u>
<u n="85" who="S0254">so scared of what?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0253">this morning when I tasted bleach on my thing</u>
<u n="87" who="S0254">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0253">it's a bit like ah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it'll be fine they're nice and white today</u>
<u n="90" who="S0253">my teeth?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> joking</u>
<u n="92" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0253">they er they've never looked better</u>
<u n="95" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="96" who="S0253">my oesophagus</u>
<u n="97" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0253">my oesophagus is somewhat hurting</u>
<u n="99" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but my teeth are pearly whites</u>
<u n="100" who="S0253">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's loads of stuff I wanted but</u>
<u n="101" who="S0254">for your wish list?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0253">I have</u>
<u n="103" who="S0254" trans="overlap">put it on your wish list</u>
<u n="104" who="S0253">the thing is is that it <vocal desc="sigh"/> apparently the <trunc>n</trunc></u>
<u n="105" who="S0254" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0253">the new <unclear/> album's really good</u>
<u n="107" who="S0254">didn't even know they're still going</u>
<u n="108" who="S0253">the thing is a lot of the stuff they recommend I've <trunc>o</trunc> I've often not bought it from them I've gone out and bought it from a shop</u>
<u n="109" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0253"><vocal desc="gasp"/> that's ridiculous <pause dur="long"/> six</u>
<u n="111" who="S0254" trans="overlap">eighteen ninety-nine</u>
<u n="112" who="S0253">yeah but this is that's</u>
<u n="113" who="S0254" trans="overlap">oh that's really creepy</u>
<u n="114" who="S0253">what the <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="115" who="S0254" trans="overlap">Swans</u>
<u n="116" who="S0253" trans="overlap">Swans? they're a bit of a creepy band <pause dur="short"/> sparklehorse are good</u>
<u n="117" who="S0254">I was looking at slightly more boring <pause dur="short"/> toothbrush holders <pause dur="short"/> though I suppose if you're getting an electric toothbrush so we'd don't need a toothbrush holder <pause dur="short"/> cos you can't put an electric toothbrush</u>
<u n="118" who="S0253" trans="overlap">don't</u>
<u n="119" who="S0254" trans="overlap">in a toothbrush holder can you?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0253">don't let that stop you if you need to er</u>
<u n="121" who="S0254">shall I show you what I was looking at? <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's ten pounds though</u>
<u n="122" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah <trunc>pl</trunc> by all means</u>
<u n="123" who="S0254">ten pounds in John Lewis for a toothbrush holder</u>
<u n="124" who="S0253">I nearly bought a self-help book today</u>
<u n="125" who="S0254">did you? bought a self-help book?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0253">it was I don't know what it was that I it was just about <pause dur="short"/> it it's one of those those popular sort of psychology books where <pause dur="short"/> it was like about you know <pause dur="short"/> control get control of your life and control anxiety and stuff like that</u>
<u n="127" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0253">and I think I cos I was like I was in the train station and I was feeling a bit anxious <pause dur="short"/> are are they Orla Kiely or whatever her name is?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0254">no it's just John Lewis tulip</u>
<u n="130" who="S0253">how much do they cost?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0254">the thing on its own is ten pound <pause dur="short"/> the soap pump's like twenty-eight quid or something oh no sixteen pound for a soap pump <pause dur="short"/> I think er not <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> this is why we should get married</u>
<u n="132" who="S0253">why?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0254">put it on our wedding list <pause dur="short"/> posh toothbrush holder <pause dur="short"/> it's the kind of stuff that people buy you isn't it?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0253">that's not the only reason to get married</u>
<u n="135" who="S0254">well it's a pretty good reason <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0253">you're so cynical</u>
<u n="137" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="138" who="S0253">that's <trunc>w</trunc> that's why I'm never gonna marry you</u>
<u n="139" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0253">cos I know it would only be for the gifts</u>
<u n="141" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0253">not for love</u>
<u n="143" who="S0254">I love you</u>
<u n="144" who="S0253">I know</u>
<u n="145" who="S0254">you know I do just be an added bonus if we get a load of presents</u>
<u n="146" who="S0253">I was speaking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about this and he said that cos I was talking about how <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know the way <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did his where he erm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0253">er he he travelled around and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said that cos er I said wouldn't that appeal to you? like you know basically pay for your honeymoon and he said no because we're getting a new we're because we're buying a house we need everything he said</u>
<u n="149" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0253">and he just said he said <pause dur="short"/> you know I mean I it's it's <pause dur="short"/> er cos I mean I dunno <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s not like very materialistic <pause dur="short"/> to be honest he's not really bothered about you know</u>
<u n="151" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0253">he's he's really not like about about like the interiors of places like he's</u>
<u n="153" who="S0254">I think he'd more er he is more than you he does have an opinion I remember them arguing over the <pause dur="short"/> style of dining plates or something</u>
<u n="154" who="S0253">really?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0254">cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was really particular he wanted a really particular <pause dur="short"/> shape of dining plate</u>
<u n="156" who="S0253">oh</u>
<u n="157" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0254">I remember <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> telling me</u>
<u n="159" who="S0253">each to their own</u>
<u n="160" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0253">but erm but it well he but he said I think when it came to furniture and stuff he just said you know <trunc>y</trunc>you have an idea of what you want but the fact is that it's all so expensive you're just gonna go to Ikea</u>
<u n="162" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0253">and you're gonna fill your <trunc>st</trunc> your house with stuff from Ikea and <pause dur="short"/> it's true isn't it? because I mean</u>
<u n="164" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0253">unless you've got bags of money <pause dur="short"/> you can't possibly furnish a house with like designer gear</u>
<u n="166" who="S0254">no not straight away <pause dur="short"/> I think what I would do if I was buying a house is <pause dur="short"/> get hand-me-downs and as many freebies from people as possible and then I'd replace each thing with what I really wanted</u>
<u n="167" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0254">so say then I'd replace <pause dur="short"/> you know you know your sofa when you could afford it with a really nice one</u>
<u n="169" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0254">so even if you were just completely mish-mashed for a while <pause dur="short"/> eventually you'd have everything you really wanted over time wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0253">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0254">cos obviously very rarely can you afford to buy <pause dur="short"/> like everything you want straight away</u>
<u n="173" who="S0253">yeah it's true <pause dur="short"/> yeah I dunno <pause dur="short"/> as I say er after after seeing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s it just made me really want my own place</u>
<u n="174" who="S0254">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0253">so is that where you'd live then? <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0254">I dunno really <pause dur="short"/> I just er well I just like seeing my nan and stuff today like I would like to be able to go and just call round</u>
<u n="177" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0254" trans="overlap">to see her like you know once a week and</u>
<u n="179" who="S0253" trans="overlap">it's on it's on the balance of things I mean <trunc>may</trunc>maybe there was a point I mean I <trunc>kn</trunc> you know where's we've been talking about <pause dur="short"/> maybe there was a point where <pause dur="short"/> I did more socialising over here than I did over on <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0253">but now</u>
<u n="182" who="S0254" trans="overlap">I just feel like I'm always travelling over to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0253">I'm but I'm starting to feel a bit now like I mean obviously I've got I mean er I'm I'm bearing in I've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s er next week in the back of my head but you know I'm thinking about like sort of if I wanna see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> more and</u>
<u n="184" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0253">erm <pause dur="short"/> you know it's nice that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s coming over on Tuesday but I'd see him a bit more I just need to see my mum and dad I'm thinking I might go home tomorrow afternoon to see my mum</u>
<u n="186" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0253">but I'm gonna do that that's definitely what I'm gonna do I've got nothing else to do tomorrow actually</u>
<u n="188" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0253">I'll be back I'll be back by dinner time though</u>
<u n="190" who="S0254">mm don't worry</u>
<u n="191" who="S0253">erm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0254">stay for tea at your mum's if you want</u>
<u n="193" who="S0253">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0253">don't want don't want turkey burgers</u>
<u n="196" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0254">turkey dinosaurs</u>
<u n="198" who="S0253">turkey dinosaurs <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0253">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I just feel like I need to see her really</u>
<u n="201" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I haven't seen her in so long</u>
<u n="203" who="S0254">well this is it and like <pause dur="short"/> it's just little things like my mum really wants to start going to yoga but she hasn't got anyone to go with and <pause dur="short"/> it's like</u>
<u n="204" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yoga?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0254">you know just stupid things I know that's really daft but it's like</u>
<u n="206" who="S0253" trans="overlap">but you'd like to go with her?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0254">I could go with her or</u>
<u n="208" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0254">you know we could ah I dunno I just</u>
<u n="210" who="S0253">yeah I <trunc>kn</trunc> I know I get it</u>
<u n="211" who="S0254" trans="overlap">I dunno what it is really</u>
<u n="212" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I get it I'm starting to feel a bit the same</u>
<u n="213" who="S0254" trans="overlap">then I could just feel like everybody you know all my friends well I say all <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0253">but but you know er</u>
<u n="215" who="S0254">but you know I don't have any friends in <anon type="place"/> any more really <pause dur="short"/> you know like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> aren't here and</u>
<u n="216" who="S0253">yeah but I mean I'm I'm the same</u>
<u n="217" who="S0254" trans="overlap">you know like the majority of my <anon type="place"/> socialising was going out with them and going out with the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> people so now that <pause dur="short"/> they're not here I kind of you know I can't even really remember the last time I was in <anon type="place"/> like even just shopping</u>
<u n="218" who="S0253">the thing is as well I suppose is that <pause dur="short"/> I mean it it like anything I'm wanting to do over here you know I've I've been fine so that you know when I was when I was in <anon type="place"/> I just commuted so like</u>
<u n="219" who="S0254" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0253">or came over for you know like on Saturdays if I wanna watch the match over here</u>
<u n="221" who="S0254" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0253">I watch the match</u>
<u n="223" who="S0254">the only thing is the price of train tickets now isn't it?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0253">that would be <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="225" who="S0254" trans="overlap">probably</u>
<u n="226" who="S0253">there's and there's no way round it er if you drive it's gonna be more expensive</u>
<u n="227" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0253">cos of parking erm</u>
<u n="229" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0253">the only way round it would be to get the bus the four ten</u>
<u n="231" who="S0254">I bet that's very expensive though isn't it?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0253">but I think it's quicker <pause dur="short"/> I think</u>
<u n="233" who="S0254" trans="overlap">do you think?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0253">I think I think it would be quicker to get the four ten from <anon type="place"/> to town than it would be to get from here of a morning</u>
<u n="235" who="S0254">maybe</u>
<u n="236" who="S0253">because if you think about the route it goes there's not much traffic even of a morning there wouldn't be much traffic <trunc>wh</trunc> like</u>
<u n="237" who="S0254">no probably not</u>
<u n="238" who="S0253">er <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="239" who="S0254">by the time you <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0253" trans="overlap">well I guess what I'm saying is it wouldn't be it wouldn't be ridiculously</u>
<u n="241" who="S0254">and we couldn't afford <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0253">no</u>
<u n="243" who="S0254">you're gonna get a new job soon anyway</u>
<u n="244" who="S0253">well I happen to know two people who are renting a room in <anon type="place"/> and would love love tenants</u>
<u n="245" who="S0254">who?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0253">mum and dad</u>
<u n="247" who="S0254">oh</u>
<u n="248" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0253">yeah no I'm starting to <pause dur="long"/> I just wish there was somewhere that I could afford to live that was a bit like <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0253"><anon type="place"/> I guess</u>
<u n="252" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0253">but that <trunc>st</trunc> but that <trunc>st</trunc> that feels a bit far away from</u>
<u n="254" who="S0254">yeah that's still just as far as here really</u>
<u n="255" who="S0253">mm <pause dur="short"/> well it's not</u>
<u n="256" who="S0254">well it kind of is it's a good twenty minutes to from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0253">mm <pause dur="short"/> not as <unclear/> though</u>
<u n="258" who="S0254">well yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0253">I dunno though you know saying that though like obviously I've been really busy the past few months but I know what'll happen as soon as say I mean <trunc>th</trunc> by the way <trunc>w</trunc> you know we can't realistically think about moving to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0254" trans="overlap">no no of course not</u>
<u n="261" who="S0253">but <pause dur="short"/> I feel like I know what would happen and it's I'd kind of like er you know you move away <trunc>some</trunc> from somewhere and you idealise it thinking</u>
<u n="262" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0253">oh it'll be a bit better and things like that and oh you know I I could I could see this person see that person but inevitably as soon as you move home <pause dur="short"/> you won't see anyone like</u>
<u n="264" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0253">my my mum my dad's always out so I never see my dad anyway my mum's always in bed like</u>
<u n="266" who="S0254" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="267" who="S0253">I'm never gonna I'm not gonna see any of them three am I like <pause dur="short"/> around <anon type="place"/> cos <trunc>th</trunc>they never see each other anyway</u>
<u n="268" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0253">erm <pause dur="short"/> and and it I'll just and then the at least here like there's a lot to do <pause dur="short"/> even on your own on a Saturday like</u>
<u n="270" who="S0254" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="271" who="S0253">I can you can go into town or you can you know</u>
<u n="272" who="S0254">yeah yeah there's stuff stuff to do</u>
<u n="273" who="S0253" trans="overlap">or me and you can go go out for some food or go for a walk in the park</u>
<u n="274" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0253" trans="overlap">just little things like that that you <trunc>ca</trunc> you do take for granted a bit</u>
<u n="276" who="S0254">I love going for a walk in the park after work <pause dur="short"/> I really like doing that</u>
<u n="277" who="S0253">well I should we should try and do it before it gets really cold</u>
<u n="278" who="S0254">yeah we should cos <pause dur="short"/> I really miss it or you know at Christmas</u>
<u n="279" who="S0253">certainly am <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="280" who="S0254">I'm looking forward to Christmas though</u>
<u n="281" who="S0253">I haven't I just I feel I just really feel like I wanna get <pause dur="short"/> I just wanna get on with the year I know that sounds really stupid <pause dur="short"/> I just feel like I've got a lot waiting in the wings I haven't really but</u>
<u n="282" who="S0254">mm <pause dur="short"/> like what?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0253">you know I'll say about <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> just in terms of your</u>
<u n="284" who="S0254">yeah well the next sort of month or so will be <pause dur="short"/> I dunno I feel like it's gonna be like decisive but it probably won't it'll be like well you haven't got an interview <pause dur="short"/> and it's like right okay then</u>
<u n="285" who="S0253" trans="overlap">end of discussion</u>
<u n="286" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> end of yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0253">I <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="288" who="S0254" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="289" who="S0253">if if that happens</u>
<u n="290" who="S0254">well I'll be really sad if I don't get an interview and I think I really deserve an interview</u>
<u n="291" who="S0253">it's <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0254">but</u>
<u n="293" who="S0253">you never know with these things do you any more</u>
<u n="294" who="S0254" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="295" who="S0253">it's <trunc>h</trunc>hard to hard to gauge whether you'll get one or not</u>
<u n="296" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0253">but I was just sort of saying this to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I said <pause dur="short"/> you know I just I feel like <pause dur="short"/> that's kind of what I'm waiting to find out about and I'll be so happy if you get you know and and even if you just get an interview</u>
<u n="298" who="S0254">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I wish you could come up with me if I got an interview</u>
<u n="299" who="S0253">I won't be able to</u>
<u n="300" who="S0254">no I know</u>
<u n="301" who="S0253">erm</u>
<u n="302" who="S0254">I'm gonna do hen party things</u>
<u n="303" who="S0253">while you're there?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0253">what do you mean like just on your own</u>
<u n="306" who="S0254" trans="overlap">bit mad though</u>
<u n="307" who="S0253">like wearing a sash?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes gonna wander round <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0253">woo</u>
<u n="310" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0253">who's that weird girl? erm</u>
<u n="312" who="S0254">there's a few things like I wanna get like maps for everyone so I need to like go into like a tourist information or something</u>
<u n="313" who="S0253">er what</u>
<u n="314" who="S0254" trans="overlap">just wanna have a wander round</u>
<u n="315" who="S0253" trans="overlap">what would you do?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0254">and <trunc>li</trunc></u>
<u n="317" who="S0253">er how would you like what would you do just stay there one night?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0254">yeah I'd have to</u>
<u n="319" who="S0253">where would you stay?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0254">I'd <trunc>ha</trunc> a Travelodge or something</u>
<u n="321" who="S0253">that's gonna be really expensive</u>
<u n="322" who="S0254">I know I was thinking of going on cos you know with that</u>
<u n="323" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I wouldn't drive</u>
<u n="324" who="S0254">no you know if we booked that one for <anon type="place"/> it was like on Hotels dot com or something</u>
<u n="325" who="S0253" trans="overlap">we need to cancel that don't we?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0254">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you can book them and cancel them so I thought if I book it now rather than wait until I know</u>
<u n="327" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0254">and then it feels a little bit half of me thinks oh you're just tempting fate but I think well no I'm not really am I</u>
<u n="329" who="S0253" trans="overlap">or like booking a day off work</u>
<u n="330" who="S0254" trans="overlap">that's just superstition</u>
<u n="331" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> pre-emptively booking your day off work for a job interview you didn't get</u>
<u n="332" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah so I think if I just book it then <pause dur="short"/> you know I'm not booking a Last Minute hotel</u>
<u n="333" who="S0253">mm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0254">I can't book my train tickets and that's gonna cost me a fortune</u>
<u n="335" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0254">erm because they only give you two weeks' notice or something I mean I had a look the other day and it was about sixteen quid return</u>
<u n="337" who="S0253">to <trunc>ch</trunc> to <trunc>n</trunc> to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah eight pound sixty single each way</u>
<u n="339" who="S0253">with a rail card?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0253">how?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0254">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it was</u>
<u n="343" who="S0253" trans="overlap">are you sure?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0253">are you sure that wasn't to get on the train?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0254">that was mid-week erm but I will be going mid-week so</u>
<u n="347" who="S0253">that's cor that's really good that</u>
<u n="348" who="S0254" trans="overlap">I know it's amazing isn't it?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0254">cos I knew it was fairly cheap if you book it three months in advance because that's what I plan to do for the hen do but</u>
<u n="351" who="S0253">mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0254">obviously I won't have the luxury of booking three months in advance so <pause dur="short"/> but it's reassuring if we end up living there that it'll just be cheaper to come home on the train cos</u>
<u n="353" who="S0253">and if you book in advance you know when</u>
<u n="354" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0253">and we could book a few in advance so like</u>
<u n="356" who="S0254" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="357" who="S0253" trans="overlap">so like we we could sort of have planned weekends home</u>
<u n="358" who="S0254">planned weekends erm <pause dur="short"/> cos otherwise I don't wanna be driving that way</u>
<u n="359" who="S0253">no</u>
<u n="360" who="S0254" trans="overlap">all that way <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0253">yeah it just erm</u>
<u n="362" who="S0254">well I don't know</u>
<u n="363" who="S0253">I mean I mean the thing is is like even if you don't get an interview I mean it doesn't change much really but I just feel like I've gotta make I just feel that we've got to make some kind of decisions about things and</u>
<u n="364" who="S0254">yeah I feel like you've gotta you've got to try and get some plans together yourself really</u>
<u n="365" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0254">so I don't feel like I'm dictating everything <pause dur="short"/> but anyway</u>
<u n="367" who="S0253">that's what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said the other day <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said you know oh make sure you know <trunc>t</trunc> cos I was talking about this and he said well make sure you know you don't just <trunc>m</trunc>mm but <pause dur="short"/> I I've made sense of it in my head I know exactly how I feel about it and I know exactly what I'm doing so</u>
<u n="368" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0253">I'm not too fussed</u>
<u n="370" who="S0254">are you gonna apply for your masters?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0254" trans="overlap">this week?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0253">I wanted to and then I told you didn't I like it it it said apply for two thousand and fifteen but the form I've I've started to fill in <pause dur="short"/> was er said it was only it was like so the form you're submitted says time of entry September two thousand and fourteen and so I don't wanna complete</u>
<u n="374" who="S0254" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="375" who="S0253">I don't wanna complete a form and then it'll be like oh sorry there was an error on that one do it all again</u>
<u n="376" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0253">but I suppose I mean I suppose I can just complete the form and then copy and paste it</u>
<u n="378" who="S0254" trans="overlap">you can copy and paste yeah like the personal statement-y bit is there that personal do they ask for a personal statement?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah of course yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0254">yeah so <trunc>wh</trunc> even if you've just written like that <pause dur="short"/> you can use stuff from your that covering letter you wrote can't you?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0253">yeah there's lots there's lots there and <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>d</trunc> I I was I <trunc>wa</trunc> that would be one of my my goals for this week</u>
<u n="382" who="S0254">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you've gotta yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0253">mm</u>
<u n="384" who="S0254">you know what my aims are this week maybe I'll book that hotel I <anon type="place"/> and cancel that one in in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0254">erm <pause dur="short"/> don't know what to do really <pause dur="short"/> feel like I need a bit of focus <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="387" who="S0253">let me see if I can find one</u>
<u n="388" who="S0254">you can't buy one on Amazon surely</u>
<u n="389" who="S0253">yeah of course</u>
<u n="390" who="S0254">four hundred quid jeez</u>
<u n="391" who="S0253">same price as <unclear/> more or less</u>
<u n="392" who="S0254">yeah will there be a girl in the <unclear/> though oh no I suppose</u>
<u n="393" who="S0253">I will get one of them soon</u>
<u n="394" who="S0254">you need to have a go on one first <pause dur="short"/> do they have them at <anon type="place"/> marina?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0253">yep</u>
<u n="396" who="S0254">you'll have to go there <pause dur="short"/> book us in <pause dur="short"/> we'll do that weekend after next instead of going to <anon type="place"/> go to <anon type="place"/> marina</u>
<u n="397" who="S0253">can I go on the ferry and go to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0254">okay we can do that</u>
<u n="399" who="S0253">yeah no you're right</u>
<u n="400" who="S0254">what I really want from that weekend is to spend some time with you and <pause dur="short"/> mm just spend some time in the flat actually I know</u>
<u n="401" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0254">we can't spend the whole weekend at the flat maybe we could go to <anon type="place"/> lake or something and then get like a dine-in from Marks and Spencer's or something</u>
<u n="403" who="S0253">yeah that's <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="404" who="S0254" trans="overlap">and have a lie in</u>
<u n="405" who="S0253">that'd be nice <pause dur="long"/> yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0254">just a part of me it seems a really long way away from here</u>
<u n="407" who="S0253">it's not <pause dur="short"/> once you're up once once you're off the ferry there's a bus direct</u>
<u n="408" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0253">it's really quick it depends on the day if the day's like <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>wea</trunc>weather's</u>
<u n="410" who="S0254" trans="overlap">crappy</u>
<u n="411" who="S0253">yeah if the weather's terrible then</u>
<u n="412" who="S0254">oh my dad sent me a oh where's my phone? yeah my dad sent me a picture he was there last night it's like sunset over <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0253">what was he doing there?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0254">having chips</u>
<u n="415" who="S0253">with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0253">that's nice</u>
<u n="418" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah fish and chips</u>
<u n="419" who="S0253">my mum rang today</u>
<u n="420" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0253">but like didn't really say much</u>
<u n="422" who="S0254">why?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0253">I don't know I feel bad I can't remember what I was thinking about at the time but you know when you're just a bit distracted?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0253">and if my mum senses that you're distracted or you're busy she just goes alright well I I'll speak to you soon so I feel I feel bad</u>
<u n="426" who="S0254">should ring her back</u>
<u n="427" who="S0253">I will text her but <pause dur="long"/> this came out this week</u>
<u n="428" who="S0254">oh <pause dur="short"/> what is it?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0253">it's a bunch of erm sort of <pause dur="short"/> rarities and B sides I think is it the track has it got the track list on it? erm <pause dur="short"/> and so there's nothing there's nothing like that's featured on any of their albums</u>
<u n="430" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="431" who="S0253">I bet there'll be some absolute gems on it though</u>
<u n="432" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="433" who="S0253">the things is they'll have had they'll have sat on these for about twenty years</u>
<u n="434" who="S0254">oh yeah with the purpose of releasing them</u>
<u n="435" who="S0253">in two thousand and fourteen Dave Gilmour and Nick Mason <pause dur="short"/> erm started with unreleased keyboard performances by Richard Wright who sadly died in two thousand and eight <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0254">oh</u>
<u n="437" who="S0253">what? yeah sorry it was Roger Waters I was thinking and I was like no he didn't</u>
<u n="438" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="439" who="S0253">erm <pause dur="short"/> so it's sixty percent <pause dur="short"/> of recording other than ninety <pause dur="short"/> those <trunc>ne</trunc> three sessions <pause dur="long"/> so it's based on The Division Bell</u>
<u n="440" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0253">which is like a brilliant album erm <pause dur="short"/> and then they've just kind of edited and rerecorded parts and make it a modern sort of Pink Floyd album that's really exciting</u>
<u n="442" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="443" who="S0253">tempted tempted to buy that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0254">well think you think there's pre-order</u>
<u n="445" who="S0253">when's it out?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0254">it's released November the tenth</u>
<u n="447" who="S0253">oh that's quite well that's not that long is it when is it?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0254">November after <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s wedding <pause dur="short"/> saw them today</u>
<u n="449" who="S0253"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0254">yeah they were walking back from er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s I just peeped them I was driving</u>
<u n="451" who="S0253">you beeped them?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0253">not peep</u>
<u n="454" who="S0254">beep peep</u>
<u n="455" who="S0253">nobody <trunc>peep</trunc></u>
<u n="456" who="S0254">pipped</u>
<u n="457" who="S0253">pipped them to the post</u>
<u n="458" who="S0254">if you have a big car it's a beep if you have a Toyota Aygo it's a peep <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0253">what does an oven do when the stuff's ready?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0254">pings</u>
<u n="461" who="S0253">it beeps</u>
<u n="462" who="S0254">well mine goes pings</u>
<u n="463" who="S0253">yeah no ding</u>
<u n="464" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0253">erm I was gonna say</u>
<u n="466" who="S0254" trans="overlap">it's it's more of a ping than a ding</u>
<u n="467" who="S0253">it was really funny cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like</u>
<u n="468" who="S0254" trans="overlap">did he come up any of this weekend?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0253">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0254" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="471" who="S0253">no so so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> text him and said just wanted to know if you're still coming and he said oh sorry mate I forgot to let you know erm I'm I'm doing <pause dur="short"/> he said I'm doing family stuff tonight on Friday <pause dur="short"/> no work stuff till on Friday and then I've got a family thing on Sunday <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just text him back and he just said Saturday is unaccounted for <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0253">and he just didn't reply</u>
<u n="474" who="S0254">oh yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0253">and then on <trunc>s</trunc> and then this is the thing with social media so and you know we just laughed about it and stuff and we laughed at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s response that was quite funny and then he's he he <trunc>wh</trunc> he snapchatted like everyone like <trunc>h</trunc> everyone on your list he just snapchats them like er anything he's done</u>
<u n="476" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="477" who="S0253">and it was like a picture of Fifa and he was like there's my weekend and he's like you've just told us that</u>
<u n="478" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="479" who="S0253" trans="overlap">you're like doing family stuff and then it's quite clear you've just but fair enough Fifa is Fifa <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="480" who="S0254" trans="overlap">it is stupid though isn't it like <anon type="place"/>'s forty minutes away he could have come Saturday morning and left Saturday afternoon just</u>
<u n="481" who="S0253"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="482" who="S0254" trans="overlap">like</u>
<u n="483" who="S0253"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="484" who="S0254" trans="overlap">he could have driven but he never drives anywhere does he?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0253"><trunc>n</trunc> he doesn't like driving <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> drives</u>
<u n="486" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0253"><trunc>ev</trunc>everywhere</u>
<u n="488" who="S0254" trans="overlap">everywhere</u>
<u n="489" who="S0253">he really can't stand it erm</u>
<u n="490" who="S0254" trans="overlap">why?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0253">it makes him feel I dunno and he he <trunc>d</trunc> he wasn't that confident when he did his test he just never never really got into driving and then</u>
<u n="492" who="S0254">yeah but</u>
<u n="493" who="S0253" trans="overlap">and then he didn't</u>
<u n="494" who="S0254" trans="overlap">if you don't do it you won't get comfortable will you?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0253">true but erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hit the nail on the head and he said that after they came here for dinner <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like drunk in the car and just like really really frank about it and just <trunc>sai</trunc> I'm just really lazy he said I just I <trunc>ca</trunc> when it comes to doing stuff I I like the idea of doing stuff and then when it comes down to it I just can't be arsed</u>
<u n="496" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="497" who="S0253">and and at least he's honest about it like</u>
<u n="498" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0253" trans="overlap">and I think that is it he just <pause dur="short"/> I think the more you <unclear>judge</unclear> stuff off and you don't you don't go out and you don't do stuff you just get more and more cosy don't you and</u>
<u n="500" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0253">more and more settled at home</u>
<u n="502" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="503" who="S0253" trans="overlap">but you know and that's fine it's just it's just</u>
<u n="504" who="S0254">well yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0253" trans="overlap">as as <trunc>lo</trunc> as long as he's not offended if people don't invite him places</u>
<u n="506" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0253">but <pause dur="short"/> you know it's no trouble is it really just to send it <trunc>p</trunc> send him an invite</u>
<u n="508" who="S0254">it's a bit</u>
<u n="509" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I felt a bit bad actually it <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> today put said sorry I couldn't make the pub guys erm me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were gonna have you all for dinner next Saturday <pause dur="short"/> so I just put and then I read it and then straight away <trunc>w</trunc> and straight away just said I didn't say where I was cos I wasn't really sure whether he'd be invited on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s stag <pause dur="short"/> I mean I kind of presume not</u>
<u n="510" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="511" who="S0253">but I thought he might be a bit offended and then I wasn't sure whether you know</u>
<u n="512" who="S0254">oh yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0253">I mean presumably <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="514" who="S0254" trans="overlap"><unclear>gone</unclear></u>
<u n="515" who="S0253"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> knows about it maybe he's going I hope he is</u>
<u n="516" who="S0254">I dunno dunno</u>
<u n="517" who="S0253">erm but then maybe not because it's his brother who's organised it and it might just be a case of like</u>
<u n="518" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0253">his like the guys from the family and your friends from school erm <pause dur="short"/> so I just put I'm out that Saturday erm would really like to catch up with you soon though and then and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> put sorry that's my hen and then like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> everyone else followed suit</u>
<u n="520" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0253">and it was like sorry that's the hen party but I didn't know whether to mention the fact it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s stag cos I feel a bit bad that he's not</u>
<u n="522" who="S0254">yeah it's not really</u>
<u n="523" who="S0253">he's he's not they're not friends <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="524" who="S0254" trans="overlap">for you mention it though</u>
<u n="525" who="S0253">and er yeah if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to say sorry that's my stag do then that's fine but it's nothing to do</u>
<u n="526" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0253" trans="overlap">with me</u>
<u n="528" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0253">but <pause dur="short"/> it's a pain it's a shame to turn down a free dinner <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="530" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0253">this side as well</u>
<u n="532" who="S0254">yeah this side of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0254">we'll go to his thirtieth though <pause dur="short"/> will we? oh you're out aren't you?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0253">I'm going</u>
<u n="536" who="S0254" trans="overlap">I'm not going on my own</u>
<u n="537" who="S0253" trans="overlap">you're in Spain</u>
<u n="538" who="S0254">no I'm not</u>
<u n="539" who="S0253">yeah you are</u>
<u n="540" who="S0254">no I'm not</u>
<u n="541" who="S0253">yoga retreat</u>
<u n="542" who="S0254">no it's like the twenty-sixth or something of October isn't it the party? <pause dur="short"/> I'll be back then</u>
<u n="543" who="S0253">but you're away the weekend before</u>
<u n="544" who="S0254">I'm away the Sunday the nineteenth to Wednesday the twenty-second</u>
<u n="545" who="S0253">oh right okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah we've got that crappy gig booked but I really listening to that band I just don't wanna go</u>
<u n="546" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="547" who="S0253">and I've got I mean it'll be I'll be nice I mean if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to go that's great</u>
<u n="548" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="549" who="S0253">I'm happy to <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="550" who="S0254">spend an evening with him</u>
<u n="551" who="S0253">yeah it's just nice to go to gigs now <pause dur="short"/> like old times</u>
<u n="552" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="553" who="S0253">but I've got a feeling that <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> won't come along</u>
<u n="554" who="S0254">no</u>
<u n="555" who="S0253">so</u>
<u n="556" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="557" who="S0253">oh but erm <pause dur="short"/> I mean I'll see I'll see if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to go to that <trunc>p</trunc> I mean</u>
<u n="558" who="S0254">is he staying here is he that weekend?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0253">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he might go home that night he's gonna stay here for Mogwai</u>
<u n="560" who="S0254">yeah when's that?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0253">on the Friday Friday the twenty-fifth</u>
<u n="562" who="S0254">okay that's fine</u>
<u n="563" who="S0253">erm so that'll be quite late one and then</u>
<u n="564" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="565" who="S0253">I need to book off the <trunc>F</trunc> the Friday off so I'll <unclear>be</unclear> <trunc>s</trunc> as well</u>
<u n="566" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="567" who="S0253">right</u>
<u n="568" who="S0254">and that's it you used up</u>
<u n="569" who="S0253">no I've got one more day I should think</u>
<u n="570" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="571" who="S0253">so I'll just take a three day weekend towards Christmas</u>
<u n="572" who="S0254">yeah <pause dur="long"/> may as well</u>
<u n="573" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0254">why are you looking at stethoscopes?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0253">it's not it's the back to school section on the</u>
<u n="576" who="S0254" trans="overlap">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0253">E45 cream</u>
<u n="578" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and Bio-Oil</u>
<u n="579" who="S0253">Bio-Oil yeah</u>
<u n="580" who="S0254">do they have clipboards?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0253">they've got Aero bubblies on them or something</u>
<u n="582" who="S0254">Rescue Remedy <pause dur="short"/> how many Aeros can you buy? can you like bulk buy them?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0253">yeah of course <pause dur="long"/> Aero Biscuits</u>
<u n="584" who="S0254">mint chocolate multi bar pack of twenty twenty-three pounds?</u>
<u n="585" who="S0253">it'll be RRP it won't be anything special</u>
<u n="586" who="S0254">think of like <pause dur="short"/> what do you call it? industry price</u>
<u n="587" who="S0253">oh <trunc>r</trunc> because you buy loads at once?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0254">yeah bulk buying Aero Bubbles that says a pack of twenty total a hundred and forty <pause dur="short"/> so is there twenty in a <pause dur="long"/> so must be <pause dur="short"/> what's that? seven in a box?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0254">and you're buying twenty <pause dur="short"/> but Aero Biscuit though <pause dur="short"/> is that like a Twix but with Aero Bubble in the middle? I think I've had them</u>
<u n="591" who="S0253">what's the name? what are they called? I <trunc>th</trunc> there's an amazing chocolate bar like the most amazing chocolate bar I've ever had Echos they're called</u>
<u n="592" who="S0254">oh yeah I love Echos</u>
<u n="593" who="S0253" trans="overlap">and they're like</u>
<u n="594" who="S0254">can you still get them?</u>
<u n="595" who="S0253">dark chocolate white chocolate and biscuit</u>
<u n="596" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="597" who="S0253">they're just</u>
<u n="598" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0253">unbelievable</u>
<u n="600" who="S0254">yeah they were good</u>
<u n="601" who="S0253">what was your favourite biscuit when you were a kid?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0254">erm <pause dur="short"/> I always liked a Twix</u>
<u n="603" who="S0253">mm Twix is awesome <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got <trunc>c</trunc> really really happy</u>
<u n="604" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="605" who="S0253">cos he said about cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying how he doesn't drink milk and he says like on his cereal he'll have like a drop of milk</u>
<u n="606" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like me</u>
<u n="607" who="S0253">and he yeah cos I was saying about how I I really understand why people don't like the idea of it and then we get onto like yeah things with milk and stuff you know</u>
<u n="608" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> obviously</u>
<u n="609" who="S0253">obviously</u>
<u n="610" who="S0254">the obviously place to go with that conversation</u>
<u n="611" who="S0253">I was pretty drunk at the time</u>
<u n="612" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0253">erm and then <pause dur="short"/> but then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was just saying how like he erm <pause dur="short"/> his his like guilty pleasure is like a muffin and a glass of milk</u>
<u n="614" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0253">and I was like yes</u>
<u n="616" who="S0254">that's a good pleasure</u>
<u n="617" who="S0253">they are both of my favourite things</u>
<u n="618" who="S0254">mm <pause dur="short"/> I'd understand that but <pause dur="short"/> I just don't like it</u>
<u n="619" who="S0253">yeah it's weird isn't it?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0254">yep mm</u>
<u n="621" who="S0253">let's play a game let's play</u>
<u n="622" who="S0254" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="623" who="S0253">let's play let's make a list of our Christmas presents now</u>
<u n="624" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I want I want a nice I want a flour sifter</u>
<u n="625" who="S0253">okay you can choose it</u>
<u n="626" who="S0254">no I it's on our wish list just it'll come on my wish list</u>
<u n="627" who="S0253">oh now it's in <trunc>m</trunc> now it's in my wish list which one do you want?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0254" trans="overlap">no I want a fancy one go and er search my wish list that one</u>
<u n="629" who="S0253">this one?</u>
<u n="630" who="S0254">yeah <trunc>retr</trunc>retro flour sifter</u>
<u n="631" who="S0253">you know the rule with kitchen appliances or kitchen just is is that</u>
<u n="632" who="S0254" trans="overlap">what is</u>
<u n="633" who="S0253">for every one you buy you have to throw one away</u>
<u n="634" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no but</u>
<u n="635" who="S0253">so so</u>
<u n="636" who="S0254" trans="overlap">I haven't got a flour sifter</u>
<u n="637" who="S0253">exactly so you'll have to <trunc>par</trunc></u>
<u n="638" who="S0254" trans="overlap">so I can't throw one away</u>
<u n="639" who="S0253" trans="overlap">er how how attached are you to the pans cos they'll have to go</u>
<u n="640" who="S0254" trans="overlap">all three I'll probably</u>
<u n="641" who="S0253">which one?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0254">your nan's one</u>
<u n="643" who="S0253">that's horrible</u>
<u n="644" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm joking I wouldn't do that</u>
<u n="645" who="S0253">and that is a better quality pan than anything</u>
<u n="646" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="647" who="S0253" trans="overlap">else we've got</u>
<u n="648" who="S0254">it is we'll throw the one pound fifty-one away from Asda I would like that and the erm icing sugar shaker</u>
<u n="649" who="S0253">I don't like it it looks a bit it's like</u>
<u n="650" who="S0254">don't you like it?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0253">it's bit pastiche</u>
<u n="652" who="S0254">what does pastiche mean?</u>
<u n="653" who="S0253">I'm not quite sure I just use words like that all the time <vocal desc="laugh"/> I use I use words I use them and I don't know what they means erm</u>
<u n="654" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="655" who="S0253">pastiche</u>
<u n="656" who="S0254" trans="overlap">the person on the recorder will be like mm incorrect use of pastiche</u>
<u n="657" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="659" who="S0253">I hope I hope no-one judges that</u>
<u n="660" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="661" who="S0253">no I think I believe pastiche is like is when you take you take like an old style of something</u>
<u n="662" who="S0254">and do it badly</u>
<u n="663" who="S0253">no cos that's parody <pause dur="short"/> so like</u>
<u n="664" who="S0254">mm but parody is like a comedy isn't it?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0253">no <trunc>pa</trunc></u>
<u n="666" who="S0254" trans="overlap">if you're parodying something</u>
<u n="667" who="S0253">yeah so like</u>
<u n="668" who="S0254">you're looking at comic effect</u>
<u n="669" who="S0253" trans="overlap">so it's so it's so it's without irony so like</u>
<u n="670" who="S0254">okay</u>
<u n="671" who="S0253">but this <pause dur="long"/> yeah it's where I think if you look at it it's like it looks like that kind of fifties</u>
<u n="672" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0253">retro styling</u>
<u n="674" who="S0254">but I don't I like I like the the motion of it the I like the gadget</u>
<u n="675" who="S0253">but that's gonna oh <pause dur="short"/> see this is me saying I don't care about what like what <trunc>goe</trunc> er goes in my house <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="676" who="S0254" trans="overlap">that's okay you don't have to if you don't agree then we won't have it in our kitchen</u>
<u n="677" who="S0253">well it I think if if if you're one of those people that like love Elvis Presley and loves the fifties and has like <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> a a jukebox in your house then yeah</u>
<u n="678" who="S0254">what other flour sifters have they got then? have they got any nicer ones?</u>
<u n="679" who="S0253">and I'm surprised that there's there's there's more than one in existence</u>
<u n="680" who="S0254">oh yeah I've never seen them before</u>
<u n="681" who="S0253"><trunc>s</trunc> well what what about a nice chrome one?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0254">mm cos they're boring</u>
<u n="683" who="S0253">they're futuristic though</u>
<u n="684" who="S0254">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="685" who="S0253">they're all pretty much the same aren't they apart from that one</u>
<u n="686" who="S0254">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay well we probably won't <trunc>p</trunc> chase it then</u>
<u n="687" who="S0253">how about that one? Mrs Anderson's baking three cup stainless steel crank flour sifter</u>
<u n="688" who="S0254">mm cos it's still stainless steel <pause dur="short"/> that's more expensive as well</u>
<u n="689" who="S0253">so? <pause dur="short"/> how much is that one? so you want that retro flour sifter yeah? I'm just gonna put it on the list <pause dur="short"/> add to wedding list</u>
<u n="690" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="691" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="692" who="S0254">add it <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> you don't have to buy it me</u>
<u n="693" who="S0253">see it's all this stuff isn't it?</u>
<u n="694" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="695" who="S0253">power</u>
<u n="696" who="S0254">not the measuring cup I think that's a bit pointless</u>
<u n="697" who="S0253">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing I think people would have like a whole fifties sort of diner</u>
<u n="698" who="S0254" trans="overlap">set</u>
<u n="699" who="S0253">diner style</u>
<u n="700" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="701" who="S0253">things anything else you want?</u>
<u n="702" who="S0254">erm</u>
<u n="703" who="S0253">just just say stuff cos I need to get ideas</u>
<u n="704" who="S0254">I like the Emma Bridgewater spice jars</u>
<u n="705" who="S0253">Emma Bridgewater spice</u>
<u n="706" who="S0254">spice tins I think they are</u>
<u n="707" who="S0253">spice tins</u>
<u n="708" who="S0254">might not have them it's old stock oh that's it so look see and it comes with erm loads of different labels so you can put your own labels on but it doesn't match all</u>
<u n="709" who="S0253" trans="overlap">does it <trunc>ac</trunc></u>
<u n="710" who="S0254">doesn't</u>
<u n="711" who="S0253" trans="overlap">does it does it actually have space these look rubbish</u>
<u n="712" who="S0254">yeah they don't have they don't match my Orla Kiely so everything has to match <trunc>Or</trunc>Orla now <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="long"/> I don't want to be one of those people that has like an entire collection of something</u>
<u n="713" who="S0253">feel like I'm in like Revolutionary Road</u>
<u n="714" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> you don't have to get me anything for the kitchen I'm quite happy with the spices being in their own spice jars that you buy them in <pause dur="short"/> I'm okay with that</u>
<u n="715" who="S0253">mm <pause dur="long"/> I dunno I don't like it when everything matches</u>
<u n="716" who="S0254">yeah no I don't either <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="717" who="S0253">sort of just</u>
<u n="718" who="S0254" trans="overlap">I like it to be I like it to erm complement but not like the entire Orla Kiely set <pause dur="short"/> like it can't look it can't clash <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="719" who="S0253">but that's what it appeals to doesn't it like sort of people's like <pause dur="short"/> fascinated with like order and like</u>
<u n="720" who="S0254" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="721" who="S0253" trans="overlap">everything matches and everything looks the same sort of kind of <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0254" trans="overlap">we need to make our seat colours</u>
<u n="723" who="S0253">I wanna get a better chair for the office</u>
<u n="724" who="S0254">what's wrong with the chair we've got?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0253">it's not comfortable</u>
<u n="726" who="S0254">isn't it?</u>
<u n="727" who="S0253">well</u>
<u n="728" who="S0254">well you haven't been in wow look at that</u>
<u n="729" who="S0253">what?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0254">it's like</u>
<u n="731" who="S0253">a hundred <trunc>fift</trunc></u>
<u n="732" who="S0254" trans="overlap">a hundred and sixty quid <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="733" who="S0253">just something a bit more comfortable than the one we've got</u>
<u n="734" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="735" who="S0253">I just can't lean back on it anything like that I feel</u>
<u n="736" who="S0254">yeah you feel like you're gonna tip over</u>
<u n="737" who="S0253">no I just feel like my back's breaking</u>
<u n="738" who="S0254">oh <pause dur="short"/> that one's quite nice Barcelona office chair</u>
<u n="739" who="S0253">that is nice</u>
<u n="740" who="S0254">what colours do they have? I like the cream actually</u>
<u n="741" who="S0253">no-one's gonna see it</u>
<u n="742" who="S0254">I know but</u>
<u n="743" who="S0253">just me</u>
<u n="744" who="S0254">eventually they might</u>
<u n="745" who="S0253">when?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0254">I don't know if we move house and <pause dur="short"/> I want it matching we wanna make our nice office <pause dur="short"/> we need to do something with that blind I think <pause dur="short"/> cos it's gonna get really cold in there soon</u>
<u n="747" who="S0253">this is your interest isn't it?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0254">what?</u>
<u n="749" who="S0253">like</u>
<u n="750" who="S0254">interior design</u>
<u n="751" who="S0253" trans="overlap"><trunc>fur</trunc>furniture do you ever think you were wasted in psychology?</u>
<u n="752" who="S0254">yeah possibly</u>
<u n="753" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="754" who="S0254">I'm no good at it though I just copy other people's ideas</u>
<u n="755" who="S0253">what psychology?</u>
<u n="756" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="757" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> just just stealing other people's research</u>
<u n="758" who="S0254">mm <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I like interior design I'm I don't have my own style I just steal things I wouldn't be interested in doing it as a career</u>
<u n="759" who="S0253">but but <trunc>wh</trunc></u>
<u n="760" who="S0254" trans="overlap">other people</u>
<u n="761" who="S0253" trans="overlap">what happens when er you get your house exactly how you want it?</u>
<u n="762" who="S0254">then I'll be quite happy then so I probably won't bother looking</u>
<u n="763" who="S0253">really?</u>
<u n="764" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="765" who="S0253">I don't think that's true</u>
<u n="766" who="S0254">do you not?</u>
<u n="767" who="S0253">no</u>
<u n="768" who="S0254">I think I'd be one of those people who'd decorate their house every <pause dur="short"/> six months</u>
<u n="769" who="S0253">no cos you'd be skint but</u>
<u n="770" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="771" who="S0253">dunno it's just just an interest like anything else isn't it?</u>
<u n="772" who="S0254">yeah it's just</u>
<u n="773" who="S0253">just an expensive</u>
<u n="774" who="S0254" trans="overlap">wiles away the</u>
<u n="775" who="S0253" trans="overlap">just just an expensive hobby we've got <trunc>wh</trunc> like <pause dur="short"/> from now I've got friends who do that like they they they redecorate</u>
<u n="776" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="777" who="S0253"><trunc>an</trunc>annually sometimes biannually</u>
<u n="778" who="S0254">we need to stay in touch with them so we can get their hand-me-downs</u>
<u n="779" who="S0253">someone was talking about going to erm if you go to auctions</u>
<u n="780" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="781" who="S0253">erm I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying that his couches are really nice and like designer couches but <pause dur="short"/> they're they're like John Lewis couches or something</u>
<u n="782" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="783" who="S0253">is that expensive?</u>
<u n="784" who="S0254">yeah John Lewis is quite expensive</u>
<u n="785" who="S0253">but they erm but they got them from an auction or something that to me that sounds really reasonable</u>
<u n="786" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="787" who="S0253">I</u>
<u n="788" who="S0254" trans="overlap">sounds like a good idea <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="789" who="S0253">erm <pause dur="short"/> you know just not sure I want like a haunted couch or anything</u>
<u n="790" who="S0254">a haunted couch <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="791" who="S0253">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="792" who="S0254">do you think that's how they'll market it? auction haunted couch lot number</u>
<u n="793" who="S0253">it was once</u>
<u n="794" who="S0254" trans="overlap">thirty-one</u>
<u n="795" who="S0253">it was one covered in</u>
<u n="796" who="S0254">in dead bodies</u>
<u n="797" who="S0253">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="798" who="S0254" trans="overlap">an old woman died on this couch</u>
<u n="799" who="S0253">great <pause dur="short"/> that must be why they go cheap though surely</u>
<u n="800" who="S0254">no it's just people redecorating and getting rid of stuff or downsizing or</u>
<u n="801" who="S0253">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0254" trans="overlap">I was looking on that Preloved website</u>
<u n="803" who="S0253">what's on it? does that have everything on it?</u>
<u n="804" who="S0254">yeah it has all sorts</u>
<u n="805" who="S0253">do they have guitars cos maybe I</u>
<u n="806" who="S0254">maybe yeah</u>
<u n="807" who="S0253">I need a guitar</u>
<u n="808" who="S0254">probably <pause dur="short"/> oh do you want any hamsters? do we want any more hamsters?</u>
<u n="809" who="S0253">no who's who's offering hamsters? do you</u>
<u n="810" who="S0254" trans="overlap">no-one's offering us hamsters <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> asked me if he wanted me to <trunc>s</trunc> if I wanted him to sell the hamster cage and I said I'd talk to you about it cos you bought it as a present for me so <pause dur="short"/> and then once I'd said it</u>
<u n="811" who="S0253" trans="overlap">would I be offended?</u>
<u n="812" who="S0254">I was like okay do I want hamsters again? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="813" who="S0253">erm</u>
<u n="814" who="S0254">but</u>
<u n="815" who="S0253">no</u>
<u n="816" who="S0254">really they are</u>
<u n="817" who="S0253">you didn't look after the last two very well</u>
<u n="818" who="S0254">they lasted ages they lived to about three for little dwarfy hamsters that's a really good age</u>
<u n="819" who="S0253">ah Lennie and George</u>
<u n="820" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="821" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="822" who="S0254">I know I don't think I ever had any pictures of them <pause dur="short"/> I don't remember taking a picture of them</u>
<u n="823" who="S0253">I used to have some on my phone</u>
<u n="824" who="S0254">did you?</u>
<u n="825" who="S0253">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> kept them a week or something</u>
<u n="826" who="S0254">that was a great present or possibly one of the best presents you ever got me for the sheer surprise factor <pause dur="short"/> cos we could call them like Curley for one and then I couldn't remember any other characters erm <unclear/> or something</u>
<u n="827" who="S0253">oh what's his name? <pause dur="short"/> it was the stable boy</u>
<u n="828" who="S0254">I know that's who I was trying to think but I can't remember</u>
<u n="829" who="S0253">it's like a don't wanna name <trunc>char</trunc> a series of hamsters names after</u>
<u n="830" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="831" who="S0253">John Steinbeck characters <pause dur="short"/> so I don't get this website what's the deal is it essentially Ebay?</u>
<u n="832" who="S0254">erm to yeah and you don't bid you just buy</u>
<u n="833" who="S0253">you just buy</u>
<u n="834" who="S0254">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you can offer a price I think <pause dur="short"/> sometimes</u>
<u n="835" who="S0253">and like</u>
<u n="836" who="S0254">like a car it's an internet version of a car boot sale</u>
<u n="837" who="S0253">I want a like an actual classical guitar not like a children's one <pause dur="long"/> that looks nice</u>
<u n="838" who="S0254">cedar top</u>
<u n="839" who="S0253">a hundred and sixty pounds</u>
<u n="840" who="S0254">that looks like the furthest possible point from us <pause dur="short"/> you have to put <anon type="place"/> in so you don't get</u>
<u n="841" who="S0253">where's that?</u>
<u n="842" who="S0254">erm they had a little thing it was like Portsmouth for something</u>
<u n="843" who="S0253">Portsmouth? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="844" who="S0254">it's a bit of a long way to go</u>
<u n="845" who="S0253">bit of a do it for pickup</u>
<u n="846" who="S0254">oh you may like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="847" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="848" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="849" who="S0253"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was on today about well when you saying about how there should be a a Magna Carta for the internet</u>
<u n="850" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="851" who="S0253">like there should be a sort of direct</u>
<u n="852" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="853" who="S0253">it's quite an interesting point but then <pause dur="short"/> do you think like people don't take that seriously it's like oh don't be silly the internet doesn't need a bill of rights but it's just accelerating isn't it in its importance in your life and</u>
<u n="854" who="S0254" trans="overlap">mm but it does need some regulation really doesn't it?</u>
<u n="855" who="S0253">badly <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> this website's rubbish</u>
<u n="856" who="S0254">your computer's rubbish</u>
<u n="857" who="S0253">no it's not</u>
<u n="858" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="859" who="S0253">it is it's really it's got worse somehow</u>
<u n="860" who="S0254">er I dunno just people aren't selling what you want to buy that's all</u>
<u n="861" who="S0253">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm trying to think there was loads of things I wanted and I was excited about my my shopping spree tonight</u>
<u n="862" who="S0254" trans="overlap">your evening of shopping</u>
<u n="863" who="S0253">and I can't think of anything that I wanted to buy</u>
<u n="864" who="S0254">it's always always the way</u>
<u n="865" who="S0253">I'm not buying any more books until I've finished</u>
<u n="866" who="S0254">no don't buy any more books we've got no more space for books</u>
<u n="867" who="S0253">oh but we've got space for</u>
<u n="868" who="S0254">a flour sifter</u>
<u n="869" who="S0253">a flour</u>
<u n="870" who="S0254">yes we've got space</u>
<u n="871" who="S0253" trans="overlap">a retro flour sifter</u>
<u n="872" who="S0254">got the space for a retro flour sifter</u>
<u n="873" who="S0253">what else do can you think of anything we need for here?</u>
<u n="874" who="S0254">just stuff that you want to make it more homely for you to make it feel like your home rather than my home</u>
<u n="875" who="S0253"><shift new="singing"/> I'm welcome no more <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="876" who="S0254">a poster you were gonna buy a poster</u>
<u n="877" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> a poster</u>
<u n="878" who="S0254">you were gonna buy a like nice art weren't you for the living room</u>
<u n="879" who="S0253">I know but now I just don't want to</u>
<u n="880" who="S0254">why?</u>
<u n="881" who="S0253">cos we'll we'll be out of here in February</u>
<u n="882" who="S0254">yeah but we'll be somewhere else</u>
<u n="883" who="S0253">true <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="long"/> trying to think of stuff stuff we need</u>
<u n="884" who="S0254">it's not about stuff you need it's about stuff you want you want stuff you want</u>
<u n="885" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> awkward</u>
<u n="886" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="887" who="S0253">no</u>
<u n="888" who="S0254">what about a new bedspread don't you feel the need to buy a new bedspread that you've chosen? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="889" who="S0253">no I like this bedspread</u>
<u n="890" who="S0254">I like this one too I haggled for this in the <anon type="place"/> or whatever the place is called</u>
<u n="891" who="S0253">I thought you were gonna say like Dar es Salaam or something like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="892" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="893" who="S0253">like I haggled for this in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="894" who="S0254"><anon type="place"/> road and there was like a market day where you could haggle for stuff <pause dur="short"/> it was fun</u>
<u n="895" who="S0253">that's good</u>
<u n="896" who="S0254">I always think that shop's going to go bankrupt and it just always seems to have a closing down sale but always keeps just keeps going</u>
<u n="897" who="S0253">that's the sort of business strategy in <anon type="place"/> street at the moment</u>
<u n="898" who="S0254">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="899" who="S0253">it's like closing down</u>
<u n="900" who="S0254">last chance</u>
<u n="901" who="S0253">like your last chance to buy</u>
<u n="902" who="S0254" trans="overlap">it's like The Works it's the <pause dur="short"/> bedding equivalent of The Works it's always closing down</u>
<u n="903" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="904" who="S0254">end of line stock and <pause dur="short"/> it's good though</u>
<u n="905" who="S0253">I want a jacket</u>
<u n="906" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="907" who="S0253">but that's not like</u>
<u n="908" who="S0254" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> how much are you willing to spend?</u>
<u n="909" who="S0253">on this company?</u>
<u n="910" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="911" who="S0253">I'd spend it all</u>
<u n="912" who="S0254"><vocal desc="yawn"/> mm</u>
<u n="913" who="S0253">did you hear about those</u>
<u n="914" who="S0254" trans="overlap">dad's going to Norway on Friday</u>
<u n="915" who="S0253">is he?</u>
<u n="916" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="917" who="S0253">that'll be good</u>
<u n="918" who="S0254">mm <pause dur="short"/> I'm quite jealous I think we should go on a driving holiday there</u>
<u n="919" who="S0253">pardon?</u>
<u n="920" who="S0254">I think we should go on a driving holiday in Norway</u>
<u n="921" who="S0253">I'd be more than happy to do that with you</u>
<u n="922" who="S0254">you need to learn to drive though and then be comfortable driving on the opposite side of the road up a mountain <vocal desc="laugh"/> so we can share the driving</u>
<u n="923" who="S0253">these jackets are all like six hundred pounds</u>
<u n="924" who="S0254">oh my god that one's only two hundred and ninety</u>
<u n="925" who="S0253">which one?</u>
<u n="926" who="S0254">the winter parka W</u>
<u n="927" who="S0253">I'm sure they're very good but it's just the same as like North Face or anything like that</u>
<u n="928" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="929" who="S0253">they're just so expensive</u>
<u n="930" who="S0254">they don't look particularly special</u>
<u n="931" who="S0253">that's the branding though isn't it like</u>
<u n="932" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="933" who="S0253" trans="overlap">it's <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="934" who="S0254">I don't like the <trunc>f</trunc>feather downed</u>
<u n="935" who="S0253">no I don't really <pause dur="long"/> so have you got any plans for this week?</u>
<u n="936" who="S0254">erm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I don't think at all <pause dur="short"/> in every night and then Friday go straight to Wales and I'll be back on Sunday <pause dur="short"/> what are you planning? oh yeah you'll go are you gonna go home after work on Friday?</u>
<u n="937" who="S0253">er yeah I should what I should do is just pack my bag and go home</u>
<u n="938" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="939" who="S0253">but I always I just</u>
<u n="940" who="S0254" trans="overlap">you should</u>
<u n="941" who="S0253">I feel too busy on the Thursday I go to work and then I get a bus back here then I get a bus back to town it's just stupid</u>
<u n="942" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="943" who="S0253">erm <pause dur="short"/> so yes I'm gonna pack my bag I mean because I I thought I was gonna see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on on Friday but he just said oh midweek would be better</u>
<u n="944" who="S0254"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="945" who="S0253"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="946" who="S0254">oh <pause dur="short"/> you've never called him <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="947" who="S0253">sometimes we call people by their first names</u>
<u n="948" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="949" who="S0253" trans="overlap"><trunc>occ</trunc><trunc>occa</trunc>occasionally</u>
<u n="950" who="S0254">his brother's broken up with his girlfriend</u>
<u n="951" who="S0253">that's sad</u>
<u n="952" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="953" who="S0253">I think he said it was <trunc>c</trunc> I remember <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> saying it was a long time coming though</u>
<u n="954" who="S0254">oh I know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was quite pleased about it but <pause dur="short"/> she's er</u>
<u n="955" who="S0253">she</u>
<u n="956" who="S0254" trans="overlap">not taking it too well anyway <pause dur="short"/> despite the fact that he was the one kind of <pause dur="short"/> holding her back really he's quite happy to sit and play games <pause dur="short"/> all day every day</u>
<u n="957" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="958" who="S0254">like he doesn't wanna go on holiday he doesn't wanna move out he doesn't wanna get a job or a life</u>
<u n="959" who="S0253">this is what a</u>
<u n="960" who="S0254" trans="overlap">it seems</u>
<u n="961" who="S0253"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to me <pause dur="short"/> that was his concern</u>
<u n="962" who="S0254">about <pause dur="short"/> his brother?</u>
<u n="963" who="S0253">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean it you shouldn't like you shouldn't sort of deride him <trunc>f</trunc> you know because his interest is computer games it's no different from being interested in</u>
<u n="964" who="S0254" trans="overlap">mm yeah of course</u>
<u n="965" who="S0253">play playing the Sunday league or</u>
<u n="966" who="S0254">but I I like painting but I don't sit at home all day every day and refuse to get a job</u>
<u n="967" who="S0253">but but but you're not</u>
<u n="968" who="S0254" trans="overlap">because I like painting</u>
<u n="969" who="S0253">but you're not like er you know you're not obsessed with it like and you know I think I tend to think with computer games people who don't play them often thing oh god sitting at home and playing computer games and they picture like a teenage boy in a bedroom with a Lara Croft poster</u>
<u n="970" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="971" who="S0253">but <trunc>th</trunc> he one I know for a fact that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is is like you know incredibly good at like certain computer games and it's it's his interest it's his passion</u>
<u n="972" who="S0254">yeah I know but</u>
<u n="973" who="S0253">but I know what you mean I'm not saying that's an excuse I mean <pause dur="short"/> hamburgers are my passion but <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't break up with you just so I could eat more <trunc>hambur</trunc> I probably would</u>
<u n="974" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="975" who="S0253">I probably would</u>
<u n="976" who="S0254">I take it back I would</u>
<u n="977" who="S0253">erm</u>
<u n="978" who="S0254">but you know unless he's pursuing that in some sort of</u>
<u n="979" who="S0253">professional</u>
<u n="980" who="S0254">yeah way</u>
<u n="981" who="S0253">but why does everything always have to be job? like</u>
<u n="982" who="S0254">well it doesn't but you can't you've gotta make a choice haven't you you either try and make that your job or you have to get a job and do that in your spare time like you can't choose to not work and live at home with your parents and <pause dur="short"/> because you don't and like not want anything else cos you just wanna spend all your money on computer games that's <pause dur="short"/> you <trunc>ca</trunc>can't really do that can you that's not being</u>
<u n="983" who="S0253">no</u>
<u n="984" who="S0254" trans="overlap">not grown up</u>
<u n="985" who="S0253">no I agree <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="986" who="S0254">I feel like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like that <pause dur="short"/> well I'm just gonna hold out until I'm a computer game expert <pause dur="short"/> how exactly do you expect to be a computer game expert when you're just sat in your bedroom? as if like someone's gonna knock on his bedroom door and be like oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> er <pause dur="short"/> there's this professional like computer game tester job opened up do you wanna do it? and that's just not gonna happen is it <pause dur="short"/> so people are quite naïve</u>
<u n="987" who="S0253"><trunc>ye</trunc>yeah that's it I do see your point</u>
<u n="988" who="S0254">like I don't</u>
<u n="989" who="S0253">I think I think you're just really like <pause dur="short"/> it's just not in your it that's not in your sort of nature to to to think like that or to be like that so</u>
<u n="990" who="S0254">mm no no it's not <pause dur="short"/> but like you know I it's fine for people to have</u>
<u n="991" who="S0253" trans="overlap">that sorry just to put that shirt is two hundred and seventy pounds are they having a giraffe?</u>
<u n="992" who="S0254" trans="overlap">a mountaineer mountaineering shirt number three <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="993" who="S0253">I'd feel I'd feel really cool in a mountaineering shirt</u>
<u n="994" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="995" who="S0253">but I'm not paying two hundred and seventy pound</u>
<u n="996" who="S0254" trans="overlap">you would also feel very poor you'd have no money to go or anywhere and wear the shirt <vocal desc="laugh"/> what possible reason can be two hundred and seventy pounds?</u>
<u n="997" who="S0253">it's made from real foxes</u>
<u n="998" who="S0254">oh that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="999" who="S0253">it's not like an ethical company</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0254">made from foxes entwined with gold thread</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>g</trunc> gold thread foxes <pause dur="short"/> but yeah no I dunno I <trunc>ju</trunc> I think it is a bit of a male thing as well <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1002" who="S0254">why I wouldn't <trunc>mi</trunc> like I feel a bit bad that you don't play on your Xbox at all like</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0253">well I've lost interest in it</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0254">well yeah</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0253">I've just grown out of it really I feel like I don't have the time <pause dur="short"/> if I was unemployed I'd be all over it</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1007" who="S0253">but <pause dur="short"/> it it's like it's like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying the other day like he's getting a PS4 like cos he's he's moving in with erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1008" who="S0254">really?</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0253"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0254">I thought he always said live apart that's the best way</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0253">it is that's why they're moving in together next year</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1013" who="S0253">it was meant to be this year</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1015" who="S0253">but erm so they've kind of they've agreed so they're gonna move in together in <anon type="place"/> but I think I think he's quite happy without it</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0253">erm but he said he said obviously I'm gonna have to get a credit card cos I don't think he can really afford it <pause dur="short"/> the or he can't afford the whole shebang</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0253">he's on he's on like a he's got a good job erm but he said so he said I'm just gonna get a PlayStation on my credit card as well and pay it off bit by bit</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> might as well</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0253">erm</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0254" trans="overlap">I'm all about the credit cards</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0253">really?</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0254">yeah you know I've got a credit card</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0253">oh just the stupidest thing</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0254">no <pause dur="short"/> the reason I have got a credit card is because when you buy flights and holidays it if you need the proof and you only get the proof if you've bought it on a credit card so when I went to Australia I bought my flights on a credit card</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0254">then just paid it off the next month essentially or no a couple of months but it's interest free so now I just move it whenever I have to start paying interest I move the account to somebody else</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0254">and then what this one I've got now I bought my car insurance on it because I didn't have enough money to buy my car insurance all in one go</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0254">but if you buy it <trunc>m</trunc>month if you pay the them monthly you end up paying an extra hundred pounds by the end of the year <pause dur="short"/> so I thought well I might as well put it on an interest free credit card and then pay it off monthly and I'll still pay the same amount rather than paying</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0253">oh</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0254">an extra hundred pounds in interest to an insurance company</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0253">yeah I get it just don't</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0254" trans="overlap">so that's why I do it I don't like I don't go out and buy things I can't afford on it</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0253">no</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0254">I'm nearly done <pause dur="short"/> I'm just paying off my car insurance on it</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0253">do you think I can get away with another grey T-shirt?</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0254">I don't like that</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0253">that logo?</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0253">what's wrong with it?</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0254">I don't know I think it's a bit how much is thirty-five quid for that?</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0254">no</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0253">no I'm not allowed to buy it?</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0254">it's it's not very nice it's like the most boring logo</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0253">I know</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0254">it's horrible <pause dur="short"/> you can get a much nicer grey T-shirt than that</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1052" who="S0254">for less money than that</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's all I own just grey T-shirts</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1055" who="S0253">yeah I don't know I just it's I <trunc>neve</trunc> I don't like the idea of money not being my own I really really don't like it and I hate</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0254">I I know exactly how you feel because if I had no way of paying that money off then I'd be freaking out but I can afford to pay it I pay that off a hundred pound a month and I know I'll have paid it off before I start paying interest on it</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0253">mm</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0254">it's just useful to have for things that you have to buy that are very expensive and you don't have the money right now you know you will in like and spreading over two or three months but to pay it all in one go is just a bit too much</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0254">so why pay interest on your overdraft when you can put it on a credit card for free?</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0254">just makes sense you've just gotta be clever with it</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0253">I just yeah I just lose track of it and then most people I know who have got credit cards always have credit cards plural never just one credit card</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah whereas I just have one</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0253">I think of it a bit like the woman who swallowed a fly</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1067" who="S0253">honestly it's like</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0254">like yeah I know I know <trunc>exac</trunc> it does</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0253" trans="overlap">they're not doing it</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0254">most people get out of their depth and then they can't pay what they've bought but that's when people go shopping and put their shopping on a credit card and then they're like oh yeah I'll put it on the credit card I'll put it on the credit card and then they completely lose track of how much they've got on their credit card <pause dur="short"/> and then they can't pay it back in monthly instalments before they have to start paying interest</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0253">yeah I dunno I just I <trunc>d</trunc> whereas I'd like to be frivolous I'd like to be frivolous and just buy like a really nice camera or a really nice computer</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0254">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0253" trans="overlap">for myself and and then just worry about it later but I just <trunc>d</trunc> I always feel that I need to watch what I spend and stuff</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0253">don't know <pause dur="short"/> but erm</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0254">I mean I would say if you were gonna buy I think if you were gonna buy like a Mac or something</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0253">mm</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0254">I'd put that on a credit card</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0253">well then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had the point of saying I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got a Mac didn't he and then he said I said how</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0254" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0253"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="1082" who="S0254">oh did he?</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0253">and I said I said how</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0254" trans="overlap">paid for by mummy and daddy like his flat and everything else he owns</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0253">yeah I said</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0254">well it's true though <pause dur="short"/> how does he afford a Mac on like one day a week employment?</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0253">I said erm</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1089" who="S0253">like <event desc="sound of phone"/> and he said well well basically a case of you get it on a credit card or borrow it off my parents and you know they don't</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0254" trans="overlap">oh and pay them then</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0253">well they don't charge interest my parents don't</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> the bank of mother and father</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0253">mm</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0254">erm <pause dur="short"/> well that's right you could put it on a credit card and you could put you could pay three hundred pounds off it straight away</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0254">and then put a hundred pound each month for the other six months or whatever it would be</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0253">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean you can afford it if you if you're really you're committed</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0254">if you really want it yeah <pause dur="short"/> just do you really want one?</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0253">nope there's other things I want</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0254">exactly</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0253">as well <pause dur="short"/> like an electric toothbrush</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> mm and flights to Australia</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0253">there's that as well <pause dur="short"/> haven't heard <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> actually she was meant to ring me this weekend</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0253">and mum said she hasn't been in touch <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure she's fine</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0254">I'm sure she is she'll be having far too much fun</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0253">there's just a picture of her today in some kind of vineyard</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0254">oh right so she is alright then <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1109" who="S0253">erm</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0254">what have I been tagged in? something borrowed bridesmaids dresses from the eighties</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1112" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think something borrowed applies to her only I will point that out <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1113" who="S0253">you don't have to wear something borrowed do you?</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0254">no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1115" who="S0253">er <pause dur="long"/> do you watch that Gogglebox?</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0254">I have watched it on the past it's quite funny</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0254">there's a family on it that own a store in <anon type="place"/> market <pause dur="long"/> and it's</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0253" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0254">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's quite a few <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> families <pause dur="short"/> there are them that own the store there's someone in like <anon type="place"/> or something in think and there's a</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0254" trans="overlap">old couple from <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> then there's like a posh couple I don't know if they've got different families or on it now</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0254">haven't seen any of this</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0253">that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s new dog</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0254">ah <pause dur="short"/> that's cute it looks like a toy</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> probably is</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I was saying to my mum yesterday cos I was genuinely thinking about it as when I was driving home on Friday I was like wouldn't it be really great if I went home and then mum had just bought a puppy and there was a puppy there</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0253">really?</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0254">yeah and just was thinking about it and I was like that would be really cool and I told my mum and she just started laughing and she said well</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0253" trans="overlap">oh right and <trunc>sh</trunc></u>
<u n="1132" who="S0254" trans="overlap">so that didn't happen</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I <trunc>th</trunc> I I I thought I thought you were gonna say that and then she had one</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0254">oh no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="long"/> I keep telling her that she should because it would make her go out for walks and stuff cos she keeps going on about how she wants to walk more and like every night they need to go out and I said well if you had a dog then that would make you go out wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0254">and she was like no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1137" who="S0253">it's</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0254" trans="overlap">don't start</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0253"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying like cos I I said I'm I'm devoid of something to do with my evenings and he said well <pause dur="short"/> he said I wouldn't</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0254" trans="overlap">have a dog and a baby <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1141" who="S0253" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah that's your solution but he said like because of <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> er he said it <trunc>lit</trunc> it just gets him out the house and he'll he'll get up really early in the morning and take him out</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0253">and it's just a nice thing I used to love walking the dog</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0253">erm <pause dur="short"/> it's just a good way it it's you know it's sort of sad that you feel you have to have an excuse to go for a walk but</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0253">having a dog just you're not you're sort of bit of company and you're not on your own and there's kind of a purpose to it</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0253">you're not just</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0254">forces you out the door a bit more doesn't it cos you have to take for a walk</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0253">yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> so he was it was something like that <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure I could handle a dog</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0254">well it's like that pre baby stage isn't it everyone I know who's had a baby recently has had a dog about a year earlier <pause dur="short"/> it's like a test</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0253">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said it does prepare you</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0253">he said he said it he said it he said it sounds stupid but he said it just gets you used to having to think about</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0254">something else</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0253">yeah and something depending on you and things like that so I'd be really I'd I'd like a dog but I just can't picture having one now</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1160" who="S0254">it would be a cruel in a small flat in <anon type="place"/> and although we are near a park so the thing is though it would be on its own from about eight in the <trunc>morn</trunc> eight o'clock in the morning till oh I suppose you come in in the afternoon</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0253">but not always and then it could be on its</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0253" trans="overlap">it could be on its own like eight till five or something</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0254">mm it's just too long isn't it?</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0254">it's cruel</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0253">what dog would you have if you could have any dog?</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0254">a Spaniel</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0253">you can't you've gotta get over like the</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0254">I know</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0253">your childhood dog it just would never be the same</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0254">mm maybe</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0253">you'd get it and it <trunc>ju</trunc></u>
<u n="1174" who="S0254" trans="overlap">but Berta's exactly the same as Barney</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0253">but you'd get one and it just wouldn't be the same</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0254" trans="overlap">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1177" who="S0253">it's like it's like our friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when she gets that cat</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0254" trans="overlap">when she gets the cat <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1179" who="S0253"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> so</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0254">yeah I really like Border Collies but they're too they need too much walking they're too lively I don't want anything that smells like your dog or <pause dur="short"/> is loads</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1182" who="S0254">really energetic or would like destroy everything</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0253">so you're not looking for an animal</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1185" who="S0253">per se?</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0254">a stuffed dog would be perfect</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0253">or or one that</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0254" trans="overlap">a toy</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0253">like a taxidermy dog</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0254">yeah what do would you have?</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0253">erm</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0254">cos I liked Tish but Tish isn't fluffy she's not cuddly</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0253">I'd have one that like rescued children from mines</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what a kangaroo?</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0253">I was thinking more of Lassie <pause dur="short"/> unsurprisingly</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0254">oh I was thinking of Skippy</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1199" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't think a kangaroo</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1201" who="S0253">erm</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0254" trans="overlap">that'd be <unclear>farmers</unclear> like I was saying about the</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I've never watched Skippy but I'm starting to think about that cos that's the thing isn't it like</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0254"><shift new="singing"/> Skippy Skippy <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1205" who="S0253">I don't have you ever actually seen it?</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0254"><shift new="singing"/> Skippy the bush kangaroo <shift new="normal"/> yeah I have I've seen one</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I'm familiar I'm familiar with the theme</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0254">one episode or something</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0253">but they</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0254" trans="overlap">maybe an end of</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0253">but how does a kangaroo save people from</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0254" trans="overlap">he's fallen down the well</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0253">but how how does the the <pause dur="short"/> does does the kangaroo climb down?</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0254">I don't know</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0253">it's not the <trunc>be</trunc></u>
<u n="1216" who="S0254" trans="overlap">just somehow gets</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0253" trans="overlap">it's not the best animal is it for</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0254" trans="overlap">he just jumps</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0253"><trunc>j</trunc>jumps around</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0254">yeah <pause dur="short"/> anyway maybe I haven't ever seen an episode</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0253">I don't think I have I think it's one of those things that's etched into my brain</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0254" trans="overlap">maybe yeah I made it up in my head</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0253">yeah <pause dur="short"/> could well do <pause dur="short"/> but erm</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0253">did I tell you about the <unclear>Top Gun</unclear> guy the other day?</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0254">mm I don't think so</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0253">is that a miniature spider crawling on the wall?</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0254">oh yeah maybe</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0253">mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't like miniature spiders do you know why I don't like miniature ones?</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0254">cos it means there's bigger ones</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0253">but it also</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0254" trans="overlap">doesn't it mean there are no bigger ones cos the bigger would have eaten it?</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0253">no it means that it's recently been born to something to another one</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1235" who="S0253">that being its first little adventures out of out of the house</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0254">oh</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0253" trans="overlap">but that's going in the wrong direction cos it will get eaten by that one that lives in the corner</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1239" who="S0253">the one in the office is really big now</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> is it?</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0254">you been feeding it?</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0253">I've been giving it giving it pork scratchings every day</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1245" who="S0253">it's massive <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's like Lake Placid</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0254">oh god</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0254">you not killed it?</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0253">no</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0254" trans="overlap">how do you sit in there with it?</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0253">cos it's I don't know I I feel a bit bad</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0254">you</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0253">I killed one today and I feel a bit bad about it</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0253">I mean</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0254">it's the time of year though isn't it?</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0253">well that one's been living there all summer and that's why I feel like I can't kill it it's got it's a bit <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="1258" who="S0254" trans="overlap">and now it's your friend</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0253">it's spent more time in the office than I have</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's more its home and yours</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0253">it's got a it's got a right to be there</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1263" who="S0253">it's like squatters' rights or something</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1265" who="S0253">what's</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0254" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0253">what was I saying before that?</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> about Skippy and <unclear/></u>
<u n="1269" who="S0253">yeah well I know it was Skippy the bush kangaroo erm in terms of a dog I'm not sure</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0254">erm there we are that's what you were talking about</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0253">maybe like <pause dur="long"/> something like warm and kind of like cantankerous like like a kind of dog that's like it doesn't it demand your attention all the time and</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0253">like Jake used to be just kind of fat</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1275" who="S0253">slow and and</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0254">an old dog</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0254">mm</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0253">arthritic</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1281" who="S0253">immediately arthritic have to like</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0254" trans="overlap">I like Cocker Spaniels as well</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0253">mm</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0254">they're nice <pause dur="short"/> I don't like that many dogs actually</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0253">don't you?</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0254">no <pause dur="short"/> most of them just look a bit mm <pause dur="short"/> there's like Westies or Terriers they're all a bit yappy and a bit bitey I don't really like them</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0253">well isn't what's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dog?</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0254">er a Lhasa Apso</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1290" who="S0254">that's just mean</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0253">I love how she hates it though <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1292" who="S0254"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0253">she used to love the <trunc>oth</trunc> like used to be like they'd put all these pictures of it on Facebook</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0254" trans="overlap">but that's a classic case of a really really loved family pet dies so they buy a new dog and then they all just hate it cos it's this horrible mean dog <vocal desc="laugh"/> that bites everyone</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0253" trans="overlap">is that Alfie? Alfie's the current dog</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0254">Alfie is the current dog Ted was the old dog who was a Westie and <trunc>wa</trunc>was like I think pre-existed <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think he was dead old and he <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>m</trunc> he must have been must have got him around the time that like they started having children</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0254">he was about nineteen or something when he died I think oh no maybe not maybe about how old? must have been fourteen fifteen maybe</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0254">so he was about seventeen I think <pause dur="short"/> cos when he got very old he went to live er with his with their nan <pause dur="short"/> cos they were out at the time and stuff</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0253">ah</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0254">erm but yeah <pause dur="short"/> alfie's just a bit grumbly isn't he? he doesn't really like people</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0253">well the funny thing is is that the number of times I've been round to her house for parties and stuff and the dog's never there</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0253">it's always shut in the front room away</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0253">from everyone</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0254">Alfie <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0253">yeah <pause dur="short"/> poor thing</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0254">yeah</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0253">I hope I've got a shirt for it tomorrow</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0254">mm have to go and have a look you must I think you will have won't you?</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0253">perhaps</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0254" trans="overlap">how many did we wash?</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0253">what?</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0254">how many did we wash?</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0253">is it five?</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0254">then maybe you won't</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0254">put a wash in tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> yawnsville</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0253">mm</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0254"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1323" who="S0253">yeah I'm gonna stop this now</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
