<text id="SKJQ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:23:29</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-20</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0198 S0229</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's parent's home, Kent</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Mobile technology, fishing, moving houses, hiring a van, Great Dorset Steam fair, meeting up family, computer games, antiques, lottery.</topics>
		<activity>Elderly father and daughter chatting around the house</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0198">
				<exactage>27</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Gillingham, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South Easten</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>27</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0229">
				<exactage>69</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>69</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0198">not too familiar with Facebook though are you dad?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0229">no <pause dur="short"/> this is as much as I can do to pick my horses out I don't know about bloody Facebook</u>
<u n="3" who="S0198">surprised you use a mobile phone it's about as good as you need</u>
<u n="4" who="S0229">well it ain't got no camera or anything on it</u>
<u n="5" who="S0198">no you don't need a camera though do you?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0229" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> my old Nokia was good I lost it had all the <unclear>bloody</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/> numbers in it didn't I?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0198">when did you lose it?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0229">boot fair</u>
<u n="9" who="S0198">oh yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0229">it was only it had no camera on it just ordinary one <pause dur="short"/> just fell out of my pocket when I got in the car and that was it</u>
<u n="11" who="S0198">that one's alright though isn't it? a similar sort of thing</u>
<u n="12" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0198">just a cheap phone</u>
<u n="14" who="S0229">just a cheap phone that's all sometimes you get reception sometimes you don't it works down at <anon type="place"/> alright</u>
<u n="15" who="S0198">that's this house though isn't it?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0229" trans="overlap">when I'm fishing</u>
<u n="17" who="S0198">oh does it?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0198">ah it's just this house that doesn't get reception</u>
<u n="20" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah really clear down there</u>
<u n="21" who="S0198">it's surprising you'd think on the coast I dunno it'd be too windy or something</u>
<u n="22" who="S0229">no it's alright <pause dur="short"/> just rubbish up there we're in a dip here aren't we?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="24" who="S0229">in a dippy dip</u>
<u n="25" who="S0198">when's the last time you went fishing?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0229">cor blimey four weeks ago</u>
<u n="27" who="S0198">you didn't catch anything did you? and mum was planning a fish supper and</u>
<u n="28" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0198">you had to get KFC</u>
<u n="30" who="S0229">caught a cold</u>
<u n="31" who="S0198">oh did you?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0229">no it was about the only thing we did catch that day that was a waste of money Jesus</u>
<u n="33" who="S0198">who'd you go with? you went on your own?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0229">yeah trouble is time you put your petrol in and get your bait you're looking at forty-five fifty quid</u>
<u n="35" who="S0198">cor</u>
<u n="36" who="S0229">just for the day</u>
<u n="37" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> how long's it take to get there then?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0229">only an hour</u>
<u n="39" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0229">an hour and ten minutes</u>
<u n="41" who="S0198">it's enough in petrol though isn't it?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0229">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it can be good sometimes but <pause dur="short"/> so many <unclear>immigrants</unclear> down there fishing now half of them haven't got a clue what they're doing</u>
<u n="43" who="S0198">trying to catch dinner</u>
<u n="44" who="S0229">yeah catch something <pause dur="short"/> I shall go again shortly I suppose</u>
<u n="45" who="S0198">mm might have to come with you sometime</u>
<u n="46" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0198">I haven't got as much time as I</u>
<u n="48" who="S0229">not at this time you won't will you?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0198">with these <pause dur="short"/> when do you stop going out like what point in the winter can't you fish anymore?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0229">you can fish all the time</u>
<u n="51" who="S0198">ah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0229">winter's better when the cod's about</u>
<u n="53" who="S0198">oh is it? <pause dur="short"/> must be a bit rough down there though isn't it?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0229">yeah it don't matter about that does it? got all the gear <pause dur="short"/> got all the gear to wear there</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="55" who="S0198">I was thinking that actually with erm <pause dur="short"/> cycling like</u>
<u n="56" who="S0229">eh?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0198">do you go when you ride your bike in the rain do you ever wear waterproofs?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0229">I don't go in the rain if I can help it</u>
<u n="59" who="S0198">yeah it's probably not a good idea is it?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0229">well I've got them but you can't it's too much <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> too heavy</u>
<u n="61" who="S0198">designed for fishing aren't they yours?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0229">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="long"/> ain't nothing on there worth <unclear>anything</unclear> tear it up</u>
<u n="63" who="S0198">I think it's just a receipt for something dad <unclear/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0229">yeah so next week we'll have to load the van up early early</u>
<u n="65" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="66" who="S0229">be just one I said to mum how the hell am I going to get over there to pick it up? unless I can leave the car there that day</u>
<u n="67" who="S0198">you should be able to shouldn't you? isn't that the whole idea?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0229">yeah I'll see leave the old car there lock it up mum could take the rest to work</u>
<u n="69" who="S0198">yeah take the</u>
<u n="70" who="S0229">get the driveway clear</u>
<u n="71" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0229">and I can back the van in we can load it up whatever we got</u>
<u n="73" who="S0198">what about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is he gonna be here in the morning to help?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0198">he will be?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0198">but he has to sign on in the afternoon?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0229">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well ten o'clock he signs on</u>
<u n="79" who="S0198">oh</u>
<u n="80" who="S0229">but he'll have <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so we can't take him anyway</u>
<u n="81" who="S0198">ah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0229">I'll have taken the satnav though cos I don't wanna get lost coming back <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0198">yeah coming back on your own</u>
<u n="84" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0198">and then just drop the van off and post the keys</u>
<u n="86" who="S0229">yeah and pick the car up</u>
<u n="87" who="S0198">yeah cos erm you leave it on your property overnight if it gets anything gets happens to it</u>
<u n="88" who="S0229" trans="overlap">oh I know I ain't having it no I ain't having that that can go back straightaway <pause dur="short"/> I won't I won't leave it too late coming back anyway you know once we've done down there then you can get sorted out and settle in can't you?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0229">then I can come away</u>
<u n="91" who="S0198">spend the evening sorting the flat out</u>
<u n="92" who="S0229">cos I wanna get back cos that's card night and all anyway</u>
<u n="93" who="S0198">oh yeah Wednesday night <pause dur="short"/> do you know is mum working a full day that day? or</u>
<u n="94" who="S0229">I don't know</u>
<u n="95" who="S0198">cos she might <unclear/> she</u>
<u n="96" who="S0229">no she's working ain't she? yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0198" trans="overlap">but I mean to <unclear/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0229">be another twelve hour shift <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> we'll sort it out</u>
<u n="99" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm when you pick up the van you wanna look it over and make sure there's no</u>
<u n="100" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0198">scratches or <pause dur="short"/> cos that's another thing they try and do although if you pay eighty pounds</u>
<u n="102" who="S0229">it covers it yeah I think it's eighty-five ain't it?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0198">it's eighty</u>
<u n="104" who="S0229">eighty then there's what the <trunc>dies</trunc> the tank's full of diesel then what it uses you have to put back in</u>
<u n="105" who="S0198">oh is that what they do?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0229">yeah so if you use twenty-five quid's worth of diesel you have to put twenty-five back in</u>
<u n="107" who="S0198">I'll give you the diesel money</u>
<u n="108" who="S0229">well don't worry about that</u>
<u n="109" who="S0198">no you're paying enough out although mum'll pay for the rental won't she?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0229">yeah course she is</u>
<u n="111" who="S0198">but still it's a lot of money</u>
<u n="112" who="S0229">it's only the once ain't it?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0198">yeah until you have to move it all back out again</u>
<u n="114" who="S0229">when you move I mean</u>
<u n="115" who="S0198">you'll have to boot it all won't you?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0229">I'll say we'll take what we think we need and then let the charity shop have the rest</u>
<u n="117" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0229">cos time if you think you're gonna hire a van again <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna cost more than some of the stuff's worth</u>
<u n="119" who="S0198">yeah I suppose so unless I can sell it locally</u>
<u n="120" who="S0229">unless you can sell it locally</u>
<u n="121" who="S0198">some of the stuff like the stuff <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s bringing down there I think his parents are only really lending it to us</u>
<u n="122" who="S0229">are they?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0198">there's tables and chairs and stuff they're not gonna let us sell them on or anything <pause dur="short"/> I think we're gonna have to take them they're gonna have to <trunc>pi</trunc> but that's up to them to pick them back up isn't it?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0229" trans="overlap">I mean the only thing that might be any good at the end of the day is the washing machine</u>
<u n="125" who="S0198" trans="overlap">washing machine yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0229">I'd probably get that in the Ford Focus</u>
<u n="127" who="S0198">maybe the I reckon I could sell the futon locally even if it's for like thirty quid or something</u>
<u n="128" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah keep it tidy keep it <trunc>ti</trunc> yeah you keep it tidy</u>
<u n="129" who="S0198">someone will have to collect it but</u>
<u n="130" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0198">someone'll buy that futons always go <pause dur="short"/> especially with all those students around there</u>
<u n="132" who="S0229">I mean all the pots and pans and that I mean</u>
<u n="133" who="S0198">yeah once pots and pans are used</u>
<u n="134" who="S0229">either chuck them or give them to charity</u>
<u n="135" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0229">anything electrical</u>
<u n="137" who="S0198">I still need <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0229">microwave well it ain't worth worrying about</u>
<u n="139" who="S0198">George Foreman</u>
<u n="140" who="S0229" trans="overlap">depends where you're gonna end up</u>
<u n="141" who="S0198">yeah yeah it does <pause dur="short"/> if I need it all then I need it all don't I?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0229" trans="overlap">if you need then we'll have to get a van back down there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0198">if I go abroad again for a year though</u>
<u n="144" who="S0229">get rid of it all <pause dur="short"/> just get rid of it</u>
<u n="145" who="S0198">see <unclear/> you don't know at that point <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might want a new microwave or George Foreman might go somewhere</u>
<u n="146" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah I don't ah get rid of it <pause dur="short"/> you can't sell it give it as charity <pause dur="short"/> as long as you've got your clothes and that that's the main thing I don't know what what else we'll have to fetch back</u>
<u n="147" who="S0198">I still need to get some er some er <unclear/> forgetting to do it yesterday</u>
<u n="148" who="S0229">what?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0198">like oven dishes stuff to cook like shepherd's pie and that in some oven <trunc>tra</trunc> er oven dishes</u>
<u n="150" who="S0229">yeah oh glass things</u>
<u n="151" who="S0198">well yeah good decent do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0229" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0198">stuff that you can cook stuff without destroying it in the oven</u>
<u n="154" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> like mum's got</u>
<u n="155" who="S0198">mm either glass or</u>
<u n="156" who="S0229">see loads of them at the boot fair</u>
<u n="157" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0229">never thought about them</u>
<u n="159" who="S0198">that's alright I'll get them and then maybe I'll like you said</u>
<u n="160" who="S0229" trans="overlap">I mean with when you're going to <anon type="place"/> there's boot fairs there</u>
<u n="161" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0229">and there's a big one <vocal desc="misc"/> right next to <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> place</u>
<u n="163" who="S0198">mm oh there is yeah oh in that field across the way yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0229"><trunc>ma</trunc>massive one</u>
<u n="165" who="S0198">when is that? on a Saturday or Sunday?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0229" trans="overlap">Sunday morning ten o'clock</u>
<u n="167" who="S0198" trans="overlap">oh that's good cos we're going to the fair on Saturday aren't we?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0229">yeah and there's a boot fair Saturday in <anon type="place"/> itself in the in the market which I'll probably go to early</u>
<u n="169" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0229">and then we can leave for the er thing about nine o'clock half nine get there for ten half ten cos it's a massive place</u>
<u n="171" who="S0198">it's a long old day though are you eating lunch and that there or take food with you?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0229">yeah no eat there</u>
<u n="173" who="S0198">eat there</u>
<u n="174" who="S0229">you wanna see it <pause dur="short"/> you ain't seen <trunc>noth</trunc></u>
<u n="175" who="S0198" trans="overlap">that's like that goes on all night though there's music and stuff in the evening</u>
<u n="176" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's in a it's in a about a thousand acres</u>
<u n="177" who="S0198">wow</u>
<u n="178" who="S0229">in the moor</u>
<u n="179" who="S0198">hope the weather's alright be a bit crap if it's pissing it down all day</u>
<u n="180" who="S0229">oh be knackered <pause dur="short"/> but there's so many big stalls there selling all kinds of food hot food</u>
<u n="181" who="S0198">yeah so you don't have to worry about taking grub then?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0229" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> no it's massive I mean it was years ago I went and <pause dur="short"/> I tell you what it took some walking round</u>
<u n="183" who="S0198">yeah I expect it did</u>
<u n="184" who="S0229">I don't think we made it all</u>
<u n="185" who="S0198">I don't bit of a suppose you did especially since it goes on all night</u>
<u n="186" who="S0229" trans="overlap">the old girl was <pause dur="short"/> the old girl sat down we had to pick her up on the way back she slept for three days <pause dur="short"/> done her right in</u>
<u n="187" who="S0198">there's a erm monster truck show car thing did you see that last time?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0229">no no <pause dur="short"/> I think now I've got the old blue badge I say I think cos we had to park right back up in the field <pause dur="short"/> so we're now I think you're allowed to get a bit closer</u>
<u n="189" who="S0198">ah I should think so</u>
<u n="190" who="S0229">and you go through what everyone goes through a little gate and the tickets and <unclear/> you hand your tickets in at the gate</u>
<u n="191" who="S0198">what if you don't have a ticket yet?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0229">you can't get in</u>
<u n="193" who="S0198">where do I buy a ticket from?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0229">well you buy one there or you <unclear>bring</unclear> it on there</u>
<u n="195" who="S0198">ah I don't think cos it's only up until the thirteenth of August online otherwise you've gotta</u>
<u n="196" who="S0229">oh you so what's it? now you've gotta buy there then <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0198">ah there's some places that you can go and buy them maybe on the Friday there might be somewhere we can go and buy it</u>
<u n="198" who="S0229">yeah we can look on their steam fair they'll tell you where to get it</u>
<u n="199" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0229">I mean you always get in at the gate anyway they'll give you a ticket at the gate</u>
<u n="201" who="S0198">when you drive in?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0229">well when you walk in</u>
<u n="203" who="S0198">oh right</u>
<u n="204" who="S0229">you have to park up outside and then you all just walk in no one drives in unless you wanna stall or pitch there</u>
<u n="205" who="S0198">ah okay</u>
<u n="206" who="S0229">there's too too many people about</u>
<u n="207" who="S0198">yeah <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="208" who="S0229" trans="overlap">and when you buy anything you have to get it on a trolley and pull it all the way back <pause dur="short"/> cor and that's some fucking walk I'm telling you</u>
<u n="209" who="S0198">it's alright free accommodation that's handy</u>
<u n="210" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0198">good timing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not being there</u>
<u n="212" who="S0229">yeah just worked out right ain't it? five cats</u>
<u n="213" who="S0198">oh god I forgot about the animals</u>
<u n="214" who="S0229">oh I don't know why <unclear>they're there</unclear> I really don't</u>
<u n="215" who="S0198"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't wanna come down then?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0229">he don't know?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0198">mm I know <unclear>he</unclear> don't</u>
<u n="218" who="S0229">course he'd come down wouldn't he? <pause dur="short"/> he'd be there in no time <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he keeps saying when we going down grandad?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0198">well you'll be going down the beginning of August with him and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> won't you?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah in the caravan so probably pop down to see <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> while we're there</u>
<u n="221" who="S0198">I'm sure mum will</u>
<u n="222" who="S0229">cos <anon type="place"/> is there innit?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0229">bold and that it's only for a couple of days</u>
<u n="225" who="S0198">oh what on the erm <pause dur="short"/> on the campsite you mean?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0229">no</u>
<u n="227" who="S0198">on the caravan site? oh no just that</u>
<u n="228" who="S0229">am but not</u>
<u n="229" who="S0198"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0229"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0198">there is stuff on the campsite as well isn't there?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0229">yeah swimming pool and that <vocal desc="yawn"/> I dunno at that time of year there <unclear>won't</unclear> be much open</u>
<u n="233" who="S0198">erm take <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s bike down there with you</u>
<u n="234" who="S0229">well it can't get in the car</u>
<u n="235" who="S0198">mm you need a rack for it don't you?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0229">yeah yeah yeah about like that</u>
<u n="237" who="S0198">ah little fella</u>
<u n="238" who="S0229">yeah he'll be alright</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="239" who="S0198">ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about which shop to go to said there's one next to the train station or they're going to Tesco's which is about fifteen minutes</u>
<u n="240" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0198">so I dunno if I should go to the Tesco's here?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0229">you can do if you want it's up to you you've got time to walk up there</u>
<u n="243" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0229">I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will probably come here anyway won't he with his bikes?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0198">oh will he? with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0198">with his bikes?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0229">well yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got a little bike he rides</u>
<u n="249" who="S0198">oh and they cycle up here?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0229">probably</u>
<u n="251" who="S0198">I suppose it depends cos if I was</u>
<u n="252" who="S0229" trans="overlap">and then when they come back tonight</u>
<u n="253" who="S0198">if you're giving us a lift they'll probably come here but if we're getting a train I'll probably go to them</u>
<u n="254" who="S0229">I'll give you <unclear/> shoot over there quickly</u>
<u n="255" who="S0198">I might pop up to Tesco's in five minutes then</u>
<u n="256" who="S0229">well you can do I mean you've got time he ain't he ain't being dropped off till ten o'clock is he?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0198">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't have to get round <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s too early anyway do we?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0229">no eleven o'clock is plenty early enough <pause dur="short"/> get there in time for lunch</u>
<u n="259" who="S0198">got all day there kids</u>
<u n="260" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> screaming kids round you</u>
<u n="261" who="S0198">they do scream</u>
<u n="262" who="S0229">I suppose the other little git'll turn up here this afternoon three or four o'clock</u>
<u n="263" who="S0198">yeah is that what you think's gonna happen today then?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0198">you don't wanna <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would have phoned would she if she was bringing them up this morning now?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he won't be here till tonight this afternoon there</u>
<u n="267" who="S0198">suppose that's alright <pause dur="short"/> as long as you're sure</u>
<u n="268" who="S0229">well</u>
<u n="269" who="S0198">well it's their own fault really they should call you before you take this anywhere shouldn't she?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0198">what time do you need to put your bet on by?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0229">doesn't matter after I drop you off</u>
<u n="273" who="S0198" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> your first race is in the afternoon?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0229">yeah two o'clock <pause dur="short"/> plenty of time</u>
<u n="275" who="S0198">still got to have your daily bet haven't you dad?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0229">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> nothing else to do have I? except sitting here on my own all day</u>
<u n="277" who="S0198">yeah it's your crossword puzzle isn't it?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0229">yeah it is</u>
<u n="279" who="S0198">someone was saying to me actually that I said about you playing your PlayStations and stuff like that and he said that it's actually proven as you get older that it's a good thing to do because it stimulates your brain</u>
<u n="280" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0198">and keeps your coordination active and stuff</u>
<u n="282" who="S0229">well I've got loads of games I need to get a couple more new ones but they come out there's so much rubbish out there though <pause dur="short"/> you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0198" trans="overlap">mm yeah I mean loads of games are rubbish aren't they?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0229">yeah I only like the war games</u>
<u n="285" who="S0198">ah your birthday's coming</u>
<u n="286" who="S0229">all the car racing rubbish that ain't no good to me</u>
<u n="287" who="S0198">if you want anything for your birthday let me know</u>
<u n="288" who="S0229">it'll only be a game if it was out <unclear/> it ain't out yet</u>
<u n="289" who="S0198">or any er DVDs or</u>
<u n="290" who="S0229">well unless there's a good cowboy out a good war film</u>
<u n="291" who="S0198">unless there's anything on at the cinema we can go and watch</u>
<u n="292" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0198">cos your birthday's on a Friday so I was gonna come up from <anon type="place"/> that day</u>
<u n="294" who="S0229">oh are you?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0198">and say hello I shouldn't have university on Friday</u>
<u n="296" who="S0229">yeah well we gotta pick you up or what?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0198">no I'll I'll train unless you wanna come to <anon type="place"/> for your birthday?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0229">we'll see what mum says</u>
<u n="299" who="S0198">have a meal down there for the spend the day round <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0229">see if she's working or not</u>
<u n="301" who="S0198">oh yeah it all depends if she's working yeah might still be alright weather in September</u>
<u n="302" who="S0229">yeah oh well we'll sort something out we'll sort something out dear</u>
<u n="303" who="S0198">are we going to <anon type="place"/> tomorrow?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0229">well yeah I was thinking about it yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean go <unclear/> at <anon type="place"/> but there ain't no <pause dur="short"/> old shops where you can get any bits or anything you know?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0229">I mean I'd go back to <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> have a look there if I had my way but</u>
<u n="307" who="S0198">oh why don't we do that then?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0229">yeah cos that's the only place you get these and these are getting very collectable now and very hard to get believe it or not</u>
<u n="309" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="310" who="S0229">and they're going for good money <pause dur="short"/> feel the weight of that</u>
<u n="311" who="S0198">it looks heavy</u>
<u n="312" who="S0229">that's a proper</u>
<u n="313" who="S0198">ah yeah it's got a nice imprint in it hasn't it?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0229">mm yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0198">Spencers Bromsgrove</u>
<u n="316" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0198">oh yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0229">and the other one the other blue one</u>
<u n="319" who="S0198" trans="overlap">how how much did you give for that one then?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0229">that? thirty quid</u>
<u n="321" who="S0198">that blue one?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0229">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0198">what about that chained one down there?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0229">I bought that little one for a fiver <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0198">cor <pause dur="short"/> but thirty quid for that new one</u>
<u n="326" who="S0229" trans="overlap">the lady that sold me that didn't realise what it bloody was I tell you</u>
<u n="327" who="S0198">that's your own little antique shop in that cupboard isn't it dad?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0229">my own bits in this one?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0198">oh yeah is that the one with the <anon type="place"/> one on it?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0229">no that's <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0198">oh crikey the same style as that one isn't it?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0229">local local one</u>
<u n="333" who="S0198" trans="overlap">ah <unclear/> it's got the original thing on it</u>
<u n="334" who="S0229">yeah of course it has</u>
<u n="335" who="S0198">wouldn't oh it's even got some liquid in it</u>
<u n="336" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0198">wouldn't somebody local want that for their collection?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah <trunc>colle</trunc> oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0198">how much did you give for that one?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0229">three pound</u>
<u n="341" who="S0198">oh where from? boot fair?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0229">boot fair</u>
<u n="343" who="S0198">see <pause dur="short"/> they'd stick a sixty pound price tag on that in a shop in <anon type="place"/> high street</u>
<u n="344" who="S0229">more than that now <pause dur="short"/> be more than that dear</u>
<u n="345" who="S0198">silly are you gonna sell them at any point?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0229">probably not till I get the full set</u>
<u n="347" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0229">I want a red one and a green one</u>
<u n="349" who="S0198">ah is that all the colours they come in?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0229">red one green one yellow one <vocal desc="cough"/> <pause dur="short"/> you need to get the full set you've doubled your money <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0229">it'd be worth a few hundred quid then</u>
<u n="353" who="S0198">mm <pause dur="short"/> playing the waiting game</u>
<u n="354" who="S0229">well you got to ain't you? cos I said it ain't worth getting rid of them when <pause dur="short"/> you could make more money later <pause dur="short"/> I thought you were going up the shop?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0198">yeah I was going I was waiting another couple of minutes</u>
<u n="356" who="S0229">you can do mum's Tesco thing can't you?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0198">lottery?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0229">lottery</u>
<u n="359" who="S0198">you want me to do your lottery while I'm in there?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0229">oh well I only want a couple of dips</u>
<u n="361" who="S0198">you just want two lucky dips?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0198">do I just say two and two lucky dips?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0198">on a separate ticket?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0198">I'll pay for it don't worry <pause dur="short"/> it's only a pound each aren't they?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0229">two pound each</u>
<u n="369" who="S0198">it's two pound a line?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0198">I mean I'll still pay for it</u>
<u n="372" who="S0229">no well pay you out of that just gimme nick the change</u>
<u n="373" who="S0198">no I'll pay for it dad</u>
<u n="374" who="S0229">you wanna save your money</u>
<u n="375" who="S0198">I think you gave me enough change</u>
<u n="376" who="S0229">save your money</u>
<u n="377" who="S0198">I don't want your five pounds</u>
<u n="378" who="S0229">save your money</u>
<u n="379" who="S0198">mm I better be able to buy a single stamp I don't really wanna buy a book of stamps</u>
<u n="380" who="S0229">no wonder mum never had any stamps</u>
<u n="381" who="S0198">I know she had a couple and then people we don't post stuff that much anymore it's usually online or whatnot isn't it?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0229">I don't</u>
<u n="383" who="S0198">I don't think you ever have have you dad? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0229">no I don't even use the stamps <unclear/> mum does your mum normally buys a book</u>
<u n="385" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no she must have been all out</u>
<u n="386" who="S0229">better recharge the <trunc>bat</trunc> no only want a pound</u>
<u n="387" who="S0198"><unclear/> have an extra <unclear>bet</unclear> a pound in your bet</u>
<u n="388" who="S0229" trans="overlap">no don't waste your money I keep telling you you wanna save it for when you get down to <anon type="place"/> and help pay the bills and in the winter time you'll be able to get a bit of grub in</u>
<u n="389" who="S0198">ah might be gone by winter</u>
<u n="390" who="S0229">well anything to help out</u>
<u n="391" who="S0198">it'll help out in the meantime yeah do a load of shopping I'm tempted to bloody do a load of shopping in Morrisons before I go it's cheaper</u>
<u n="392" who="S0229">well do it</u>
<u n="393" who="S0198" trans="overlap">the nearest supermarket's Sainsbury's</u>
<u n="394" who="S0229">I mean</u>
<u n="395" who="S0198">although there is a Morrisons down in <anon type="place"/> it can't be too far from us</u>
<u n="396" who="S0229" trans="overlap">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh it's yeah now you can't don't wanna get stuff if it's gonna thaw out before you get there</u>
<u n="397" who="S0198">no I mean I couldn't buy anything frozen could I?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0229">no</u>
<u n="399" who="S0198">no I'll just do a shop when we get <unclear/> something we'll do that Wednesday evening</u>
<u n="400" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="401" who="S0198">still <vocal desc="yawn"/> ah although I'm only gonna be there for the first couple of days aren't I? and then er</u>
<u n="402" who="S0229">eh?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0198">I'm only gonna be there those first two nights and then I'm coming you're gonna pick me up to go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0229"><anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0198"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll have to hold the fort on his own</u>
<u n="406" who="S0229">yeah well can't be helped can it?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0198">no it'll be fine something I mean it's only really well it's Friday night Saturday night</u>
<u n="408" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0198">his dad might even spend the night</u>
<u n="410" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0198">if he wants to but then no he can't can he? cos he's got to get that van back by eight thirty <unclear/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0229" trans="overlap">well that's it see that's the trouble</u>
<u n="413" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="414" who="S0229">how much did his van cost?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0198">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> looked up some local company in <anon type="place"/> and thought it was gonna cost about forty pounds but maybe he wasn't looking at the right van or <pause dur="short"/> or it wasn't in the right I don't know?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0198"><trunc>seem</trunc> that place seemed more expensive where we went to today er yesterday <pause dur="short"/> so I'm not really sure</u>
<u n="418" who="S0229">I just wondered if we did do need that long wheelbase cos a short wheelbase would be better and it's be better for parking <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> cos I'll</u>
<u n="419" who="S0198" trans="overlap">it's only gotta be the fit a mattress in it hasn't it? how short is short wheel?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0229">no the <pause dur="short"/> futon bed</u>
<u n="421" who="S0198">the futon yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0229">sofa bed</u>
<u n="423" who="S0198">measure it and then look at</u>
<u n="424" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0198">measure the futon and then I'll look up the measurements of the thing</u>
<u n="426" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> van</u>
<u n="427" who="S0198">and then if we have to phone them up and change it we'll change it</u>
<u n="428" who="S0229" trans="overlap">well yeah short wheelbase cos when I when we get down there you might just have a car space to get in and unload</u>
<u n="429" who="S0198">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm sure <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wasn't looking at the biggest vans just ones that were <trunc>li</trunc>like a van <pause dur="short"/> saying that you do wanna have enough space</u>
<u n="430" who="S0229">yeah it it's only the sofa bed really I mean the mattress'll go in easy</u>
<u n="431" who="S0198">mm and the washing machine</u>
<u n="432" who="S0229">the washing machine's nothing</u>
<u n="433" who="S0198">and some boxes and suitcases</u>
<u n="434" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah be</u>
<u n="435" who="S0198">also I was thinking anything like clothes suitcasewise that I mean if there isn't space and there should be space but you can always bring it down in the car</u>
<u n="436" who="S0229" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> there'll be plenty of room to pack it in</u>
<u n="437" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0229">plenty of room</u>
<u n="439" who="S0198">it might be cheaper to get short based</u>
<u n="440" who="S0229" trans="overlap">I ain't worried about that it's just I <unclear/> down the other end</u>
<u n="441" who="S0198">parking?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0229">parking</u>
<u n="443" who="S0198">yeah I mean I have</u>
<u n="444" who="S0229">I mean unloading like you know?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0198">I haven't seen that road so that's that's why in a way I think in a way it's better that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad isn't coming down with a van on the same day</u>
<u n="446" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="447" who="S0198">cos we both have to be there at the same time to sign the contract</u>
<u n="448" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0198">so you'd both be there with your vans I don't think you could both be outside the house would you?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0229">well</u>
<u n="451" who="S0198">maybe if enough people have gone to work</u>
<u n="452" who="S0229">trouble is once we've unloaded unless I can park in anywhere <pause dur="short"/> put my badge in</u>
<u n="453" who="S0198">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0229">well you might be able to get outside the house</u>
<u n="455" who="S0198">I need to look that up actually because you're gonna want <trunc>some</trunc>something to eat and everything before you go home</u>
<u n="456" who="S0229">well there's shops there's loads of shops there</u>
<u n="457" who="S0198">yeah I know but I mean</u>
<u n="458" who="S0229" trans="overlap">there up in the corner's a café</u>
<u n="459" who="S0198">but it's parking in the meantime</u>
<u n="460" who="S0229">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="461" who="S0198">I suppose you can park long enough to have something to eat</u>
<u n="462" who="S0229">yeah there's always somewhere to find to park <pause dur="short"/> with that disabled badge I can get away with it now <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0198">can try and contact the agency and ask them what people do when they're parking when they move all their stuff in</u>
<u n="464" who="S0229" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0198">they might have some er have they got can you park outside the agency did you notice?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0229" trans="overlap">no it's in the main road</u>
<u n="467" who="S0198">er</u>
<u n="468" who="S0229">right in the corner</u>
<u n="469" who="S0198">they haven't got a car park or anything similar?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0229" trans="overlap">no no no <pause dur="short"/> no you just go in and upstairs</u>
<u n="471" who="S0198">mm</u>
<u n="472" who="S0229">the two girls are upstairs</u>
<u n="473" who="S0198">small little operation I suppose</u>
<u n="474" who="S0229">yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0198">it's nearly ten o'clock <unclear/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0229">wanna get up the shop</u>
<u n="477" who="S0198">go quickly up the shop</u>
<u n="478" who="S0229" trans="overlap">get mum's lottery</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
