<text id="SKKU">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:16:13</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-17</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0439 S0441</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Kitchen - home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Work and living situation. Legal problems with renting. </topics>
		<activity>Discussion about legal problems. </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, Inquiring, complaining, advising, requesting, announcing, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0439">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern - Non-accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0441">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridgeshire - Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Mental Health Nurse</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0439">how come it's busy? just in general</u>
<u n="2" who="S0441">loads of calls and stuff <pause dur="short"/> I never I never have any calls when I'm not there but it's just like</u>
<u n="3" who="S0439">the moment you're yeah the moment you're here it's like ah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0441">loads of calls</u>
<u n="5" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="6" who="S0441">how was your day?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0439">erm how was my day? it was fine it was just more like a balancing act between my new job and my old job and</u>
<u n="8" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0439">yeah nothing particularly exciting but just <pause dur="short"/> it's like the girl who I've taken over from has left literally the shittiest instructions</u>
<u n="10" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0439">ever</u>
<u n="12" who="S0441">great</u>
<u n="13" who="S0439">and it's just did you even it's like you it's when someone writes instructions when they know what to do?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0439">they don't write instructions for somebody who will have no idea what they're talking about and it's just</u>
<u n="16" who="S0441">she obviously thinks she's very <unclear>important</unclear></u>
<u n="17" who="S0439">she's an idiot <pause dur="short"/> so I've got that to work through but it should be fine once you've done something once it's fine isn't it? but it's just that first time it's knowing well actually how do I do this?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0439">but erm</u>
<u n="20" who="S0441">you'll get used to it</u>
<u n="21" who="S0439">yeah just feels like she's it feels like it should it feels like it should be much later in the week</u>
<u n="22" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> it's only Tuesday although <unclear/> if you want it</u>
<u n="23" who="S0439">weeks always go quickly at the moment</u>
<u n="24" who="S0441">they do <pause dur="short"/> I wonder when it'll slow down</u>
<u n="25" who="S0439">never it'll get quicker and quicker until we get old and die</u>
<u n="26" who="S0441">when we retire it'll slow down</u>
<u n="27" who="S0439">yeah true <pause dur="short"/> mum okay she found out today that she is gonna be made redundant</u>
<u n="28" who="S0441">oh</u>
<u n="29" who="S0439">yeah but she's quite happy about it actually</u>
<u n="30" who="S0441">well I guess they've dicked her around so much yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah and I think they're gonna have the garage converted and then grandad's gonna come and erm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0441">okay</u>
<u n="33" who="S0439">live at our house so</u>
<u n="34" who="S0441">yeah I had all that lowdown when she was here what she like</u>
<u n="35" who="S0439">yeah when I was late</u>
<u n="36" who="S0441">when you were late or not</u>
<u n="37" who="S0439">but not late yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0441">so <pause dur="short"/> I think she secretly wanted that</u>
<u n="39" who="S0439">oh yeah she definitely was like in the mindset that she wanted to be made redundant if they she hadn't it would have ruined like all her plans</u>
<u n="40" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she would have been upset which is really funny</u>
<u n="41" who="S0439">yeah no</u>
<u n="42" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0439">you've got me in a job?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0439">and I've actually got to do some work?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0441">not lady of leisure anymore</u>
<u n="47" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so yeah she's looking</u>
<u n="48" who="S0441" trans="overlap">she'll quite like being a lady of leisure</u>
<u n="49" who="S0439">me too but I don't think it would be particularly good for her</u>
<u n="50" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh no it won't be good for her but it</u>
<u n="51" who="S0439">like a lazy person who has no like obligation to do anything</u>
<u n="52" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0439">is not very good</u>
<u n="54" who="S0441"><unclear>endless combo</unclear></u>
<u n="55" who="S0439">exactly <pause dur="short"/> but erm yeah so how was today? how was erm how was the phone call?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0441">well it was bloody long it's like er erm who did I ring first? oh the law the <unclear/> place</u>
<u n="57" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0441">and they were like oh this isn't our department so can you call back? and I was like okay that's really helpful and they weren't really <unclear/> anyway it's like <unclear/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0439">yeah of course yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0441">and then I rang the council and they said for me to ring Citizens Advice even though <unclear/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0439" trans="overlap">even though they sent us through a letter</u>
<u n="62" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0439" trans="overlap">being like if you need any help?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I think I think the guy that I spoke to was an idiot basically</u>
<u n="65" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="66" who="S0441">which was fun <pause dur="short"/> erm and <pause dur="short"/> then <pause dur="short"/> I rang Citizens Advice and he was actually very helpful he sent over some stuff in an email about what you can do and told me to ring Shelter so I rang Shelter and that was probably helpfullest</u>
<u n="67" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0441">erm so basically <pause dur="short"/> what it boils down well <trunc>a</trunc>actually no that's not true I spoke to the legal team again first I actually got through to the right department and she</u>
<u n="69" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0441">she was actually quite rude and it really got on my nerves</u>
<u n="71" who="S0439">really?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0441">yeah like just annoying</u>
<u n="73" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0441">so she was just like erm <pause dur="short"/> if we don't pay the <trunc>c</trunc> the money then she could that's what I told you about she could</u>
<u n="75" who="S0439">she could</u>
<u n="76" who="S0441">take legal action against us</u>
<u n="77" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0441">if we haven't met the contract</u>
<u n="79" who="S0439">which no offence if she's not gonna actually make er she's not gonna take the whole erm repossession seriously I doubt if she'll take us to court but I get the point yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah just in case</u>
<u n="81" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I mean we're not about to go to court</u>
<u n="83" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="84" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm so basically she was like I I can't help you basically and I was like fine <vocal desc="laugh"/> er ring Citizens Advice so I already had</u>
<u n="85" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0441">erm so I rang Shelter and they</u>
<u n="87" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0441">sort of said erm if we're in a <trunc>bi</trunc> I think it's basically what we said before if we're in a binding contract then the people that the lender will take over <pause dur="short"/> with the rent paying</u>
<u n="89" who="S0439">oh okay</u>
<u n="90" who="S0441">so we'll just have to pay the lender anyway</u>
<u n="91" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0441">and it would've been a binding contract if the lender was happy that it was it was a tenancy mortgage then it's a binding contract cos they're aware of the situation</u>
<u n="93" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0441">it wouldn't be a binding contract if it wasn't a</u>
<u n="95" who="S0439">tenancy</u>
<u n="96" who="S0441">tenancy mortgage erm and we can find that out the agency might know that or <pause dur="short"/> we</u>
<u n="97" who="S0439">well it's worth asking the question isn't it?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0441">yeah or we just tell them that if <pause dur="short"/> basically if if it is if it isn't a binding contract</u>
<u n="99" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0441">then we have the right to leave anyway because</u>
<u n="101" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="102" who="S0441">she's not our landlady anymore</u>
<u n="103" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0441">erm <pause dur="short"/> it's so difficult like</u>
<u n="105" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0441">cos I'm not I I don't know</u>
<u n="107" who="S0439" trans="overlap">the legalities of it</u>
<u n="108" who="S0441" trans="overlap">the language</u>
<u n="109" who="S0439">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0441" trans="overlap">it's really hard so <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>hang on</unclear> let me just think about this so that was that erm I asked about the in fact I looked at the contract again I I did talk to her about the contract and <trunc>t</trunc> and said about that thing and she said well erm if it says that then erm <pause dur="short"/> because it's a contract you still have to pay because it's a contract</u>
<u n="111" who="S0439">oh okay</u>
<u n="112" who="S0441">and I did actually look into that that contract thing isn't what what what we thought it is anyway</u>
<u n="113" who="S0439">oh is it not?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I I googled it it's not <vocal desc="laugh"/> thank god we didn't go to them and be like look at this <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos it's like actually not even that</u>
<u n="115" who="S0439">what <unclear>does</unclear> it mean?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0441">it means that the tenancy can be ended if she wants to sell her house basically</u>
<u n="117" who="S0439">oh I see</u>
<u n="118" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that was a bit embarrassing</u>
<u n="119" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0441">erm so we haven't even got that clause so what we can do is it's called I always forget what it's called but it's something where you basically what what they said to us when we when they said that we could move out er in December and not pay</u>
<u n="121" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0441">that's called a something er it begins with an S but I can't remember what it's called a surrender a surrender</u>
<u n="123" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0441">erm of the tenancy but they have the right to change that at any time</u>
<u n="125" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="126" who="S0441" trans="overlap">if and and if they decide that that's not gonna happen anymore that's not gonna happen anymore</u>
<u n="127" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="128" who="S0441">if it's not in writing as well</u>
<u n="129" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0441" trans="overlap">you have to sign it both have to sign it and agree to the terms <pause dur="short"/> what we can do though is do another surrender on paper send it to them and say we want to move out on this date erm and then they can come back to us I suppose so that can be an option erm <pause dur="short"/> there was that thing about the deposit but that's fine like they couldn't <trunc>d</trunc>do anything on there so that's fine erm <pause dur="short"/> what else did she <trunc>s</trunc>? oh if it is a binding contract and the lender takes over from the payment the rent receiving the rent then and the estate agents aren't letting us leave on on the said date then we can ring up the lender er and move out in</u>
<u n="131" who="S0439" trans="overlap">what in December?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0441">if it gets repossessed</u>
<u n="133" who="S0439">but we don't have to pay for January?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0441">no we wouldn't cos the lender would probably it would be in our their interest to get us out anyway so</u>
<u n="135" who="S0439">oh I see so</u>
<u n="136" who="S0441" trans="overlap">so if it gets repossessed you can ring the lender and say we wanna move out on this day and then they can <unclear/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="138" who="S0441">cos with the surrender if if they agree to the terms then we can move out without any rent anyway</u>
<u n="139" who="S0439">so what does the surrender include? what does it?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0441">the surrender just says that we're ending our tenancy on this date and that's it it's it's basically if you so for example she she put it to me like in terms of a phone contract so if if you have a phone contract out and it's coming to the end and at the end sort of you say erm I'm not gonna pay the last two months</u>
<u n="141" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0441">because I'm signing a new contract and taking out a new contract with you</u>
<u n="143" who="S0439">oh okay</u>
<u n="144" who="S0441">so basically there has to be something in their interest</u>
<u n="145" who="S0439">but we're not taking out a new contract with them</u>
<u n="146" who="S0441">no I know but it's got to be something from their interests for it to happen so for example they've got new tenants coming or erm I don't know she wants a month to redecorate or something like it's got to be something that's in their interest</u>
<u n="147" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="148" who="S0441">so we haven't really got anything of that</u>
<u n="149" who="S0439">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0441">but I mean it's worth a try if if we actually cos we haven't really explicitly said that we want to move out on a particular date have we? I mean we have but we haven't officially</u>
<u n="151" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0441">emailed them and told them this</u>
<u n="153" who="S0439">I said we wanted well we were gonna have we envisage I said the <unclear/> booked in like</u>
<u n="154" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0439" trans="overlap">the sixteenth and seventeenth</u>
<u n="156" who="S0441" trans="overlap">and I've I've confirmed that with her anyway and she said that's fine</u>
<u n="157" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0441" trans="overlap">we'll confirm that nearer the time but that's what I mean we haven't really got any rights in that</u>
<u n="159" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0441" trans="overlap">cos they are the ones that are releasing us from the tenancy</u>
<u n="161" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0441">so basically I think our next move we we we can't really do anything until we oh that's another thing we we can't find out whether it's been repossessed or not because it's not anything to do with us</u>
<u n="163" who="S0439" trans="overlap">but can we find out if it's a binding contract?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0441">if they have the paperwork but no otherwise not they might not have that paperwork</u>
<u n="165" who="S0439">so could we ring them and ask them if they could we email them and ask them if they have that contract?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0441">uhu well it's it's not them it's kind of the the estate er whether the woman has taken out a mortgage that makes it a binding contract so she <trunc>sh</trunc>she would have had to have taken out a tenancy mortgage</u>
<u n="167" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="168" who="S0441">not a normal mortgage if it's a normal mortgage then it's not a binding contract</u>
<u n="169" who="S0439">and how do and we can't know that?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0441">if they have that information but again if they'd protections in for this into this they might not give us that information anyway</u>
<u n="171" who="S0439">true</u>
<u n="172" who="S0441"><vocal desc="cough"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think it's really bad that there's not a lot of rights for tenants really is there?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="174" who="S0441">cos a lot of the stuff that I was looking at online as well is all to do with landlady rights and landlord rights and stuff and it's nothing really they don't really look at the tenants <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0439">we ought we could ask when they're expecting the new tenants to move in</u>
<u n="176" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0439">cos I very much think it's unfair that if they're that's if we move out and the the new tenants move in like the day before and they haven't</u>
<u n="178" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I don't think they know though to be honest and I don't think</u>
<u n="179" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh do they not?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0441">I don't think they <trunc>tol</trunc> they told them about this potential repossession</u>
<u n="181" who="S0439" trans="overlap">repossession <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0441">so until we know when they're moving in and until we know what's gone on we're not I don't think we should pay the rent on the sixteenth anyway I mean we'll pay it if we need to but we just won't</u>
<u n="183" who="S0439">pay it bang on the sixteenth</u>
<u n="184" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="185" who="S0439">well we should find out by the <unclear>fortieth</unclear> shouldn't we?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0441">probably not cos it's gonna come out by by post so it won't come out like <trunc>w</trunc>we won't know on the fourteenth cos we haven't got the rights to that information</u>
<u n="187" who="S0439">do we have the right to know whether she attended the hearing?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="189" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="190" who="S0441">we have no right to know like anything <pause dur="short"/> we'll know the outcome</u>
<u n="191" who="S0439">well yeah obviously <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0441">but they'll notify the outcome by post <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0439">mm okay</u>
<u n="194" who="S0441">so really at the moment it's looking like we'll probably have to pay</u>
<u n="195" who="S0439">disaster okay</u>
<u n="196" who="S0441">but</u>
<u n="197" who="S0439">it's just so poorly organised by them</u>
<u n="198" who="S0441">I know they don't know whether they're coming or going really</u>
<u n="199" who="S0439">cos we were we were just <trunc>li</trunc> so explicit when we said we wanted to move out</u>
<u n="200" who="S0441">I know</u>
<u n="201" who="S0439" trans="overlap">at the <trunc>e</trunc> like</u>
<u n="202" who="S0441" trans="overlap">but then I think they've got the rights haven't they? so I think they were they knew but I think that since this has happened <pause dur="short"/> they've changed the goalpost which they are actually entitled to do</u>
<u n="203" who="S0439">it's just so unfair</u>
<u n="204" who="S0441">it's really annoying <pause dur="short"/> the moral of the story is for everything to be in writing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0441">but they were so sneaky about that I think</u>
<u n="207" who="S0439">well if you look how <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> followed up today I mean like about the blind she's like well I said that I'm like yeah you said that and I replied</u>
<u n="208" who="S0441">which <trunc>wasn</trunc> yeah saying we can't do that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <trunc>li</trunc> you asked me in October</u>
<u n="210" who="S0441">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0439">for a bill from like April like I'm sorry</u>
<u n="212" who="S0441">not likely</u>
<u n="213" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> like <pause dur="short"/> if you'd actually done your fucking job properly and ordered a blind when the blind man came we wouldn't be in this situation fucking twat <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0441">so <pause dur="short"/> we can draw up a a sort of our own contract stating that we want to leave it's not a contract that's actually the it's the surrender <pause dur="short"/> and they</u>
<u n="215" who="S0439" trans="overlap">but they'd still charge us wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0441">no no that's the whole point it's a surrender if if it becomes the whole <trunc>t</trunc> if <unclear/> terms <pause dur="short"/> but the thing is we haven't got the <unclear/> really <trunc>a</trunc>apart from tenants cos well we've got <unclear/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well we can ask could we pay up until January the first or pay up until December the thirty-first and then the new tenant pays on the first well and give and ask the estate agents to offer the new tenants the option of moving in you know straight away in January?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0441">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0439">it's just so <trunc>incon</trunc> it's so annoying that we can't talk to the tenants <pause dur="short"/> if that makes sense <pause dur="short"/> I'm pretty sure if we'd</u>
<u n="220" who="S0441">I'm sure if we <unclear>can't talk to the</unclear></u>
<u n="221" who="S0439" trans="overlap">spoken to the tenants like the new ones this would have been like well like we could have just altered it ourselves</u>
<u n="222" who="S0441">I know</u>
<u n="223" who="S0439">but the estate agent is so shit</u>
<u n="224" who="S0441">and it's annoying that we can't talk to the landlady as well</u>
<u n="225" who="S0439">yeah cos I'm pretty sure if they actually asked the <trunc>landlor</trunc> lady she probably wouldn't care</u>
<u n="226" who="S0441">no <pause dur="short"/> I think she's quite hard to track down though</u>
<u n="227" who="S0439">true <pause dur="short"/> I'm not overly impressed with our estate agents to be honest <unclear/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0441">not for much longer</u>
<u n="229" who="S0439">no it won't be for much longer will it really? <pause dur="short"/> oh well <pause dur="short"/> what are you up to this weekend?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0441">going to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="231" who="S0439">are you?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0441">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0441">erm if <pause dur="short"/> I'll I'll still probably move out on on the weekend that I was moving out</u>
<u n="235" who="S0439">yeah me too yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0441">but <pause dur="long"/> in all fairness we should probably just <pause dur="short"/> cancel the bills as well</u>
<u n="237" who="S0439">yeah I was going to anyway</u>
<u n="238" who="S0441">I thought you wanted to live in here if if <trunc>y</trunc> if you <unclear/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well I was going to because it was gonna be a pain but erm I actually I'm gonna move into the place in <anon type="place"/> and because overall it's three hundred and seventy pounds a month including bills</u>
<u n="240" who="S0441">mm so that's actually a lot yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0439">so it's a lot cheaper in the long term</u>
<u n="242" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0439">so even though it will cost me extra what? three hundred odd quid to stay in this stupid shitty house <pause dur="short"/> it'll actually be more expensive in the long term I think so I'm just gonna have to take the financial hit</u>
<u n="244" who="S0441">yeah I guess well until after er but <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
