<text id="SKNF">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:36:22</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-12-30</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0015 S0281</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's house Brighton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Buses, day's activities, pension, sleep</topics>
		<activity>Talking with sister about recent events</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, </conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T04</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0015">
				<exactage>68</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Scotland</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Scotland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Brighton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>67 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0281">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Brighton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>30</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0281">yeah it is a bit cold erm</u>
<u n="2" who="S0015">it's very cold and there's a thick fog isn't there? was it still on the ground? it was when you went and did you get the bus?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0281">well yes I did but not at the time you said</u>
<u n="4" who="S0015">oh what time? which bus?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well you said you said seven forty-seven yeah?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0281">and it eventually came at five past eight</u>
<u n="8" who="S0015">oh that's a different bus then</u>
<u n="9" who="S0281">well the when I got to the bus stop it <trunc>wa</trunc> it was sixteen minutes past it said bus due in sixteen minutes</u>
<u n="10" who="S0015" trans="overlap">oh and that was the five <trunc>wa</trunc>was that the five or the five A?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0281" trans="overlap">that was the first that was the five A</u>
<u n="12" who="S0015">oh</u>
<u n="13" who="S0281">and erm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0015">mm oh well they've changed the bus timetable in the winter but I don't know or what to</u>
<u n="15" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah well it's</u>
<u n="16" who="S0015">but that was on that was online this morning wasn't it? how weird never mind the main thing is you got a bus but you got there in time did you?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0281">yeah I got there about erm twenty to and er there were three people waiting apparently one a really nice chap and we started a conversation and we were chatting about this and that</u>
<u n="18" who="S0015">oh</u>
<u n="19" who="S0281">he was there because he was er his landlady refused to get the heating fixed</u>
<u n="20" who="S0015">oh</u>
<u n="21" who="S0281">and he wanted to find out what recourse he had and because he was wouldn't let it go she gave him his notice two months' notice and he went down and I saw him when he came out and he says he's stuffed <unclear/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0015" trans="overlap">nothing you can do</u>
<u n="23" who="S0281">no</u>
<u n="24" who="S0015">I think you know it's amazing isn't it what people can do? and there's nothing you can do to make <unclear/> nothing you can do to make things make them <unclear/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0281" trans="overlap">apparently not erm they've got they've got a rent agreement that's and I <unclear/> presumably she's in er</u>
<u n="26" who="S0015">yeah the landlord <unclear/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah she she's in the wrong there you know because she she's has agreed to do what she said she would do but apparently the bottom line is that she's got the rights and he hasn't so yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0015">and the heating's not been working but is that a boiler or what what is that <unclear/> a boiler or?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I don't know he didn't <trunc>s</trunc>say exactly what it was but there's a there's a problem with the heating and erm he said they they couldn't er <pause dur="short"/> they couldn't make her do anything so she she</u>
<u n="30" who="S0015" trans="overlap">to sort it out?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0281">yeah <trunc>sh</trunc>she she gave him the two months' notice and presumably er she'll do nothing about the heating</u>
<u n="32" who="S0015">she'll have to when the new tenant goes in surely?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I don't know I don't know</u>
<u n="34" who="S0015">very odd anyway how did you get on?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0281">well erm <unclear/> we're given a number and I was number four I had to wait again <unclear/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0015" trans="overlap">it's quite a long time isn't it?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0281">yeah nearly erm nearly an hour</u>
<u n="38" who="S0015">do you want something to eat?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0281">mm I would actually</u>
<u n="40" who="S0015">what would you like?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0281">erm well anything thanks</u>
<u n="42" who="S0015">well do you want a sandwich now or do you want?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0281" trans="overlap">anything honestly <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0015">porridge or?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0281"><trunc>any</trunc>anything</u>
<u n="46" who="S0015" trans="overlap">it's a bit late for porridge</u>
<u n="47" who="S0281">a bit late for porridge <vocal desc="laugh"/> er so erm then it was just putting on the computer my details and she said well what do you want to to see us about?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0015">everything <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and well yeah that on the on the form you had to fill in before you go and see them er then you're only allowed to tick one of the items</u>
<u n="50" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0281">so I I ticked benefits and I told her it was er it's the <trunc>sit</trunc> I told her my situation and er she went to see her supervisor</u>
<u n="52" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah they'll have to be</u>
<u n="53" who="S0281">and they came back and said well we'll make an appointment at er for somebody to see you tomorrow so I've got to go back again at half past nine tomorrow</u>
<u n="54" who="S0015">oh well at least it's half past nine</u>
<u n="55" who="S0281">yeah erm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0015">that's good because it's New Year's Eve and erm I thought you might not get anything you know until later</u>
<u n="57" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0015">well that's good then so did you did they talk about anything?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0281">no not really but I <trunc>w</trunc>while I was waiting I was looking through the leaflets that they've got there booklets and one of the things they said er as looking at er cos I didn't you know I don't know anything about anything like really you know?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0015" trans="overlap">no of course not no</u>
<u n="61" who="S0281">and er if you are a pensioner</u>
<u n="62" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0281">you cannot claim Jobseeker's Allowance</u>
<u n="64" who="S0015">no</u>
<u n="65" who="S0281">no so</u>
<u n="66" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well I I did</u>
<u n="67" who="S0281">but what I can do is apply for Pension Credits</u>
<u n="68" who="S0015">yeah and top it up</u>
<u n="69" who="S0281">yeah so I said you know I want to is it worth erm? and I'd planned to er I told them my plans to to go down to the pension office after I I left there and said would it I would be er doubling would it be necessary? so I was gonna see somebody tomorrow you know and she said well you can go down and tell them what they've said so I did go down to the pensions people</u>
<u n="70" who="S0015" trans="overlap">you did?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0281">and they said oh it's all centralised now</u>
<u n="72" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="73" who="S0281">you have to ring this number</u>
<u n="74" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0281">so then I told him well what I was given the runaround yesterday</u>
<u n="76" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0281">and they said that I'd got to ring er one of the numbers that I rang yesterday</u>
<u n="78" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0281">and <trunc>apparent</trunc></u>
<u n="80" who="S0015" trans="overlap">did they tell you what to ask for though did they? cos sometimes unless you're asking for the right thing erm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah well it's to top up pension erm so</u>
<u n="82" who="S0015" trans="overlap">Ppension Credit</u>
<u n="83" who="S0281">Pension Credits yeah so erm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well that sounds quite good though doesn't it?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0281">yeah well if if I can get to talk to somebody er that's what I'm gonna do now er or after I've had something to eat</u>
<u n="86" who="S0015" trans="overlap">but it's you know these there is some things that you can</u>
<u n="87" who="S0281">well yeah I I suppose you know you've got to two things I learnt today and one is patience and the other is perseverance</u>
<u n="88" who="S0015">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="89" who="S0281">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0015">mm well I think that's the way of the world unfortunately because what you're dealing with is they're dealing with is people who aren't working and have got time so therefore you know that's how they are they're because you can wait for me kind of approach</u>
<u n="91" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0015">did you have to wait there then when you went today?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0281">no</u>
<u n="94" who="S0015"><unclear/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0281" trans="overlap">that was <vocal desc="laugh"/> well it's in the job centre there which is</u>
<u n="96" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0281">you know right next to the law courts</u>
<u n="98" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0281">and the first two guys are there are two obviously bouncers</u>
<u n="100" who="S0015">yeah security</u>
<u n="101" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I know yeah erm both playing with their phones</u>
<u n="102" who="S0015">oh cool</u>
<u n="103" who="S0281">and then you see somebody somebody will come up to you and say oh can I help you?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0281">which is quite nice erm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0015" trans="overlap">eventually</u>
<u n="107" who="S0281">and then you know he told me you know you've just got to phone you you can't see anybody the only person you could see there is somebody who actually pops in and he said he just pops into the office because essentially his job is going around to see pensioners who can't get out</u>
<u n="108" who="S0015">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0281">so he said it's all got to be done over the phone</u>
<u n="110" who="S0015">mm and they'll probably send you forms and then you'll fill those forms in</u>
<u n="111" who="S0281">yeah maybe</u>
<u n="112" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0281">maybe anyway I'll find out later</u>
<u n="114" who="S0015">so you've got you've got to ring there?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0015">what time is that? so right now it's probably?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0281">well it's twelve o'clock now so</u>
<u n="118" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah you've got to it's probably lunchtime</u>
<u n="119" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh I don't think they that matters about lunchtime erm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0015">well <unclear/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0281" trans="overlap">cos they got they've got calls from all over the world coming</u>
<u n="122" who="S0015">yeah well <unclear/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0281">I expect they have a staggered lunch you know these</u>
<u n="124" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0281">maybe it's less chance of getting <unclear/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah or yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0281" trans="overlap">what are the chances of them replying in the lunchtime? so</u>
<u n="128" who="S0015" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0281">maybe I should wait a couple of hours</u>
<u n="130" who="S0015">yeah well yeah I would say by two o'clock anyone going to lunch is coming back now and don't forget between Christmas and New Year there'll be a skeleton staff</u>
<u n="131" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0015">you know? <unclear/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0281">yeah I suppose people do take holidays now it's like that</u>
<u n="134" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0281">er policewoman that</u>
<u n="136" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0281">er filled in the form and she said</u>
<u n="138" who="S0015" trans="overlap">everywhere you go <unclear/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><unclear/> until the twelfth</u>
<u n="140" who="S0015">yeah the twelfth mm well I mean the garage that we go to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been down there twice to pay them and they're and he went on Christmas Eve and he went yesterday and they're not open until the fifth of January <pause dur="short"/> I suppose they know they haven't got anybody booked in and they choose when to have their holidays <pause dur="short"/> but our erm the guy that runs the garage owns the garage we've been with him for years and years and he would retire but he's got staff that wanna keep going so he has lots of holidays and they they keep the garage going while he's away</u>
<u n="141" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0015">but anyway <pause dur="short"/> so your plan is to phone them up and try and get that sorted out</u>
<u n="143" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0015">you're going back tomorrow</u>
<u n="145" who="S0281">mm mm</u>
<u n="146" who="S0015">and erm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0281">well I'll have a clearer idea of erm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0015">mm where to</u>
<u n="149" who="S0281" trans="overlap">what I'll be entitled to</u>
<u n="150" who="S0015">yeah so tomorrow it's a specialist person is it?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0281">yes it's a</u>
<u n="152" who="S0015">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's good then</u>
<u n="153" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0015">and did you have to explain about your circumstances like what you've been doing and you know?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0281">mm yeah yeah vaguely without going into much detail</u>
<u n="156" who="S0015" trans="overlap">I mean did you tell them about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0281">yes they asked me and I said I've got family in <anon type="place"/> dependants</u>
<u n="158" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0281">erm so I expect they'll want <unclear>to be able to</unclear></u>
<u n="160" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well that</u>
<u n="161" who="S0281">take take people <unclear/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0015" trans="overlap">you might get child benefit</u>
<u n="163" who="S0281">well</u>
<u n="164" who="S0015"><unclear>you don't know</unclear></u>
<u n="165" who="S0281">maybe if I can prove she exists</u>
<u n="166" who="S0015">well that's why I said birth certificates</u>
<u n="167" who="S0281">yeah but it's in Chinese you see</u>
<u n="168" who="S0015">well you know</u>
<u n="169" who="S0281" trans="overlap">because I I</u>
<u n="170" who="S0015">they can be translated</u>
<u n="171" who="S0281">but I have got erm the form that says she's registered with the British government as erm British father</u>
<u n="172" who="S0015">mm well you you need to have a copy of her birth certificate and they will translate it over here</u>
<u n="173" who="S0281">ah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0015">if need be and that that's why I said to you you need it as proof and you could be I mean I don't know how much erm family allowance is but it's quite a lot about ten pounds or more it might be even</u>
<u n="175" who="S0281" trans="overlap">is it?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0015">I don't know it might be even eighteen pounds a week which is a lot if you've got to pay school fees</u>
<u n="177" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="178" who="S0015">and</u>
<u n="179" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well we'll <trunc>s</trunc> I'll see tomorrow what they say and if I need it or not or if if <pause dur="short"/> but these Pension Credits er it seems like that's</u>
<u n="180" who="S0015">that's the way to go</u>
<u n="181" who="S0281">that's</u>
<u n="182" who="S0015">what you need to find out about also have you they asked about <trunc>you</trunc>your savings?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0281"><trunc>y</trunc> they will do but</u>
<u n="184" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0281">it's it's all done on a on a scale here see there look</u>
<u n="186" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm okay god it's hard to follow isn't it?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="188" who="S0015">the Pension Credits chart for people age you're not single actually</u>
<u n="189" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no well the different</u>
<u n="190" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0281">well</u>
<u n="192" who="S0015">people aged sixty-five and over</u>
<u n="193" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah but I'm not a couple either am I?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0015">no so you god <unclear/> get the credit <pause dur="short"/> your income <pause dur="short"/> is rock bottom isn't it then? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0281">well my income will be just what I'm being paid</u>
<u n="196" who="S0015" trans="overlap">on the pension</u>
<u n="197" who="S0281">on the pension at the moment so</u>
<u n="198" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0281">I'm pretty</u>
<u n="200" who="S0015" trans="overlap">and it starts at a hundred</u>
<u n="201" who="S0281">yeah a hundred yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0015" trans="overlap"><unclear/> and a hundred pounds</u>
<u n="203" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0015">but you're below the scale</u>
<u n="205" who="S0281">mm I'm <trunc>pr</trunc> I'm pretty sure that</u>
<u n="206" who="S0015" trans="overlap">you will get</u>
<u n="207" who="S0281">I'll get something</u>
<u n="208" who="S0015">well yeah mm it's that</u>
<u n="209" who="S0281">and they asked me if I'm paying any rent and I said no I'm just er staying with my sister at the moment</u>
<u n="210" who="S0015">but you or what you have you asked them will you get housing benefit if you want to take a flat you know?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0281">yes yeah and and</u>
<u n="212" who="S0015" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0281"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been pushing me to he said well get your <trunc>hou</trunc> get your name down on the housing list</u>
<u n="214" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="215" who="S0281">I said what?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0015" trans="overlap">forget that forget that they <unclear/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I saw a thing on the TV recently er that said in in <anon type="place"/> there's a is it sixteen thousand people on the housing list or something like that?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah well they're mainly people with children and <unclear/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0015">you know and and they have to be overcrowded if you can put your name down on the housing list here we're not overcrowded</u>
<u n="221" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0015">so that's you know that's what they would say well you've got rooms you know?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0015">where you're living you've got a bedroom to yourself if you put it down as <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then</u>
<u n="225" who="S0281">well he's he said he he</u>
<u n="226" who="S0015" trans="overlap">he would</u>
<u n="227" who="S0281">he could yeah he would do that but that would mean erm that it would show up that he's he's getting an unearned income or something like that you know er and that and that that would</u>
<u n="228" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well only only</u>
<u n="229" who="S0281">that would actually affect and also it would affect his rates because</u>
<u n="230" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0281">that would be more than one person living in the house</u>
<u n="232" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0281">and he said you can do that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but you'll have to pay the difference in rates</u>
<u n="234" who="S0015">yeah yeah which isn't a huge amount though</u>
<u n="235" who="S0281">well I'll have to find out when I see him</u>
<u n="236" who="S0015">erm it's erm it's what they call erm community tax tomato sauce?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0281">please yeah since you told me the benefits of</u>
<u n="238" who="S0015">tomato sauce absolutely I mean I don't eat it myself I can't stand it but everyone tells me it's do you want a cup of tea?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0281">lovely</u>
<u n="240" who="S0015">camomile?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0281">er peppermint please</u>
<u n="242" who="S0015">peppermint okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah so <trunc>th</trunc>this is the thing so if you put it down here we're not overcrowded we've got rooms if you put it down at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s then it'll show that you're you know haven't got a bedroom of your own and you are overcrowded but if you it might <trunc>compli</trunc> you don't have to say you're paying him any rent</u>
<u n="243" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="244" who="S0015">so it won't affect his income</u>
<u n="245" who="S0281">no but it will affect his rates</u>
<u n="246" who="S0015">yeah it would affect his er his erm community tax the only thing is of course he's got his nephew staying there and he might not want that to be</u>
<u n="247" who="S0281">well technically his his his property is four to six actually</u>
<u n="248" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm right oh right</u>
<u n="249" who="S0281">and where his nephew's staying there's a door that leads into the</u>
<u n="250" who="S0015">other room</u>
<u n="251" who="S0281">the other room where his bedroom is</u>
<u n="252" who="S0015" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="253" who="S0281">he's got a bedroom and that is technically number four</u>
<u n="254" who="S0015">right</u>
<u n="255" who="S0281">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is number six</u>
<u n="256" who="S0015">right okay <pause dur="short"/> what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> needs to do is get the other ones up and running</u>
<u n="257" who="S0281">mm well</u>
<u n="258" who="S0015">and you pay rent and get housing benefit that would be the thing that would be the ideal</u>
<u n="259" who="S0281">he showed me his new New Year's resolutions for two thousand and thirteen</u>
<u n="260" who="S0015" trans="overlap">oh major New Year's resolutions</u>
<u n="261" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah for two thousand and thirteen</u>
<u n="262" who="S0015">oh for two thousand and thirteen</u>
<u n="263" who="S0281">and that erm one of them is to erm do his property up at least</u>
<u n="264" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0281">one day a week</u>
<u n="266" who="S0015" trans="overlap">oh that's good</u>
<u n="267" who="S0281">and that I think it's going to be on his list of <trunc>th</trunc>things to do</u>
<u n="268" who="S0015" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0281">and I told him yeah I told him I'll be you know more than happy to help out</u>
<u n="270" who="S0015">yeah give you something to occupy yourself</u>
<u n="271" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="272" who="S0015">and actually probably be very good for you because using physical energy makes you tired and sleep well</u>
<u n="273" who="S0281">mm well in theory <vocal desc="laugh"/> I thought that that would be the case erm the day before yesterday</u>
<u n="274" who="S0015">yesterday?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0281">no it was on Sunday</u>
<u n="276" who="S0015" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0281">you know when we did did all that walking?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0281">didn't do much <unclear/> but</u>
<u n="280" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0281">walking around <anon type="place"/> along the seafront and er</u>
<u n="282" who="S0015" trans="overlap">well <unclear/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0281">well when the time time to go to bed I still didn't have my pills with me right?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0015">right</u>
<u n="285" who="S0281">so I wasn't sure how that would affect me but I kept you know thinking and things go around in your head you know</u>
<u n="286" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0281">about the past and the future and</u>
<u n="288" who="S0015">so you've got to leave the past behind</u>
<u n="289" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and I <unclear/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0015">really <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and think of the future</u>
<u n="291" who="S0281">I know well apparently you should live in the now live in the present</u>
<u n="292" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="294" who="S0015">mm well yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0281">well</u>
<u n="296" who="S0015">I agree with that</u>
<u n="297" who="S0281">but erm</u>
<u n="298" who="S0015">because I also</u>
<u n="299" who="S0281">er you know it's it's the mind that keeps grabbing you back</u>
<u n="300" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="301" who="S0281">you know mine loves problems and it presents you with all the problems that it's going to think about</u>
<u n="302" who="S0015">well especially at night</u>
<u n="303" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0015">I often anything I anything on my mind worries me at night</u>
<u n="305" who="S0281" trans="overlap">but also they</u>
<u n="306" who="S0015">but in the morning I come up with a solution often</u>
<u n="307" who="S0281">sure</u>
<u n="308" who="S0015">I go oh that's it you know? that's what I'll do or that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0281">but essentially you know for my particular problem there is no solution really er</u>
<u n="310" who="S0015">well there are solutions</u>
<u n="311" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0015">they're not they're not in you know not maybe ideal solutions but there are solutions and</u>
<u n="313" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="314" who="S0015">you know and it's erm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0281">but also he's got this grandfather clock</u>
<u n="316" who="S0015" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0281">yeah well he's got two actually he's got one on the landing on the on the stairs leading up and another in the living room and it's so loud</u>
<u n="318" who="S0015">ah ticking</u>
<u n="319" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and yeah and two o'clock in the morning and I was still</u>
<u n="320" who="S0015" trans="overlap">tearing your hair out</u>
<u n="321" who="S0281">not asleep but I got up and stopped the pendulum</u>
<u n="322" who="S0015">did you?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0281">mm well it was still you know but I I I couldn't get back to sleep and I turned the TV on and watched erm a programme about autopsies called</u>
<u n="324" who="S0015" trans="overlap">lovely</u>
<u n="325" who="S0281">erm Michael Jackson how</u>
<u n="326" who="S0015" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0281">you know the reason yeah the reason why he died</u>
<u n="328" who="S0015">oh</u>
<u n="329" who="S0281">another programme about John Denver and</u>
<u n="330" who="S0015" trans="overlap">I'll give you that back <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0281">oh in the end well no</u>
<u n="332" who="S0015"><unclear/> it's floating around and it's getting tomato sauce</u>
<u n="333" who="S0281">well put it in your bag it's yours</u>
<u n="334" who="S0015">I told you it's fine keep it</u>
<u n="335" who="S0281">so I don't know eventually I must have dropped off about four or five or something</u>
<u n="336" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0281">I got a couple of hours sleep and er</u>
<u n="338" who="S0015">so do you think the tablets that you're taking they do help?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0281">I think they do</u>
<u n="340" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0281">well so last night I went to because I had slept so little the night before</u>
<u n="342" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="343" who="S0281">around ten o'clock I just couldn't keep my eyes open</u>
<u n="344" who="S0015">well that's good though</u>
<u n="345" who="S0281">well it was except I woke up at midnight and then</u>
<u n="346" who="S0015" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="347" who="S0281">well I <trunc>we</trunc>went back to sleep again but then I then I woke up again at four o'clock and and that was it</u>
<u n="348" who="S0015">oh</u>
<u n="349" who="S0281">so I was awake at four this morning</u>
<u n="350" who="S0015">oh that's no good well I wonder why though I mean do you think your body clock's still?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0281">no</u>
<u n="352" who="S0015">no?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0281">no</u>
<u n="354" who="S0015">it does take a long time to adjust you know and you just think it's sleepless nights and stressing</u>
<u n="355" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="356" who="S0015">insomnia they call it don't they? if you can't sleep</u>
<u n="357" who="S0281">yeah I was renowned in my <trunc>young</trunc>younger days erm for</u>
<u n="358" who="S0015" trans="overlap">leave that there</u>
<u n="359" who="S0281">for er sleeping</u>
<u n="360" who="S0015">for sleeping?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0015"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and now you're renowned for waking</u>
<u n="363" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and I could sleep anywhere any time <unclear/> but it's getting into regular you know</u>
<u n="364" who="S0015" trans="overlap">a routine</u>
<u n="365" who="S0281">have a routine</u>
<u n="366" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah that's one of the things though when you when you erm can't sleep at night you don't want to get up in the morning but if you get up in the morning at least you're tired at night you know what I mean? you might yawn a lot during the day but I I know that unless I keep my routine well I wouldn't sleep I I'm awake later at night now than I ever used to when I was working mm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="368" who="S0015">yeah and that Dell computer that's what keeps me awake on the computer my laptop and and they say the blue light from emitted from er screens is erm prevents sleep</u>
<u n="369" who="S0281">really?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0015">yeah so they say you shouldn't watch TV which I do and you shouldn't use a laptop or or erm tablet because or even a phone because they emit a blue light which affects your sleep and I don't know I don't know whether that's true but not that I ever have trouble sleeping except if I've got an inspection at college <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> then I can't sleep probably but erm it's a shame sleep is so important to your you know your health and wellbeing but</u>
<u n="371" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah it's</u>
<u n="372" who="S0015">you've got to well get back in a routine maybe what you know what you're doing get up and go out for a walk is very good a brisk walk</u>
<u n="373" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0015">something like that get a pair of roller skates on</u>
<u n="375" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well I've done my exercise for the day</u>
<u n="376" who="S0015"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you what?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0281">I've done a bit of exercise today</u>
<u n="378" who="S0015">mm did you walk from <anon type="place"/> then to or did you catch the bus?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="380" who="S0015">no you got the bus</u>
<u n="381" who="S0281">well I got the bus to erm the pavilion</u>
<u n="382" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="383" who="S0281">and then walked up <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0015">oh right yeah mm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0281">and then back to the bus stop and just up here so I actually didn't do a lot of walking but I've been doing something all morning</u>
<u n="386" who="S0015">yeah yeah mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0281">since seven o'clock</u>
<u n="388" who="S0015">mm mm so back tomorrow and did they say to take any papers with you tomorrow or?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0281">yes</u>
<u n="390" who="S0015">and what's that that you've got to take <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well they didn't specify they just said bring all your papers</u>
<u n="392" who="S0015">what are they? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0281">not a lot</u>
<u n="394" who="S0015">well I mean you you should</u>
<u n="395" who="S0281" trans="overlap">but I've got my my pension things here and er</u>
<u n="396" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah your</u>
<u n="397" who="S0281">I've got my marriage book</u>
<u n="398" who="S0015">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0281">and I'll take er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s er <pause dur="short"/> form I've got to say that er</u>
<u n="400" who="S0015" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0281">she's registered with the British government</u>
<u n="402" who="S0015" trans="overlap">with the yeah yeah so you've got all that that's you know erm <pause dur="short"/> then I suppose you you need to write a list of things you want to talk to them about</u>
<u n="403" who="S0281">it's funny you should say that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said exactly the same thing <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I said I know what I've got to talk about</u>
<u n="404" who="S0015">yeah but it's so easy to forget when you're talking about like some one thing you go off on one direction</u>
<u n="405" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0015">if you've got them on a list you can say oh yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah you're probably right</u>
<u n="408" who="S0015">I just wanted to ask about this so <trunc>i</trunc>it's worth doing</u>
<u n="409" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="410" who="S0015">erm <pause dur="short"/> well one of them of course that you haven't thought about perhaps isn't er er wasn't on your mind is Child Benefit</u>
<u n="411" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="412" who="S0015">say I've got to contribute to her</u>
<u n="413" who="S0281">well I have actually</u>
<u n="414" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah yeah of course I know you have</u>
<u n="415" who="S0281">you know I I agreed to pay the school fees</u>
<u n="416" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="417" who="S0281">so</u>
<u n="418" who="S0015">which is more than you actually get coming in at the moment</u>
<u n="419" who="S0281">maybe yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0015">don't don't tell them that you're she's in a private school or anything</u>
<u n="421" who="S0281">well</u>
<u n="422" who="S0015">she's</u>
<u n="423" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="424" who="S0015">just say you have to pay for school over there</u>
<u n="425" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0015">schooling it's not free erm so and which of the <unclear/> about the property or anything because that would complicate things but</u>
<u n="427" who="S0281">well it wouldn't make any difference it's not er there's only one of them is in my joint name</u>
<u n="428" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="429" who="S0281">but</u>
<u n="430" who="S0015">mm but they'll be looking at that</u>
<u n="431" who="S0281">yeah but I I</u>
<u n="432" who="S0015" trans="overlap"><trunc>in</trunc> as income income from that</u>
<u n="433" who="S0281">well fair enough yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0015">what you could say is that she's living in it</u>
<u n="435" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0015">has has it <trunc>g</trunc> has it got a mortgage or anything like that? do they have mortgages like we do?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0281">we did actually well after we bought the first one we got a a a loan</u>
<u n="438" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="439" who="S0281">I suppose you could call it a mortgage but er for because we didn't have quite enough to buy it and it's it's weird you can the erm the Chinese they they've got a can do attitude to everything you know?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0281">and there's no way they're gonna give me a loan</u>
<u n="442" who="S0015">no</u>
<u n="443" who="S0281">but <trunc>a</trunc>and again you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't have a job but so they created a job for her they made her manageress of McDonald's</u>
<u n="444" who="S0015"><vocal desc="laugh"/> really?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0015">how weird</u>
<u n="447" who="S0281">so they yeah so that we could get the loan</u>
<u n="448" who="S0015">good grief how weird is that? because she's not <trunc>eli</trunc> because you're not eligible to have a loan?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I I wasn't eligible and er</u>
<u n="450" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah we can give you a loan</u>
<u n="451" who="S0281">and and she wasn't working so she suddenly became employed</u>
<u n="452" who="S0015">mm and so no paperwork or no nothing for it</u>
<u n="453" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="454" who="S0015">it was just</u>
<u n="455" who="S0281" trans="overlap">just to</u>
<u n="456" who="S0015">put it on a paper bit of paper</u>
<u n="457" who="S0281">yes just</u>
<u n="458" who="S0015" trans="overlap">fill in the form tell a little lie and you can have what you want what would happen if if the loan hadn't been repaid then? what do they do about that?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0281">well they repossess the property</u>
<u n="460" who="S0015">yeah I suppose so yes so it wasn't a loan against the the property then rather than just a personal loan?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0281">well it must have been they wouldn't have taken a chance of</u>
<u n="462" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="463" who="S0281">of doing that but the the Chinese are trying to cut down on the amount the banks are giving cos all the banks are underwritten by the government</u>
<u n="464" who="S0015">cut down on the amount of?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0281">money they're lending</u>
<u n="466" who="S0015">oh right yeah yeah mm they're all under well it's a bit like here ours are aren't they really?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well yeah</u>
<u n="468" who="S0015">more or less</u>
<u n="469" who="S0281">more or less aren't they?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="471" who="S0281">I mean the RBS and</u>
<u n="472" who="S0015">Lloyds</u>
<u n="473" who="S0281">Lloyds yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0015">our bank Lloyds</u>
<u n="475" who="S0281">no mine is <unclear/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0015">is it? yeah yeah well yeah I do know that yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no it's TSB</u>
<u n="478" who="S0015">I thought you would have had Barclays because you worked for Barclays didn't you?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0281">well I don't know why when I I got this started when I came over erm for my sixtieth and er</u>
<u n="480" who="S0015">oh so you didn't have a bank account here <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no I don't know why I went to Lloyds TSB I can't remember but it doesn't matter I mean</u>
<u n="482" who="S0015" trans="overlap">Lloyds cos you were down in <anon type="place"/> I suppose it was you know convenient wasn't it?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0281">well no I wasn't I wasn't in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="484" who="S0015">where?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0281">because I was staying with you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wasn't I? well it was only when I came over to <unclear/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0015" trans="overlap">not here but it was at <anon type="place"/> we were at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0281">yeah but I didn't have a bank account then</u>
<u n="488" who="S0015">no but what I'm saying is <anon type="place"/> was convenient then for <anon type="place"/> it was probably the nearest bank</u>
<u n="489" who="S0281">oh I see oh oh for my address cos yeah my address</u>
<u n="490" who="S0015" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0281">then was <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0015">yeah so erm</u>
<u n="493" who="S0281">but I don't know I don't know yeah I can't remember the reason why I chose that</u>
<u n="494" who="S0015">mm I bet that would be why cos it's just nearest and the easiest erm what was I going to say? oh god it's cold are you cold? <unclear/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="496" who="S0015">the heating on freezing freezing sneezing I'm gonna do a shepherd's pie for tonight</u>
<u n="497" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="498" who="S0015">I think cos it's cold it makes it warm and it's nice and easy to sort out so what else have you got to do today then is that it?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0281">er that and I've got to write to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0015">got to write to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I erm sent you an email last night did you get it?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0281">I haven't checked yet</u>
<u n="502" who="S0015">I haven't got that email from you</u>
<u n="503" who="S0281">really?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0015">yeah and you said you sent me an email or something?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0281">I sent you two</u>
<u n="506" who="S0015">yeah and I haven't got them something's wrong with the email address that you've got for me and I sent you one last night cos I I when I went to bed I looked on my laptop and checked my emails and emailed you back er <unclear/></u>
<u n="507" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well I'll tell you why cos since <unclear/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0015" trans="overlap">it should come up on your phone shouldn't it?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0281">since</u>
<u n="510" who="S0015">that's your phone there</u>
<u n="511" who="S0281">since</u>
<u n="512" who="S0015" trans="overlap">you can't you can't do it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0281">since I erm I've got to wait until <unclear/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0015" trans="overlap">mind you it wasn't Gmail I sent it to</u>
<u n="515" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="516" who="S0015">Hotmail</u>
<u n="517" who="S0281">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="518" who="S0015">mm I don't feel you but I haven't got your Gmail erm</u>
<u n="519" who="S0281">well I'd oh well I can try Gmail if there's something wrong and we're not getting each other's emails</u>
<u n="520" who="S0015" trans="overlap">I'll put the laptop on this new laptop of mine that I've I don't know how to use it and I don't have to <unclear/> been there and try it it doesn't hold its battery <unclear/> I need to buy a new battery yeah they did say that to me it's the battery <unclear/> any good <pause dur="short"/> so I <unclear/> online is that the right button? yeah here we go but it won't turn on cos there's nothing in the battery <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> or maybe I just turned it off and now it's on <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> no I'll find out whether it's any good I haven't really used it yet <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> switched off? yeah I'm waiting for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to ring me back I reckon she must have gone out somewhere <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got the day off today so she's probably happy</u>
<u n="521" who="S0281">where does she work again?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0015">she works at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="524" who="S0015">a call centre hates the job but it's quite well paid she's been there I don't know quite a long time now</u>
<u n="525" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="526" who="S0015">about fourteen years and she keeps hoping they'll make her redundant and then she'll look for a job nearer <anon type="place"/> but erm they're quite a difficult company to work for</u>
<u n="527" who="S0281">I suppose she should consider herself lucky to have a job in these days</u>
<u n="528" who="S0015">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="529" who="S0281">what is unemployment like here now?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0015">sorry?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0281">what is unemployment like?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0015">not bad now it's come right down you know it's erm I don't know exactly it's the young that are unemployed</u>
<u n="533" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0015">predominantly and that's why they're trying to develop thousands more apprenticeships</u>
<u n="535" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well well absolutely and so they should</u>
<u n="536" who="S0015">mm</u>
<u n="537" who="S0281">I think you know it went out of fashion for a while</u>
<event desc="sound of phone"/>
<u n="538" who="S0015">that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> no it's <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> hello? hello alright? did you get my message? oh I rang and just said erm <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> got some presents here still yeah I know he's over at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but is he coming home any time soon? oh right okay mm on Thursday okay we'll leave it until Thursday then if that's alright erm <trunc>h</trunc>have you managed to do any studying?</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
