<text id="SKPP">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:03:54</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-10</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0202 S0208</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>France</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Internet followers, people leaving, along, talking about other friends</topics>
		<activity>Friends chatting about general stuff</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, Explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0202">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0208">
				<exactage>19</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- advanced</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0202">oh for fuck's sake</u>
<u n="2" who="S0208">retard</u>
<u n="3" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0208">they've got erm thirty thousand followers</u>
<u n="5" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="6" who="S0208">and</u>
<u n="7" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and they're following you?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0208">and they follow six thousand people and they started following me and I was like right</u>
<u n="9" who="S0202">I'm a <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0208">no no</u>
<u n="11" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0208">cos I know like I've learnt with pages like that what they do is they follow people and then obviously when it's like follow for follow</u>
<u n="13" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0208" trans="overlap">it's like if someone follows me I'll look through their stuff if they're interesting like yeah I'll follow you back if they're not interesting I'm like oh fuck you but erm cos they were interesting and like I really liked the outfits that they put up and like it was quite trendy</u>
<u n="15" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="16" who="S0208">erm I was like yeah I'll follow you back but then I thought</u>
<u n="17" who="S0202" trans="overlap">then they unfollowed you</u>
<u n="18" who="S0208">that's no no well they didn't but usually that is what happens</u>
<u n="19" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="20" who="S0208">like some girl from <anon type="place"/> actually has quite a few hundred followers like <pause dur="short"/> now each have started following me she was like a third year or something and I started following her because I was like oh <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0202">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you must do <pause dur="long"/> oh <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0208">mm <pause dur="short"/> but then once I followed her back I re fronted my page and I'd gone down to like a hundred and eighty followers and I was like you fucking bitch sorry I <trunc>apol</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0202">so is that what they do then? they follow you so you follow them back and then they unfollow you?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0208">not not all the time some people do but like</u>
<u n="25" who="S0202">that's really sad</u>
<u n="26" who="S0208">because I don't really care it's like <pause dur="short"/> like it sounds great but it's like I've got a hundred and eighty followers like that's not much <pause dur="short"/> like I don't care</u>
<u n="27" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="28" who="S0208">and I've made my profile erm public because there's nothing on there that I don't like but I made it public public sorry back when me and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> were gonna start doing the Youtube video</u>
<u n="29" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0208">so I was in my bio was gonna put my Youtube link I was gonna make it public so that more people would see it</u>
<u n="31" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0208">cos it sounds really sad but what I'm genuinely scared of happening is me putting videos up on Youtube and like and practically no one seeing them or liking them and them just being like a flop <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0208">know what I mean? so like I made it public <pause dur="short"/> but since I made it public so many more people followed me like I've got forty more followers this summer just from making it public <pause dur="short"/> but I think what it is is like I know personally when I go on Explore cos I love Instagram I love it because I look at all the food stuff all the fitness stuff and just like pretty girls</u>
<u n="35" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0208">it's like one of my hobbies and I just enjoy it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0208"><event desc="unintelligible"/> and erm so I started doing that and that's what I see is that when the person is private I don't bother adding them cos I don't know what their photos are like I don't know if I'm gonna enjoy following them</u>
<u n="39" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0208">I don't like I don't like stuffing up on my news feed for no reason</u>
<u n="41" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0208">I like enjoying the pictures whereas when they're public and I can look through their pictures and I can see if I get a sense if I like following them</u>
<u n="43" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0208">or if I like the pictures that they're gonna pin up</u>
<u n="45" who="S0202">yeah I know what you mean</u>
<u n="46" who="S0208">so I started doing the same cos there's <trunc>noth</trunc> there's nothing on there that needs to be hidden <pause dur="short"/> er it's not like Facebook where it has to go like private</u>
<u n="47" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0208">yeah like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> thanks <pause dur="short"/> thank you she's got mm <pause dur="short"/> two thousand and something followers</u>
<u n="49" who="S0202">cos she's makeup and stuff innit?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0208">that is from her Youtube videos</u>
<u n="51" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0208">like a lot of like sometimes I read the comments on pictures I can see a picture of her that's really beautiful and you comment and I read the other ones and it's people who are like oh you're so beautiful your videos inspire me blah blah blah and she's always so lovely back to them thing is she gets gift packages from her followers</u>
<u n="53" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0208">on Youtube yeah cos she does makeup and stuff like a fashion blog she's <trunc>d</trunc>done a bit of music erm <pause dur="short"/> she gets packages from people cos like when she puts on like <pause dur="short"/> she does these videos where it's like her summer favourites or her autumn favourites or stuff like that and she'll say like all her products that she likes using and the clothes she likes <pause dur="short"/> she's gotten a few packages from like her followers and like people who like her fans basically and they sent her packages with her like her favourite stuff in</u>
<u n="55" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0208">and it is so cute like when I was at hers the last time and she explained to me and she was like yeah I got this from a follower and it's like that's my favourite lipstick and she's sent it to me and stuff like the <trunc>t</trunc> she gets packages in the post</u>
<u n="57" who="S0202">how do they know her address?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0208">probably look her up and find it</u>
<u n="59" who="S0202">that's creepy</u>
<u n="60" who="S0208">it's it's</u>
<u n="61" who="S0202">it's sweet and it's really nice like I would love that</u>
<u n="62" who="S0208">it's</u>
<u n="63" who="S0202" trans="overlap">if like having people</u>
<u n="64" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it's creepy</u>
<u n="66" who="S0208">but it is really sweet and like all the people that she talks to on Instagram like the people who she replies comments to are like oh thank you love you're so sweet and she's met loads of other bloggers</u>
<u n="67" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0208">mm <pause dur="short"/> like from it like <pause dur="short"/> really famous bloggers and like she left a a comment saying had a dinner date with and like tagged it so I just looked like out of interest and this person had like twenty-one thousand followers <pause dur="short"/> like on Youtube like subscribers and I was like wow like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s met them and like I genuinely reckon that she's gonna break into like internet business</u>
<u n="69" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0208">because she's got that style about her to be a blogger and to be like being famous on internet isn't big but there's a girl that a follow called Christian Bazan</u>
<u n="71" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0208">and she <pause dur="short"/> is she's stunning and she does beauty stuff and she started off as a beauty blogger and she did blogs and like put pictures up and stuff and now she's been recruited by some agency that's called Kayture On The Go</u>
<u n="73" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0208">and she travels the world she goes to different countries and she wears their like like their culture and she like she wears different outfits and like she's gotten famous and is paid for that and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s a few <trunc>subscr</trunc> well a few I'd say like a couple of hundred <pause dur="short"/> a couple of hundred subscribers away on Youtube to be paid to make videos</u>
<u n="75" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0208">cos when you get to I think it's three thousand or three thousand five hundred or something around that mark when you get to that many subscribers Youtube pays you to make videos because they get people in to like pay for advert time</u>
<u n="77" who="S0202">adverts yeah and that's when your videos start getting adverts on</u>
<u n="78" who="S0208">exactly so she's almost hit that point where her videos she's gonna be paid to do them</u>
<u n="79" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0208">and when when she came to <anon type="place"/> and she told me that <pause dur="short"/> sorry keeping it lit erm <pause dur="short"/> she got approached by a beauty company like a makeup company erm who approached her and sent her an email and was like we want you to erm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0202" trans="overlap">promote our product</u>
<u n="82" who="S0208">promote our product so just basically use our product and promote it and tell <trunc>y</trunc> tell er tell people what you think and I don't know if she's done it yet I'm not sure if it was like you need a few more subscribers to do it or can you do it whatever? but she told me that someone had approached her asking her to do that so she did it and she got loads more subscribers but can you imagine she's being paid like at first it's not much like don't get me wrong but</u>
<u n="83" who="S0202" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0208">there's a girl that I follow on Instagram I didn't know she did Youtube videos <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her Youtube name is Velvet Ghost <pause dur="short"/> she does the most random videos but they're so much fun to like watch</u>
<u n="85" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0208">she does like a home haul and there's like all her favourite products all her favourite things in her house like she just does random things but so many people love her and they watch her and they're like when it's her birthday or whatever like so many people wish her happy birthday</u>
<u n="87" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0208">and like it's just it's just really lovely like it brings people together</u>
<u n="89" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0208">like I really really love that and that's why I wanted to start doing videos but for my music cos like I've wanted to do that for a while I've been too shy</u>
<u n="91" who="S0202">why though? cos er you're on the internet it's not</u>
<u n="92" who="S0208" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0202">you don't even have to put your face on it you can just like</u>
<u n="94" who="S0208">I know it's</u>
<u n="95" who="S0202">blur that part out sort of thing like</u>
<u n="96" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="97" who="S0202">you don't even need to you know</u>
<u n="98" who="S0208">it's like I want to cos like <pause dur="short"/> I love I love singing it brings me so much joy like I really love singing and I'd love to share it but I'm I'm worried that like people will reject it it sounds really lame</u>
<u n="99" who="S0202">no I no I understand <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="100" who="S0208" trans="overlap">cos what should I care? but it's still it's it's putting my face in the</u>
<u n="101" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you yeah it's a <trunc>neg</trunc> it's and you're scared of <trunc>negativ</trunc>negativity there's nothing wrong about that or weird about that er like <pause dur="short"/> everyone fears that everyone fears getting rejected I mean</u>
<u n="102" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0202">a a simple example what last time I went round <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I went out with all lads it were <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house warming party like it were the night before I came to your friend's actually</u>
<u n="104" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0202">and er we went out and we went to this bar the <anon type="place"/> bar and erm we were there till like half one in the morning and like are we actually gonna leave yet? we've been here all night we've not left are we staying here all night why aren't we why aren't we leaving? so oh well there's some fit girls here right okay you gonna speak to them? no <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="106" who="S0208" trans="overlap">scared of rejection</u>
<u n="107" who="S0202" trans="overlap">why the fuck are we here then?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0202">like why aren't you speaking to them? it was like oh well <pause dur="short"/> they might they might not like me</u>
<u n="110" who="S0208" trans="overlap">and that's like me yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0202" trans="overlap">well how do you know until you speak to them? like I don't get it I don't get that but that's because I've always been confident in myself that if I go and speak to a guy I can get laid but</u>
<u n="112" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0202">I suppose I'm a girl guys will</u>
<u n="114" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0202">sleep with anything it's harder for guys girls have higher standards</u>
<u n="116" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah and like erm when you er when <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> was here the first time and we were saying I need to just have to put that song online cos I said I'm gonna start up a Youtube channel but I don't want my first video to be just by myself</u>
<u n="117" who="S0202">you should do it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because you are such</u>
<u n="118" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="119" who="S0202" trans="overlap">a good singer</u>
<u n="120" who="S0208">think</u>
<u n="121" who="S0202" trans="overlap">like and you</u>
<u n="122" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I'm not</u>
<u n="123" who="S0202" trans="overlap">no like</u>
<u n="124" who="S0208" trans="overlap">saying it for that</u>
<u n="125" who="S0202">I'm <trunc>n</trunc> no I know you're not but the the thing is like you <trunc>n</trunc> you've never sung properly in front of me but I've heard you singing like in the shower and</u>
<u n="126" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0202">like the stuff like that and you're such a beautiful singer and you've got such a beautiful face and a beautiful personality like people will love you people will be people are drawn to you and that is a reason like that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and all them lot never fell out with you because they were drawn to you because you are such a beautiful person like you don't have a negative bone in your body</u>
<u n="128" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0202">no I'm not saying it for any</u>
<u n="130" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no I know but I</u>
<u n="131" who="S0202" trans="overlap">anything but I'm really</u>
<u n="132" who="S0208" trans="overlap">get really <event desc="unintelligible"/> situation</u>
<u n="133" who="S0202" trans="overlap">genuinely mean it no but</u>
<u n="134" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0202">I know you do I do but honestly you are genuinely a beautiful person and it makes me happy in a way that you are you shy away from it cos that tells me that that makes you even more of a beautiful person if that makes sense like</u>
<u n="136" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0202">if you were the sort of person that were to turn around and say oh <trunc>y</trunc> I know like I'm so amazing like</u>
<u n="138" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0202">I love myself that'd make you so much that'd</u>
<u n="140" who="S0208" trans="overlap">that's not attractive</u>
<u n="141" who="S0202" trans="overlap">make you a dickhead it's not attractive but the fact that you don't know it and the fact that you're so insecure receiving compliments makes it more clear that you are a beautiful person</u>
<u n="142" who="S0208">oh thank you</u>
<u n="143" who="S0202" trans="overlap">like so anyway let's just forget I said that because I don't want you to feel awkward</u>
<u n="144" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/> thank you</u>
<u n="145" who="S0202" trans="overlap">but like that's what I think about you</u>
<u n="146" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0202">like I genuinely believe that you are a beautiful person and sometimes I wonder why you're my friend and</u>
<u n="148" who="S0208" trans="overlap">why?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I genuinely think that cos <pause dur="short"/> yeah just</u>
<u n="150" who="S0208">well you know what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0202" trans="overlap">insecurities</u>
<u n="152" who="S0208">I see a lot of myself in you <pause dur="short"/> but mostly I see a lot of my personality in you but it's parts of my parts of my personality that I would never show</u>
<u n="153" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0208">I think that's what drew me to you at first is because I'd love to be outgoing and I'm really outgoing with the people that know me <pause dur="short"/> but with strangers I'm not like when you were so outgoing with strangers and so came to my door and so easily made friends so this is the kind of person I need to be with because you'll you bring out like the better side of me</u>
<u n="155" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="156" who="S0208">if you know what I mean <pause dur="short"/> whereas if I was to hang out with another shy person it would be awkward like erm <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s friend <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> I had a absolutely fantastic night when I went out with them that was the first night I went out with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> black <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0208">and all of that lot <pause dur="short"/> and that was the night that erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> invited me to live with them</u>
<u n="159" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0208">because they were like oh we love you so much you have to live with us and I was like well thank you but I'm previously engaged</u>
<u n="161" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0208">I said that because I knew I was gonna live with you</u>
<u n="163" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0208">and because you didn't know then yet wasn't gonna be like okay but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has to come cos they didn't know you</u>
<u n="165" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0208">so I just like yeah thanks I'm previously engaged <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0208">but erm that was the first night I went out with them but <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is basically very much socially awkward like I am but all the same things so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and me and her I was already ready cos I'd came down for pre drinks it was about nine o'clock in the evening and I went down to her flat and I was in her room with her and I was getting to know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and like I saw the pictures on her wall and I was like used to go to school with that girl cos she went to erm <anon type="place"/> and I went to <anon type="place"/> high school and they were two private schools in the same town two girls' schools but right next to each other</u>
<u n="169" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0208">like I almost went to <anon type="place"/> I visited that school and everything the same year that she went and we used to get the same bus we lived in the same area and we never met each other like that's so weird</u>
<u n="171" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0208">but she went on the <pause dur="short"/> morocco holiday that all of my friends from England went on and I remember talking to a girl called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who I was really good friends with erm who'd gone to the Morocco holiday and I remember asking her this was I mean I was quite old I was about fifteen or sixteen at the time and I was still talking to her and like I was still friendly with her and erm I remember just chatting to her and like oh what are you up to this summer? and she was like I'm going to Morocco on a girls' holiday with some girls from our school and from <anon type="place"/> because you know and I was like oh wow that's such a <trunc>s</trunc>small world you know that's amazing and she was like yeah you would have been here had to stayed and all that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="173" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0208">turns out <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was one of those girls <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0202">yeah it's such a small world innit?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0208" trans="overlap">it's just so weird and I was looking at all these pictures like I used to go to school with all of these girls like they like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was one of my closest friends it was just so weird <pause dur="short"/> but yeah basically <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went to the kitchen to sort some stuff out with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and it was just me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and oh my god it was so awkward</u>
<u n="177" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0208">l actually broached the awkwardness and I was like</u>
<u n="179" who="S0202">like me with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0208">I was like I'm sorry that I'm so awkward but I'm quite shy in these situations and she was like oh my god me too and as soon as we broached that subject</u>
<u n="181" who="S0202">you bonded over the yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0208" trans="overlap">we we bonded over our mutual awkwardness</u>
<u n="183" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0208">and then the whole night it was amazing because I didn't know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> very well at that point this was still very early this was in like first semester</u>
<u n="185" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0208">and we went to <anon type="place"/> that night near there's the house section and the R and B section I'm always happy in the R and B like put me in R and B with the rap and all that kind of stuff and I was like I'm in my element</u>
<u n="187" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0208">which is so weird I know</u>
<u n="189" who="S0202">me too</u>
<u n="190" who="S0208">but we went into there and I remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> kept asking me all night she was like are you happy here are you happy here? and I was like you don't have to keep asking me and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like I'm a bit bored <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will you come to the house with me? and I was like yeah sure we went there and it was just us two and she was like us white girls got to stick together</u>
<u n="191" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0208">it was hilarious er that's the only night that I genuinely kind of bonded with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and since it's been different</u>
<u n="193" who="S0202">the thing is with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0208" trans="overlap">but not in a nasty way</u>
<u n="195" who="S0202">no just that</u>
<u n="196" who="S0208" trans="overlap">it's just cos we're not very close</u>
<u n="197" who="S0202">the thing is with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has a lot of friends and she only considers a small group of them close</u>
<u n="198" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0202">because she has so many cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is one of them girls she's the diplomat she doesn't get involved in shit she doesn't oh she doesn't want to upset anyone I mean</u>
<u n="200" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I guess kinda like me</u>
<u n="201" who="S0202">yeah and she's so outgoing and loud and not in a bad way loud but she's just loud and she's nice and <pause dur="short"/> all that sort of stuff like people are people gravitate towards her and she's the same with everyone so like over the summer holidays I've become really close to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos we spent like four days together and</u>
<u n="202" who="S0208" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="203" who="S0202">we really bonded and stuff and I found out a lot about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that I didn't know before</u>
<u n="204" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0202">like she really likes you like</u>
<u n="206" who="S0208">really?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0202">we talked about you like even <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has only met you a handful of times when we were watching Game of Thrones and stuff</u>
<u n="208" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0202">but like it's so weird like how I met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos like I met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on that night out at the <anon type="place"/> sorry</u>
<u n="210" who="S0208">no no it's I'm just <unclear>rewinding</unclear></u>
<u n="211" who="S0202">erm so I met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that night out at <anon type="place"/> when you couldn't come I don't know why but you couldn't come and we all went out on that <anon type="place"/> night out and stuff</u>
<u n="212" who="S0208">oh it's because I went to erm I left that day remember I left down to London that day?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0208">and you guys went out</u>
<u n="215" who="S0202">and erm like we were all wearing colours from our block and all this and it was just such a good night and like that's the first time I've met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was just like why the fuck have I not met you before? you're awesome and like me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> bonded straight away and after that I just made an effort and I'm like oh you should come and watch Game of Thrones like come up and watch it and I made a conscious effort to become her friend and become friends with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="216" who="S0208">I was like don't take this the wrong way well there's nothing to take the wrong way but I was so so happy when you told me that you'd were getting closer to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and getting closer to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because I was like <pause dur="short"/> I was sort of saying to myself like she's finally gotten over that insecurity of making new friends</u>
<u n="217" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0208">so cos it's like I know I'm the same it's like I made you as a friend and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I felt like that was enough for me like I I feel more comfortable</u>
<u n="219" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0208" trans="overlap">in smaller numbers and when you started branching out I was like I was so happy for you I was like I'm so happy that you've gotten over that insecurity because of everything that happened with our flatmates</u>
<u n="221" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0208">and that you'd made other friends and I was like that's gonna force me to make other friends when I get back then</u>
<u n="223" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0208">I was so happy for you like literally I was oh new people</u>
<u n="225" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0208">going to get to like do all this stuff with</u>
<u n="227" who="S0202">yeah you just it was so shit though cos you couldn't be there <pause dur="short"/> like I were glad that you were there like after but it was so shit that you couldn't be there cos it was such a it</u>
<u n="228" who="S0208">I know <pause dur="short"/> that snap that you sent me with you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> though saying we miss you I screenshotted it</u>
<u n="229" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0208">and then when I was about to come home I sent it back saying</u>
<u n="231" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah you did on our Facebook walls yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I can't wait to see you guys yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0202">but like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and everyone really likes you like and they've talked about you all the time when I'm with them and asking me how you were doing and</u>
<u n="234" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I find that so strange cos I've never been close to any of them</u>
<u n="235" who="S0202">no but they they consider you a friend</u>
<u n="236" who="S0208">it's lovely though</u>
<u n="237" who="S0202">but like next year cos like obviously I say to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's like <pause dur="short"/> I say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's like a week <pause dur="short"/> and like</u>
<u n="238" who="S0208" trans="overlap">you guys have proper bonded</u>
<u n="239" who="S0202">yeah and like she and black <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as well black <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like oh how's your bedroom do you like it blah blah blah? I went yeah it's amazing cos I was in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s bedroom and she was like oh good she'll be staying here loads and I can't wait to have you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> over and</u>
<u n="240" who="S0208" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0202">all this lot and that and like all of them really like both of us</u>
<u n="242" who="S0208">that's so so sweet</u>
<u n="243" who="S0202" trans="overlap">like</u>
<u n="244" who="S0208" trans="overlap">it makes me feel really good because I've always gotten on really well with black <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="246" who="S0208">like from that first night we bonded because when I said</u>
<u n="247" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and she'll getting her arse out and stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0208">yeah like from that first night when we bonded over <unclear>Betty Crocker</unclear> and the fact that she got naked in front of me</u>
<u n="249" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0208">and then the fact that we were both dancing to R and B but then when that Drake song came on I just I lost it and I I've told you about that when I started rapping it</u>
<u n="251" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0208">and then I always have my eyes closed like that and I opened my eyes and there was like a little circle like around us</u>
<u n="253" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0208">and it was just me and I was like <vocal desc="laugh"/> can you come back people? don't leave me alone here</u>
<u n="255" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0208">cos people obviously were like wow and like black <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was especially like oh wow I like you</u>
<u n="257" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0208">I didn't know you were like that and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as well and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like I thought you were my white friend <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0208">I'm sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no well they all really love you all of them like</u>
<u n="262" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0202">I mean I don't see it's weird cos like I really close relationship with <trunc>j</trunc> er not black <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but I don't have a close relationship with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="265" who="S0202">I find it hard I do like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> don't get me wrong but I find it hard to like her</u>
<u n="266" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="267" who="S0202">because she's <trunc>s</trunc> she's so dramatic and she lies a lot and</u>
<u n="268" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0202">I just find it hard to not feel awkward around her <pause dur="short"/> but that's the same as <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I <trunc>fee</trunc> I will always feel like awkward around <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> even though after our library sessions and all our like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were one of the first people I told all that happened with them and they were calling me a slag and all that even after that I still feel awkward around them but that's cos I've not spent enough time with them not to feel awkward</u>
<u n="270" who="S0208">whereas mine's different I've got so close to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> straight away</u>
<u n="271" who="S0202">yeah and you feel awkward around the rest it's it's the same</u>
<u n="272" who="S0208" trans="overlap">especially as awful as this sounds cos I know that white <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is really nice like all the things that I've heard <trunc>fr</trunc> about her like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> raves on about her as if she was royalty</u>
<u n="273" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0208">like in a nice way not being bitchy</u>
<u n="275" who="S0202">yeah I know what you mean</u>
<u n="276" who="S0208">like I've never gotten</u>
<u n="277" who="S0202">I don't get it either</u>
<u n="278" who="S0208" trans="overlap">and I've never gotten a <trunc>n</trunc> a nice vibe from her</u>
<u n="279" who="S0202">no me neither</u>
<u n="280" who="S0208" trans="overlap">and it's like I'm gonna give her time because obviously she's friends with my friends and like she seems like a really lovely person but when I went out with I can't remember why you couldn't come but the night out the night I went out with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0202" trans="overlap">out at the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0208">yeah the night I went out with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and we went to meet her cousin er with <unclear/> mm</u>
<u n="283" who="S0202">well I've got a funny story for you before you finish that</u>
<u n="284" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0202"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> raves on about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but she said as <trunc>soo</trunc> as soon as she started seeing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she changed and maybe that's why you don't get that vibe from her because I don't get</u>
<u n="286" who="S0208" trans="overlap">maybe</u>
<u n="287" who="S0202" trans="overlap">a nice vibe from her either</u>
<u n="288" who="S0208">because the first time I met white <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she wasn't with that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> guy</u>
<u n="289" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0208">she was with her ex boyfriend and erm we went to <anon type="place"/> to a bar to meet her <trunc>cous</trunc> er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s cousin I went out with she didn't wanna go alone so I went with her and she promised me a great night out and she'd buy me a free drink so I was like yeah I'll come with you <pause dur="short"/> so <vocal desc="laugh"/> we went up to meet with her cousin and her cousin was hilarious and all of his friends like they were older</u>
<u n="291" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0208">they'd already left uni but they were coming back</u>
<u n="293" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0208">so I went with them and it was a really really fun night like we sat in <anon type="place"/> for a few drinks and were like out clubbing but erm <pause dur="short"/> like I met them we met up with white <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like pure coincidence she was walking around with her boyfriend and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> saw her outside when we went out for a cigarette and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> scrounged a cigarette off me even though when I'm completely sober I would never let <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> smoke</u>
<u n="295" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0208">as soon as she's drunk and I'm drunk and I'm smoking she's like can I have a bit? and I'm like yeah go on smoke it like</u>
<u n="297" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0208">and I'm the one that taught her <vocal desc="laugh"/> how to smoke properly</u>
<u n="299" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0208">and I feel <trunc>s</trunc>so bad about that</u>
<u n="301" who="S0202">yeah but she doesn't smoke normally</u>
<u n="302" who="S0208">no no</u>
<u n="303" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it's only when she's drinking so it's fine</u>
<u n="304" who="S0208" trans="overlap">even though she still doesn't smoke like she says she hates it <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="305" who="S0202">go on I'll have a drag</u>
<u n="306" who="S0208">I still feel bad but anyway <pause dur="short"/> we met up with white <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so she came into the bar with us to have a few drinks like with everyone there was like a massive table of her cousin's friends they were all having dinner</u>
<u n="307" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0208">we were at like a separate table</u>
<u n="309" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0208">white <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her boyfriend came round and we're like we were having a laugh and a drink and a joke and then they got into an argument and they went home and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like no I don't wanna come out with you guys I'm gonna go home so we were like okay we went out but that was the only time I properly bonded with her like we had one on one conversations</u>
<u n="311" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0208" trans="overlap">and everything like when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went off to see her cousin and I didn't wanna go and interrupt so</u>
<u n="313" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I was chatting to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it was fine and the next few times like the time that we went out for pre drinks and I don't know if you remember I went down a bit earlier than you</u>
<u n="315" who="S0202">yeah cos I was still getting ready yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0208">and you came down and I was like I'm gonna go down and meet you and erm we started off and it was alright and we were playing like it was the night that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was there and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friends from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="318" who="S0208" trans="overlap">came up so I was really like I'm gonna feel fine because there's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> there's black <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <trunc>ev</trunc> black <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was pre drinking with us even though she didn't come out and I was like you're gonna be down soon and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was there so I felt quite comfortable <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> immediately became like bezzy bezzy mates with one of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friends <pause dur="short"/> just wanna tell the story it's more easy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0202">go on</u>
<u n="320" who="S0208">so I was er already feeling a little bit awkward because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was with her flatmates who I'm close to but not you know</u>
<u n="321" who="S0202" trans="overlap"><trunc>be</trunc>bezzy mates with</u>
<u n="322" who="S0208" trans="overlap"><unclear/> and you weren't there yet and I was just like I just need someone that I can like make me feel comfortable</u>
<u n="323" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0208">cos as soon as you're around it's like I find it very hard to instigate conversation</u>
<u n="325" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0208">whereas when you're there and you start up a conversation I find it easy to slide in</u>
<u n="327" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0208">but I need someone to make the first move so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was bezzy mates with her I'm already a little bit awkward with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but just because we've never had the bonding experience so like it was fine but then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came down with her boyfriend and I was chatting to them and we were playing never have I ever and me and her boyfriend drank at the same thing I can't remember what it was it was something funny and he was like oh you too and we started laughing and I could just see her sort of like eyeing me a bit weird</u>
<u n="329" who="S0202"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0202">white <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0208">yeah but because I knew he was I knew that he was her boyfriend so like <vocal desc="sigh"/> it sounds really stupid but as soon as I saw her eyeing me I was purposefully brushing off any conversation he made with me and he was standing next to me and he kept making conversation and I was just like yeah and I was trying to be purposefully a bit shut off so that she would see that I wasn't</u>
<u n="333" who="S0202">interested</u>
<u n="334" who="S0208">trying to go anywhere</u>
<u n="335" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0208">but it's it it turned out fine and then cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was there a really good friend of</u>
<u n="337" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah from your course yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0208">yeah erm Asian Asian <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0202">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0208">and we started erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> we just started talking about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he was like yeah I saw you were really good friends with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he told me that he was really offended that I'd gravitated towards <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> rather than him</u>
<u n="341" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0208">cos we were all in in first semester for er a <trunc>c</trunc> I think it was political theory</u>
<u n="343" who="S0202">let's go inside it's cold</u>
<u n="344" who="S0208">we were bring the wine</u>
<u n="345" who="S0202">yeah I'm bringing it don't worry</u>
<u n="346" who="S0208">we were all in the same seminar which I don't know if I've ever told you actually <pause dur="short"/> but the whole reason me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> became friends is because erm we were in the same seminar for that on a Friday morning but we had erm a next seminar together so I remember once she just thank you erm she <vocal desc="laugh"/> as we were standing up to leave she was just like does anyone have to go to Making of the Modern World? and I stood up and I was like me</u>
<u n="347" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0208">and that's how we became friends but before that I was friends with erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like before I got friends with her like we'd sit next to each other and chat and then <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was really good friends with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0202">the Asian guy?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0208">yeah so it was me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and him and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and then we became like a kind of foursome</u>
<u n="351" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0208">which is completely coincidental because then we got put into groups and our group because we were all sitting together talking our group was me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and this other guy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="353" who="S0202" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="354" who="S0208">who I still don't like <pause dur="short"/> erm so</u>
<u n="355" who="S0202"><unclear/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0208">we only met up we were supposed to meet up every week before our seminar to discuss the questions <pause dur="short"/> which we did once and ended up only talking about shit</u>
<u n="357" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="358" who="S0208">so we decided let's just not do this again we'll just wing it the next time <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0208">cos no one wanted to meet up that early in the morning cos our seminar was already at ten and we had to meet up and nine and no one wanted to do that</u>
<u n="361" who="S0202">yeah no one wants to do that</u>
<u n="362" who="S0208">so we met up once <vocal desc="laugh"/> but then I always just gravitated a bit <trunc>t</trunc> <trunc>m</trunc>more towards <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so like I'd sit by me sitting next to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> there'd be a space next to me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would come</u>
<u n="363" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="364" who="S0208">and sit and like we would chat and stuff and then <vocal desc="laugh"/> that night cos I'd never spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> really he was like yeah you were always so much more friendlier with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and it made me feel really excluded and like he'd always talk about you and how nice you were</u>
<u n="365" who="S0202" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0208">and I was like oh but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I loved you</u>
<u n="367" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0208">I was like you were so sweet and I loved you so much</u>
<u n="369" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0208">so we just became friends that's why that night at <anon type="place"/> I was really happy to see them cos it was the first time I'd socialised with them <trunc>outs</trunc>outside</u>
<u n="371" who="S0202" trans="overlap">that's the first time you disappeared as well</u>
<u n="372" who="S0208">I'm sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0202">no I disappear all the time</u>
<u n="374" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I had such a good <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0202">I disappear all the time like how many times do I disappear?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0208">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0202">over the course of the year just the</u>
<u n="378" who="S0208" trans="overlap">Halloween was the worst</u>
<u n="379" who="S0202">yeah cos it were my birthday as well weren't it?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0208">oh god I literally</u>
<u n="381" who="S0202">I didn't right</u>
<u n="382" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I was feeling horrible I was looking for you everywhere we were sending people off in groups to look for you</u>
<u n="383" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0208">and then when you sent me that message saying you're being such a dick and all that kind of stuff I literally cried in the middle of the of the club</u>
<u n="385" who="S0202">I'm so sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0208">and I was like she just called me a dick and I was like</u>
<u n="387" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0208">she's completely right and everyone was like no she was the one that left we tried looking for her we couldn't find her</u>
<u n="389" who="S0202">no</u>
<u n="390" who="S0208">that was her decision I was like yeah but I should have been with her I should</u>
<u n="391" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0208" trans="overlap">have been looking after her</u>
<u n="393" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0208">and everyone was like shut up cos they were annoyed at me because I was getting up upset and I was like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="396" who="S0208">and all this</u>
<u n="397" who="S0202">no to be fair I think it were like <trunc>par</trunc> fifty fifty blame cos like I managed to get us into the VIP area but I can't remember how we got in <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I was like</u>
<u n="398" who="S0208" trans="overlap">we were walking out of the smokers' corner</u>
<u n="399" who="S0202">yeah we and we walked</u>
<u n="400" who="S0208" trans="overlap">and there was a door to get in</u>
<u n="401" who="S0202" trans="overlap">up instead of down didn't we?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0208" trans="overlap">and there was a walk to go up so we went up</u>
<u n="403" who="S0202">but the</u>
<u n="404" who="S0208">you blagged us in but</u>
<u n="405" who="S0202">at the time I was hammered</u>
<u n="406" who="S0208" trans="overlap">then we were up there</u>
<u n="407" who="S0202">I didn't remember</u>
<u n="408" who="S0208">but when we got up there I remember everything clearly cos I wasn't that drunk</u>
<u n="409" who="S0202">I was battered</u>
<u n="410" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0208">I know</u>
<u n="412" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0208">erm when we got up there I said to everyone right I need a wee and people were like yeah I wanna come yeah and I wanna come yeah and I wanna come so I went with I think it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0202">you went with everyone I was on my own</u>
<u n="415" who="S0208" trans="overlap"><unclear/> girls</u>
<u n="416" who="S0202">cos I said I didn't want to come</u>
<u n="417" who="S0208">and you said you didn't want a wee</u>
<u n="418" who="S0202">I'll wait here</u>
<u n="419" who="S0208">so we were like alright wait here and the guys were there as well like wait here we're going to the toilet</u>
<u n="420" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="421" who="S0208">when we came out of the toilet you were gone we asked the guys and like yeah she went off to see someone she said she'd come back</u>
<u n="422" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0208">we waited upstairs for about half an hour</u>
<u n="424" who="S0202">how did I find my way back upstairs though?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0208" trans="overlap">you didn't</u>
<u n="426" who="S0202">I don't understand</u>
<u n="427" who="S0208">but you went off to see someone you didn't come back we waited there for half an hour and we were like right we need to start looking for her so we some of us stayed upstairs me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was there as well we went downstairs everyone else stayed upstairs</u>
<u n="428" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0208">we went downstairs walked all the way round the stage in a massive circle <pause dur="short"/> you didn't come so that's when I sent you the message saying we're by the bar by the smokers' exit because that was the last time we got our drinks</u>
<u n="430" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0208">we were by the exit there was a bar by the exit and then the smokers' thing</u>
<u n="432" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="433" who="S0208">and it's like that's where I am then you were like I can't find that and I was like well stay exactly where you are</u>
<u n="434" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="435" who="S0208">we're coming to find you if you keep moving around we can't find you and that's when you replied saying you're being a dickhead and stuff</u>
<u n="436" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0208">and I was just like but we've been looking for you for two hours</u>
<u n="438" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="439" who="S0208">and like short of saying you ruined our night because we were looking for you rather than enjoying it I was like just stay fucking exactly where you are stop moving at the same time we are</u>
<u n="440" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0208">and then when you said I'm going home and all that kind of stuff I was like</u>
<u n="442" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0208">but instead of being angry I got upset</u>
<u n="444" who="S0202">oh I'm sorry</u>
<u n="445" who="S0208" trans="overlap">because that time because I was no no I'm not saying this to make you upset it's just I'm telling you my side because</u>
<u n="446" who="S0202" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0208">we were so close I literally I felt so guilty like I couldn't enjoy myself without you being there</u>
<u n="448" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="449" who="S0208">and that's why I felt so bad and like when you told me that I was a dickhead it just sort of confirmed all the guilt that I had inside myself</u>
<u n="450" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0208">and I was just like</u>
<u n="452" who="S0202" trans="overlap">such a dickhead <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0208">I was like oh my god I feel so bad but the next day you were completely fine with me the next day when you</u>
<u n="454" who="S0202" trans="overlap">like</u>
<u n="455" who="S0208">when you woke up and I was like text me when you wake up and stuff and you did and I was like my god she's gonna really shout at me</u>
<u n="456" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0208">I was literally getting like and my palms were sweating and I was literally I I'm having to get ready for the shouting and</u>
<u n="458" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0208">and I came over and it was fine and you were like hi how are you? and stuff and I was like <pause dur="short"/> you don't know?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0208">and that's when you were like no no I'm sorry it was my fault and you said all this kind of stuff and I was like I have been worried</u>
<u n="462" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0208">for twenty-four hours</u>
<u n="464" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0208">about you and it turns out you're fucking fine</u>
<u n="466" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0208">and I was just like <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0202">yeah well that's the night that I found that handbag with that phone in</u>
<u n="469" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0202">I'm such a dick I'm sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0208">no but from now</u>
<u n="472" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0208">cos I know you that bit better and I know</u>
<u n="474" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I go on adventures</u>
<u n="475" who="S0208" trans="overlap">your personality and I know that you go on adventures and I know that you get a bit more</u>
<u n="476" who="S0202">aggressive when I'm drunk</u>
<u n="477" who="S0208">wouldn't say yeah aggressive when you're drunk</u>
<u n="478" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah I do yeah</u>
<u n="479" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I've stopped taking it personal personally</u>
<u n="480" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0208">cos it's like that night out that we went with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and your new friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when you said you wanted to go home I knew that you wouldn't take it bad that I said that and no matter what bad things you say to me I knew that you wouldn't</u>
<u n="482" who="S0202" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="483" who="S0208" trans="overlap">feel like that the next day so I was like when I sent you home and gave you the keys I knew that you'd be fine</u>
<u n="484" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0208">but it's like at first because you were <pause dur="short"/> like I knew it back then that you were my only true friend and I was like I can't fuck this up</u>
<u n="486" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0208">and that's why felt such an obligation to like</u>
<u n="488" who="S0202" trans="overlap">no I felt so bad as well</u>
<u n="489" who="S0208" trans="overlap">be</u>
<u n="490" who="S0202" trans="overlap">a lot of the times</u>
<u n="491" who="S0208">like that with you but now on like even next year or anything if you go off on an adventure I hope you know</u>
<u n="492" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you're just gonna leave me</u>
<u n="493" who="S0208" trans="overlap">er I'm I'm just gonna leave you</u>
<u n="494" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0208">because I'm not saying this nasty like obviously I'll check that you were okay and like ring you if you stop answering or whatever if you've gone home to sleep I'm just gonna like she's fucking fine</u>
<u n="496" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="497" who="S0208">because that night was honestly I I was sick with worry</u>
<u n="498" who="S0202" trans="overlap">oh I'm so sorry</u>
<u n="499" who="S0208">no no I was sick with worry because</u>
<u n="500" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I'm so sorry</u>
<u n="501" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I knew how drunk you were I was sick with worry because I thought something would have happened to you that's the I mean</u>
<u n="502" who="S0202" trans="overlap">can you imagine me getting raped? that would never happen <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no you'd rip off someone's penis before that happened but I just</u>
<u n="504" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I would bite it off <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0208">but I just I just I felt sick with worry but now that I know you because that was that was a month after we met each other</u>
<u n="506" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="507" who="S0208">not even or a bit more</u>
<u n="508" who="S0202">we were still like even then we were like mega close though weren't we like?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah but it was still it was still new</u>
<u n="510" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="511" who="S0208">and I still felt like</u>
<u n="512" who="S0202" trans="overlap">didn't really know each other</u>
<u n="513" who="S0208">it sounds</u>
<u n="514" who="S0202" trans="overlap">that deeply</u>
<u n="515" who="S0208" trans="overlap">really sad like I feel I can tell you now but I still felt like I had to impress you</u>
<u n="516" who="S0202">yeah I felt</u>
<u n="517" who="S0208" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="518" who="S0202" trans="overlap">the same about you for up until like January</u>
<u n="519" who="S0208">yeah it's like don't</u>
<u n="520" who="S0202" trans="overlap">even when I</u>
<u n="521" who="S0208" trans="overlap">don't</u>
<u n="522" who="S0202" trans="overlap">even though when I were at your house with your parents I felt like I had to impress</u>
<u n="523" who="S0208">so</u>
<u n="524" who="S0202">everyone</u>
<u n="525" who="S0208">don't take this the wrong way because I don't feel like that now</u>
<u n="526" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="527" who="S0208">and honestly it's not a a problem but I felt like I had to agree with you on everything because you were so strong personality wise</u>
<u n="528" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="529" who="S0208">and like your rants and stuff I'm not gonna lie</u>
<u n="530" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="531" who="S0208">at first fucking terrified me</u>
<u n="532" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0208">cos I'd never seen anyone apart from my mum use such profuse language and I'd be like yeah I agree</u>
<u n="534" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0208">fucking fucking dickhead cunt yeah yeah cos I was scared about what you'd like turn on me if I said no don't agree</u>
<u n="536" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="537" who="S0208">whereas now I'm just like no come no erm but yeah that's why I got so scared that night of Halloween and I told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and we have to leave now I was like I have to make sure she's okay</u>
<u n="538" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="539" who="S0208">I can't have her being mad at me</u>
<u n="540" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I'm such a dickhead</u>
<u n="541" who="S0208" trans="overlap">she's gonna yell at me tomorrow and all that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="542" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0208">but he was like why do you care so much blah blah blah and I was like she's my only friend <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="545" who="S0208">but he was like you're out with all these people and I was like yes but I don't like them</u>
<u n="546" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="547" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so that's why at first I was so scared because I felt like I had to agree with like all of your opinions</u>
<u n="548" who="S0202" trans="overlap">opinions yeah</u>
<u n="549" who="S0208">and it sounds really stupid but now I know that I can I can say no and like you don't care</u>
<u n="550" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="551" who="S0208">like at first I felt like I was</u>
<u n="552" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I accept it</u>
<u n="553" who="S0208">like I I have to agree with her because otherwise we won't be friends</u>
<u n="554" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="555" who="S0208">and I can't lose her as a friend</u>
<u n="556" who="S0202">I used to think the same about you it's really weird cos like</u>
<u n="557" who="S0208" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0202">yeah cos like <pause dur="short"/> don't judge me on this okay?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0202">you <trunc>ca</trunc> there's no judgement allowed</u>
<u n="561" who="S0208">listen</u>
<u n="562" who="S0202">okay</u>
<u n="563" who="S0208">all the nights I've been like don't take offence don't take offence</u>
<u n="564" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so before I met you I would have been the sort of person to do that to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s Ipad and laptop I would have done that</u>
<u n="565" who="S0208">right</u>
<u n="566" who="S0202">I would not have thought twice about it I would have before I met you I would have done that to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s door before I met you if</u>
<u n="567" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="568" who="S0202">if in September I didn't meet you and we weren't friends and all that happened I would have done that I would not have thought twice about it and I felt guilty after I did it and my conscience would not let me rest like I wouldn't have been able to sleep blah blah but wouldn't have thought any twice about doing it but as soon as I met you and as soon as we got to know each other and as soon as we became really good friends I always found myself thinking what would <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> say? what would <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> think?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0208">really? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0202"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wouldn't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would not agree with this if cos <pause dur="short"/> cos I had so much anger inside me like that that night that I snapped the reason I snapped was cos I weren't with you if I were was with you I wouldn't have snapped and like as soon as I did it I deleted it because I knew that you would have disapproved of it I knew that that's not who I was and I knew <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> as much as I want as much as I try to be that person who was aggressive and who was mouthy and who was all this or that I'm not that person and that's why I deleted it instantly</u>
<u n="571" who="S0208">but that</u>
<u n="572" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and like</u>
<u n="573" who="S0208">I don't take offence by that I actually find that's quite a complement because I know that I have a very high tolerance and I know that I will always give people the benefit of the doubt or I'm always one for giving second chances and all that kind of stuff I mean <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> as an example</u>
<u n="574" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="575" who="S0208">like I just I don't</u>
<u n="576" who="S0202">hold grudges</u>
<u n="577" who="S0208">no I</u>
<u n="578" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you're not a bitter person</u>
<u n="579" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I I can't like I physically can't</u>
<u n="580" who="S0202">it takes too much energy</u>
<u n="581" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="582" who="S0202" trans="overlap">like</u>
<u n="583" who="S0208">I just don't have time for it</u>
<u n="584" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and <trunc>y</trunc> and the thing is you've taught me that like</u>
<u n="585" who="S0208">and I've I've always told you that as well it's like when you would always go off on a rant or stuff like with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and all that kind of stuff I would always say I don't have time for that</u>
<u n="586" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="587" who="S0208">it's like I just don't care I nothing them</u>
<u n="588" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="589" who="S0208">and I find that quite a compliment that you say that because <pause dur="short"/> like don't take this nastily or anything but I'd never</u>
<u n="590" who="S0202" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="591" who="S0208">I'd never met anyone who was so like expressive</u>
<u n="592" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0208">with their feelings I guess</u>
<u n="594" who="S0202">but it helps me because</u>
<u n="595" who="S0208" trans="overlap">so because I was also quite young I mean I was only eighteen like I'm nineteen now it's not a big difference but because I'd never <pause dur="short"/> lived through all the stuff that</u>
<u n="596" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="597" who="S0208" trans="overlap">you'd lived through you opened my eyes as well just the way I guess you opened mine</u>
<u n="598" who="S0202" trans="overlap">in the opposite way yeah like</u>
<u n="599" who="S0208">but I find that as a compliment rather than offensive because it feels nice to be able to know that I'm able to</u>
<u n="600" who="S0202" trans="overlap">made a positive impact</u>
<u n="601" who="S0208">calm you in a certain way</u>
<u n="602" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah cos</u>
<u n="603" who="S0208">just the way that you bring out the fire in me</u>
<u n="604" who="S0202">cos the thing is like with me like before I went to university I went to see a psychic you know the story I've</u>
<u n="605" who="S0208" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="606" who="S0202">told you <pause dur="short"/> and she's the whole <trunc>rea</trunc> the psychic is the only the whole reason that I have this relationship with my mum she's my own mum</u>
<u n="607" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="608" who="S0202">didn't I didn't speak to her for four years I used to tell her how much I hated her</u>
<u n="609" who="S0208">do you wanna go over this thing?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0202">yeah like</u>
<u n="611" who="S0208" trans="overlap">again</u>
<u n="612" who="S0202">I used to tell her how much I hated her like I never used to get a birthday card off her I didn't get a birthday card off her from being fifteen</u>
<u n="613" who="S0208">that's really sad though that's really</u>
<u n="614" who="S0202">like</u>
<u n="615" who="S0208" trans="overlap">it's alight <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="616" who="S0202">and I went I went to see this psychic and she told me all this stuff like I were carrying on this taking this around with me and had all these problems and</u>
<u n="617" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="618" who="S0202">it was weird I don't know why <event desc="unintelligible"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="619" who="S0208">alight <pause dur="short"/> frodo Frodo <vocal desc="misc"/> Frodo come on</u>
<u n="620" who="S0202">like and she were telling me like I were carrying this bitterness around with me and I was such an angry person and like I thought right I reckon if it were mum I'm gonna stop carrying this bitterness around with me and I thought that would be enough and then I met you and like <pause dur="short"/> I hate admitting this but I was such an angry person I was so angry at the world I was so angry at everyone like I were angry at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or angry at my mum I were angry at my life I were angry at everyone and there were no reason for it</u>
<u n="621" who="S0208">the thing is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> though</u>
<u n="622" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and</u>
<u n="623" who="S0208">you say that you were a really angry person until you met me but I was too calm a person till you met me I was a pushover I'm not afraid of admitting it I still am I'm working at</u>
<u n="624" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and you still are but</u>
<u n="625" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I'm working on it</u>
<u n="626" who="S0202">the thing is I'm still an angry person but I'm working on it</u>
<u n="627" who="S0208">and I think that's what</u>
<u n="628" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you know?</u>
<u n="629" who="S0208">that's what we bring each other we complement each other because I teach you how to calm down and maybe think a bit more rationally or whatever</u>
<u n="630" who="S0202">and I teach you how to stand up for yourself a little bit more</u>
<u n="631" who="S0208" trans="overlap">you teach me how to stand up for myself because I mean there are things that people have done to me that I have let go because I haven't been bothered or I've been too scared of confrontation <pause dur="short"/> and it's stuff that I regret now</u>
<u n="632" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0208">whereas no having that argument with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the other night I don't regret it at all the only thing I regret is that it didn't happen sooner but I'm always too afraid of what other people will think and I'm always afraid of repercussions</u>
<u n="634" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0208">feels like even though I knew that I like what I've said to you from the start even though I knew that I would never be friends with any of those people regardless of what I said whether I was nice to them or not <pause dur="short"/> I knew I was never going to be friends with them I still couldn't be angry towards them</u>
<u n="636" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0208">but I'm working on it</u>
<u n="638" who="S0202">but that really upset me as well and I'm so I'm saying this now but it really upset me that they were doing all these things to me and you couldn't stand up for me and then I took a step back and realised that you're not me <pause dur="short"/> you are a shy person you are not like me I'm fiery I am a loud person I will stand up for anyone anyone who I think is being hurt I will stand up for them and no questions asked but</u>
<u n="639" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="640" who="S0202">you are not like that</u>
<u n="641" who="S0208" trans="overlap">but I</u>
<u n="642" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and you're that that's not a fault</u>
<u n="643" who="S0208">no but I've</u>
<u n="644" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it's a fault of mine that I thought that of you</u>
<u n="645" who="S0208">I've always always felt every time something happened and I er I couldn't not that you were insinuating because I know you didn't mean it to put me down but when you'd say or when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actually would say I hope like people would stick up or whatever it's when I realised I was like I I need to I need to stick up cos I was like I I love her so much and I can't even stick up for my friend who is in need of it and that's when I really realised that there was a problem and I tried to make a difference like that</u>
<u n="646" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and you did though</u>
<u n="647" who="S0208" trans="overlap">that meeting that you had</u>
<u n="648" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you made a difference by being my friend</u>
<u n="649" who="S0208">that's <trunc>diff</trunc> that erm meeting that you had</u>
<u n="650" who="S0202" trans="overlap">but does it even matter about the meeting?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0208" trans="overlap">with that guy at university that's I said I was gonna use my voice but like honestly you saying that it's like it's not it's not news to me because I knew every time that you wanted me to stick up for you and I didn't do it it's something that I regret</u>
<u n="652" who="S0202">but you stuck up for me in a different way</u>
<u n="653" who="S0208" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="654" who="S0202">you stuck up for me by still being my friend</u>
<u n="655" who="S0208">well I'm</u>
<u n="656" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and standing by me by and</u>
<u n="657" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I'm glad you see it that way because</u>
<u n="658" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you know</u>
<u n="659" who="S0208">even even <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="660" who="S0202">you didn't stand up with your gob you stood up by being my friend</u>
<u n="661" who="S0208">that's</u>
<u n="662" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and you stood up in a different way</u>
<u n="663" who="S0208">I I guess that's just kind of how I use myself it's like I will always show support where it's needed <pause dur="short"/> but like I'm not the kind of person that will put myself out there and say stuff and as <trunc>mu</trunc> no matter how much I try and rectify that or try and stand up</u>
<u n="664" who="S0202">no it's who you are</u>
<u n="665" who="S0208" trans="overlap">not not only for myself though it's just for you it's for myself I'm not even capable of saying stuff for myself like when I heard <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> saying that stuff I still didn't say something it was for myself <pause dur="short"/> well I just can't do it but</u>
<u n="666" who="S0202">no and I understand that and it's like I mean <pause dur="short"/> the hardest part for me well like I've said to this I've said this to you so many times I were twenty-two I were going into an environment where I were gonna be surrounded by eighteen year olds</u>
<u n="667" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0202">and everything was so perfect like you remember that little white board that we had?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="670" who="S0202">like erm so and so in this flat</u>
<u n="671" who="S0208">put all our names on it</u>
<u n="672" who="S0202" trans="overlap">love so and so in four 0 seven and it was so nice and then as soon as <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came into the situation everything changed and it just</u>
<u n="673" who="S0208" trans="overlap">not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="674" who="S0202">no just not even <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="675" who="S0208" trans="overlap">because I don't know if I told you this but <pause dur="short"/> ages ago I mean like it was a while after all of that shit happened <pause dur="short"/> a long time after that I mean it was just before it happened with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just before exams and stuff I was going to uni and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was obviously going up at the same time and we got into the elevator er elevator? am I American?</u>
<u n="676" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="677" who="S0208">got into the lift together and it was it was so awkward I mean I wasn't gonna say anything because well as much as I I don't have the guts to stick up for people that I love and stuff I have the guts to just remain silent so like I like I'm like my mum I'm very much like my mum I like to please people</u>
<u n="678" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="679" who="S0208">whether I like them or not I like to be liked and that's one of my faults I I I need to be liked</u>
<u n="680" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="681" who="S0208">so that's probably one of the reasons why I always stay silent but when we go into the lift I didn't say anything and I didn't look in her direction and I was like this is awkward but I'm I'm staying silent I was like I don't need to please this person I don't like this person and she started talking to me and she was like hi <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so I knew it was obviously directed at me and I was like hi didn't wanna be rude erm but then when I was like in my head I was like why am I even speaking to this person? why am I giving her the time of day it was like so what if I'm rude to her? I was like she's been so rude to my friend but then instantly she was like I'm so sorry for everything that's happened like instantly <pause dur="short"/> and she wasn't with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I sort of that's when I sort of started to realise I was like you really are a lapdog I didn't say it but I was like I don't want your apology she was like no but I I feel genuinely bad about everything that's happened and I was like I don't care and she was like so I know I I haven't spoken to you in a while but like how is everything how are you? and she seemed genuinely</u>
<u n="682" who="S0202">interested</u>
<u n="683" who="S0208">like no worried like genuinely worried</u>
<u n="684" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="685" who="S0208">and I was like things could be better thanks like I was being short and I was</u>
<u n="686" who="S0202" trans="overlap">civil</u>
<u n="687" who="S0208">I was proud of myself in that moment because usually I would be civil as fuck but to this person I just I felt like I owed her nothing <pause dur="short"/> and I feel really bad because we were walking to uni together we were in the lift together we were going up the steps together and when we got to the top of the steps she kept walking straight and I walked over the cross lights but I always walk over that way anyway</u>
<u n="688" who="S0202">yeah we both do it's a habit yeah</u>
<u n="689" who="S0208">but she was I could tell she was trying and I just wasn't interested and I was like this is my time to rectify all those times I didn't stick up for you like do you know what I mean? because</u>
<u n="690" who="S0202" trans="overlap">but I don't need you to stick up for me</u>
<u n="691" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no I know</u>
<u n="692" who="S0202" trans="overlap">but like in my head</u>
<u n="693" who="S0208" trans="overlap">and you're saying you're saying this now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="694" who="S0202" trans="overlap">in my head it's like</u>
<u n="695" who="S0208" trans="overlap">but at the time</u>
<u n="696" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I wanted you to but then</u>
<u n="697" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="698" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I think to myself I don't need anyone to stick up for me because end of the day I did nothing wrong I did nothing to deserve that the thing is with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she doesn't like other people being looked at she doesn't like other people being pretty</u>
<u n="699" who="S0208">no but <trunc>h</trunc></u>
<u n="700" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and that's all it were</u>
<u n="701" who="S0208" trans="overlap">hear me out like this isn't nasty at all you're saying this now but at the time I know you wanted to stick up for me I could see it in your eyes I could sense it in what you were saying even <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I think the worst part was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because he was the one that made me feel the worst I can't remember exactly what it was that he said or what would be said but he would make it known that he was disappointed in the fact that I wasn't <pause dur="short"/> sticking up do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="702" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="703" who="S0208">and that's when I tried to make a difference but I'm just I'm not that person no matter what someone does to me or as well as awful as it sounds especially to someone else because if someone does something awful to someone else as awful as it sounds they didn't do it to me</u>
<u n="704" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="705" who="S0208">and I think in my head I have no right to be horrible to this person</u>
<u n="706" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="707" who="S0208" trans="overlap">because of what they've done to someone else because no matter how close that person is to me or whatever I if unless they hurt me personally I physically can't muster that strength and that anger</u>
<u n="708" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="709" who="S0208" trans="overlap">to pull them up on it and I love you so much and I hope you know that</u>
<u n="710" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I know you do</u>
<u n="711" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I would do anything for you</u>
<u n="712" who="S0202" trans="overlap">of course I do of course I do</u>
<u n="713" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I hope you know that I just</u>
<u n="714" who="S0202" trans="overlap">er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="715" who="S0208">I can't</u>
<u n="716" who="S0202">I know</u>
<u n="717" who="S0208">voice it</u>
<u n="718" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and I know that and I always knew that and like that's why I always stuck up for you not because of any other reason but I knew that you couldn't do it yourself and that's why I always</u>
<u n="719" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I can't do it for myself</u>
<u n="720" who="S0202">that's why I always put myself out there that's why I always made it known that I was not happy with how</u>
<u n="721" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="722" who="S0202" trans="overlap">they were treating you</u>
<u n="723" who="S0208">I'm sorry because I realise that</u>
<u n="724" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and I didn't do it for anything else other than I wanted them to stop</u>
<u n="725" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no because I think you need</u>
<u n="726" who="S0202" trans="overlap">doing what they were doing to you as well</u>
<u n="727" who="S0208" trans="overlap">you need to hear this</u>
<u n="728" who="S0202" trans="overlap">what they were doing to me</u>
<u n="729" who="S0208" trans="overlap">because half of the stuff that you've lived through with all of those horrible people is because of me because you've been sticking</u>
<u n="730" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it's not because of you</u>
<u n="731" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no listen it's because you've been sticking up for me and you'd always put yourself out there for my sake and defend me and I wasn't able to do the same for you and I'm so sorry that you had to live through all of that with the people and I wasn't there to stick up for you</u>
<u n="732" who="S0202">do you know what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? we've both lived through it we both lived through it you put up with as much shit as I did let's face it you put up with shit because you were my friend</u>
<u n="733" who="S0208">but I would always choose you over anyone else</u>
<u n="734" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I know you would that is <trunc>n</trunc> I'm not protesting that at all</u>
<u n="735" who="S0208">no I</u>
<u n="736" who="S0202" trans="overlap">but my point is</u>
<u n="737" who="S0208">I know</u>
<u n="738" who="S0202">you <pause dur="short"/> stuck up for me by being my friend and not being friends with them and not entertaining their bullshit</u>
<u n="739" who="S0208">I'm just sorry that I couldn't</u>
<u n="740" who="S0202">what?</u>
<u n="741" who="S0208">give you more</u>
<u n="742" who="S0202">what? be angry at them make yourself a victim</u>
<u n="743" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah but I</u>
<u n="744" who="S0202" trans="overlap">or a target like me?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I didn't care what they thought that's the thing is like</u>
<u n="746" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I know but that's the thing you showed them that</u>
<u n="747" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I didn't care and I'm so sorry</u>
<u n="748" who="S0202">don't don't seriously <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> don't apologise</u>
<u n="749" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no because you lived through so much shit</u>
<u n="750" who="S0202">and so did you <pause dur="short"/> we both lived through it together and let's face it I didn't fucking help myself when I put that Facebook status like I was just as much to blame as they were when I put that and yet I apologised and yet it went too far after that but before that as soon as I put that status I were inviting this shit I were inviting the fact that I didn't like them and they didn't like me we made it known by me putting that status you know? and it doesn't matter what you said or it didn't say they were always gonna do what they were gonna do whether I put that status or not or whether you said something or if I said something</u>
<u n="751" who="S0208">I just hope you know that</u>
<u n="752" who="S0202" trans="overlap">the fact is that I stood up to them and they're bullies that's all they were that is all <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will ever be and she makes her friends do that and the fact of the matter is when they leave university and when they have children <pause dur="short"/> and they look back they will realise and do you know what? it doesn't even matter whether you said anything to them or not you're my friend you stuck by me through all of it through all my rants through all my tears</u>
<u n="753" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="754" who="S0202">through all this shit that I deserved</u>
<u n="755" who="S0208" trans="overlap">well of course</u>
<u n="756" who="S0202" trans="overlap">or didn't deserve you were there as my friend you're still my friend now you know? and you didn't have to be the easy way out would have been do what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did going and being friends with them and not being my friend</u>
<u n="757" who="S0208">I wouldn't have done that ever</u>
<u n="758" who="S0202">exactly and that's your way of sticking up for me and being my friend</u>
<u n="759" who="S0208">I'm sorry that I couldn't voice it is all I'm saying but</u>
<u n="760" who="S0202">it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="761" who="S0208">through you helping me and showing me that it's okay to stick up for yourself and it's okay to get angry at people it's not the end of the world <pause dur="short"/> because I I guess that from where I came from it's it was it was quite an enclosed environment like with my parents and my friends <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="762" who="S0202">eh up then ginger <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="763" who="S0208">so because I had had quite a closed upbringing and was so different to your situation I just want you to know that you have helped me to find the voice that I guess I've always wanted to have but I've been too scared to voice if you know what I mean it sounds really weird but because what I lived through with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and all that like I did I did stick up for myself for six months we didn't talk I literally couldn't look at her the silence I get I think that silence is my worst weapon because people always accept me to be that sweet person that's always gonna be forgiving or that I think the silence is the worse treatment I can give someone</u>
<u n="764" who="S0202">it is because I'm not being funny or anything but <pause dur="short"/> I wish that I'd have just not given them any er recognition at all</u>
<u n="765" who="S0208">but I think that's the worse I think that's the <trunc>wor</trunc> well <pause dur="short"/> I think that because I feel it's the worst treatment someone can give me when someone's mad at me and the silent treatment</u>
<u n="766" who="S0202">it's the worst</u>
<u n="767" who="S0208">it's the worst feeling I can have because I'd rather someone shout at me and me explain my side or me shout back than silence and I think you and seeing how the way you handle things and learning about your upbringing and just a completely different side to what I've ever lived through has helped me find it and this summer with all the shit that's gone through with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when I was actually proud of myself for doing this because when I stood up to her and told her every single thing I had on my chest against her</u>
<u n="768" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and I was I'm proud of you as well</u>
<u n="769" who="S0208">and it was fine and as soon as I realised and I saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s reaction yes she was hurt but talked through it and then we went out together and it was fine like it was absolutely fine there was</u>
<u n="770" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah you worked it out</u>
<u n="771" who="S0208">not even an awkwardness because she wanted to hear it and I was ready to say it it made me realise that I've got nothing to be afraid of by standing up for myself and that's because of you <pause dur="short"/> so I want you to know that if anything happens if ever I run into any of those girls or if ever they say something to me I'll be ready to say something back and if ever you have any problem with anyone else I'm I'm ready to stick up for you it's like</u>
<u n="772" who="S0202" trans="overlap">do you know?</u>
<u n="773" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I had to live through this year of being nave and being the sweet little shy girl or whatever to actually realise that life doesn't work like that you can't be nice to everyone and not everyone's gonna like you and I had to learn that but I learnt it from you because my parents have given me a sheltered upbringing and I have had that all through my life because I've never had to live through it do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="774" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="775" who="S0208">so like what I lived through with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like yeah fair enough it was awful but it was nothing compared to this last year that we've lived <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="776" who="S0202">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="777" who="S0208">and I'm gonna say you've lived because I know it was ten times worse for you than it was for me <pause dur="short"/> but I want you to know that I'm I'm ready <pause dur="short"/> to stick up for you</u>
<u n="778" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I know what you mean</u>
<u n="779" who="S0208">in the way that you want me to</u>
<u n="780" who="S0202" trans="overlap">do you know what? I hope you never have to</u>
<u n="781" who="S0208">I</u>
<u n="782" who="S0202" trans="overlap">for my sake</u>
<u n="783" who="S0208">I hope I never have to but</u>
<u n="784" who="S0202" trans="overlap">cos do you know what? like I <trunc>d</trunc> I <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="785" who="S0208">it's gonna happen all through life and it's gonna happen to me</u>
<u n="786" who="S0202" trans="overlap">of course it is</u>
<u n="787" who="S0208">it's gonna happen to you it's gonna happen to everyone</u>
<u n="788" who="S0202">the thing is like the thing that bothered me the most about the whole situation is that they didn't know me they was making all this judgements judgements about me they and from this one status that I put on Facebook that I deleted straight away which should have told them everything they should know I apologised to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at the ball</u>
<u n="789" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="790" who="S0202">and I made this effort and I've made this effort from September and blah blah like <pause dur="short"/> they didn't know me like they didn't know anything about me and they were making these judgements about me and I think that's what that was the hardest part and I didn't think until later well actually they don't know me and they're making these judgements so what does that make them? like they don't know anything about me they don't know who I am they don't know what I've lived through they don't know my life they don't know</u>
<u n="791" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="792" who="S0202">anything they don't know me personally they don't know my likes or dislikes</u>
<u n="793" who="S0208" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="794" who="S0202">all they know is what they see</u>
<u n="795" who="S0208">having said that and all that you've lived through and living through that and <unclear/> the way you deal with things is going on the defensive and defending yourself and showing your side of the story my way of dealing with stuff like that is very different</u>
<u n="796" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="797" who="S0208">rather than immediately defending myself what I do is I I mull it over it builds deep inside of me and then one day I snap</u>
<u n="798" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="799" who="S0208">and I fucking I mean I fucking snap like no one wants to be there when that happens</u>
<u n="800" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="801" who="S0208">but <pause dur="short"/> because I was alone when it did happen I think that's why all this shit happened like to me personally because I inflicted all of the things that I had on myself and I think that's that's I mean that is the worst way of dealing with things but I'm very much like my dad</u>
<u n="802" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="803" who="S0208">in that sense of things because</u>
<u n="804" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you just worry</u>
<u n="805" who="S0208">he's</u>
<u n="806" who="S0202">and it builds up</u>
<u n="807" who="S0208">he lets it build up he <trunc>d</trunc> he won't say anything he won't do anything he won't act but he'll let it build up and I'm very much like him in that sense not saying that he's <pause dur="short"/> bulimic or depressive or anything <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="808" who="S0202">you're not bulimic <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="809" who="S0208">no I know I'm not but you know</u>
<u n="810" who="S0202">I know what you mean</u>
<u n="811" who="S0208">I inverted it on myself</u>
<u n="812" who="S0202">I worried about you so much</u>
<u n="813" who="S0208" trans="overlap">but now I</u>
<u n="814" who="S0202" trans="overlap">when you told me that</u>
<u n="815" who="S0208" trans="overlap">feel like I'm I'm not gonna do that to myself anymore because it's not me that's the problem it was them the whole time</u>
<u n="816" who="S0202">I'm so glad that you've you've told me what you've told me because like ever since you you opened up to me and told me that I've done nothing but worry about you</u>
<u n="817" who="S0208">I'm sorry for doing that to you</u>
<u n="818" who="S0202">no mm babe don't be stupid like <pause dur="short"/> cos when you told me I were <pause dur="short"/> I were in a state of shock and facing that I said to you you shouldn't do that why are you doing that? like I reprimanded you straight away and I felt bad for doing that because that's not how you should deal with it you should do this and you should do that and blah blah but <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know what to say I didn't know what to do and I were just like look and all I could say to you were look whatever you do I'm here and like I felt bad for saying that as well because I felt well no she shouldn't be doing that and I should tell her that but I did tell her that and then I were thinking well I shouldn't have said this or should have said that and</u>
<u n="819" who="S0208">no there's nothing</u>
<u n="820" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and then ever since then</u>
<u n="821" who="S0208" trans="overlap">you can say to anyone</u>
<u n="822" who="S0202">I know</u>
<u n="823" who="S0208">when they tell you something like that like</u>
<u n="824" who="S0202" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="825" who="S0208">I shouldn't have put you in that even though you are</u>
<u n="826" who="S0202" trans="overlap">no you're my friend</u>
<u n="827" who="S0208">no but</u>
<u n="828" who="S0202" trans="overlap">if anything like that ever happens I want you to tell me like</u>
<u n="829" who="S0208"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="830" who="S0202" trans="overlap">don't no listen to me</u>
<u n="831" who="S0208" trans="overlap">you are my closest friend</u>
<u n="832" who="S0202">don't ever feel like you need to be drunk to tell me shit like that ever</u>
<u n="833" who="S0208">okay</u>
<u n="834" who="S0202">because it just it I don't care whether you've got warts growing out of your fucking face whatever you problem you've got</u>
<u n="835" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I know it's just</u>
<u n="836" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you should come to me and tell me because</u>
<u n="837" who="S0208">well</u>
<u n="838" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I might not be able to help but I can at least support you</u>
<u n="839" who="S0208">I was so ashamed at it and the fact that it was happening and I was so ashamed that I'd gone back to that after having it happen before I was so ashamed at myself that I felt like the only way I could genuinely get it out was if I was drunk and I wouldn't have any inhibitions or anything but genuinely you are my closest closest friend and I would tell you anything <pause dur="short"/> but I felt bad at the way that I did it because I felt like I owed you more than telling you my deepest darkest secret when I was drunk I felt like I owed it to you to tell you when I was sober</u>
<u n="840" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="841" who="S0208">and like I felt awful at the way I sprung it on you when we were both drunk we had no real way of dealing with it and I felt awful at the fact that that's the way it came out and I was like you deserved</u>
<u n="842" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it</u>
<u n="843" who="S0208">more as a as my closest friend than saying that</u>
<u n="844" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it it doesn't matter how it comes out as long as you tell me that's all I ask like I can't help you if I don't know and like you can't help me I you don't know my shit and it's</u>
<u n="845" who="S0208" trans="overlap">it's happened exactly three times since I've been home and all of that was in the month of June</u>
<u n="846" who="S0202">I'm so glad that</u>
<u n="847" who="S0208" trans="overlap">so nothing since July or August or</u>
<u n="848" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I'm so glad that you're okay though</u>
<u n="849" who="S0208" trans="overlap">a bit of September</u>
<u n="850" who="S0202">cos ever since you told me all I've done is worry about it and worry about you and</u>
<u n="851" who="S0208" trans="overlap">well I feel like since I've been back in my home environment and I've been with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos I think as sad as it is he's he is the most important person in my life</u>
<u n="852" who="S0202">of course he is</u>
<u n="853" who="S0208">but in different ways so like you are a very very <unclear>impert</unclear> like you're more important to me than</u>
<u n="854" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I don't think I'd compare myself to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at all</u>
<u n="855" who="S0208" trans="overlap">my friends in France like I need you to know that like your opinion of me counts more than anything that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or anyone could tell me like I trust your judgement more than anyone <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is different obviously it's a guy he's my boyfriend</u>
<u n="856" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it's different it's different completely different</u>
<u n="857" who="S0208">but I guess since I've been back with him and it's actually been me with him and it's not a limit the amount of time it's not a week and it's a good three months and it's a good you know of time</u>
<u n="858" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it's not even the same it's a nice environment</u>
<u n="859" who="S0208">I've calmed</u>
<u n="860" who="S0202">non stressed environment</u>
<u n="861" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I've calmed down and I haven't been stressed and I haven't had worries or since I saw my sister and it's been fine <pause dur="short"/> but like honestly I think it's just cos I've been away from him like the only person whose opinion of myself and my body matters because like it does get away with yourself like when you were saying when we go to the gym and we see those really skinny girls always doing stuff</u>
<u n="862" who="S0202" trans="overlap">peacocks <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="863" who="S0208">and like we make jokes about it but secretly I'd be dying inside I'd look at all those people and I'm like <vocal desc="sigh"/> what the fuck am I coming here working my arse off for when I can't even look like them?</u>
<u n="864" who="S0202">excuse me hello</u>
<u n="865" who="S0208">no I know you say that but people have different visions of their own bodies</u>
<u n="866" who="S0202">yeah but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do you think I'm putting it on? you you've seen how many times when I get dressed and I'm just like I don't wanna wear this and I don't wanna wear that cos I just <trunc>f</trunc> I look at myself in <trunc>th</trunc> like I might have <unclear/> I don't know but I look in the mirror at myself and I just like now I feel self conscious where I'm sat</u>
<u n="867" who="S0208">no but</u>
<u n="868" who="S0202">like my weight</u>
<u n="869" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="870" who="S0202">bothers me so much</u>
<u n="871" who="S0208" trans="overlap">shut up</u>
<u n="872" who="S0202" trans="overlap">and I can't</u>
<u n="873" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="874" who="S0202">no but seriously</u>
<u n="875" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="876" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I can't even</u>
<u n="877" who="S0208" trans="overlap">shut up</u>
<u n="878" who="S0202" trans="overlap">begin to explain how much</u>
<u n="879" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="880" who="S0202" trans="overlap">how much it bothers me</u>
<u n="881" who="S0208">you need to be quiet now</u>
<u n="882" who="S0202">but how much do you think it bothers me</u>
<u n="883" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no I'm</u>
<u n="884" who="S0202" trans="overlap">going to the gym and seeing that seeing them girls like that?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I'm talking now I'm talking now you put yourself down so much but the thing is you always compare yourself to me and I'm not saying that in a nasty way</u>
<u n="886" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I don't compare myself to you I compare myself to fucking ridiculous things like celebrities and</u>
<u n="887" who="S0208">I'm not putting you down by saying that but I know that you do it I see you doing it when I come in wearing an outfit for a night out and you're wearing yours I see you looking at me but the thing is <pause dur="short"/> no one's perfect everyone has their imperfections but I need you to stop looking at me and making little jokes that maybe make yourself feel better not in a nasty way to me but saying oh yeah you're small it's cos you're small all that kind of stuff it doesn't hurt me like that's not why I'm saying it but it puts you down whether you do it on purpose or not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because I look at you and you're everything I've ever wanted as a person you're outgoing you're so smart and beautiful and naturally lovely but you have this bodacious curvy womanly look that I have always wanted that I'll never have because of my build and that's just the way it is but you look at me and you see everything that you're not I'm small and I have a completely different build to you but you always everyone always compares themself to something that they can never be <pause dur="short"/> and I just I just wish that you would see that and know how beautiful you are not only to me as a friend but to complete strangers who look at you and envy you and are jealous are literally jealous because of how beautiful you are and how perfect your body is like you have such right I'm gonna go for it you have perfect tits</u>
<u n="888" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="889" who="S0208">okay your shoulders no matter how much you're like oh my shoulders are too big shut up because you're not</u>
<u n="890" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="891" who="S0208">they are perfect in comparison to your body and your boobs and your waist goes in so much and you have perfect curves in an arse it's like it's like looking at Iggy Azalea</u>
<u n="892" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="893" who="S0208">but you have the tits that go with it</u>
<u n="894" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="895" who="S0208">and it's so irritating because</u>
<u n="896" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="897" who="S0208">I've always wanted boobs</u>
<u n="898" who="S0202" trans="overlap">tits <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="899" who="S0208">but a bum as well because I know that I'm petite but I'm a kind of curvy petite</u>
<u n="900" who="S0202">well</u>
<u n="901" who="S0208">that's really weird because <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="902" who="S0202">it's not weird</u>
<u n="903" who="S0208">most petite people's I I think of petite and I think of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> small boobs small body</u>
<u n="904" who="S0202">you've not got small boobs</u>
<u n="905" who="S0208" trans="overlap">but it's all in proportion whereas mine I'm average I'm not gonna lie I'm average</u>
<u n="906" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="907" who="S0208">I'm alright but I've got the curves that go with it but not the kind of arse that goes with it</u>
<u n="908" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="909" who="S0208">like everything's kind of just out of proportion with my body but that's the kind of thing that when you look at me you don't see my insecurities but it's the same with me I look at you and I don't see your insecurities because I don't know what the fuck you bang on about all the time</u>
<u n="910" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="911" who="S0208">because I literally look at you and I'm just like what the fuck are you talking about now?</u>
<u n="912" who="S0202">and I feel the same when you <vocal desc="laugh"/> fucking say the same shit</u>
<u n="913" who="S0208">that's what I mean it's like we have to start understanding each other rather than looking at each other and we're like just block it out because I'm not gonna lie sometimes when <unclear/> about your body or you look yourself in the mirror I kind of block it out</u>
<u n="914" who="S0202">same <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="915" who="S0208">I look at you</u>
<u n="916" who="S0202" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> are you being serious like or whatever?</u>
<u n="917" who="S0208" trans="overlap">and I'm just like I'm just gonna sing a song in my head cos I'm just gonna look at you and put wiggle wiggle wiggle next to it</u>
<u n="918" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="919" who="S0208">and just watch you look at yourself and just be like yeah</u>
<u n="920" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="921" who="S0208">that's fine and then you turn around and look at me and I'm like yeah yeah I agree I'm just like what's she talking about?</u>
<u n="922" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="923" who="S0208">have I agreed to having a threesome? what have I agreed to?</u>
<u n="924" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="925" who="S0208">I just I need I'm making a joke out of it but this is dead serious</u>
<u n="926" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="927" who="S0208">I need you to stop</u>
<u n="928" who="S0202">I need you to stop</u>
<u n="929" who="S0208">and hearing this from me okay</u>
<u n="930" who="S0202" trans="overlap">I need you to stop</u>
<u n="931" who="S0208">I've gotten over</u>
<u n="932" who="S0202" trans="overlap">about your shit</u>
<u n="933" who="S0208" trans="overlap">my problems but I've lived through problems and I need you to stop before you get to where I was <pause dur="short"/> okay?</u>
<u n="934" who="S0202">do you know what a weird thing is? do you know up until <pause dur="short"/> I was seventeen I thought I was god's gift I thought the most beautiful woman in the world I thought I were gonna be famous I thought I were gonna be a model I thought I were amazing</u>
<u n="935" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="936" who="S0202">and then this one girl don't even know her name and don't even remember her Bebo name</u>
<u n="937" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="938" who="S0202">she were on Bebo <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="939" who="S0208">I used to love Bebo</u>
<u n="940" who="S0202">same yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't even remember anything about her but all I remember is her saying fucking hell look at your muffin tops</u>
<u n="941" who="S0208">oh bitch</u>
<u n="942" who="S0202">and from that moment on I've been insecure <pause dur="short"/> but in a way I think it were a good thing because I was so sure of myself and thought I were this amazing person I thought I was so beautiful and I was so full of myself and so stuck up my own arse like she did bring me down to earth but then she introduced all these insecurities as well and I don't even know who this girl is</u>
<u n="943" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="944" who="S0202">I don't even remember her name like</u>
<u n="945" who="S0208" trans="overlap">but there's a difference between being confident in yourself and being arrogant and being confident in yourself and being insecure you just have to find that balance</u>
<u n="946" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="947" who="S0208">it's like <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="948" who="S0202" trans="overlap">everyone thinks I'm confident until I'm a friend</u>
<u n="949" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="950" who="S0202">and then they realise that I'm not</u>
<u n="951" who="S0208" trans="overlap">that that's what I thought about you and why I was so <trunc>intimat</trunc> I don't <unclear/> so bad</u>
<u n="952" who="S0202">thank you</u>
<u n="953" who="S0208">but I think one of the reasons is that I've always been pretty confident in myself like I have always just like not cared well I say that apart from a few hiccups along the way I've always just sort of not cared and I've been like this is who I am and no matter how much I diet and no matter how much I do sport my body just never changes <pause dur="short"/> so like whatever but then when I came to Leeds and like I found you and like how confident you were and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> how confident she is and stuff it just sort of made me think about little things that I'd never thought about before it just makes everything go into like overdrive which I'm sure is what's happened with you as well like you just look at other people and just</u>
<u n="954" who="S0202" trans="overlap">fake it until you make it</u>
<u n="955" who="S0208">exactly</u>
<u n="956" who="S0202">like you fake like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you'd think he'd be the most confident guy in the world he is the most insecure person I've ever met other than myself</u>
<u n="957" who="S0208" trans="overlap">the same I would never ever think that about him</u>
<u n="958" who="S0202">but how confident does he come across?</u>
<u n="959" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="960" who="S0202">because he fakes it and he's always said to me fake it until you make it</u>
<u n="961" who="S0208">that's</u>
<u n="962" who="S0202" trans="overlap">that is his catchphrase like if you were</u>
<u n="963" who="S0208">I've heard that</u>
<u n="964" who="S0202" trans="overlap">gonna be a TV show presenter that would be him</u>
<u n="965" who="S0208">and fucking cheesy</u>
<u n="966" who="S0202">no but seriously</u>
<u n="967" who="S0208" trans="overlap">I can imagine him as a sport commentator</u>
<u n="968" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="969" who="S0208">on like a news channel it's like remember guys fake it until you make it</u>
<u n="970" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="971" who="S0208">I can actually see him doing that</u>
<u n="972" who="S0202" trans="overlap">go like that and winking</u>
<u n="973" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="974" who="S0202">like Anchorman</u>
<u n="975" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> except <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can't grow a beard or a moustache</u>
<u n="976" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="977" who="S0202">cos he's not manly enough <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="978" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/> neither is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> his beard grows here</u>
<u n="979" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> hi five to <unclear/> boys</u>
<u n="980" who="S0208">but no like I know we're all girls and we all live through it and everyone has their own problems and their own insecurities but as much as I'm such a hypocrite saying this because I don't actually believe it in myself but I will always put it out there</u>
<u n="981" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="982" who="S0208">like to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when she's always like I always think that guys are gonna think of me as a child when they look at my body</u>
<u n="983" who="S0202" trans="overlap">she said that to me as well</u>
<u n="984" who="S0208">and I'm not gonna be rude <pause dur="short"/> I think that when I look at her body</u>
<u n="985" who="S0202">yeah me too</u>
<u n="986" who="S0208">but</u>
<u n="987" who="S0202">I would never say that to her</u>
<u n="988" who="S0208">I will always promote to her be like if you're confident in yourself guys will feel that guys will think it's sexy it only becomes a problem when you show that it's a problem</u>
<u n="989" who="S0202" trans="overlap">mm and voice it</u>
<u n="990" who="S0208">exactly so it's like if you tell people that you are happy with the way that you are if you like you're happy the way you are no one will give a shit like literally no one will even notice</u>
<u n="991" who="S0202">we should like go to the</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
