<text id="SKPX">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:17:06</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-01-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Football, sports sponsorship, football strip designs, McDonalds.</topics>
		<activity>Talking about the football on TV (which was muted), sports sponsorship, football strip designs, McDonalds.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="2" who="S0115">what's the score?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0037">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> eh I think it was I think Cardiff are winning but I just I was just channel hopping and they em <pause dur="short"/> it was like they ran they had a really good run like he ran they all round the goalie like they thought he was offside and so <trunc>ev</trunc> all the other team they put their hand up for offside but like he just ran past the goalie and like literally ran past the post by about two millimetres</u>
<u n="4" who="S0115">oh so it was  it was  a pretty spectacular</u>
<u n="5" who="S0037">I don't even know what the I don't even know what this game is though like is it the League Cup or something? I don't know even know what the League Cup is</u>
<u n="6" who="S0115">league Cup semi-final? Cardiff versus Crystal Palace?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0037">I didn't even but what? Like <trunc>wh</trunc> they've changed it so many times <pause dur="short"/> like what was it called the Coca Cola Cup? Was it the FA Cup or something different?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0115">eh that was the League Cup I think the Coca Cola was the league one then <pause dur="short"/> f A  F A</u>
<u n="9" who="S0037">so what is the difference?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0115">was always F A wasn't it?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0037">was it?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0115">well</u>
<u n="13" who="S0037">is it not the something FA Cup like they sort of</u>
<u n="14" who="S0115">well maybe but you don't sort of need to say that do you?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0037">I don't know</u>
<u n="16" who="S0115">for those that <unclear/> green <unclear/> or something</u>
<u n="17" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like pots pies <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0115">eh what's a wind screen? Yeah the I mean but em</u>
<u n="19" who="S0037">anyway</u>
<u n="20" who="S0115">but also wind screens one or whatever it was I think that was like the</u>
<u n="21" who="S0037">there's the <trunc>Ca</trunc> the Carling Cup as well what was that?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0115">wasn't there a Leyland DAF Cup or something?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0037">Don't be silly there wasn't a Leyland DAF Cup was there?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0115">I don't know</u>
<u n="25" who="S0037">I'd like it if there was <pause dur="short"/> what would be the most inappropriate thing for there to be like an FA Cup names after <pause dur="short"/> like fags or something</u>
<u n="26" who="S0115">well they</u>
<u n="27" who="S0037">and</u>
<u n="28" who="S0115">they do that in you know in snooker don't have the Embassy snooker</u>
<u n="29" who="S0037">oh is that where that comes from?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0115">eh</u>
<u n="31" who="S0037">that just shows my ignorance</u>
<u n="32" who="S0115">eh and of course eh</u>
<u n="33" who="S0037">oh there look the Carling Cup</u>
<u n="34" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and of course eh Formula One is is famous for eh</u>
<u n="35" who="S0037">there look Middlesbrough's first and all the <unclear/> success <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0115">when when was that? A hundred and twenty-eight years ago</u>
<u n="37" who="S0037">probably <vocal desc="laugh"/> Middlesbrough <unclear/> football wasn't even invented a hundred and twenty-eight years ago</u>
<u n="38" who="S0115">eh <pause dur="short"/> yeah just about</u>
<u n="39" who="S0037">that Steve McClaren that's a</u>
<u n="40" who="S0115">just about yeah I think they were actually oh <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah no <pause dur="short"/> eh this was eh Birmingham winning the eh Birmingham winning the the League Cup eh against Arsenal <pause dur="short"/> I think I watched that one actually last year</u>
<u n="41" who="S0037">oh yeah you did <pause dur="short"/> yeah I remember watching that <pause dur="short"/> and you were like yes</u>
<u n="42" who="S0115">topping of the shocks this but this is that was a section of the top of the <trunc>shoc</trunc> that was number one on top of the shocks Birmingham</u>
<u n="43" who="S0037">so</u>
<u n="44" who="S0115">beating eh</u>
<u n="45" who="S0037">Arsenal yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0115">Arsenal in the  in the  League Cup</u>
<u n="47" who="S0037">but like</u>
<u n="48" who="S0115">which ranks after the FA Cup but I think the there was an <trunc>e</trunc> there was an even another cup that was  that was  a bit lower</u>
<u n="49" who="S0037">more rubbish</u>
<u n="50" who="S0115">but I think that was the one that I think Birmingham won a while ago</u>
<u n="51" who="S0037">I don't know</u>
<u n="52" who="S0115">where you</u>
<u n="53" who="S0037">I've not seen I'm not up to date</u>
<u n="54" who="S0115">where you  you only entered it if you're like the em one of the lower like if you're in then the third division or below</u>
<u n="55" who="S0037">I think I was put off of football like for life after that whole like working at the Stadium of Light thing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0115">oh eh</u>
<u n="57" who="S0037">I had the pies the pie aspect</u>
<u n="58" who="S0115">yeah but that was</u>
<u n="59" who="S0037">it was a bit of</u>
<u n="60" who="S0115">enterprising you know I mean it was industrious like you were</u>
<u n="61" who="S0037">I don't know if it was enterprising</u>
<u n="62" who="S0115">you were  working that age <pause dur="short"/> when did you start that?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0037">em well you were supposed to be sixteen but I wasn't sixteen I just said I was and like they weren't bothered <pause dur="short"/> and they didn't check <pause dur="short"/> although I'm sure they had my national insurance numbers so they should probably of well who knows? It was all a bit dodgy <pause dur="short"/> they used to put the pies like</u>
<u n="64" who="S0115">yeah best  Yeah best  left unsolved</u>
<u n="65" who="S0037">like the pies</u>
<u n="66" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0037">like if they didn't sell them they used to just put them in a box and then put them in a cupboard and then the next week just like crack the pies back out and the put them in the warmer</u>
<u n="68" who="S0115">that's scandalous</u>
<u n="69" who="S0037">and be like <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0037">because if somebody got like a em like a bad belly from eating a dodgy pie you would never know because like I suppose a lot of the blokes and that who go to football and eat those horrible pies like would have had twenty pints of beer anyway <pause dur="short"/> so they would never think do you know what</u>
<u n="72" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0037">that was a bad pie <pause dur="short"/> like people would laugh wouldn't they if they said that?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0115">yeah I think there wasn't probably much in the pies apart from</u>
<u n="75" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="76" who="S0115">sort of potatoes butter or</u>
<u n="77" who="S0037">like sawdust and like</u>
<u n="78" who="S0115"><trunc>Y</trunc> yeah I mean</u>
<u n="79" who="S0037">and hooves in that</u>
<u n="80" who="S0115">I never  I never  had a I I never went to a football match <pause dur="short"/> I've never had a football pie so em</u>
<u n="81" who="S0037">oh we need to rectify that</u>
<u n="82" who="S0115">what are they like?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0037">well there's the the <trunc>bra</trunc> they branched out</u>
<u n="84" who="S0115">is it just like the ones you get in the chippie?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0037">em yeah more or less <pause dur="short"/> but they branched out like obviously this is like more than ten years ago but I remember like they introduced a new like a chicken tikka pie and eh</u>
<u n="86" who="S0115">oh yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0037">everyone was like chicken tikka pie? Why do I want one of them? Like cos people used to just be like give us a pie love <pause dur="short"/> and then you'd be like oh what flavour do you want? And they'd be like meat <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="88" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0037">it didn't those didn't really sell very well</u>
<u n="90" who="S0115">well in the chippie you know it used to be steak and kidney or eh</u>
<u n="91" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0115"><trunc>c</trunc> eh chicken and mushrooms and <pause dur="short"/> then in Greggs obviously you got the</u>
<u n="93" who="S0037">ah kidneys</u>
<u n="94" who="S0115">rump steak and you have a a</u>
<u n="95" who="S0037">eh <trunc>kid</trunc> do you like kidneys?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0115">cheese cheese and onion pie but eh if you</u>
<u n="97" who="S0037">oh yeah cheese and onion pie</u>
<u n="98" who="S0115">and then there's Cornish pasty  Cornish pasty  which is mainly potatoes in a cut in squares or cubes I should</u>
<u n="99" who="S0037">I remember when I first <trunc>start</trunc></u>
<u n="100" who="S0115">eh with peas and a very small amount of mince</u>
<u n="101" who="S0037">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> cornish pasties are always quite like peppery though aren't they?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0115">yeah really loads of like I guess this white mainly white pepper but also</u>
<u n="103" who="S0037">I don't know</u>
<u n="104" who="S0115">they are very like quite quite hot aren't they?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0115">but not like chilli hot sort of pepper hot</u>
<u n="107" who="S0037">no peppery like tickle your nose</u>
<u n="108" who="S0115">and yes so eh you eh worked at the Stadium of <pause dur="short"/> but it wasn't called that then was it or was?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0037">yeah yeah no</u>
<u n="110" who="S0115">oh yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0037">come on I'm not that old</u>
<u n="112" who="S0115">oh I don't don't know eh</u>
<u n="113" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah I worked at the stadium but it was it wasn't it hadn't been open that long though</u>
<u n="114" who="S0115">em</u>
<u n="115" who="S0037">to be fair <pause dur="short"/> but anyway</u>
<u n="116" who="S0115">oh yes so eh <trunc>fo</trunc> em I was</u>
<u n="117" who="S0037">the football <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="118" who="S0115">gonna say another <pause dur="short"/> there was a lot of tobacco sponsorship in the old days where</u>
<u n="119" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0115">the Formula One was on</u>
<u n="121" who="S0037">oh yeah Formula One loads</u>
<u n="122" who="S0115">was heavily eh <pause dur="short"/> I think it's it's banned now isn't it? But it used to be really heavily <trunc>ban</trunc> eh</u>
<u n="123" who="S0037">do you think they'll ban like?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0115">heavily sponsored by eh</u>
<u n="125" who="S0037">do you think they'll ever ban like McDonald's sponsoring things?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0115">em</u>
<u n="127" who="S0037">you know because they've they've banned cigarettes or like you know alcohol?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0115">no because McDonald's are sneaky <trunc>y</trunc> you know the eh <pause dur="short"/> there's a  there's a  quote for you eh <pause dur="short"/> no? But they eh well they don't just sell unhealthy food do they? Some of it some of the things they sell are actually like salads and that like Mc Salad or something?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0037">I suppose</u>
<u n="130" who="S0115">although I haven't been to McDonald's for a very long time so</u>
<u n="131" who="S0037">I haven't <pause dur="short"/> I can't even remember <pause dur="short"/> actually I do remember it was the time do you remember when my brother had been round and we were really hung-over and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like oh stop at McDonald's <pause dur="short"/> and then the car got beached on like one of those like weird concrete things</u>
<u n="132" who="S0115">oh yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0037">and I couldn't get it off</u>
<u n="134" who="S0115">oh that that was just a really bad moment wasn't it em?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0037">it was funny <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0115">so just kicking off the second half eh Cardiff one</u>
<u n="137" who="S0037">oh it is</u>
<u n="138" who="S0115">Crystal Palace nil <pause dur="short"/> yeah oh</u>
<u n="139" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh you're not going to commentate the whole match are you?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0115" trans="overlap">ah no I'm not actually gonna  I'm not actually gonna  commentate the whole match</u>
<u n="141" who="S0037">I don't think I'd like to be a sports commentator</u>
<u n="142" who="S0115">well well I <trunc>ca</trunc> I don't know any of the players so eh currently</u>
<u n="143" who="S0037">you could just make up names for them</u>
<u n="144" who="S0115">em I could just say the teams where Cardiff has it's a list of</u>
<u n="145" who="S0037">yeah but it's</u>
<u n="146" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so it's either Cardiff Cardiff Cardiff <pause dur="short"/> cardiff</u>
<u n="147" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I I like the which which kit do you prefer?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0115">oh Cardiff <pause dur="short"/> but eh no it's cos <pause dur="short"/> honestly</u>
<u n="149" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Which kit  Which kit  do you prefer like I like that custardy sort of colour</u>
<u n="150" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that's a <pause dur="short"/> sorry?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0037">I like that sort of yellowy bananay canary colour</u>
<u n="152" who="S0115">yeah well I think that some of the kits that they have em could be more  could be more  extravagant I suppose em</u>
<u n="153" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0115">but they must think that it's eh that's it's off-putting or something to have</u>
<u n="155" who="S0037">yeah like highler <trunc>pe</trunc> highlighter pen colours</u>
<u n="156" who="S0115">really bright sort of <pause dur="short"/> or it's not you know it's not masculine enough to have em</u>
<u n="157" who="S0037">I'm <trunc>su</trunc></u>
<u n="158" who="S0115">pink kits so I don't  I don't  know any</u>
<u n="159" who="S0037">I'm sure that someone's</u>
<u n="160" who="S0115">teams that have a pink kit</u>
<u n="161" who="S0037">I'm sure someone's got like a purpley pink <pause dur="short"/> did Arsenal not have like a sort of how would you call it? Like a magenta sort of coloured one for a while?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0115">em I don't know</u>
<u n="163" who="S0037">maybe it wasn't them</u>
<u n="164" who="S0115">I think Northampton Town has purple</u>
<u n="165" who="S0037">oh do they?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0115">but eh</u>
<u n="167" who="S0037">oh that would be good</u>
<u n="168" who="S0115">eh</u>
<u n="169" who="S0037">also I think like</u>
<u n="170" who="S0115">there should be more I suppose but</u>
<u n="171" who="S0037">there's a lot of stripes on the goal <pause dur="short"/> I I I'm fancying a few polka dots?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0115">yeah I don't know they don't really have spotty ones do they?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0037">you know like jockeys have?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0115">but I think that would be like sort of distracting with the  with the  ball wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0037">or like some chevrons?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0115">eh <trunc>y</trunc> yeah that <unclear/> that's probably a bit distracting as well isn't it?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0037">or like em</u>
<u n="178" who="S0115">animal patterns or flame flame patterns like eh</u>
<u n="179" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><trunc>Anima</trunc> Animal patterns <pause dur="short"/> that would be good wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0037">like a leopard print?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0115">yeah I suppose you could but</u>
<u n="182" who="S0037">like a zebra?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0115">oh yeah cos if they had names like the <pause dur="short"/> you know like the tigers or something then they could actually look like tigers then that would be</u>
<u n="184" who="S0037">oh yeah that's a good idea</u>
<u n="185" who="S0115">yeah so kind of like</u>
<u n="186" who="S0037">like rugby league does that though don't they?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115">like the cowboys and and the indians or something I wonder <pause dur="short"/> actually look like that that would be a</u>
<u n="188" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I saw like</u>
<u n="189" who="S0115">like the <trunc>vi</trunc> the the vipers or something?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0037">well I saw like you know  you know  I've been knitting stuff and that at the minute</u>
<u n="191" who="S0115">yeah?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0037">for a the baby <pause dur="short"/> well I saw this pattern like I like sort of unusual patterns and I saw this one and it was like for a tuxedo but it wasn't it was just a knitted jumper</u>
<u n="193" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0037">but it looked like a baby tuxedo like a dicky bow tie and like a white shirt with like buttons and like a cumberband and then like a jacket</u>
<u n="195" who="S0115">blimey</u>
<u n="196" who="S0037">but it was a jumper <pause dur="short"/> so I could do that <pause dur="short"/> could have been like dinner you know dinner suits?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0115">em you know people dress sort of babies in that sort of</u>
<u n="198" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0115">thing nowadays don't they?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0037">eh I'm not sure if they dress them in knitted dinner jackets <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but eh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0115">well <unclear/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0037">that's going to be a bit of a niche audience <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0115">eh</u>
<u n="204" who="S0037">but they dress them as like big pumpkins and stuff don't they on Halloween?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0115">I can see how eh you know you might want to <trunc>y</trunc> you could make anything out of knitting I suppose and</u>
<u n="206" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115">you for clothes like you could imitate things like couldn't you? Sort of imitate like like a football kit <pause dur="short"/> I suppose you could knit a football  a football  shirts</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037">yeah you could <pause dur="short"/> that would be nice and warm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0115">eh <pause dur="short"/> or</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037">could do <pause dur="short"/> a military one</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115">I don't know if I've seen that <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if there is a market for knitted eh sportswear? But eh</u>
<u n="212" who="S0037">maybe maybe there is</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115"><trunc>Kni</trunc> knitted em</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037">Cos it they're all a horrible sort of nylon aren't they? Is it nylon?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115">for <trunc>ba</trunc> for babies that have grown up supporting Everton or something and they would have like the Everton woolly jumper or something</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well I can definitely knit a red and white stripy one <pause dur="short"/> that would be quite nice wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115">for for eh Southampton or?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037">not Southampton <pause dur="short"/> you know what for</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115">I mean <pause dur="short"/> yeah the colours could be  could be  more extravagant</u>
<u n="220" who="S0037">like you know like jockeys have?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115">eh</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037">like where they have like</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115">well they have yeah they have more crazy</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037">like hoops and</u>
<u n="225" who="S0115">eh colours it's like yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037">and like you know like even rugby does like even rugby has the the kind of</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115">all  harlequins and</u>
<u n="228" who="S0037">the harlequin thing</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115">I like  I like  there one it's got sort of</u>
<u n="230" who="S0037">and like the em hoops and stuff don't they?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0037">although <trunc>Q</trunc> QPR has blue and white hoops doesn't it?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115">yeah and Celtic</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037">oh yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115">em</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037">that's probably about the</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115">there is too much</u>
<u n="238" who="S0037">limits of my footballing knowledge</u>
<u n="239" who="S0115">too much just red white red white <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="240" who="S0037">nothing wrong with red and white <pause dur="short"/> I think that's about the the limit of my football knowledge though I just I like watching it but I think that's because I like watching anything like I could happily get consumed by the darts or the snooker</u>
<u n="241" who="S0115">yeah well sport is good to watch eh especially in the pub em where</u>
<u n="242" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0115">but also <pause dur="short"/> if you get into it you can get quite you know you become engrossed in it</u>
<u n="244" who="S0037">I think so</u>
<u n="245" who="S0115">and and sort of</u>
<u n="246" who="S0037">like when that time when we got really into the curling?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0115">huh that was it was watchable you see you can <pause dur="short"/> it's it's addictive and if you watch eh you know the Olympics or whatever then you sort of miss it when it finishes or something or</u>
<u n="248" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0115">when the</u>
<u n="250" who="S0037">are you looking forward to the Olympics?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0115">em <trunc>y</trunc> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't normally watch loads of of Olympics but em because it is in London this time I suppose <pause dur="short"/> eh I suppose I should get more involved into it so</u>
<u n="252" who="S0037">yeah?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0115">I suppose you can't just turn up and then just go in and watch it</u>
<u n="254" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> I think you can for like the one the marathon you can</u>
<u n="255" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you can't to go to the swimming or something</u>
<u n="256" who="S0037">all the outdoor ones like the road races but no <pause dur="short"/> I tried to get tickets but</u>
<u n="257" who="S0115">no</u>
<u n="258" who="S0037">I even applied for like the most rubbish things like the tiddlywinks or like the you know</u>
<u n="259" who="S0115">eh they don't do tiddlywinks do they?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> that's the joke</u>
<u n="261" who="S0115">but em</u>
<u n="262" who="S0037">no I didn't get any tickets but em</u>
<u n="263" who="S0115">but they do do some strange things like like archery</u>
<u n="264" who="S0037">beach volleyball in London</u>
<u n="265" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0037">it's going to be an interesting one</u>
<u n="267" who="S0115">yeah em <pause dur="short"/> I I don't know what my favourite eh Olympic thing to watch is</u>
<u n="268" who="S0037">I quite liked the swimming ones last time <pause dur="short"/> cos we won a lot of stuff</u>
<u n="269" who="S0115">cycling eh <pause dur="short"/> we won a lot of cycling</u>
<u n="270" who="S0037">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> the commentator was good wasn't he? Em <pause dur="short"/> so I've got a bit bored of the ones that everyone likes like the hundred metre final and that</u>
<u n="271" who="S0115">well it's very quick <pause dur="short"/> very quick</u>
<u n="272" who="S0037">it's a bit sort of murgh sort of everyone likes it but I don't know</u>
<u n="273" who="S0115">do they?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0037">well that's like the most expensive tickets are for that <pause dur="short"/> the men's one hundred metre final</u>
<u n="275" who="S0115">how much would it cost just to watch the men's hundred metre final?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0037">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I think it depends on where you're sat <pause dur="short"/> I think all of the ones had like cheap seats</u>
<u n="277" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0037">for some of them <pause dur="short"/> em but for a lot of them like</u>
<u n="279" who="S0115">ooh there's Chris Martin?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0037">who's Chris Martin?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0115">he plays for Crystal Palace</u>
<u n="282" who="S0037">did <pause dur="short"/> did you know him before or have you just read him off the screen?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0115">no it's cos he <pause dur="short"/> he</u>
<u n="284" who="S0037">oh Chris Martin? Chris Martin</u>
<u n="285" who="S0115">he's he's em</u>
<u n="286" who="S0037">oh he's having a break? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0115">he eh he used to be  used to be  a singer didn't he?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> But yeah he had a better offer so now he plays football for Crystal Palace</u>
<u n="289" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> em well I think he just wanted a change of scene</u>
<u n="290" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> a change of pace <pause dur="short"/> so like Gwyneth's in the <trunc>sa</trunc></u>
<u n="291" who="S0115">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0037">stand with like Apple and Moses or whatever his kids are called</u>
<u n="293" who="S0115">apple and Moses?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0115">oh is he going through the Bible? Then the next thing he's going to be like</u>
<u n="296" who="S0037">oh you mean Apple <vocal desc="laugh"/>?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0115">den or something</u>
<u n="298" who="S0037">den?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0115">yeah from em Daniel and the lions' den</u>
<u n="300" who="S0037">oh right</u>
<u n="301" who="S0115">apple from Adam and Eve that apple</u>
<u n="302" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> moses from Moses</u>
<u n="303" who="S0115">Moses from the Moses</u>
<u n="304" who="S0037">the story of Moses</u>
<u n="305" who="S0115">Moses' adventures and em</u>
<u n="306" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> The adventures of Moses part one</u>
<u n="307" who="S0115">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't know that is is that  is that  what's his he started with Adam and Eve the apple and he started</u>
<u n="308" who="S0037">well he didn't have</u>
<u n="309" who="S0115">he was planning to go all the way to I don't know</u>
<u n="310" who="S0037">I don't know if Apple was a very  was a very  standard choice</u>
<u n="311" who="S0115">I think Apple is I can see why</u>
<u n="312" who="S0037">maybe he could have gone for</u>
<u n="313" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I can see it's <trunc>b</trunc> I can see it's better than some other fruits that you might wanna use but</u>
<u n="314" who="S0037">like what? Like pawpaw?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0115">well it's better than <trunc>m</trunc> many fruits I think</u>
<u n="316" who="S0037">Mango Martin's got a nice ring to it</u>
<u n="317" who="S0115">eh banana <pause dur="short"/> mango? Yeah I think it's like</u>
<u n="318" who="S0037">Mango Martin</u>
<u n="319" who="S0115">it's it's man and go isn't it so? It's you know</u>
<u n="320" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mango yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0115">it means  it means  something yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0037">mushroom? Mushroom Martin? That's quite nice</u>
<u n="323" who="S0115">eh yeah his name would be  would be  magic wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0037">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> like it</u>
<u n="325" who="S0115">em</u>
<u n="326" who="S0037">but so I think instead of like Moses he should have just gone for basket like Moses basket you know? Apple and Basket?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0115">em</u>
<u n="328" who="S0037">what do you think?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0115">eh there's a lot of things around Moses aren't there so? You've got the Ten Commandments haven't you and eh</u>
<u n="330" who="S0037">I don't know if commandment would be a nice name for a person</u>
<u n="331" who="S0115">eh <pause dur="short"/> the plagues em</u>
<u n="332" who="S0037">buboes <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> That's the wrong sort of plague</u>
<u n="333" who="S0115">em I don't know if that would work</u>
<u n="334" who="S0037">that's it <pause dur="short"/> the Black Death <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0115">the the the locusts</u>
<u n="336" who="S0037">locust <pause dur="short"/> locust? mm <pause dur="short"/> lovely</u>
<u n="337" who="S0115">em <pause dur="short"/> and eh</u>
</body>
</text>
