<text id="SKRZ">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:20:02</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-11</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0058 S0179</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's car</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Cities, holidays, friends, family, films, TV, cars, adverts, music, food</topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0058">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Corpus Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0179">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harpenden, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years, 7 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Consultant engineer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0179">I do have to say <anon type="place"/> is quite a nice place <pause dur="short"/> it's got character to it</u>
<u n="2" who="S0058">it has got character to it <pause dur="short"/> I think you're right <pause dur="short"/> I think a lot of cities now especially the kind of newer ones are really faceless and not very yeah <pause dur="short"/> they don't have a character the people don't <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="3" who="S0179">like Peterborough for example has <trunc>ab</trunc> has about as much character as my left butt cheek <pause dur="short"/> which</u>
<u n="4" who="S0058">yeah it's got quite a lot of character yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0179">is quite distinctive <pause dur="short"/> but you know that's an entire city</u>
<u n="6" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I guess <anon type="place"/>'s a bit more sprawling <pause dur="short"/> it's got lots of different bits <pause dur="short"/> also there's some bits which don't have a very nice character <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="7" who="S0179">well never having been to those bits</u>
<u n="8" who="S0058">I was going to say yeah <pause dur="short"/> em I'll take you now to kind of one of the not very nice bits</u>
<u n="9" who="S0179">can we hire a car to do it?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> one of the it's obviously eh</u>
<u n="11" who="S0179">that is cool though that eh that building</u>
<u n="12" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> She was interesting looking <pause dur="short"/> being quite demonstrative with her arm <unclear/> as well</u>
<u n="13" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0058">bless her <pause dur="short"/> frustrated traffic director</u>
<u n="15" who="S0179"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0058">we could have gone left <unclear/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0179">I'm glad we didn't</u>
<u n="18" who="S0058">me too</u>
<u n="19" who="S0179">have you got your thing going?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0058">this</u>
<u n="21" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0179">Good</u>
<u n="24" who="S0058">yeah it'll be nice actually</u>
<u n="25" who="S0179">it's a little bit eh</u>
<u n="26" who="S0058"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s a  fan</u>
<u n="27" who="S0179">it's good <pause dur="short"/> we could have gone to see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> again today but I think that would have been pushing it</u>
<u n="28" who="S0058">yeah I think so yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure we'll see him again soon</u>
<u n="29" who="S0179">I love that the eh the eh <unclear/> have got a jacket tied on to a <unclear/> thing poking out saying yeah <pause dur="short"/> that doesn't make it safe</u>
<u n="30" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's quite scary some people they just you know <pause dur="short"/> balance stuff on the back of the truck not too worried <pause dur="short"/> don't even fasten it down <pause dur="short"/> we'll be fine it won't fall off</u>
<u n="31" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0058">it's like when people em have like van doors at the back and they sort of have stuff sticking out the back of them and at the end they sort of tie a bit of string to the end to them so you you know can see where they are but</u>
<u n="33" who="S0179">em em</u>
<u n="34" who="S0058">yeah <anon type="place"/> won em Britain in Bloom a few years running <pause dur="short"/> this bit was always very nice when they had the competitions</u>
<u n="35" who="S0179">for the greater good</u>
<u n="36" who="S0058">the greater good <pause dur="short"/> basically yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it it was nice actually when they were doing it cos they always had really lovely kind of flowers in the town centre and stuff and you know they brighten things up a little bit <pause dur="short"/> which is not necessarily a bad thing <pause dur="short"/> it was quite bad though when the queen visited the hospital they I think they were opening a new wing and the queen came to open up</u>
<u n="37" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0058">and they  And they  planted loads of em flowers and lovely arrangements and plants and you know all kinds of stuff they made it look lovely outdoors <pause dur="short"/> and then the next day the dug them all up again and sent them back <pause dur="short"/> which is quite bad</u>
<u n="39" who="S0179">seriously?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0179">I thought it would take more effort to</u>
<u n="42" who="S0058">well maybe they didn't completely plant them <pause dur="short"/> maybe they just had them in pots and stuff <pause dur="short"/> but yeah they just packed them all up again and sent them back <pause dur="short"/> so they just borrowed them for the day</u>
<u n="43" who="S0179">who wouldn't <unclear/> Rent a garden</u>
<u n="44" who="S0058">well yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0179">when you're desperate rent a whippet</u>
<u n="46" who="S0058">rent a whippet?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0058">who's going to rent a whippet?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0179">no to fit in</u>
<u n="50" who="S0058">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0179">with the class environs <pause dur="short"/> environs</u>
<u n="52" who="S0058">environs yes <pause dur="short"/> ah love it</u>
<u n="53" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0058">are you going to get your flat cap?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0179">I'm considering it</u>
<u n="56" who="S0058">Cos it would be different sort of flat caps <pause dur="short"/> a flat cap and whippet combination</u>
<u n="57" who="S0179">in what sense?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0058">well flat cap and whippet is you know very working class miner sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> whereas flat cap shooting jacket large gun crocked over the arm</u>
<u n="59" who="S0179">well actually it wasn't what I was going for</u>
<u n="60" who="S0058">no? Fair enough</u>
<u n="61" who="S0179">it was just</u>
<u n="62" who="S0058">you just fancied a flat cap?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0179">yeah basically</u>
<u n="64" who="S0058">I'm sure can find one at <unclear/> on me</u>
<u n="65" who="S0179">I just remember my dad had one when I was growing up and it was <unclear/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0058">you thought it was me <unclear/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0179">where's your dad's cap</u>
<u n="68" who="S0058">he's got one now?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0179">no he doesn't wear it much</u>
<u n="70" who="S0058">he does occasionally wear it</u>
<u n="71" who="S0179">yeah but it's <unclear/> You know it's an adult's</u>
<u n="72" who="S0058">yeah a manly hat</u>
<u n="73" who="S0179">exactly <pause dur="short"/> as <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't a baseball cap</u>
<u n="74" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="75" who="S0179">no that it wasn't</u>
<u n="76" who="S0058">I think that's the difference between our fathers <pause dur="short"/> yours wears a flat cap mine wears a baseball cap</u>
<u n="77" who="S0179">he doesn't does he?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0058">yeah sometimes</u>
<u n="79" who="S0179">seriously?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0058">well yeah cos his head burns quite easily <pause dur="short"/> he's got a rather snazzy flat cap</u>
<u n="81" who="S0179">yeah so does my dad's but that's why he wears a Tilly hat</u>
<u n="82" who="S0058">yes indeed <pause dur="short"/> my dad doesn't have one of those <pause dur="short"/> I will suggest it as a fashion option</u>
<u n="83" who="S0179">oh</u>
<u n="84" who="S0058">I don't think he'd like it</u>
<u n="85" who="S0179">I used to want one <pause dur="short"/> remember my dad's bag full of hats?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0058">yeah what was that about? We were packing up and there was some <trunc>co</trunc> some argument about the fact that your mum hadn't included his bag full of hats <pause dur="short"/> em at which point she had a bit of a go about the fact that he was just leaving stuff lying about the house and expecting her to know exactly what he wants taking <pause dur="short"/> how is she meant to know he had to take a bag full of hats with him?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0179">then God we're not going on this holiday</u>
<u n="88" who="S0058">yeah I was it was stressful just being in the kitchen with them <pause dur="short"/> seriously <pause dur="short"/> it was quite funny but I was just like oh my God <pause dur="short"/> let me go now</u>
<u n="89" who="S0179">well that's a decent side road <pause dur="short"/> no wait <pause dur="short"/> not good with the other cars <unclear/> but it was still shut</u>
<u n="90" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I think that must have been night time raid works</u>
<u n="91" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0058">I'm trying to think eh <pause dur="short"/> what was I just thinking about? Yeah oh that's what it was <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> how many grams are in a kilogram? Is it?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0179">A thousand</u>
<u n="94" who="S0058">A thousand <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's was mad I just</u>
<u n="95" who="S0179">Cos otherwise it could be a centigram</u>
<u n="96" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh of course <pause dur="short"/> I was like a centigram am I going mad?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0179">or something to do with a hundred not a thousand</u>
<u n="98" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0179">I'm glad we got that figured out</u>
<u n="100" who="S0058">yeah that's good that's sorted <pause dur="short"/> now I'm just thinking the way to the meet <pause dur="short"/> it was relevant to something</u>
<u n="101" who="S0179">remind me to start carrying around sunglasses okay?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just get a pair just to eh keep in here</u>
<u n="103" who="S0179">well I've got two pairs anyway so I might keep one in the car as a sort of emergency pair</u>
<u n="104" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0179">or at least no <pause dur="short"/> I</u>
<u n="106" who="S0058">in all fairness</u>
<u n="107" who="S0179">well I will actually need to remember that I need to start taking them with me</u>
<u n="108" who="S0058">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's not a bad idea anyway cos I guess even in winter you can have bright sun</u>
<u n="109" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> see <pause dur="short"/> on <pause dur="short"/> it's weird cos the only time I used to see the sea was on holiday</u>
<u n="110" who="S0058">right yeah <pause dur="short"/> so it's kind of a holiday feeling I guess</u>
<u n="111" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/>  a weekend</u>
<u n="112" who="S0058">no no it is nowadays <pause dur="short"/> I just mean for me it's not necessarily the same association because you know we used to have trips out to the beach but it wasn't quite so big a thing</u>
<u n="113" who="S0179">yeah for me it's a it would be a long drive to get  to get  to a holiday location <pause dur="short"/> you know you're getting close when you see the sea <pause dur="short"/> that's the <unclear/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a nice thought when you're driving into somewhere you know really well and you've got to see the familiar places on the way and you know you're getting close <pause dur="short"/> so like driving to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> you see the sort of you pass particular things and little pottery shop and you know all the sort of <pause dur="short"/> yeah landmarks</u>
<u n="115" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I'm hoping that the A1 M junction should be pretty clearly signposted</u>
<u n="116" who="S0058">I would imagine so</u>
<u n="117" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0058">do you want me to have a look so you know where it is?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0179">no it's okay I just want to see where they <unclear/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0058">yeah I don't think they're going to let you miss that one</u>
<u n="121" who="S0179">I hope not anyway</u>
<u n="122" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0179">so em do you want to give <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a a bell and make some plans for him and tell him to bring <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s stuff if he wants to?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I mean do we definitely want to go? Do you I'm just thinking in terms of eating like whether there will actually be enough time for gym session three showers and then get the meat on and you know whether it will just be a bit late? For <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to get back and for us to <pause dur="short"/> well it's up to you what do you think?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0179">I think I would like to get some <unclear/> today <pause dur="short"/> it's just kind of a fun way of <unclear/> And I'd like at least us to go</u>
<u n="126" who="S0058">okay well I maybe <pause dur="short"/> cos</u>
<u n="127" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0058">I'm trying to think what em <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what time the last bus is</u>
<u n="129" who="S0179">well no it's it's about seven o'clock on a Sunday but he's going to have to get a taxi anyway to get there</u>
<u n="130" who="S0058">Nn no no not going back but coming to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it's quite as late as seven <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing I mean I was wondering if he'd kind of have to come if we were going to the gym <pause dur="short"/> because of the last bus time <pause dur="short"/> I'll ask him what time the last bus is</u>
<u n="131" who="S0179">can you not?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0058">that's fine I'll ask him what time the last bus is <pause dur="short"/> he did ring me quite late last night that was quite odd</u>
<u n="133" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0058">he rang quite late last night <pause dur="short"/> like quarter past eleven <pause dur="short"/> I don't know it just seems like an odd time to ring <pause dur="short"/> and he didn't get very much sleep em <pause dur="short"/> he got he said he got like two hours sleep the previous day <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't really listening I was em I had some <unclear/> But he said something about em you know it's been this  weekend thing <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> and he hadn't had much sleep the previous night and em someone one of his housemate's called <pause dur="short"/> I presume it's a sort of different area of the country</u>
<u n="135" who="S0179">I like housemates <pause dur="short"/> I would actually <unclear/> housemates <unclear/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0058">yeah yeah exactly</u>
<u n="137" who="S0179">I didn't think of that</u>
<u n="138" who="S0058">oh right yeah <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure he said something else <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember why he got up so early <pause dur="short"/> it's like yesterday morning</u>
<u n="139" who="S0179">well what was the <unclear/> about anyway?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0058">I think it's just sort of part of their idea of em kind of <trunc>get</trunc> making you feel part of a company making you feel like a kind of community <pause dur="short"/> and I think they like also to link up the different offices so there's like there's a few people stuck up in Aberdeen <pause dur="short"/> but obviously you don't have that much contact <pause dur="short"/> so then they like to make them feel past of the group I think</u>
<u n="141" who="S0179">humungous waste of time and funds</u>
<u n="142" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> I mean they obviously feel it has enough beneficial effects to make it worth it but <pause dur="short"/> it does seem</u>
<u n="143" who="S0179">barely <unclear/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0058">yeah it just seems like a kind of slightly odd yeah use of eh</u>
<u n="145" who="S0179"><unclear/> Interesting choice of phrase <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> tangible benefits</u>
<u n="146" who="S0058">yeah exactly it's so hard to measure the fact whether you'll get any <unclear/> fun out of this <pause dur="short"/> em so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was basically saying yes it's kind of less important for the people in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> but you know it's worthwhile <pause dur="short"/> I'm not really sure whether it was sort of team building or whether it was more kind of talks or you know more kind of em</u>
<u n="147" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but if he enjoyed it that's all that matters</u>
<u n="149" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a good situation to be in</u>
<u n="150" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so em yeah it was something he's doing <pause dur="short"/> is he doing anything next weekend I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure there was something he was doing on Saturday</u>
<u n="151" who="S0179">em <pause dur="short"/> no I don't think so I mean I think it was completely clear</u>
<u n="152" who="S0058">oh right okay <pause dur="short"/> sounds quite that's better for him then?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0179">yeah yeah that's what he was saying</u>
<u n="154" who="S0058">cool</u>
<u n="155" who="S0179">it should be quite a nice weekend</u>
<u n="156" who="S0058">yeah it'll be nice actually I'm really looking forward to it</u>
<u n="157" who="S0179">that's a problem <pause dur="short"/> watch him come back and say no I can't <unclear/> anymore</u>
<u n="158" who="S0058">if we stop at <unclear/> is it going to go is it <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0058"><unclear/> Or so that alright? Yeah when you think <pause dur="short"/> we'll have a look at the map and see em about that walk and see if there's an alternative route back <pause dur="short"/> what do you think?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0179">an OS map if we can <unclear/> so I might ask Dan if he's got one <pause dur="short"/> I don't think we've got one</u>
<u n="162" who="S0058">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah and just see if there's sort of <pause dur="short"/> see if you can make it into a circular one <pause dur="short"/> if not I mean you can just turn around <pause dur="short"/> and yeah the views would be different so <pause dur="short"/> there'll be a lot of tunnels</u>
<u n="163" who="S0179">where does it go? Not sure em <pause dur="short"/> ah ha <pause dur="short"/> good place to go for a walk</u>
<u n="164" who="S0058">yeah how random</u>
<u n="165" who="S0179">why is there a footpath</u>
<u n="166" who="S0058">well you know fair enough <pause dur="short"/> you might really like walking by the side of the A19</u>
<u n="167" who="S0179">who <pause dur="short"/> lost it there</u>
<u n="168" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> they did <pause dur="short"/> the walk is over <pause dur="short"/> cos you're not actually allowed to walk by the side of that are you?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0179">eh yeah <pause dur="short"/> you are on the dual carriageway</u>
<u n="170" who="S0058">alright just if there's no wind</u>
<u n="171" who="S0179">unless it's a specifically restricted dual carriageway which this might be I don't know I don't think so</u>
<u n="172" who="S0058">is that when they have those big signs no pedestrians no horse drawn carriages</u>
<u n="173" who="S0179">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="174" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0179">yes if go back to space you might collect <pause dur="short"/> wait a second <pause dur="short"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="176" who="S0058">ah silly car</u>
<u n="177" who="S0179">leaving that aside it's actually very pleasant driving</u>
<u n="178" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0179">it's a very interesting road</u>
<u n="180" who="S0058">yeah that was good idea <pause dur="short"/> it's nice to have sort of different options</u>
<u n="181" who="S0179">oh wind turbine <pause dur="short"/> l</u>
<u n="182" who="S0058">ah that's a nice view actually <pause dur="short"/> kind of the straight road and then the wind turbine <pause dur="short"/> I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was impressed by our wind turbine project</u>
<u n="183" who="S0179">how the hell did that come up?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0058">I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> I think it was something about <unclear/> loaning everyone</u>
<u n="185" who="S0179">oh yes</u>
<u n="186" who="S0058">that was quite a bizarre night but quite fun</u>
<u n="187" who="S0179">totally bizarre yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0058">how cool is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s job <pause dur="short"/> it sounded mental</u>
<u n="189" who="S0179">it sounded pretty awful</u>
<u n="190" who="S0058">it's sounds awful yeah I'm sure it is awful one kind of yeah <pause dur="short"/> on a work life balance basis <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> it's very cool <pause dur="short"/> I guess what she loses in term of yeah her own life she gets back in terms of going to film premiers and <pause dur="short"/> it's just very glamorous I guess to me who's you know publishing sounds quite glamorous <pause dur="short"/> my job's not very glamorous <pause dur="short"/> whereas that really is good</u>
<u n="191" who="S0179">my job is inadvertently quite glamorous</u>
<u n="192" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly yeah <pause dur="short"/> I want to see that film now</u>
<u n="193" who="S0179">which film?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0058">Snow White and the Huntsman</u>
<u n="195" who="S0179">it had a cool trailer <unclear/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0058">yeah it did actually yeah <pause dur="short"/> in <unclear/> finding out the well kind of finding out the solution to Sherlock <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure we really did</u>
<u n="197" who="S0179">no I'm not</u>
<u n="198" who="S0058">she didn't seem massively sure <pause dur="short"/> we do need to watch it back though with that in mind <pause dur="short"/> but no it's em <pause dur="short"/> I love how every time you mention someone it's like oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> works for us <pause dur="short"/> were his agents <pause dur="short"/> you know oh yeah I've done that film <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> but the Hobbit that's a pretty cool thing to get accredited on <pause dur="short"/> cos Howard Shore and em</u>
<u n="199" who="S0179">it looks shit</u>
<u n="200" who="S0058">well yeah but she did say that the trailer is the funniest thing ever <pause dur="short"/> and she only did the music I mean she's not responsible for the acting or the dialogue or the film or anything like that <pause dur="short"/> just you know so long as the mixing of the score is good</u>
<u n="201" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0058">the supervision of music</u>
<u n="203" who="S0179">in fairness though <pause dur="short"/> it em I got on much better with her than I was expecting to</u>
<u n="204" who="S0058">yeah yeah I mean <pause dur="short"/> it was what the way I kind of felt about it was we both had different trump cards <pause dur="short"/> so she had this really cool amazing life doing all the films <pause dur="short"/> but we were talking about <anon type="place"/> which is  which is  a kind of another really good thing <pause dur="short"/> I mean do you know what I mean? We both had real things <pause dur="short"/> no but it was really nice <pause dur="short"/> I said my parents were saying you know did you enjoy sort of catching up with your cousin I said yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos we haven't actually really spent any time together since we were children <pause dur="short"/> you know we don't really know each other as adults <pause dur="short"/> because we we're generally just with our parents in a big holiday group and we've never kind of hung out <pause dur="short"/> em but no it was  it was good  it was good fun <pause dur="short"/> she's nice she is a really nice person <pause dur="short"/> very confident and outgoing and loud</u>
<u n="205" who="S0179">not particularly</u>
<u n="206" who="S0058">no she's very confident <pause dur="short"/> which is nice</u>
<u n="207" who="S0179">not particularly</u>
<u n="208" who="S0058">Don't you think?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0179">it wasn't my overwhelming impression</u>
<u n="210" who="S0058">fair enough</u>
<u n="211" who="S0179">em</u>
<u n="212" who="S0058">but yeah em it was funny this morning we were like I didn't realise she had such a deep kind of throaty laugh and I was like don't mention the fags <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> I did have an image of her accidentally leaving them on the  on the  table and eh my parents being like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are these yours?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0179">your parents would actually ask you that question?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0058">no no no they wouldn't but I was a bit like</u>
<u n="215" who="S0179">no as in your parents would ever be in any doubt whether you might <unclear/></u>
<u n="216" who="S0058">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't think they would be <pause dur="short"/> I think they would like hey <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are these <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s? Em so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just texted back <pause dur="short"/> em latest he can arrive on the bus is about six thirty</u>
<u n="217" who="S0179">well do you want to <pause dur="short"/> hang on did we say we'd meet him?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0058">yeah but okay <pause dur="short"/> I can text him</u>
<u n="219" who="S0179">and just sort of <unclear/> Tell him to bring some wine</u>
<u n="220" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="221" who="S0179">well actually tell him that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> brought some wine and to was really nice <pause dur="short"/> em and</u>
<u n="222" who="S0058">he's also said em I'm thinking I should probably stay until latest tenish <pause dur="short"/> that should be doable</u>
<u n="223" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="224" who="S0058">probably wants an early night</u>
<u n="225" who="S0179">eh yeah and em <unclear/> about that and the gym see if he wants to</u>
<u n="226" who="S0058">cool <pause dur="short"/> cos that I mean yeah <pause dur="short"/> he could come earlier and come to the gym with us <pause dur="short"/> or if he comes at half six we'll probably have been to the gym anyway <pause dur="short"/> so we will <pause dur="short"/> that could fit in fine I think</u>
<u n="227" who="S0179">yeah well see if he wants to come along</u>
<u n="228" who="S0058">okay cool</u>
<u n="229" who="S0179">I'm also possibly thinking <unclear/> is one of <unclear/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0058">yeah no definitely <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="answers phone"/> Hello? Hello sorry I didn't catch you there <pause dur="short"/> is it?  Is it?  Can you hear me? Cool hello <pause dur="short"/> I'm just <pause dur="short"/> yes I did just get your text <pause dur="short"/> em yeah so em we're on our way back <pause dur="short"/> we did sort of we set off em you know kind of not so early <pause dur="short"/> so em couple of options <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> em either <pause dur="short"/> we were thinking about going to the gym and having a play with they've got these like em you know like the pads that you sort of punch and kick and stuff</u>
<u n="231" who="S0179">sparring pads</u>
<u n="232" who="S0058">sparring pads apparently they're called <pause dur="short"/> we were thinking about going to have a play with them so if you want to join us that's fine <pause dur="short"/> so kind of come earlier bring gym kit <pause dur="short"/> or you can come through em after and you know kind of and you know come through later on <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> in that case eh yeah we tried to get a badminton court but there's some kind of children's party on <pause dur="short"/> we tried to get a badminton court but there's some kind of children's party on <pause dur="short"/> terrible <pause dur="short"/> em okay well in that case half past six is probably a good time <pause dur="short"/> cool <pause dur="short"/> yeah sounds about right yeah <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> cool and em <pause dur="short"/> another thing we em we brought the food but we didn't em get any wine <pause dur="short"/> em is there any chance you fancy bringing a bottle of wine? Cool that sounds good <pause dur="short"/> eh red <pause dur="short"/> it's beef so I think red would go nicely <pause dur="short"/> that sounds good <pause dur="short"/> awesome <pause dur="short"/> cool eh well in that case we'll we'll sort of let you know kind of you know <pause dur="short"/> and let you change your <unclear/> but that sounds good <pause dur="short"/> cool okay <pause dur="short"/> we'll see you later on then <pause dur="short"/> okay bye <pause dur="short"/> that sounds really <unclear/> Em yeah he said em these eh sparring pads doesn't sound like his thing and he's not really very keen for that <pause dur="short"/> em which is fair enough so <pause dur="short"/> I said half six <pause dur="short"/> but we'll let him know if there's change of plan <pause dur="short"/> and he said he will bring some wine</u>
<u n="233" who="S0179">alright <pause dur="short"/> incidentally could you possibly phrase it a little less diffidently? As in its we've got food can you bring the wine?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="235" who="S0179">or that's your contribution <pause dur="short"/> not would you mind awfully it's eh can you just do it?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0058">I didn't say would you mind awfully</u>
<u n="237" who="S0179">no but that's why how it was phrased</u>
<u n="238" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> I said do you want to? The implication being bring some wine</u>
<u n="239" who="S0179">yeah it was very hesitant</u>
<u n="240" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah em so that's good plan</u>
<u n="241" who="S0179">this isn't best way of servicing the <unclear/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0058">it's not no</u>
<u n="243" who="S0179"><unclear/> substantial improvements to the place</u>
<u n="244" who="S0058">it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0179">ah yes</u>
<u n="246" who="S0058">I think it was cool</u>
<u n="247" who="S0179">again</u>
<u n="248" who="S0058"><unclear/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0058">okay that sounds like a plan for the evening then</u>
<u n="251" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> if he comes over <pause dur="short"/> can we put some music on?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0058">any eh <pause dur="short"/> what do you feel like?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0179">I'm really not sure</u>
<u n="254" who="S0058">what's a nice sort of sunny day</u>
<u n="255" who="S0179">beach boys</u>
<u n="256" who="S0058">beach boys?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0179">maybe some ABBA</u>
<u n="258" who="S0058">aBBA that would fun <pause dur="short"/> let's try that</u>
<u n="259" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we can try <pause dur="short"/> see how we get on</u>
<u n="261" who="S0179">it's worth a try</u>
<u n="262" who="S0058">and not Dancing Queen</u>
<u n="263" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="264" who="S0058">we should watch Mamma Mia <pause dur="short"/> that would be fun <pause dur="short"/> has it got to be comedy horror now?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="unintelligible"/> Yeah I know that's one of the reasons I always keep to the <unclear/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0179">as ever</u>
<u n="268" who="S0058">yeah the em the kind of weirdly shaped hill is called</u>
<u n="269" who="S0179">Roseberry Topping</u>
<u n="270" who="S0058">Roseberry Topping yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0179">Roseberry Topping</u>
<u n="272" who="S0058">it does sound like a dessert</u>
<u n="273" who="S0179">yes it does rather</u>
<u n="274" who="S0058">what will the <pause dur="short"/> what are they going for a <unclear/> tonight? We can just see what we feel like when we get there <pause dur="short"/> it's quite grim but at the same time sort of the ridge is quite cool from the sort of <unclear/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="277" who="S0179">eh I don't relay know how many DVDs <pause dur="short"/> so we have the final sort of feature length film episode em film length feature episode <pause dur="short"/> or whatever they call it <pause dur="short"/> eh and then I feel like em we've got a VHS a sort of poster thing of the series the two new series but not</u>
<u n="278" who="S0058">right hard to know whether it would be kind of you know thirty pounds no one really buys them so they can charge more</u>
<u n="279" who="S0179">I think we found her for a tenner in HMV the other day</u>
<u n="280" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's a bit better <pause dur="short"/> well that will be fun <pause dur="short"/>  I've never really watched it <pause dur="short"/> it would be nice to eh</u>
<u n="281" who="S0179">watch it by <unclear/> a series of <unclear/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> well look how much that is on Amazon cos it's quite expensive in the shops <pause dur="short"/> occasionally you find them in sales but more often it's</u>
<u n="283" who="S0179">I found them in HMV and they were about twenty quid</u>
<u n="284" who="S0058">I think it was twenty something it was</u>
<u n="285" who="S0179">well that's fine</u>
<u n="286" who="S0058">it's fine but I think look on Amazon because</u>
<u n="287" who="S0179">it's cheap for two box sets like that</u>
<u n="288" who="S0058">but yeah but I think it's worth looking on Amazon because they might just have it reduced I think they're more likely to have it reduced and it's not you know not any different from getting it from town</u>
<u n="289" who="S0179">well it is because you have to wait and I want to <unclear/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0058">depends</u>
<u n="291" who="S0179">well if not you have to wait about a week</u>
<u n="292" who="S0058">yeah that's not et end of the world <pause dur="short"/> we don't need it urgently</u>
<u n="293" who="S0179">I'd like it urgently</u>
<u n="294" who="S0058">okay fair enough <pause dur="short"/> I was going to say if we order tonight or tomorrow that's as quick as going to get it next weekend</u>
<u n="295" who="S0179">yes it would <unclear/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0058">I didn't realise you were feeling for urgent but yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0179">no I just want to <unclear/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> imagine if we got it for you know eight ninety-nine it might be worth</u>
<u n="299" who="S0179">but it won't <pause dur="short"/> there's no way it'll be on for that</u>
<u n="300" who="S0058">okay well we'll have a look <pause dur="short"/> it's kind of weird I mean I'm kind of wondering what the last series is going to be like <pause dur="short"/> whether it's going to be just a bit sad you know cos they're all a bit older and <pause dur="short"/> or whether it's going to stay being good <pause dur="short"/> cos it hasn't really got worse quality I don't think</u>
<u n="301" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="302" who="S0058">and I I wouldn't particularly be able to pick out a favourite series <pause dur="short"/> but I think they've all been a very similar quality</u>
<u n="303" who="S0179">I think it even improves with age because the relationships develop</u>
<u n="304" who="S0058">yeah I think they <pause dur="short"/> I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has got more interesting</u>
<u n="305" who="S0179">yeah I found myself liking <unclear/> wife for example</u>
<u n="306" who="S0058">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think em <pause dur="short"/> there's eh picture on the back of the last series makes you think oh <pause dur="short"/> cos does doesn't he die at the end of the seventh series or apparently like Sherlock Holmes <unclear/> But then that's really bad for the last series</u>
<u n="307" who="S0179">I've not heard that <pause dur="short"/> I don't know where you've got that</u>
<u n="308" who="S0058">off the back of the boxes</u>
<u n="309" who="S0179">oh right</u>
<u n="310" who="S0058">maybe it wasn't maybe it was deliberate so maybe it was kind of it was a cliff hanger where you thought he was dead <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> maybe it wasn't sort of that impression <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="311" who="S0179">wow</u>
<u n="312" who="S0058">what's that?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0179">we'll find out in a minute</u>
<u n="314" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh it's one of those with a box at the back I love those <pause dur="short"/> rudimentary boots <pause dur="short"/> ah cool <pause dur="short"/> it has got the box on the back <pause dur="short"/> ah that's so cool</u>
<u n="315" who="S0179">that is very cool</u>
<u n="316" who="S0058">sweet</u>
<u n="317" who="S0179">this guy is <unclear/> Cos he's managing sixty quite comfortably</u>
<u n="318" who="S0058">yeah not bad <pause dur="short"/> how is the <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0179">he's not <unclear/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="321" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="322" who="S0058">in <pause dur="short"/> it did look in very condition <pause dur="short"/> it was awfully shiny <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't mind going for a driven a really sort of classic car <pause dur="short"/> that would be cool</u>
<u n="323" who="S0179">talking of driving at some point I do probably next Saturday need to check the oil and tyre pressures</u>
<u n="324" who="S0058">right yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> put it on the board</u>
<u n="325" who="S0179">I think you need to <unclear/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0058">yeah I did <unclear/> I could do that today</u>
<u n="327" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0058">we can do it now <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's always gaps in the complete process so I could do that if it doesn't take long so I could do that when I've got something in cooking for a little while</u>
<u n="329" who="S0179">yes you could</u>
<u n="330" who="S0058">it doesn't have to be particularly nice you know <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> yeah that would work <unclear/> It is a good vacuum for doing that with actually</u>
<u n="331" who="S0179">it's a good vacuum for doing almost anything</u>
<u n="332" who="S0058">yeah pretty much <pause dur="short"/> I don't yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean the only thing that a lot of people were bothered by is the fact that you <unclear/> and it's not really an issue but they don't have that much force <pause dur="short"/> if it doesn't get too full</u>
<u n="333" who="S0179">then you don't have the change bags</u>
<u n="334" who="S0058">yeah well exactly <pause dur="short"/> that is nice <pause dur="short"/> no faffing about <pause dur="short"/> and that's one less thing to buy <pause dur="short"/> once you've bought the units you don't really have to buy the new parts</u>
<u n="335" who="S0179">and of of course in ten years that pays for itself</u>
<u n="336" who="S0058">exactly yeah <pause dur="short"/> the thing is like you know hoover bags bin bags is they're really expensive <pause dur="short"/> especially if you've got a fancy hoover and you need to get the branded hoover bags <pause dur="short"/> and you <unclear/> you need to get the ones that fit</u>
<u n="337" who="S0179">well it's probably not patented as a new so you probably get sort of home brand ones <pause dur="short"/> you get a a <unclear/> It looks far far better in <unclear/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0058">so funny last night when you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0179">yeah it was wasn't it</u>
<u n="340" who="S0058">that was really funny <pause dur="short"/> oh my goodness <pause dur="short"/> cos it was oh that ones' a bit better looks more like a bird <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> it was interesting though that you'll like there's things that we like because our father's had them</u>
<u n="341" who="S0179">yes but I now like <unclear/> for different reasons</u>
<u n="342" who="S0058">yeah but we do all like the cars our father have driven <pause dur="short"/> I think it's really interesting <pause dur="short"/> em but yes ha ha very amusing <pause dur="short"/> it does look better with the <unclear/> you're right <pause dur="short"/> ah Frank's factory flooring <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Used to be em so Frank's Flooring Store <pause dur="short"/> used to be Frank's Factory Flooring and then they changed it cos it sounded a bit cheap and knock off <pause dur="short"/> but the tag line is I love carpet's me <pause dur="short"/> so there's these radio adverts <pause dur="short"/> franks factory flooring <pause dur="short"/> I love carpet's me <pause dur="short"/> it's excellent</u>
<u n="343" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0058">and my other favourite is Hadglider <unclear/> had a bric-a-brac random kid of electrical type shop but you know a kind of second hand store <pause dur="short"/> and the tag line was up for sale give us a bell <pause dur="short"/> which was excellent <pause dur="short"/> what was the other weird one that my dad always talks about when em <pause dur="short"/> cos it was for some kind of tailor <pause dur="short"/> em when he's talking you know kind of saying you know we em <pause dur="short"/> you know an Indian man you know doing the voice over saying em  tailors we do em <unclear/> everything <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> bikini and anorak <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's just bizarre <pause dur="short"/> ha <pause dur="short"/> a list of items they can put <unclear/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0179">suit and a bikini</u>
<u n="346" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0179">I like this</u>
<u n="348" who="S0058">use the accent <pause dur="short"/> ha <pause dur="short"/> yeah but a beach holiday in Barbados sound kind of interesting</u>
<u n="349" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0058">beach holiday in Barbados <pause dur="short"/> fancy it?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0179">maybe</u>
<u n="352" who="S0058">I love that stay stay in a hostel cos it's better to meet people <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to meet people on holiday <pause dur="short"/> did did you? And maybe <unclear/> a little bit too much</u>
<u n="353" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just as well</u>
<u n="354" who="S0058">yeah exactly yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's time to be cautious <pause dur="short"/> don't want to end up in a Thai prison <pause dur="short"/> oh good that's finished</u>
<u n="355" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0058">that's finished <unclear/> Oh we could watch the last Harry Potter today</u>
<u n="357" who="S0179">yes we could</u>
<u n="358" who="S0058">I imagine it's very long <pause dur="short"/> so we can start it before then we'll finish it after</u>
<u n="359" who="S0179">well if not tonight then certainly tomorrow</u>
<u n="360" who="S0058">yeah that'd be fun</u>
<u n="361" who="S0179">no I'd like to watch it all the way through so maybe tomorrow</u>
<u n="362" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="363" who="S0179">that looks like a dog</u>
<u n="364" who="S0058">what does?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0179">Small <unclear/> Oh it's dog</u>
<u n="366" who="S0058">in the back? I didn't see it</u>
<u n="367" who="S0179">oh <pause dur="short"/> I could have sworn</u>
<u n="368" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="369" who="S0179">I love that <pause dur="short"/> a café and take away <pause dur="short"/> and it's been changed to café <pause dur="short"/> café and <unclear/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0058">ah yes it's in Chinese <pause dur="short"/> doesn't look massively inviting <pause dur="short"/> a bit fifties <pause dur="short"/> it's kind of cool even in a retro <pause dur="short"/> but weird though</u>
<u n="371" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> very pleasant</u>
<u n="373" who="S0179">I imagine the hills would be accessible <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> hills <pause dur="short"/> that is easy access</u>
<u n="374" who="S0058">I like the hills like I like my women <pause dur="short"/> accessible <pause dur="short"/> ah dear <pause dur="short"/> joy <pause dur="short"/> so they finished <pause dur="short"/> sorry they haven't finished <pause dur="short"/> they've em had some <unclear/> three</u>
<u n="375" who="S0179">eh?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0058"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said last night well they've stopped shooing anyway so there's no you know  on board <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why <pause dur="short"/> I did maybe think that I should get into a slightly more exciting  where I'll have trade secrets to give out</u>
<u n="377" who="S0179">you do <pause dur="short"/> about bibles</u>
<u n="378" who="S0058">exactly about ELT <pause dur="short"/> it's not massively you know interesting to anyone else <pause dur="short"/> I mean I do have  but I'm not  They're not massively interesting to anyone so not really an issue</u>
<u n="379" who="S0179">well I have  more ideas for our oxygen thing</u>
<u n="380" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> that stuff is really good I mean I guess that's it's really key you're getting you know getting firsthand kind of</u>
<u n="381" who="S0179">actually let's think about this for a second <pause dur="short"/> what would be useful here?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0058">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's great <pause dur="short"/> thirty-five to <anon type="place"/> itself <pause dur="short"/> I think <anon type="place"/> is quite a bit north of us <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> So it's yeah cool</u>
<u n="383" who="S0179"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> The tangerine</u>
<u n="384" who="S0058">you should watch Mamma Mia at some point <pause dur="short"/> it's very good</u>
<u n="385" who="S0179">I saw the first half and it's not too bad</u>
<u n="386" who="S0058">it's a really good film <pause dur="short"/> it's very sunny <pause dur="short"/> it features Colin Firth singing which is always a pleasure</u>
<u n="387" who="S0179">it does feature Colin Firth singing which is why I want to watch it</u>
<u n="388" who="S0058">oh god so bad</u>
<u n="389" who="S0179">and the other chap I just can't think who he is</u>
<u n="390" who="S0058">Stellan Skarsgard</u>
<u n="391" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0058">he is actually getting really famous <pause dur="short"/> em he's in</u>
<u n="393" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0058">no no well he was in Pirates I think <pause dur="short"/> yeah he's in Pirates but not in <unclear/> and he's in em the new <unclear/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0179">oh</u>
<u n="396" who="S0058">and he was in that weird oh probably a film that you wanted to watch about the em the kind of school <pause dur="short"/> the you know kind of em detention centre for young boys <pause dur="short"/> I think it was in Norway</u>
<u n="397" who="S0179">oh yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> that looked really good</u>
<u n="398" who="S0058">that looked really good <pause dur="short"/> was that subtitled or? I can't remember</u>
<u n="399" who="S0179">probably yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0058">well it did look really good <pause dur="short"/> and he was in that as well he was the kind of evil person from it <pause dur="short"/> I think he was in something else as well <pause dur="short"/> yeah he's doing quite well for himself</u>
<u n="401" who="S0179">yeah well <unclear/> I didn't actually watch it I was</u>
<u n="402" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we watched films <unclear/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="404" who="S0058">I love that <pause dur="short"/> paid forty pounds they never let me go <pause dur="short"/> isn't that good?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0179">forty</u>
<u n="406" who="S0058">well no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying that em she's cos she's a member of Love Film but you've got to send the DVDs back and she's had one for months <pause dur="short"/> so she's paying like five pound a month for it and she said she's paid you know kind of six months' worth of payments for just one DVD <pause dur="short"/> he was thinking like going to <unclear/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="408" who="S0058">hey <pause dur="short"/> I wonder what incident support is doing <pause dur="short"/> looks like he's picking up road kill</u>
<u n="409" who="S0179">okay <pause dur="short"/> there's a <unclear/> unit there <pause dur="short"/> oh it didn't actually read that at the back but you can tell that because of the presence of</u>
<u n="410" who="S0058">oh the cooling things</u>
<u n="411" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0058">ah <pause dur="short"/> right now I'd read the back and seen that you could <pause dur="short"/> ah that's really interesting yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos you have to keep them cool enough don't you? In the back <pause dur="short"/> ah you learn something new every day</u>
<u n="413" who="S0179">yeah just that you should not be pulled out in front of us <pause dur="short"/>  to slow down</u>
<u n="414" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0179">I don't care who you are it's not acceptable</u>
<u n="416" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> quite bad</u>
<u n="417" who="S0179">is he breaking the speed limit?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0058">interesting</u>
<u n="419" who="S0179">to be foolish</u>
<u n="420" who="S0058">well we've got it recorded but unfortunately not in any way that would eh provide evidence <pause dur="short"/> ah it's the lorries again doing their thing <pause dur="short"/> it's so annoying</u>
<u n="421" who="S0179">it is very annoying <pause dur="short"/> again what is the advantage of driving like this?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0179">just what are they gaining</u>
<u n="424" who="S0058">just you can't do that <pause dur="short"/> causing a massive tailback <pause dur="short"/> for what? Yeah for another few metres <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's still not passed him <pause dur="short"/> has he just pulled in there now? It's stupid <pause dur="short"/> the other guy wants to drive in but you know is <unclear/></u>
<u n="425" who="S0179">which other guy?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0058">this other guy behind him wasn't going to give him lots of room so <pause dur="short"/> he's sticking right up behind him</u>
<u n="427" who="S0179">what the lorry?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0058">yeah sorry the lorry behind well isn't just pulled back in</u>
<u n="429" who="S0179">yeah they <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well the gap now turns into ten yards</u>
<u n="430" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's not very patient <pause dur="short"/> furniture warehouse and distribution</u>
<u n="431" who="S0179">em <pause dur="short"/> superb</u>
<u n="432" who="S0058">mm? What did you say there?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0179">I was just saying superb</u>
<u n="434" who="S0058">superb <pause dur="short"/> sorry?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0179">that car has very constructively speeded up aggressively <pause dur="short"/> so This police car is just <unclear/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0179">alright <pause dur="short"/> stop</u>
<u n="438" who="S0058">yeah it's really bad <pause dur="short"/> it's not at all <pause dur="short"/> you know you've got you just need to set an example <pause dur="short"/> it's really bad <pause dur="short"/> of course you couldn't say well I saw a police car doing this speed recently you know</u>
<u n="439" who="S0179">well you could  you could  if you'd actually caught it <pause dur="short"/> if you had it on video camera or</u>
<u n="440" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0179">you're either  on you're not <pause dur="short"/> unless you are you're <unclear/> by the traffic acts <pause dur="short"/> which does actually apply to you unless you're training or responding to an emergency</u>
<u n="442" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0179">ah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0058">yes never mind</u>
<u n="445" who="S0179">oh cyclists</u>
<u n="446" who="S0058">I didn't think you were allowed cyclists <pause dur="short"/> maybe it isn't a kind of restricted one <pause dur="short"/> seems to be <unclear/></u>
<u n="447" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="448" who="S0058">yeah afar enough I guess <pause dur="short"/> yeah so maybe you can cycle along the <pause dur="short"/> yeah it just seems like it wouldn't be much fun</u>
<u n="449" who="S0179">I don't know it's a straight road <pause dur="short"/> there's enough  There's enough  of a verge for you to be in actually</u>
<u n="450" who="S0058">yeah there is actually nice little cycle lane down here</u>
<u n="451" who="S0179">bizarrely</u>
<u n="452" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> fair enough I guess</u>
<u n="453" who="S0179"><unclear/> So I'm hoping that we just sit on this road and then it just fits on to the A1M <pause dur="short"/> I think that's what happens</u>
<u n="454" who="S0058">do you want me to have a look?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0179">yeah just to check</u>
<u n="456" who="S0058">but all the signs have been saying A1 <trunc>si</trunc> or there have been signs for it so</u>
<u n="457" who="S0179">we're getting to the <unclear/> of James Harriet <pause dur="short"/> yey</u>
<u n="458" who="S0058">oh that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0179"><unclear/> Pass the police car</u>
<u n="460" who="S0058">wouldn't do that <pause dur="short"/> we're going at a reasonable speed</u>
<u n="461" who="S0179">no it's there <pause dur="short"/> it's just turned off <pause dur="short"/> it actually did sort of</u>
<u n="462" who="S0058">yeah so em we need to go on <pause dur="short"/> it's so it's like coming off again we we the A19 doesn't actually go directly into the A1M but em <pause dur="short"/> we go on to the A168 and I imagine it will be signposted</u>
<u n="463" who="S0179">but it's a direct <unclear/> isn't it? As in we just take this road it just changes its name</u>
<u n="464" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh sorry yeah yeah we stay on <pause dur="short"/> yeah no you're right the A19 comes off at a junction <pause dur="short"/> we are close enough to <unclear/> It's that first <pause dur="short"/> yeah we sit stay on this road <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> and then that feeds into the A1M so yeah it should be nice and straight forward <pause dur="short"/> yeah like I said I think there will be services further north than <anon type="place"/> itself <pause dur="short"/> em so</u>
<u n="465" who="S0179">likely I should think</u>
<u n="466" who="S0058">I've got <unclear/> on here <pause dur="short"/> a specialised tourist attraction for somebody in the country</u>
<u n="467" who="S0179">it's actually <unclear/> that place?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0058">yeah it's on the <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0179">oh</u>
<u n="470" who="S0058">it's impressive <pause dur="short"/> considering it's just house <pause dur="short"/> that is of interest to a few literary people <pause dur="short"/> maybe I'm underestimating it but I just don't think I am</u>
<u n="471" who="S0179">have you what sorry?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0058">underestimating his appeal <pause dur="short"/> I just don't think he has massive appeal <pause dur="short"/> yes so we stay on this road now this is where the A19 comes off we em we don't want to carry on <pause dur="short"/> I think it carries on down to York</u>
<u n="473" who="S0179">yeah I think that's that  We were on it when we went to em  or whatever it is</u>
<u n="474" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="475" who="S0179">that's <trunc>ri</trunc> that's good</u>
<u n="476" who="S0058">shandy Hall yes <pause dur="short"/> it's well of course it's not <pause dur="short"/> that's what it's been called since <pause dur="short"/> em it got named after the house in <unclear/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0179">oh right</u>
<u n="478" who="S0058">so yeah sorry yeah so I should explain <pause dur="short"/> em it's not it's just Coxwold Priory house or whatever the priory and Coxwold vicarage <pause dur="short"/> and it I don't think it had any particular interesting name but they called the house in Tristram Shandy is called Shandy Hall and they've named it in honour of Laurence Sterne</u>
<u n="479" who="S0179">because it was <unclear/> autobiographical</u>
<u n="480" who="S0058">they were what sorry?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0179">it was semi-autobiographical</u>
<u n="482" who="S0058">em kind of em <pause dur="short"/> as in it wasn't about his life but he's very much the figure of supposed to be writing down the story <pause dur="short"/> so it's a <trunc>ki</trunc> it's not autobiographical as such but you can identify the two figures <pause dur="short"/> and Tristram doesn't really figure in it very much <pause dur="short"/> does that make sense em <pause dur="short"/> it's a very odd novel it's more about his family and what happened before he was born and what happens when he's a very young child and stuff <pause dur="short"/> eh</u>
<u n="483" who="S0179">right <pause dur="short"/> and <unclear/> is a vicar yeah?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0179">eh <unclear/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0058">very nice</u>
<u n="487" who="S0179">interesting just to <unclear/> to Yorkshire and <unclear/> about</u>
<u n="488" who="S0058">yeah no I mean what I'd really like to do is em we all go to  so we leap to <unclear/> Eh yeah I mean <pause dur="short"/> I think I spent a bit of time in Yorkshire as a child like on holiday and stuff but haven't really been there since <pause dur="short"/> it would be nice to explore a bit of the country <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's a Roman site at Thorough bridge just off the A1 <pause dur="short"/> loads of kind of interesting sounding properties and things</u>
<u n="489" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0058">yeah files miles to the <unclear/>  <unclear/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0179">just get a <unclear/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0058">get a what sorry?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0179">get our roast dinner sorted out</u>
<u n="494" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we need like a ramp to come down at the back and drive on to it <pause dur="short"/> one of my favourite things was is when he's em flying the helicopter along the road</u>
<u n="495" who="S0179">that's <unclear/> about eighteen inches</u>
<u n="496" who="S0058">ah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0179">my favourite bit is when he's eh up at <unclear/> and they're doing the <unclear/> and you can tell <unclear/> keep you safe but</u>
<u n="498" who="S0058">oh yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0179">by memorising this leaflet</u>
<u n="500" who="S0058">so good <pause dur="short"/> and they offer you drinks <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> it's just a funny film</u>
<u n="501" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0058">sorry?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0179">ah I'm just feeling <unclear/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0058">my parents want to borrow it at some point I think</u>
<u n="505" who="S0179">do they? Fine</u>
<u n="506" who="S0058">I think they said they would <pause dur="short"/> they wanted to see how it ended</u>
<u n="507" who="S0179">I'll give it to dad when he turns up <pause dur="short"/> tuesday <pause dur="short"/> I need to phone him tonight when we get back</u>
<u n="508" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="509" who="S0179">eh I do need to text <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as well <pause dur="short"/> maybe you can do that now?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0058">text <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? Yeah sure</u>
<u n="511" who="S0179">Great</u>
<u n="512" who="S0058">I'll just say how are you going?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0179">how are we going em <pause dur="short"/> any idea when you might be <unclear/> soon <pause dur="short"/> if not we're thinking you've got <unclear/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0179">something like that</u>
<u n="516" who="S0058">just wondering if you know em when you're back again <pause dur="short"/> something like that? Yeah?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0179">let's see eh <pause dur="short"/> when you might next be in Cambridge</u>
<u n="518" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0179">otherwise <unclear/></u>
<u n="520" who="S0058">yeah yeah it's true <pause dur="short"/> I'll put would be  would be  great to see you or something <pause dur="short"/> I'll tell her we can we could pop down and see you sometime if you like? Something like that</u>
<u n="521" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0179">ah yes this is a straight feed in</u>
<u n="524" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> nice and easy <pause dur="short"/> it's very straight forward <pause dur="short"/> you get onto the A19 and just sit on the road <pause dur="short"/> like there isn't anything to do</u>
<u n="525" who="S0179">ah <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> yeah all one motorway</u>
<u n="526" who="S0058">that was unfortunate <pause dur="short"/> I accidentally pressed too many keys when I was typing in pop and it came <trunc>o</trunc> came out as porn</u>
<u n="527" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> well that's the unpredictive text</u>
<u n="528" who="S0058">not really sure why</u>
<u n="529" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it should be becoming  shortly <pause dur="short"/> well that's a very civilised</u>
<u n="530" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0179">way to get here</u>
<u n="532" who="S0058">it's very easy isn't it all this eh <pause dur="short"/> this going north to south stuff</u>
<u n="533" who="S0179">much easier as well <pause dur="short"/> I'm actually inclined to have to say that's a nicer default</u>
<u n="534" who="S0058">that's easier than going up and then coming off the <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="535" who="S0179">with that really annoying bit at Busford</u>
<u n="536" who="S0058">cross the what?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0179">at Busford there with the <unclear/></u>
<u n="538" who="S0058">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> true <pause dur="short"/> well that's the way my dad always go <pause dur="short"/> but I think it is yeah it's very civilised <pause dur="short"/> and you get to do the cool <unclear/> bit <pause dur="short"/> so is this the em <anon type="place"/> services in forty miles</u>
<u n="539" who="S0179">yeah that'll be them <pause dur="short"/> I assume so yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0058">cool <pause dur="short"/> yeah I hope she's eh feeling alright</u>
<u n="541" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="542" who="S0058">so <pause dur="short"/> a place called Snape</u>
<u n="543" who="S0179">Snape?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0058">Snape yeah as in the character <pause dur="short"/> not too for from here actually</u>
<u n="545" who="S0179">oh so</u>
<u n="546" who="S0058">this is an awesome song <pause dur="short"/> my mum's got all the ABBA stuff on record <pause dur="short"/> so it's pretty cool <pause dur="short"/> I think I've told you my sister and me used to listen to it <pause dur="short"/> you know we weren't allowed to take the ones of the record playing cos we'd smash them <pause dur="short"/> so we just used to sit and listen to them and then when they'd finish my mum would change them over for us</u>
<u n="547" who="S0179">nice</u>
<u n="548" who="S0058">of course it is difficult to like switch track on a record <pause dur="short"/> you can't skip one so you've got to listen to whole thing in the order intended <pause dur="short"/> it's a very different way of looking at music</u>
<u n="549" who="S0179">yes it is</u>
<u n="550" who="S0058">like in the past the the order of song an album is recorded in now</u>
<u n="551" who="S0179">yes now but yes in terms of its <unclear/> So that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0058">yeah I mean in all fairness I still like listening to albums in sequence <pause dur="short"/> I think artists do put thought into it and it often balances the songs better cos otherwise you end up with a a load of happy ones and a load of miserable ones all din of bunched up <pause dur="short"/> em whereas it's normally kind of balanced out <pause dur="short"/> but yeah people shuffle through individuals there's less of a kind of <trunc>me</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> you know whereas the record is necessarily a whole <pause dur="short"/> obviously you can skip tracks but it's not easy and you've just got listen to it</u>
<u n="553" who="S0179">yeah so we'll be at Wetherby in in about ten minutes</u>
<u n="554" who="S0058">get some food</u>
<u n="555" who="S0179">are we going to have lunch?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah good <pause dur="short"/> my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has a record player <pause dur="short"/> it's a very <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> way of listening to music</u>
<u n="557" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> not very efficient</u>
<u n="558" who="S0058">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> kind of a bit pretty and a little bit silly and old fashioned but <pause dur="short"/> having said that he has got a you know an Apple laptop so he's not exactly eh <unclear/> I think that was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s influence as well <pause dur="short"/> I think he was quite keen for him to get one</u>
<u n="559" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="560" who="S0058">ah it's so sad</u>
<u n="561" who="S0179">haven't met the new boy yet</u>
<u n="562" who="S0058">no true he might be amazing</u>
<u n="563" who="S0179">true but it would be hard to beat <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="564" who="S0058"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was awesome <pause dur="short"/> I don't know you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> seems really keen on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and you know he wasn't to love in York and yeah that's nice</u>
<u n="565" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="566" who="S0058">I do think it's really interesting though how it's worked out for him cos he always oh <unclear/> Em</u>
<u n="567" who="S0179">who is he?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0058">em it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh I'll see what she says <pause dur="short"/> ah badly <pause dur="short"/> I was in hospital on Friday home at the weekend having surgery tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> I'll let you know when I'm back in town <pause dur="short"/> poor soul <pause dur="short"/> right I'll em I'll <trunc>e</trunc> text her back and say em</u>
<u n="569" who="S0179">say we're just both thinking about you and</u>
<u n="570" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0179"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0058">sorry? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s cool</u>
<u n="573" who="S0179">six minutes</u>
<u n="574" who="S0058">awesome <pause dur="short"/> I'm hoping that's been nice just to to be remembered is sometimes nice if you're away from people <pause dur="short"/> it's easier to forget if you if someone's not around you so <pause dur="short"/> I hope it's nice to be reminded that people are you know rooting for her <pause dur="short"/> yeah em so <pause dur="short"/> I just think it's interesting what's happened with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that he's you know he always seems quite em you know really into the theatre thing and more career focused than kind of plays or relationships or whatever and <pause dur="short"/> you know more I could have imagined him doing that <pause dur="short"/> taking it quite seriously and willing to give up a lot for it but actually</u>
<u n="575" who="S0179">he's decided not to</u>
<u n="576" who="S0058">it's interesting that he's not that bothered and it's not really his thing <pause dur="short"/> he's actually picked different priorities <pause dur="short"/> I just think it's really interesting <pause dur="short"/> I mean yeah I'm not massively surprised but I think it's em <pause dur="short"/> it's not entirely unlike <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but I mean yeah it just makes me think that it's sort of quite serious because he's never really been like that with when we've been talking about relationships in the past <pause dur="short"/> he's never given that impression of being really into long term <pause dur="short"/> giving up things for for relationship and you know <pause dur="short"/> more into kind of you know <pause dur="short"/> he's quite openly been into you know having fun and maybe a relationship but more into just meeting people and you know <pause dur="short"/> it's all it's just the beard you see the beard has made him sensible and not into</u>
<u n="577" who="S0179">well they tend to have that effect</u>
<u n="578" who="S0058">I was very dubious but he said it should be done <pause dur="short"/> I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got a beard <pause dur="short"/> I can see that happening <pause dur="short"/> as in my cousin <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="579" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s boyfriend called again?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0058"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="581" who="S0179"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="582" who="S0058">yes and em next next time we go we'll make sure we meet him <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> they have like fancy dress parties <pause dur="short"/> posh dinner parties where there's just</u>
<u n="583" who="S0179">yes <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is well suited to his cousins and</u>
<u n="584" who="S0058">he is it's great <pause dur="short"/> well he always used to talk very kind of warmly and excitedly about spending time with them and going up to Yorkshire and you know it seemed to be a nice thing that he loved doing <pause dur="short"/> I I mean I do sort of wonder how his parents feel <pause dur="short"/> but they must be aware of how well he did <unclear/> I'm just not sure if he gets on quite so well with his parents</u>
<u n="585" who="S0179">well I suppose they're people of his own generation</u>
<u n="586" who="S0058">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> well no I mean but the fact he's now living with another boyfriend <unclear/> his parents <pause dur="short"/> I just wonder if they're a little bit</u>
<u n="587" who="S0179">well that is mostly for <unclear/> I think</u>
<u n="588" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="589" who="S0179">as in if it's something he wants to do it is a very good job</u>
<u n="590" who="S0058">what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to do sorry?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0179">I said if it was something he wanted to do it's a very good job</u>
<u n="592" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="593" who="S0179">it's very good</u>
<u n="594" who="S0058">yea yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I guess it was either your <trunc>bu</trunc> em south <trunc>af</trunc> em or em what's it called?</u>
<u n="595" who="S0179">Southend</u>
<u n="596" who="S0058">Southend <pause dur="short"/> I was thinking Southport? Yeah it was either there or Southend to do it for free <pause dur="short"/> as in could have afforded to do it and not have lots of family there so <pause dur="short"/> but no its em <pause dur="short"/> I'm just really pleased that he seems happy</u>
<u n="597" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> excuse me</u>
<u n="598" who="S0058">sorry?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0179">I said excuse me</u>
<u n="600" who="S0058">Excused <pause dur="short"/> I'm not quite sure what for but</u>
<u n="601" who="S0179">Cos I burped</u>
<u n="602" who="S0058">no need to be excused for that <pause dur="short"/> it's no problem</u>
<u n="603" who="S0179">thank you</u>
<u n="604" who="S0058">anything bigger <unclear/></u>
<u n="605" who="S0179">em <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0058">expensive</u>
<u n="607" who="S0179">it's about ninety seconds</u>
<u n="608" who="S0058">cool</u>
<u n="609" who="S0179"></u>
<u n="610" who="S0058">I just no I started saying that yes <pause dur="short"/> nice <pause dur="short"/> flappy thing on the car in front</u>
<u n="611" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0058">it must be making a racket inside the car</u>
<u n="613" who="S0179">it's half a mile now <pause dur="short"/> to be fair we pulled in <unclear/> but now</u>
<u n="614" who="S0058">he's pulling back in <pause dur="short"/> let him overtake you</u>
<u n="615" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what the fuck do you think you're doing?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0058">bloody hell <pause dur="short"/> that is scary</u>
<u n="617" who="S0179">that is very scary <pause dur="short"/> how about <unclear/> your vehicle a metre in front and behind <pause dur="short"/> we've seen quite a lot today</u>
<u n="618" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've seen a lot of that <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why specifically it's been such a <pause dur="short"/> this wasn't the ready rent-a-van you see <pause dur="short"/> he's been better behaved</u>
<u n="619" who="S0179">now I'm interested to see where this individual parks</u>
<u n="620" who="S0058">probably right in the middle of two spaces</u>
<u n="621" who="S0179">no I meant close to us or not</u>
<u n="622" who="S0058">oh right</u>
<u n="623" who="S0179">shall we eat lunch and then go into the tour bus?</u>
<u n="624" who="S0058">yeah I'm happy to do that</u>
<u n="625" who="S0179">Cos then we can sort of <pause dur="short"/> the next leg is longer <pause dur="short"/> it would probably make sense to set off as soon as after that as possible <pause dur="short"/> five past now <pause dur="short"/> no sorry</u>
<u n="626" who="S0058">I respectfully disagree</u>
<u n="627" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="628" who="S0058">ah lovely</u>
<u n="629" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="630" who="S0058">shall I get lunch?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0179">I would yes</u>
<u n="632" who="S0058">there's all the thing <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="633" who="S0179">yeah that's fine <pause dur="short"/> it's all in the one bag yeah?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0058">yeah I think so yeah <pause dur="short"/> yep <pause dur="short"/> and some horseradish</u>
<u n="635" who="S0179">oh good <pause dur="short"/> just for dipping</u>
<u n="636" who="S0058" trans="overlap">put that in the back <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah excellent <pause dur="short"/> so the chicken is here</u>
<u n="637" who="S0179">thank you <pause dur="short"/> what did you have again?</u>
<u n="638" who="S0058">I've got ham and cheese <pause dur="short"/> cheese?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0179">cheese of the fruit variety</u>
<u n="640" who="S0058">ah ha</u>
<u n="641" who="S0179">and motorway noise</u>
<u n="642" who="S0058">lovely spot for a picnic</u>
<u n="643" who="S0179">maybe not entirely <pause dur="short"/> but to fair we could probably just take these inside and eat them there but eh</u>
<u n="644" who="S0058">this is nice <pause dur="short"/> it <unclear/> out a little bit even if you're in the car it's pretty em</u>
<u n="645" who="S0179">if you say so <pause dur="short"/> what's this again? Roast chicken and lemon and herb mayonnaise</u>
<u n="646" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="647" who="S0179">quite nice</u>
<u n="648" who="S0058">mine's ham hock and extra mature cheddar cheese on multi-seed farmhouse brown bread</u>
<u n="649" who="S0179">ah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know you like it mature</u>
<u n="650" who="S0058">what do you think about my mum's bread? What? Oh no link there <pause dur="short"/> thanks for that</u>
<u n="651" who="S0179">when did we have your mum's bread?</u>
<u n="652" who="S0058">as toast</u>
<u n="653" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> I thought why not just buy bread?</u>
<u n="654" who="S0058">well I do wonder if it's any cheaper <pause dur="short"/> it's very nice</u>
<u n="655" who="S0179">the cakes weren't <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's nothing wrong with them but there's nothing right with them either</u>
<u n="656" who="S0058">of course cos you've had them before cos I've brought some on holiday once</u>
<u n="657" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's funny but given it was your family that introduced me to wraps how your parents are eating them with knives and forks</u>
<u n="658" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they enjoyed them once we kind of <pause dur="short"/> when I said oh you know are you ready to go in a minute they were like is the chicken cooked? I was like yes it's cooked <pause dur="short"/> I'm not going to poison you <pause dur="short"/> and your dad was like your mum normally cooks it you know nuke it's nuke's it completely <pause dur="short"/> I'm like I know <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't need cooking for that long <pause dur="short"/> strips that long you can do in about three minutes <pause dur="short"/> we've had significantly longer</u>
<u n="659" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> this is pretty good actually <pause dur="short"/> m and S quality</u>
<u n="660" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> well these Taste the Difference one's are nice <pause dur="short"/> and they're not <pause dur="short"/> because they're part of the deal</u>
<u n="661" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> I mean do you want to swap or do you want to keep what was yours?</u>
<u n="662" who="S0058">em I'm happy either way <pause dur="short"/> if you're</u>
<u n="663" who="S0179">I'd quite like to keep it personally I just thought I should offer</u>
<u n="664" who="S0058">no it's fine <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no that's very kind of you <pause dur="short"/> I'm good <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure the eh I'm not sure the grapes are necessarily the best quality item <pause dur="short"/> they were the best value item but you know</u>
<u n="665" who="S0179">didn't want anything else</u>
<u n="666" who="S0058">well exactly <pause dur="short"/> I think most of them probably chocolate and crisps <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> Really need to stop inhaling the bread</u>
<u n="667" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="668" who="S0058">we could still smell Catherine's fag a little bit in the  in the  kitchen when she was smoking it</u>
<u n="669" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> I was far too drunk to care by that point</u>
<u n="670" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't that keen on her lighting the fag on the hob <pause dur="short"/> I was like my there's been too much gas</u>
<u n="671" who="S0179">I was quite proud of the solution</u>
<u n="672" who="S0058">no it was a very clever solution <pause dur="short"/> but I was bit like uh</u>
<u n="673" who="S0179">shows I have working class roots too <pause dur="short"/> well at least I've watched working class people</u>
<u n="674" who="S0058">nice</u>
<u n="675" who="S0179">on television</u>
<u n="676" who="S0058">which working class person have you seen lighting a fag on a hob?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0179">Terry</u>
<u n="678" who="S0058">ah right <pause dur="short"/> that does make sense</u>
<u n="679" who="S0179">want to get a lead on that dog otherwise it's going to have a very short life</u>
<u n="680" who="S0058">what's this?</u>
<u n="681" who="S0179">oh there's a spaniel out the <unclear/> Gorgeous but he's quite frisky <pause dur="short"/> as you might understand having been shoved in a car for a while</u>
<u n="682" who="S0058">well quite <pause dur="short"/> grape?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0058">grape? Eh</u>
<u n="685" who="S0179">yes I will <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> quality</u>
<u n="686" who="S0058">not very nice not to tell us that the em mango wasn't <unclear/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> then in out roundabout</u>
<u n="688" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="689" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="690" who="S0058">cued</u>
<u n="691" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="692" who="S0058"><unclear/> the dog</u>
<u n="693" who="S0179">in principle yeah in practice no <pause dur="short"/> it's okay for a while but you do need someone to look after it <pause dur="short"/> it's not really fair to leave it at home all day when you're at work I don't think <pause dur="short"/> unless you've got two</u>
<u n="694" who="S0058">Cos dogs keep each other company kind of well enough</u>
<u n="695" who="S0179">some dogs do <pause dur="short"/> so dog's like Beagles <pause dur="short"/> oh god <pause dur="short"/> are pack dogs so they prefer basically prefer <pause dur="short"/> you need if you have one you need two really <pause dur="short"/> they prefer dog company to human company</u>
<u n="696" who="S0058">whereas for some dogs would it not make much difference em</u>
<u n="697" who="S0179">well the spaniels are sort of neither here nor there <pause dur="short"/> and collies are fairly sort of people dogs</u>
<u n="698" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm just having an image of those blue napkins I was presented with the first time I went on holiday with your family</u>
<u n="699" who="S0179">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a special car for special people <pause dur="short"/> now <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm glad that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s joined and I've had a chance to get to know him <pause dur="short"/> because apart from anything else it's given me a good idea of <pause dur="short"/> I didn't actually want to do a PhD <pause dur="short"/> you know I'm getting a bit bored with <pause dur="short"/> I almost getting a bit bored of work at the moment and that's on quite a variety of projects</u>
<u n="700" who="S0058">yeah it's much more fun on a PhD?</u>
<u n="701" who="S0179">well I enjoyed the fourth year project a lot but it was only half the time <pause dur="short"/> there was a lot of other stuff going on <pause dur="short"/> and I enjoyed a lot of it because it was in a lab at a workshop which was great <pause dur="short"/> but a PhD mostly wouldn't be and I'm not sure I could eh</u>
<u n="702" who="S0058">yeah it would be a lot more just sitting doing things by yourself as opposed to</u>
<u n="703" who="S0179">yeah I think that would have been the wrong decision <pause dur="short"/> because it would essentially have been a job that you got less out of</u>
<u n="704" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="705" who="S0179">but except wasn't brilliantly well paid and not that interesting</u>
<u n="706" who="S0058">yeah so I mean</u>
<u n="707" who="S0179">I mean it it didn't occur to me that it was essentially a job until</u>
<u n="708" who="S0058">until you talked to</u>
<u n="709" who="S0179">right yeah until</u>
<u n="710" who="S0058">well that's good I mean <pause dur="short"/> I'm glad you had the opportunity to do that and revaluate your choices <pause dur="short"/> it's always nice</u>
<u n="711" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> anyway shall we eh call it a day</u>
<u n="712" who="S0058">yes</u>
</body>
</text>
