<text id="SL46">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:11:57</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-24</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0261 S0262</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's house, Cambs</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>blogs, publishing companies, books on Amazon, travel plans. </topics>
		<activity>A couple at home eating dinner together talking about how to launch an e-publications and travel plans. </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, inquiring, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0261">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British/New Zealand</nat>
				<birthplace>Wellington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>New Zealand</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/NZ</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Kiwi English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>non_uk</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>non_uk</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>non_uk</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Entrepreneur</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0262">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dorchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South of England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0262">yeah so which one do you think is going to be the best for the blog then?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="2" who="S0261">that would be this one</u>
<u n="3" who="S0262">mm <pause dur="long"/> Tumblr or the other one?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0261">well <pause dur="short"/> well Tumblr has got a bigger audience so I think that's pretty straightforward but erm <pause dur="long"/> it wouldn't hurt to publish different articles on both of them</u>
<u n="5" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="6" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0262">there's also MacMillan</u>
<u n="8" who="S0261">yeah and you can test these things</u>
<u n="9" who="S0262">mm <pause dur="long"/> Macmillan's got erm the late the the erm it has got a bit it has got a bit out of date but they did have erm some guest blogs</u>
<u n="10" who="S0261">mm mm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0262" trans="overlap">on the subject of small talk <pause dur="short"/> that's from a little while ago <pause dur="short"/> but that's okay I mean we could do that for for later</u>
<u n="12" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0262" trans="overlap">when I'm when I'm a bit more kind of into it</u>
<u n="14" who="S0261">to start with I wonder whether Macmillan Macmillan's the right type of site? <pause dur="short"/> what erm <pause dur="short"/> because it is a publisher isn't it?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0262">yeah but</u>
<u n="16" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and so do people buy books straight from their site?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0262">the guest blog is just about small talk</u>
<u n="18" who="S0261">mm mm I know that</u>
<u n="19" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0261">so you want to put it in front of an audience?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0262">and well yeah I see what you are saying so what kind of direct direct sales would you say would come from Tumblr? was it push it to Amazon? or how does it click through?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0261">well the intention would be <pause dur="short"/> push it through to Amazon</u>
<u n="23" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="24" who="S0261">erm so people read the blog click through that goes to a website</u>
<u n="25" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="26" who="S0261">which then advertises the book and site that talks about small talk</u>
<u n="27" who="S0262">yeah so it's really it's a you know</u>
<u n="28" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and then people click through from that site</u>
<u n="29" who="S0262">and you are also having to advertise on Amazon too to get people to Amazon <pause dur="short"/> to the book</u>
<u n="30" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0262" trans="overlap">which is part of the way it works</u>
<u n="32" who="S0261">yeah you don't want to be writing something and advertising <trunc>A</trunc>Amazon or a click through straight to Amazon because people won't buy it</u>
<u n="33" who="S0262">ah right so how do you do it instead?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0261">you do the click through to your website which provides extra valuable information</u>
<u n="35" who="S0262">oh so you have to have a website</u>
<u n="36" who="S0261">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0262">oh right oh</u>
<u n="38" who="S0261">so</u>
<u n="39" who="S0262">and does that mean that people can also order a erm a hard copy too <pause dur="short"/> from the website?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0261">at the moment because of the erm the arrangement with Amazon you can't you can't sell directly from your website</u>
<u n="41" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0261">yeah so if we had a different arrangement you could</u>
<u n="43" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="44" who="S0261">so <pause dur="short"/> but Amazon's obviously got a big crowd so <pause dur="short"/> erm millions and millions larger than than the crowd that we have so that that makes sense to just have it there at the moment</u>
<u n="45" who="S0262">mm</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="46" who="S0261">and you may decide down the track that you take the book off there and you sell it directly from your own website or something</u>
<u n="47" who="S0262">okay so as long as you're <pause dur="long"/> as long as you are following the Amazon <trunc>ru</trunc>rules you should be sweet</u>
<u n="48" who="S0261">yes that's it that's the thing</u>
<u n="49" who="S0262">mm mm so <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> and do they? how do it how do you learn about what they're actually proposing? is there it's kind of like a you know a quite a detailed bunch of information?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0261"><trunc>wh</trunc>who is proposing?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0262">Amazon how they <vocal desc="cough"/> how they get you to you know publish your book online and <pause dur="short"/> how do how you find out about the latest developments do they email you? or do they just expect you to sort of know it?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0261">no they have a massive resource centre behind them</u>
<u n="53" who="S0262">do they?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0262">so there's people you can even contact and say look I don't really understand how to do this bit and they would get back to you?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0261">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="57" who="S0262">oh okay</u>
<u n="58" who="S0261">mm <pause dur="short"/> they run it like erm <pause dur="long"/> like a business you know you're you're a customer of theirs</u>
<u n="59" who="S0262">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0261">and they are selling you the idea that you can publish your stuff on this site</u>
<u n="61" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0261">and sell your products through them or whatever yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0261">so the other day I was listening to a podcast where this guy was saying how erm <pause dur="short"/> he had asked a question about he had a family business he had been running it for they had been running it for many years they manufactured products and they sell them from a store <pause dur="short"/> erm and that Amazon had directly contacted them and <pause dur="short"/> asked them do they want to sell their products on Amazon?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0262">oh right</u>
<u n="66" who="S0261">so this guy was seeking advice</u>
<u n="67" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0261">about <pause dur="short"/> bearing in mind Amazon has a large a lot larger customer base</u>
<u n="69" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0261">should should they do this? should they be erm they don't have to worry about the hassle they basically supply Amazon with the product and Amazon does all of the <pause dur="short"/> selling and shipping</u>
<u n="71" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="73" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0261">so the feedback to this guy was well <pause dur="short"/> erm hey look man <trunc>you</trunc>you've got <pause dur="short"/> your own existing customer base if you then go and sell your products on Amazon your own personal customer base is moving to Amazon so it becomes Amazon's customers they are no longer your customers</u>
<u n="75" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0261" trans="overlap">so then what control do you then have? yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0261">so as good a deal as it might be it takes a lot of the hassle out of the business and all that kind of thing the major part of it is that Amazon end up with your customers</u>
<u n="79" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0261">so that that isn't a great idea you know</u>
<u n="81" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="82" who="S0261">now there might be another situation where you as a <pause dur="short"/> as a company are selling your products via Amazon yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0261">and then Amazon pitches to you well <pause dur="short"/> we'll do all of that fulfilment stuff just leave it up to us and so <pause dur="short"/> there was a discussion behind that that kind of point of view as well and you could apply that first kind of reason</u>
<u n="85" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0261" trans="overlap">with your customers but in fact they're not your customers they are Amazon's customers who happen to buy your products that you're providing through Amazon's platform store</u>
<u n="87" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0261">so <pause dur="short"/> that in itself could be seen as a as a benefit unless you were the type of business person who would actively try to chase Amazon's customers having bought your products because once they've bought them you have got some of the details</u>
<u n="89" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and that you would then <pause dur="short"/> be seeking to provide them with some kind of customer follow up <pause dur="short"/> based on you know you have bought my product here are some other products that you might like and that kind of stuff yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0261" trans="overlap">now if they're Amazon's customers Amazon has that data you will only have that if you have got to ship stuff to them if you don't ship stuff to them then how do you get hold of that data?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0262">mm I see <pause dur="long"/> what do you think of the curry?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0261">yeah it is good <pause dur="long"/> reliably spicy</u>
<u n="95" who="S0262">mm <pause dur="long"/> so <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> so you who are you expecting tonight then?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0261">well tonight we are having a chat about that <anon type="place"/> event</u>
<u n="97" who="S0262">oh yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0261">erm <pause dur="short"/> travelling to <anon type="place"/> just to try and set an agenda for it</u>
<u n="99" who="S0262">yep</u>
<u n="100" who="S0261">for for for the weekend</u>
<u n="101" who="S0262">mm mm so who do you think will be hanging out?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0261">well there's a couple of people who have been involved in setting it up so they're there</u>
<u n="103" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0261">I haven't really checked out who else has kind of put their hand up to say they would be going along</u>
<u n="105" who="S0262">oh right</u>
<u n="106" who="S0261">like going along to this hang out tonight</u>
<u n="107" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh right okay but there's more</u>
<u n="108" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah and then there's erm over twenty people who have <unclear/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0262">and how long do you think you will go for?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0261">well I've I had a look at kind of return flights and Sunday Monday are very expensive so I was thinking about popping back on Tuesday</u>
<u n="111" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0261">but erm I got in touch with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he's just got some skinny flat so he doesn't have any room</u>
<u n="113" who="S0262">oh</u>
<u n="114" who="S0261" trans="overlap">for me to stay so I am going to share a place with some of the people for the Thursday Friday and Saturday <pause dur="short"/> and then I have got to find somewhere to stay for Sunday and Monday</u>
<u n="115" who="S0262">oh god</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="116" who="S0261">I'm kind of surprised there's only like one person based in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0261">and he's in this group and then well there's one person in the group that's placed in <anon type="place"/> and then there's this other guy and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> of course erm <pause dur="short"/> that certainly made me think well <pause dur="short"/> if we put it out on the wire who would be based there?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0262">mm <pause dur="short"/> well I know what you mean it's a shame that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't have enough space <pause dur="long"/> so be it</u>
<u n="120" who="S0261">yes <pause dur="short"/> so be it <pause dur="short"/> so how do you</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
