<text id="SL76">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:32:08</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-02-26</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0058 S0179</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's car</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Parks, travelling, friends, unpaid internships, unemployment, renewable energy, careers services, work, animal rights, Yorkshire, giving directions</topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T04</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0058">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Corpus Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0179">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harpenden, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years, 7 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Consultant engineer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0179">so that's the er the start of it <pause dur="short"/> it's very erm that section's very enclosed</u>
<u n="2" who="S0058">yeah well the the the whole park's in a big dip</u>
<u n="3" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0058">so</u>
<u n="5" who="S0179">well no but I suppose the whole bit of it's called <anon type="place"/> is</u>
<u n="6" who="S0058">mm yeah fair enough <pause dur="short"/> but yeah it's erm it's got a large feel to it <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> it's quite nice in a way but it's also slightly odd</u>
<u n="7" who="S0179"><unclear/> to it</u>
<u n="8" who="S0058">erm oh tunes <pause dur="short"/> and it's just the feel of the main <anon type="place"/> is is my dad's right it's slightly odd it's not nowhere near as nice as <anon type="place"/> so it's like erm <pause dur="short"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0179">you need to keep your head back for this bit here?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="10" who="S0179">what were you saying?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0058">er hang on what did you just say? <unclear/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0179">just one disk free</u>
<u n="13" who="S0058">mm mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0179">yes still disk one</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="15" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0058">or what you've done before <unclear/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0179">I'll be very smart</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="18" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="19" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="20" who="S0058">yeah like I said erm so <anon type="place"/> is a very modern style of doing parks as as <unclear/> like it's it's all sort of done to look slightly natural but with plastic in it <pause dur="short"/> easy accessible nature whereas <anon type="place"/> is very much a Victorian don't you think? <trunc>V</trunc> very Victorian style of park</u>
<u n="21" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="22" who="S0058">sort of little walks and little hills and a little pond and it's it's it's yeah definitely <pause dur="short"/> oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="24" who="S0058">erm okay so yeah <pause dur="short"/> thank you very much for bringing me I think it's been a really good visit</u>
<u n="25" who="S0179">yeah I like that <unclear/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0058">yeah well I I think my parents have been the ones that's made the difference today ironically of course</u>
<u n="27" who="S0179"><anon type="place"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0058">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I didn't realise quite how stressed about everything</u>
<u n="29" who="S0179">yeah I've become quite used to all of this</u>
<u n="30" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm sort of used I think they're maybe more well I think they think I'll be more bothered by the fact he's a bit confused but just from the you know the</u>
<u n="31" who="S0179">well it's a not bad confused</u>
<u n="32" who="S0058">exactly yeah <trunc>a</trunc> and I think he's doing quite well and if if he asks me the same question twice I just answer it twice it's not  it's not  a big deal</u>
<u n="33" who="S0179">yeah less than five times is good</u>
<u n="34" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah erm I mean my gran said as well that he was pleased to see us so like I said if you sort of if that's one thing in his head that's a good thing and it's in his head is a a really nice good thing and he's reminded of it then that's that's fine <pause dur="short"/> but yeah I think er</u>
<u n="35" who="S0179">because if he used to know cars <unclear/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0058">yeah the band can go in it yeah <pause dur="short"/> if the balloon goes in that odd thing because it's the the back windows are blacked out it can go in there</u>
<u n="37" who="S0179">well no <unclear/> any car</u>
<u n="38" who="S0058">oh yeah yeah fair enough</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="39" who="S0058">but yeah erm thanks for doing the driving <unclear/> I think it's been really worth coming even though we didn't see him very much</u>
<u n="40" who="S0179">well I think it's er the gesture's important</u>
<u n="41" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="42" who="S0058">you can see up on the side there where all the cars have gone up on the edge to get around into that lane</u>
<u n="43" who="S0179">superb</u>
<u n="44" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="45" who="S0179"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0058">it's funny in there isn't it?</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="47" who="S0179">that really annoys me</u>
<u n="48" who="S0058">what?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0179">we all pay road tax</u>
<u n="50" who="S0058">oh right yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it's stupid I mean</u>
<u n="51" who="S0179">it doesn't help the car traffic flow at all and I'd just like to know what other vehicles</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="52" who="S0058">I mean sort of bus names yes <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure yes I mean</u>
<u n="53" who="S0179">possibly but I think it's literally just taxis <unclear/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0179">I think that's slightly offensive</u>
<u n="56" who="S0058">well because yeah if you own a taxi</u>
<u n="57" who="S0179">and it's a car</u>
<u n="58" who="S0058">that's yeah <pause dur="short"/> you can use it as a car though</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="59" who="S0179">oh I see what you mean</u>
<u n="60" who="S0058">so you could just be driving in your taxi so like erm you know I've I've got  I've got  friends whose dads are taxi drivers and you know driving us about in them and you know that's a taxi <pause dur="short"/> I was going</u>
<u n="61" who="S0179">the <unclear/> hill's over there</u>
<u n="62" who="S0058">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I always feel like there's like I've forgotten something <pause dur="short"/> probably not</u>
<u n="63" who="S0179"><unclear/> my glasses</u>
<u n="64" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> I've got <unclear/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0058">shit I've forgotten my house keys</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="69" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's handy having my old house keys on as well it's just you don't need to remember to bring anything different when you're</u>
<u n="70" who="S0179">how you can <unclear/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0058" trans="overlap">I've I've still got them on the same key ring yeah <pause dur="short"/> well cos they were on originally and I just put the new ones on but actually it's it's quite handy having them</u>
<u n="72" who="S0179">oh you see I've got a whole set on my keying <unclear/> in my pocket</u>
<u n="73" who="S0058">yeah I'd say I don't have them in sort of trouser pockets so it's not so bad <pause dur="short"/> oh actually <unclear/> car just went past then</u>
<u n="74" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0058">yeah it was silver but it was covered up with duct tape</u>
<u n="76" who="S0179">oh right</u>
<u n="77" who="S0058">so it kind of completed the colour but it looks sort of wiggly and wrong</u>
<u n="78" who="S0179"><unclear/> duct tape</u>
<u n="79" who="S0058">mm yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="80" who="S0058">I got a text from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this morning apologising for the texts</u>
<u n="81" who="S0179">yeah apologise and those were the texts we wanted to see <pause dur="short"/> did he do anything?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="83" who="S0179">of course not <pause dur="short"/> it's a good opportunity</u>
<u n="84" who="S0058">well it was</u>
<u n="85" who="S0179">and you shouldn't go out with someone in your team</u>
<u n="86" who="S0058">no well</u>
<u n="87" who="S0179">that's just leads to <unclear/> saying you shouldn't but not casually anyway that could lead to all sorts of problems</u>
<u n="88" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think erm yeah er yeah he said what to do and I said well ask her to dance so I think it was the ceilidh erm I said ask her to dance and he said he did but it wasn't taken in a romantic way <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="89" who="S0179">how does he know?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0058">presumably yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0179">ooh hang on</u>
<u n="92" who="S0058">oh yes <trunc>so</trunc> sorry I should have er</u>
<u n="93" who="S0179">no it was just instinct <unclear/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0058" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0179">force of habit</u>
<u n="96" who="S0058">oh a coach for London</u>
<u n="97" who="S0179">cool <pause dur="short"/> I bet that takes a while</u>
<u n="98" who="S0058">I'm sure I've looked into this because I was looking for you know when I was sort of coming down to see you a lot?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0058">and it's not that cheap to get from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> and I was looking for sort of cheaper ways of doing it erm and I looked into coaches <pause dur="short"/> but the problem was it was something like eight and a half hours but that's cos it stopped for three hours in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0179">well we could have come and got you from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it wasn't that cheap actually <pause dur="short"/> if you book it a long way in advance it is a lot cheaper but if you're booking it erm sort of you know at at the you know kind of very short notice it wasn't that much cheaper than the train <pause dur="short"/> and I thought well it's easier for everyone and I may as well pay the extra ten quid you know it really wasn't any cheaper</u>
<u n="103" who="S0179">yeah well it'd cost <unclear/> anyway</u>
<u n="104" who="S0058">exactly that's what I thought <pause dur="short"/> erm whereas if you book it a long time in advance then yeah it would have been cheaper but I thought it would save the effort you know? Well in other words <unclear/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0179">what were you saying?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0058">erm yeah one of the nicest ways to do it is to get the Sunderland to London train so that's a really nice train <pause dur="short"/> erm it's quite fast as well</u>
<u n="109" who="S0179">and then come out again?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0058">and then come out of London yeah <pause dur="short"/> but and that has the advantage that it's a fixed price so if you're booking in advance don't do that because it's quite expensive <pause dur="short"/> if you've booking on the day you can literally get on the train and buy a ticket on the train and it's not horrendous <trunc>bec</trunc> you know because we did that one time and we got we bought out tickets on the day and it was horrendously expensive</u>
<u n="111" who="S0179">who's we?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0058">Us two <pause dur="short"/> we erm we were coming down from</u>
<u n="113" who="S0179">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0058">what what was the situation? We we were getting a?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0179">Holiday</u>
<u n="116" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0179">which is <unclear/> we had to go back to get the other car</u>
<u n="118" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh right yeah we had to go down yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="119" who="S0058">and that was ridiculously expensive getting them on the day but yeah so this particular Sunderland train you can get on the train and buy it on the train which is also a key to sort of urgently <pause dur="short"/> but it's still gonna be like sixty quid which is really good and it may be more than that now but yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0179">of course what we could have done on that day is go through to Sunderland and get the train</u>
<u n="121" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0179">but then of course you actually wanted to get off at <anon type="place"/> </u>
<u n="123" who="S0058">I was gonna say that that doesn't stop after York so it would have been sort of Newcastle Sunderland Sunderland to London London to <unclear/> which would have been a pain</u>
<u n="124" who="S0179">I see</u>
<u n="125" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I miss the sea</u>
<u n="126" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0058"><unclear/> We'll get to see it next time we'll do this <pause dur="short"/> next time we'll do that</u>
<u n="128" who="S0179">what like yesterday you mean?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0058">well no it's just sort of today we've been saying you know erm I'll have to go to <anon type="place"/> next time and we'll have to what was it? It was something else we said as well <pause dur="short"/> yeah we'll have to go down to the seafront next time</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="130" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0058">mm</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="132" who="S0058">yeah erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sounded really pleased that we were going I think he's looking forward to seeing us which is nice <pause dur="short"/> maybe he feels a bit out on a limb</u>
<u n="133" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0058">and of course he doesn't have any money so travelling up around <unclear/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0179" trans="overlap">is his job paid well?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0058">he's paid I think it is a job but erm I feel very certain it's not paying him an awful lot</u>
<u n="137" who="S0179">well no it's almost a certainty</u>
<u n="138" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well he's probably minimum wage but having said that I don't know if he's paying very he won't be paying very much rent or you know that kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> he he might be <trunc>con</trunc> contributing because it's his family <pause dur="short"/> it's it's not like he's gonna be paying commercial rent so it's not going be quite as bad as <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was</u>
<u n="139" who="S0179">no <pause dur="short"/> who seems to be doing okay in her new situation</u>
<u n="140" who="S0058">yeah well she's actually staying at erm <unclear/> and she was saying when she was you know when she was looking for jobs the first time around straight out of uni?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0179"><unclear/> initially worked out very badly</u>
<u n="142" who="S0058">yeah it wasn't really</u>
<u n="143" who="S0179">I don't know if you realised that?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I did because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was also talking to Simon on the <pause dur="short"/> simon <pause dur="short"/> no I realised that</u>
<u n="145" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0179">erm I did actually end up just getting into that conversation</u>
<u n="148" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0179">erm but <unclear/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0179">er and you <unclear/> to me</u>
<u n="152" who="S0058">well I'd gone out and I I'd been moved down one I think</u>
<u n="153" who="S0179">yes but for whatever reason</u>
<u n="154" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0058">yeah sorry it didn't work out necessarily very well for you</u>
<u n="157" who="S0179">no you just didn't spend <unclear/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0058">sorry <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0179">it <unclear/> initially</u>
<u n="160" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0058">erm what was I going to say? Yes erm so I thought <pause dur="short"/> so anyway she was saying when when she was first applying for jobs and there was one erm in Hull which she went for the interview and everything and she the feedback was basically we'd really really like you but and we'd love to give you the job but unfortunately you just don't have any experience <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0058">but <pause dur="short"/> well exactly</u>
<u n="165" who="S0179"><unclear/> give me something</u>
<u n="166" who="S0058">well apparently there was somebody else they realised who had experience and it wasn't that they didn't like her it was just you know couldn't just <unclear/> with her <pause dur="short"/> but and so anyway but she's this job</u>
<u n="167" who="S0179">this is in Hull?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0058">has come up <pause dur="short"/> in Hull yeah <pause dur="short"/> but this job has come up again and erm she rang the woman and who'd you know had given her this feedback and said right <pause dur="short"/> so if I apply for this job I've now got a year and whatever how many months of experience in this industry</u>
<u n="169" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0058">what are my chances? And the woman said well I'm actually leaving before the interviews happen but I will be erm passing on my er my recommendation and my kind of my my thoughts to all <trunc>do</trunc> doing the interviews <pause dur="short"/> erm you know and just say that I think you'd be an excellent choice</u>
<u n="171" who="S0179">that's cool</u>
<u n="172" who="S0058">well it is cool</u>
<u n="173" who="S0179">so obviously not <unclear/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0058">yeah they've taken the top off <pause dur="short"/> that's really good</u>
<u n="175" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0058">yeah <unclear/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> sort of windmill <trunc>s</trunc> shape as well <pause dur="short"/> that's really cool</u>
<u n="177" who="S0179">so anyway so this <unclear/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0058" trans="overlap">so anyway yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I think she yeah erm I mean I didn't know how keen she was in this one at Basingstoke which presumably she's more keen on the one in Hull</u>
<u n="179" who="S0179">well what is her job?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0058">I think it's very similar but probably slightly better paid erm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0179">so so yeah so</u>
<u n="182" who="S0058">so so I think it's marketing yeah <pause dur="short"/> so a similar sort of thing I think just promotions erm and that sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> I'm really pleased that she's managed to make inroads into it because it could have been a bit of nightmare</u>
<u n="183" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0058">but she's yeah I think a lot of people like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well seems to be making inroads into theatre which is impossible so I think he's doing really well</u>
<u n="185" who="S0179"><unclear/> starting places?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0179">so <unclear/> difficult</u>
<u n="188" who="S0058">it's difficult yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0179"><unclear/> middle-class basis thing as in he does have <unclear/> family which supports him while he does it</u>
<u n="190" who="S0058">yeah yeah sure <pause dur="short"/> yeah he's abled to kind of not earn very much and he can't yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0179">looking <unclear/> because he's found <unclear/> Yeah but his parents have worked hard to give him a <trunc>ch</trunc> a chance</u>
<u n="192" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0179">and that's how life works <unclear/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah I mean there's only so much you can <pause dur="short"/> I mean I I do think it's unfair to because the whole thing about internships in erm was it in government where it was like six months unpaid internships in Central London? So the only way you could do it was if you had parents who</u>
<u n="195" who="S0179">no but that should just be <unclear/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0058" trans="overlap">well no exactly</u>
<u n="197" who="S0179">I think they should be well you can't have work experience over two weeks unpaid</u>
<u n="198" who="S0058">well that's what erm this whole hoo-ha is about with erm because of David David Cameron's work experience scheme <pause dur="short"/> was it Tesco's</u>
<u n="199" who="S0179">oh yes</u>
<u n="200" who="S0058">pulled out because it was saying we can't take slave labour we can't not pay people to work for us</u>
<u n="201" who="S0179">well because it was only like twenty-five thirty hours a week wasn't it?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah but it was for quite a long time wasn't it?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0179">the idea was <unclear/> employment benefit</u>
<u n="204" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm but they were basically saying we can't accept this work I think is what they were saying <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah but I think the point was they had to do this work in order to get their benefits which kind of makes sense because it's giving it's helping them essentially you know? But it I think they were saying they were expecting to sort of work as in like staff</u>
<u n="205" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/> well two things <pause dur="short"/> firstly I <unclear/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="207" who="S0179">people most of who <unclear/> Secondly <pause dur="short"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="208" who="S0058">mm?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0179">there's Bentley that just went past behind us <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="210" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> I think fifty-eight it was fifty-eighth birthday</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="212" who="S0058">but anyway yeah erm yeah I mean I don't kind of know how I feel about that because to a certain extent</u>
<u n="213" who="S0179">you've got sort of</u>
<u n="214" who="S0058">making them <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean as you say making them go to work would really help them because that'll help them back into employment in a way that so many other things won't <pause dur="short"/> but also yeah there's I mean there's <unclear/> that have they're they're you know why would you?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0179" trans="overlap">oh dear Lord</u>
<u n="216" who="S0058">mm?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0179"><unclear/> behind us erm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0058" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="219" who="S0179"><unclear/> stop</u>
<u n="220" who="S0058">yeah sorry <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah the the work experience thing erm yeah <unclear/> But I think</u>
<u n="221" who="S0179">but the purpose <unclear/> annoying me about that <unclear/> a caveat which says that <unclear/> placements before it's completed they forfeit benefits <unclear/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="223" who="S0179">which <unclear/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0179">they could be really really badly treated</u>
<u n="226" who="S0058">yeah because</u>
<u n="227" who="S0179">you know to have a family emergency <unclear/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm I mean that's yeah that's <pause dur="short"/> it seems a bit you can see what they're trying to do with it but there's so many people just wouldn't bother and they'd just drop out of it and you need to have some kind of reason for finishing I <pause dur="short"/>E <pause dur="short"/> cos they won't get any benefits personally <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="229" who="S0179">but you can't <unclear/> small</u>
<u n="230" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0179">minority to</u>
<u n="232" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0179">to effectively do the majority that's not <unclear/> work</u>
<u n="234" who="S0058">yeah exactly I mean you should have the right to leave employment</u>
<u n="235" who="S0179">without</u>
<u n="236" who="S0058" trans="overlap">even if yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="239" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0179"><unclear/> change</u>
<u n="241" who="S0058">yeah lovely <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think they might have to er rethink it all <pause dur="short"/> but I mean it it's hard to know how easy most people find it because I thought it was actually quite a bit you had to do to get it but I mean maybe that's because I was</u>
<u n="242" who="S0179">you need to do an activity <unclear/> and another activity erm <unclear/> erm looked at a jobs website</u>
<u n="243" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> whereas I was writing down sort of you know you had to do four things or whatever so I was writing down erm August yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0179">why do people see work <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0058">they're lovely aren't they? They're so elegant I think they look great</u>
<u n="246" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0058">yeah I mean that's ugly there isn't it?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0179">yeah <unclear/> when did you last see a coal fire power station?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0058">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> if you want <unclear/> And they don't <unclear/> do they?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0058">I was gonna say <unclear/> kind of it's a bit of a <unclear/></u>
<u n="252" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/> documentary made apparently <unclear/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0179">released in the cinemas about it which community <unclear/> where <unclear/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="256" who="S0179">and they were saying like or like <unclear/> but it's driving me insane</u>
<u n="257" who="S0058">well no you were being you were kind of</u>
<u n="258" who="S0179">well basically they're saying <unclear/> vibration and like <unclear/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="260" who="S0179">the shadow from the window or whatever <pause dur="short"/> and <unclear/> people <unclear/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0179">or to er you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="263" who="S0058">yeah well exactly <unclear/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0058">yeah under an airline under a flight path</u>
<u n="266" who="S0179">you know it's not maybe worth it</u>
<u n="267" who="S0058">obviously <unclear/> you have to build them to be considerate to people you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0058">yeah exactly and still be a part of the <unclear/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0179"><unclear/> we don't you here</u>
<u n="271" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="272" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0058">yeah where where are you planning on getting your power from? And for <trunc>com</trunc> companies to get <unclear/> to make all the things that you like and use you know <unclear/> I mean there seems to be plenty of it the natural thing <unclear/> let's use it</u>
<u n="274" who="S0179">cool</u>
<u n="275" who="S0058"><unclear/> Yeah erm I was listening to a recording of some students and their project was to get a erm like a tidal turbine but it fixed onto an existing erm wind turbine out at sea</u>
<u n="276" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0058">erm which is quite a neat sort of as in if you're gonna have all the instructions about <unclear/> you can sort of build in a tidal thing so</u>
<u n="278" who="S0179">yes er it's probably not tidal it's wave</u>
<u n="279" who="S0058" trans="overlap">oh sorry yeah sorry wave yeah <pause dur="short"/> I forget <unclear/> Erm but <unclear/> that one that people really are talking about the erm footballers Alan Shearer <pause dur="short"/> erm oh we were sorry you weren't there <pause dur="short"/> sorry no erm <unclear/> a bit of er the area where footballers live Shearer lives anyway</u>
<u n="280" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0058">yeah Shearer lives in <unclear/> Park</u>
<u n="282" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0058">yeah yeah but it's sort of the same idea look very posh</u>
<u n="286" who="S0179">that's probably where that Bentley was going to</u>
<u n="287" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0058">yeah that's alright</u>
<u n="290" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0058">why do they have country roads just cheaper?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0179">I'm not sure</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="293" who="S0058">sorry?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I mean</u>
<u n="296" who="S0179">it was a huge mistake <unclear/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0058">yeah I mean a lot of people who were it depends <unclear/> most likely to need it in the sense that they don't have any work experience on their CV <pause dur="short"/> the sort of the fifty plus who are finding it hard to get into work they have got often obviously very good experience it's the age that's the <pause dur="short"/> all of them worked all their life in one area and don't have any sort of different things so yes they could work but I just think that that would be a more useful thing for the younger people to do whereas the older people might need help with CV writing and applying for jobs where to look for jobs and stuff <pause dur="short"/> you know the kind of things that have moved on since they may be <trunc>s</trunc> starting and in the one company twenty-five years ago</u>
<u n="298" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0058">I mean that must be awful if you've sort of worked all your life done all this occupation the company's gone bust and now you can't get a job because of everyone <trunc>y</trunc> you just older and people don't want to take you on <pause dur="short"/> or you've done something very specific for a long time and people don't <pause dur="short"/> yeah it must be very hard <pause dur="short"/> I guess retraining and stuff if you can</u>
<u n="300" who="S0179">actually <unclear/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="302" who="S0058">yeah I mean I'd say it's more useful than I mean so what if I hadn't erm got that job when I did I'd be I would have been on benefits long enough to have to go and do like erm erm is it a session thing? <unclear/> and I think it was a sort of erm yeah helping you get back into work sort of session <pause dur="short"/> helping you get into work whatever erm</u>
<u n="303" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0058">yeah I mean I'm not sure firstly that was no help to me and it wasted my time <pause dur="short"/> and secondly just to give someone a lesson people who haven't necessarily excelled at accepting information in a school setting</u>
<u n="305" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0058">it's stupid <pause dur="short"/> I I kind of feel like giving them placements is more useful and maybe <unclear/> doing and enjoy doing it</u>
<u n="307" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Cambridge University <unclear/> service <unclear/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0058">yeah I'd basically say they they sort of you know they mentioned as well and it's like well you know <pause dur="short"/> oh no that was it I'd got the job but I wasn't starting it erm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0058">so from yeah and they were like well if you want to receive benefits for that time or whatever you've got to go along <pause dur="short"/> but I it was some for some I think what they managed to do was I said well I can't do this session because of x so can I get booked on to the next session?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0058">yes which was after</u>
<u n="313" who="S0179">after</u>
<u n="314" who="S0058">which was after  when I started the job which is how I got around it <pause dur="short"/> and they certainly knew what I was doing but yes I basically said look I've got this job <unclear/> you know I'm not lying I'm not just messing about and they believed me <pause dur="short"/> I think I looked different to a lot of the people in there</u>
<u n="315" who="S0179"><unclear/> transporter bridge</u>
<u n="316" who="S0058">yeah and then there's a funny-shaped <unclear/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0179"><unclear/> bridge is in the er what do you call it?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0058">the transporter bridge?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0179">yeah it's in er?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0058" trans="overlap">it's in Auf Wiedersehen Pet isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> it's in Billy Elliot as well <pause dur="short"/> have you seen that film?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="322" who="S0058">you might actually like it <pause dur="short"/> it's not it's and you know it it's it's kind of about dancing but there isn't that isn't really the the point of it it's about sort of</u>
<u n="323" who="S0179">it's about dancing all about dancing</u>
<u n="324" who="S0058" trans="overlap">about dancing yeah erm but it's yeah it's it's funny and it's it's got a lot of really good erm good scenes in it and it I think you might enjoy it <unclear/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0058">picturesque</u>
<u n="327" who="S0179">not usually</u>
<u n="328" who="S0058">you're not  you're not  a massive <unclear/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0179">as in I've seen more picturesque places in my time</u>
<u n="330" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> the biggest thing <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm sure the energy N R G</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="331" who="S0058">because Durham has a campus in Teesside you know? Durham University</u>
<u n="332" who="S0179">why?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0058">has a</u>
<u n="334" who="S0179" trans="overlap">I didn't know that</u>
<u n="335" who="S0058">I think it's Stockton <unclear/> there's certain courses are taught here it's really weird <pause dur="short"/> and I think sort of the slightly more vocational ones</u>
<u n="336" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0058">mm that's that's the point I think Durham's got to teach them but on a sort of separate bit so you're not part of the kind of college system</u>
<u n="338" who="S0179">yeah so it's not a problem</u>
<u n="339" who="S0058" trans="overlap">so it's not <pause dur="short"/> no exactly <pause dur="short"/> it's slightly weird</u>
<u n="340" who="S0179">that is weird</u>
<u n="341" who="S0058" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> so I think yeah so there's I think erm I know somebody that did sports science at Durham but it was in Teesside <pause dur="short"/> you see you don't really win in that regard <pause dur="short"/> but Teesside Uni is sort of relatively popular with people but not for you know if if you're gonna go to Teesside you may as well go to Sunderland kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> if you're from Sunderland I mean</u>
<u n="342" who="S0179">yeah where's Teesside again?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0058">teesside is kind of this area and I don't know where the actual uni is it's just called Teesside Uni</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="344" who="S0058"><unclear/> we know it well <pause dur="short"/> and I did feel sorry when I did that erm that thing at <anon type="place"/> with the careers event I felt really sorry for some of the kids <pause dur="short"/> erm you know and just it must be hard to to get going when you're worrying about the kids <pause dur="short"/> I mean there was some of them who weren't interested but some of them you just thought ah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I really hope it works out you know? Well it's twenty-one to Thirsk which is where we come off</u>
<u n="345" who="S0179">why would you go if you weren't interested?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0058">well I don't know just some of it was  it was  hard to yeah they were quite enthusiastic <pause dur="short"/> I mean I think they've probably just gone along because it was an event at <anon type="place"/> you know? I guess it's a step in the right direction going to a careers event <pause dur="short"/> erm but it was quite sad you know for for both sides it was sad because people who you knew really wanted to work and this thing had happened to them and they sort of you know in the middle of it <pause dur="short"/> and as well it's sad for the ones who just I felt sorry for how they were gonna bring their kids up</u>
<u n="347" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know it was like a lot of the problems with erm I think it's very it must be very embittering to work in that sort of area so er work in an unemployment centre</u>
<u n="348" who="S0058">yes very</u>
<u n="349" who="S0179">but that means when it's not it doesn't provide a very good service to people like you</u>
<u n="350" who="S0058">no I know exactly and I imagine most of your time is spent with people who aren't interested in working <pause dur="short"/> so then yeah for me who really really was doing everything I and saying yeah possibly could to get any job as soon as possible <pause dur="short"/> yeah it it wasn't they weren't helpful and and you know but I <trunc>w</trunc> I was able to look for help in other places and I knew where to look and I got it you know?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0179">well a bit of service</u>
<u n="352" who="S0058">well Sunderland careers service is actually really helpful erm they felt like they had less of a erm a kind of a <trunc>s</trunc> a party line</u>
<u n="353" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> well that's the problem with <unclear/> many times but <unclear/> they don't have a very difficult job</u>
<u n="354" who="S0058">no they don't</u>
<u n="355" who="S0179">therefore <unclear/> justifying their existence</u>
<u n="356" who="S0058">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="357" who="S0179">and that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="358" who="S0058">yeah they have a very strong party line about what's what's what they recommend for CVs and stuff whereas the Sunderland one felt a lot more flexible erm and they <trunc>ta</trunc> they listened to what I was saying and sort of said well we can help you with this and just were a lot more open basically <pause dur="short"/> the the Cambridge one wasn't very open but I guess that's because I was a very very standard case for them <pause dur="short"/> english two one looking for sort of jobs you know? Erm not really standing</u>
<u n="359" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0058">yeah they weren't helpful with that at all which like I mean you know whereas the Sunderland one would just I think they were helpful where I wanted them to be helpful which was great which when I went with sort of interviewing practice and just sort of saying oh I'll need to get over this final hurdle <pause dur="short"/> you know I'd I'd been to all these interviews and haven't got the jobs can you help me to erm</u>
<u n="361" who="S0179"><unclear/> the interview skills so much as <unclear/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0058" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="363" who="S0179">as it was just erm the experience that you</u>
<u n="364" who="S0058">I think it was confidence which they helped me with to <unclear/> They sort of yeah took me erm just yeah took me through some of the questions and helped me think about a little bit more and and helped me to be more confident in my answers maybe and say I can do this you know which was was good <pause dur="short"/> and you know just they were just a lot nicer about the whole thing to be honest <pause dur="short"/> erm but it was the reason I got on to them was because erm my dad worked with somebody whose partner was one of the staff there</u>
<u n="365" who="S0179">I still can't understand why they helped you <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0058">er because I was a student from the area or sorry a graduate from Wearside <pause dur="short"/> they help <trunc>the</trunc> they they help they work slightly differently in that they <pause dur="short"/> yeah I I was  I was  living in Sunderland where I was from Sunderland and I had a degree and was looking for jobs so they were fine to</u>
<u n="367" who="S0179">that's weird</u>
<u n="368" who="S0058">it's very weird yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I don't think they bent the rules at all either I explained the full situation you know?</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="369" who="S0058">it was quite weird actually erm when I was looking to put erm job adverts up recently erm I was I went on the careers website to have a look at the format and stuff and all my old searches were still saved</u>
<u n="370" who="S0179">job adverts</u>
<u n="371" who="S0058">so the job for recorders</u>
<u n="372" who="S0179">oh right</u>
<u n="373" who="S0058">erm we were gonna stick it on there and see if any students were interested so erm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0179">only Cambridge <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0058">yeah or any other university yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I erm you know I logged in to to have a look at the format and sort of erm see what kind of information we needed to put up what <unclear/> Erm and you can't see the adverts unless you log in <pause dur="short"/> so yeah so I logged in and it was my old account and it had all the old searches and all the old jobs that I applied for that was still saved</u>
<u n="376" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0058">which was very weird <pause dur="short"/> and sort of and then be looking at it from the other side as well</u>
<u n="378" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0058">it's weird</u>
<u n="380" who="S0179">I can imagine</u>
<u n="381" who="S0058">I was registered with all kinds of sites and in the end it didn't really come down to that you know to find jobs on weird internet sites <pause dur="short"/> it came down to going to a company's website and looking for it and er applying <pause dur="short"/> they've got loads of erm ECM information in the er foyer to the university centre</u>
<u n="382" who="S0179"><unclear/>?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0058">yeah and I was erm that's where <unclear/> the other day and they're obviously trying to get more undergraduates interested</u>
<u n="384" who="S0179">well there's quite a lot of the engineering department actually</u>
<u n="385" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> where did you find that by the way was it listed events?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0179">I think I just Googled it</u>
<u n="387" who="S0058">is that how you found it?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0058">oh right</u>
<u n="390" who="S0179">and subsequently <unclear/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0058">right yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> remember if they'd sort of if you know if if so if you've come across them somewhere or whether you'd gone right I want <unclear/> to help me do all the work?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0179">well it it was just quite an easy way of doing it so</u>
<u n="393" who="S0058">no it was great</u>
<u n="394" who="S0179">information about <unclear/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0179">erm <unclear/> and it was but it was fantastic <unclear/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="398" who="S0179">because we don't have success figures as such because</u>
<u n="399" who="S0058">no exactly</u>
<u n="400" who="S0179"><unclear/> job that they are only gonna earn money if they place me and I</u>
<u n="401" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0179">actually attempt it <pause dur="short"/> so <unclear/> accepted</u>
<u n="403" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah there's no point in them not you know they need to look at the areas you're interested in and</u>
<u n="404" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0058">listen to you properly and stuff <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0179">so it's certainly interesting</u>
<u n="407" who="S0058">it sounds like it was a great service</u>
<u n="408" who="S0179">yeah <unclear/> and see what sort of <unclear/> interest what else would be available in the areas?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0058">now that you've now that you're in this position and what you could?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0179">maybe in a year or two <unclear/> continuously re-evaluate this one</u>
<u n="411" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0179">er I mean I think I've come to the conclusion that I don't want to I'm not going to <unclear/> reapply for post <unclear/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="414" who="S0179">erm yeah that's sort of organically happened and of course that was an option</u>
<u n="415" who="S0058">yeah yeah definitely</u>
<u n="416" who="S0179">but I'd need to be sort of applying now and I don't feel like <unclear/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0058">I mean it seems to me that you've got more to gain from this <pause dur="short"/> you know you sort of</u>
<u n="418" who="S0179">yes and the problems I have with this sort of aren't I don't think about the job in a lot of ways <unclear/> lifestyle</u>
<u n="419" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0179">but it's changed <unclear/> anyway and that's not coming back so</u>
<u n="421" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0058">exactly it wouldn't be  it wouldn't be  going back to uni as such it would be</u>
<u n="424" who="S0179">no it would be <unclear/></u>
<u n="425" who="S0058">I mean it seems to me as well that you I mean</u>
<u n="426" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/> quite dark</u>
<u n="427" who="S0058" trans="overlap">it's dim isn't it? Yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0179">sorry what were you saying?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0058">erm you know it seems to me that that the project management aspect of it which <trunc>h</trunc> you haven't really kicked off with yet</u>
<u n="430" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="431" who="S0058">it's something that you'd really enjoy so it's kind of worth sticking in and getting you know waiting until you've got some of that</u>
<u n="432" who="S0179"><unclear/> be very fascinated to see how this <unclear/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0058">yes but when when does this all happen is that six months?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0179">end of the financial year</u>
<u n="435" who="S0058">ah of course yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0179">which will be <unclear/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0058">and yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="439" who="S0058"><unclear/> But that'll be very interesting yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0179" trans="overlap">but that'll be a very interesting indicator of where <unclear/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean it sounds like they're quite happy with you to talk quite openly about them so talk openly to them about salary and promotion and stuff so see how that one goes and then you can maybe discuss it <pause dur="short"/> it sounds like that you can be quite frank <unclear/> something about your expectations and</u>
<u n="442" who="S0179">I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0058">be a woman</u>
<u n="444" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh clearly <pause dur="short"/> well done for <unclear/> It's horrible isn't it it's really coming down?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0179">well I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="447" who="S0058">the Cotswolds it's actually erm further south it's London it's sort of south of Thirsk so</u>
<u n="448" who="S0179">is it?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0058">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> so we'd have come more</u>
<u n="450" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="451" who="S0058"><unclear/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0058"><unclear/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0179">erm no I'm gonna find that very interesting <unclear/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0058">definitely yeah <pause dur="short"/> and like I say I think well I think when you've enjoyed what you've been doing I think I can't help think the best is yet to come sort of thing</u>
<u n="458" who="S0179">yeah and I think</u>
<u n="459" who="S0058" trans="overlap">A bit more interesting than what you're doing now</u>
<u n="460" who="S0179"><unclear/> I like being noisy and doing <unclear/> I look at sort of er action projects as <unclear/> I prefer working <unclear/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0179">just sort of going about <unclear/> working on strategy and stuff</u>
<u n="463" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0179">I love that</u>
<u n="465" who="S0058">exactly and I think you should stick at it until you've got some experience with that and and then see whether you want to you know which direction you want to go in <pause dur="short"/> erm but like I say that's the only but I think you've enjoyed what you've been doing but imagine that combined with you know some project management</u>
<u n="466" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="468" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="469" who="S0058">yeah it will <unclear/> Yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0179">but <unclear/> experience and learning <pause dur="short"/> again it's learning about <unclear/> stuff</u>
<u n="471" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's really good erm</u>
<u n="472" who="S0179">I am actually using <unclear/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0058">and that was what you wanted wasn't it? This like kind of intellectual</u>
<u n="474" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="475" who="S0058">having to work things out that that way which?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0058">I mean</u>
<u n="478" who="S0179"><unclear/> as in I'm still <unclear/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0058">yeah so that particular aspect of it yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0179">well I I think that possibly have <unclear/> Yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0058">oh yeah didn't you say there was something you'd worked out and somebody else hadn't been able to work out how to do it?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0179">it's difficult <unclear/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0058">no I mean that's really great <pause dur="short"/> that's the kind of thing that's gonna help you get erm get on as well</u>
<u n="488" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0058">if they feel that you're an indispensable thing you know part of the team with skills that they don't have or that you're better at those skills</u>
<u n="490" who="S0179">yeah obviously it is sort of <unclear/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="492" who="S0179"><unclear/> very good to work with <unclear/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0058">but they've yeah they always come out you mean?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0179">well possibly yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0058">people skills</u>
<u n="496" who="S0179">no just <unclear/> Yeah I mean <unclear/></u>
<u n="497" who="S0058">sort of you mean like the sort of nine to five?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0179">which is sometimes <unclear/></u>
<u n="501" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I guess it's it's sort of that transfer as well from the union <unclear/> because you were so very good at the uni planning and got so into it and you kind of got it down to a fine art <pause dur="short"/> I guess it's then hard to transfer to a to something so very different in terms of pacing?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0179">yeah I mean I liked</u>
<u n="503" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0179"><unclear/> department <unclear/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0058">yeah a very different kind of like a different kind of pace I guess</u>
<u n="506" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0058">and a lot more autonomy for individual sort of oh I feel like doing this now</u>
<u n="508" who="S0179">I mean I've still got a huge <pause dur="short"/> no I can still do that but it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0058">that's what I mean you can't just get up and say oh right I'm going for a walk <pause dur="short"/> too much</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="510" who="S0179">no but you see <unclear/> first</u>
<u n="511" who="S0058">erm yes we're not so we're not far away now <pause dur="short"/> it's erm possibly erm six miles to the town <pause dur="short"/> and it'll be the junction four first erm and we'll go through a roundabout but then we go away from Thirsk <unclear/></u>
<u n="512" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/> roundabout I trust then <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm well yeah no sorry we're gonna come off at the junction and then we hit a roundabout</u>
<u n="514" who="S0179">right so it's a slip road and do a roundabout?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="516" who="S0179">this is a really quite civilised way to go about the country <unclear/> you see more</u>
<u n="517" who="S0058">yeah it's very nice</u>
<u n="518" who="S0179">and at least driving conditions is more relaxing</u>
<u n="519" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's very pleasant <pause dur="short"/> sunday is always the er good time</u>
<u n="520" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0058">lovely green fields</u>
<u n="522" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="523" who="S0058">very English</u>
<u n="524" who="S0179">it appeared to me at some point in the near future we should <unclear/> holiday</u>
<u n="525" who="S0058"><unclear/>?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="528" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="529" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0179">but I'm planning on not taking any until this er end of year review has gone through because it looks better</u>
<u n="531" who="S0058">yeah what does that mean you can get over a hundred percent project time for it? You see there's the turn off for Castle Howard and that's Brideshead</u>
<u n="532" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="533" who="S0058">and so</u>
<u n="534" who="S0179">the World of James Herriot?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0179">how?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0058">you see we could have a day and we could go to Castle Howard and the World of James Herriot and that would be brilliant <pause dur="short"/> let's do that <pause dur="short"/> okay so this is the turn we want</u>
<u n="538" who="S0179" trans="overlap">Scarborough <pause dur="short"/> we want this turn?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0058">we want this turn yeah A61</u>
<u n="540" who="S0179">and I need warning <unclear/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0058" trans="overlap">I know sorry <pause dur="short"/> okay sorry</u>
<u n="542" who="S0179">as in we'd passed the end of the slip road when you told me about it and I need to know this was the next turn</u>
<u n="543" who="S0058">yeah sorry I</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="544" who="S0058">and going straight over this roundabout so towards</u>
<u n="545" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="546" who="S0058">oh hang on <pause dur="short"/> no sorry we're gonna go <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="547" who="S0179">so we're going left?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0058">right hang on</u>
<u n="549" who="S0179">I need to know now</u>
<u n="550" who="S0058">we're gonna go right</u>
<u n="551" who="S0179">right are you sure?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0058">right yes</u>
<u n="553" who="S0179">not</u>
<u n="554" who="S0058">not there no <pause dur="short"/> no not ah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="556" who="S0058">okay I've</u>
<u n="557" who="S0179">okay work it out quickly</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="558" who="S0058">erm</u>
<u n="559" who="S0179">we can't keep doing this you need to work it out</u>
<u n="560" who="S0058" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> okay erm yeah if you go straight over and go to Northallerton</u>
<u n="561" who="S0179">right so not towards Thirsk on the A61 and I need to go to the next exit here?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0179">right you need to get your finger out <unclear/></u>
<u n="564" who="S0058" trans="overlap">I mean we should <pause dur="short"/> yeah we should come to another roundabout where we're gonna go right</u>
<u n="565" who="S0179">right <pause dur="short"/> how far was this roundabout <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0058">oh shit no that wasn't the right junction that's why</u>
<u n="567" who="S0179">right</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="568" who="S0058">oh no erm</u>
<u n="569" who="S0179">where are we now?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0058">turnaround yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="572" who="S0058">so erm if you take the next going on the left</u>
<u n="573" who="S0179"><unclear/> this road?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="575" who="S0058">I thought that junction came out too early <unclear/> that was why I didn't give you more warning because I wasn't expecting it then</u>
<u n="576" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0058">yeah if you go back to that roundabout erm rather than go back onto the <unclear/> bring you back onto the <unclear/> you can take the second exit onto the A61 then go up to that <unclear/> back down and <unclear/> Yeah sorry about that <unclear/> Sorry about that</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="578" who="S0179">it's a pity you can't just drive south on roads like this you could actually</u>
<u n="579" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it would take you longer I think</u>
<u n="580" who="S0179"><unclear/> because that happens to be <unclear/> where we want to go to</u>
<u n="581" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah because that is <unclear/> the other way</u>
<u n="582" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> alright so we're coming up to?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0058" trans="overlap">so so we're gonna take the second exit A61</u>
<u n="584" who="S0179">yeah we don't need the <unclear/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0058">no I mean  I mean  the third exit the third yes</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="586" who="S0058">okay</u>
<u n="587" who="S0179">South Kilvington does that sound right?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0058">er yes that's right yeah so we carry on through South Kilvington erm and yeah so we're going to we're on the A61 now and we're gonna come to the roundabout that I was aiming for anyway <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah at which point we're gonna take the first exit and that should be signposted Sutton Colesly is in the A one seventy</u>
<u n="589" who="S0179">I'm not <unclear/> details</u>
<u n="590" who="S0058">okay sorry yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="591" who="S0179">so where are we coming up to?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0058">erm so erm the next thing on the map after this town erm we've got about another mile then there's a right hand junction which we don't want and then so we stay on this road until we come to the roundabout <pause dur="short"/> so erm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0179" trans="overlap">so basically we're coming to a roundabout?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0058">yeah in about a mile we're gonna come to a roundabout</u>
<u n="595" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="596" who="S0058">mm?</u>
<u n="597" who="S0179">it's Yorkshire then?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0179">what county are we in again?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0058"><unclear/></u>
<u n="601" who="S0179"><unclear/> James Herriot <pause dur="short"/> no it's not</u>
<u n="602" who="S0058">the Herriot Centre it's the home of the Herriot Centre anyway</u>
<u n="603" who="S0179">it could be the home of the author</u>
<u n="604" who="S0058">oh yeah well probably but <unclear/> the books is it? It's possibly where he was born <pause dur="short"/> birth places get <unclear/> obviously</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="605" who="S0179"><unclear/> James Herriot audience it might be</u>
<u n="606" who="S0058">probably yeah <pause dur="short"/> it isn't <unclear/></u>
<u n="607" who="S0179">right <pause dur="short"/> a useful piece of knowledge about that then the priority of <unclear/> roundabout <unclear/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0058">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="609" who="S0179">are we in the High Street?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0058">Scarborough A170</u>
<u n="611" who="S0179">right so left here?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0058" trans="overlap">get to the left here yep <pause dur="short"/> great and we're now on that road heading due east</u>
<u n="613" who="S0179">the one you wanted to be on?</u>
<u n="614" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="615" who="S0179" trans="overlap">do you want to get my iPad out?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0058">yeah I'll erm <pause dur="short"/> mind you Flaxton is on here</u>
<u n="617" who="S0179">okay well you can try just using that</u>
<u n="618" who="S0058">yeah I was gonna say yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll I'll use this and then once we're in Flaxton it seems like it should be really obvious <pause dur="short"/> yeah no I'm happy to stick with this to be honest</u>
<u n="619" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="620" who="S0058"><unclear/></u>
<u n="621" who="S0179">yes I know I said why is it <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0058">why why?</u>
<u n="623" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="624" who="S0058">mm it does seem odd that was that little bit there <pause dur="short"/> this is Sutton Bank or approaching Sutton Bank anyway</u>
<u n="625" who="S0179">right so <unclear/> navigations and tell me what's coming up?</u>
<u n="626" who="S0058">erm yeah so now there really isn't anything coming up erm we will stay on this road erm it goes through the town and then yeah then we get to Sutton Bank which is <unclear/> Erm and yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/>?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0058">steep</u>
<u n="629" who="S0179">what do you mean steep?</u>
<u n="630" who="S0058">there's a steep gradient bit that caravans aren't allowed on</u>
<u n="631" who="S0179">oh right</u>
<u n="632" who="S0058">erm</u>
<u n="633" who="S0179"><unclear/> it might be a bit more scenic if we go this way</u>
<u n="634" who="S0058">yeah yeah definitely <pause dur="short"/> but I mean erm I think my dad doesn't like Sutton Bank because it was one time we came this way in the old Polo and he was really worried we wouldn't make it up <pause dur="short"/> erm but yeah caravans aren't allowed on it erm yeah it's because they're not</u>
<u n="635" who="S0179">there's many many places caravans shouldn't go but do</u>
<u n="636" who="S0058">the roads</u>
<u n="637" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> plant pots cheap <pause dur="short"/> cheap plant pots if you're gonna put those three words on it</u>
<u n="638" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="639" who="S0179">it's a better order please</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="640" who="S0058">yeah so yeah this bit isn't very erm very exciting <unclear/></u>
<u n="641" who="S0179" trans="overlap">well there's some nice views</u>
<u n="642" who="S0058">it's lovely yeah <pause dur="short"/> but actually in terms of directions you just just stay on the road</u>
<u n="643" who="S0179">well this'll be North York Moors <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="644" who="S0058">er yes they are yeah <pause dur="short"/> north York Moors National Park</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="645" who="S0058">yeah they're not quite as <pause dur="short"/> I don't know they don't seem as threatening as the erm like the the moors that the erm Hound of the Baskervilles was on <pause dur="short"/> the Spaniel of the Baskervilles</u>
<u n="646" who="S0179">what now?</u>
<u n="647" who="S0058">the Spaniel of the Baskervilles if it was on the North York Moors</u>
<u n="648" who="S0179">Yorkshire Terrier</u>
<u n="649" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="650" who="S0179">Small but fix</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="651" who="S0179">A bit more driving around as well</u>
<u n="652" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="653" who="S0058"><unclear/> if this is Sutton under Whitestone</u>
<u n="654" who="S0179" trans="overlap">if we can find it</u>
<u n="655" who="S0058">yes</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="656" who="S0179">this is where is that?</u>
<u n="657" who="S0058">this is erm Sutton under Whitestonecliffe <pause dur="short"/> all one word</u>
<u n="658" who="S0179">brilliant</u>
<u n="659" who="S0058">maybe it's Whitestonecliffe <pause dur="short"/> it's very picturesque isn't it?</u>
<u n="660" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="661" who="S0058">lovely</u>
<u n="662" who="S0179">I'm not sure I'd want to live here?</u>
<u n="663" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> you can smell the erm real real stoves or real fires rather</u>
<u n="664" who="S0179">that's weed</u>
<u n="665" who="S0058">nice <pause dur="short"/> beaver furniture <pause dur="short"/> amazing <pause dur="short"/> can you imagine a team of workers he's got out at the back</u>
<u n="666" who="S0179">alright lads there's some nice bamboo for you <unclear/></u>
<u n="667" who="S0058">nice</u>
<u n="668" who="S0179">bizarrely if you wanted to get a lot of <trunc>ch</trunc> trees chopped down it would probably be quite a good idea to just employ a lot of beavers</u>
<u n="669" who="S0058">is it employ?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0179">well yeah just get a load of beavers</u>
<u n="671" who="S0058">get a load of beavers yeah</u>
<u n="672" who="S0179">fence them in <unclear/> probably be quite happy</u>
<u n="673" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's not cruel because they like felling trees I assume</u>
<u n="674" who="S0179">well give them something to you know <unclear/> you take like fifty percent of what they fell but you could <unclear/> food <pause dur="short"/> that seems fair</u>
<u n="675" who="S0058">mm it seems fair</u>
<u n="676" who="S0179"><unclear/> build their dams</u>
<u n="677" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="678" who="S0179"><unclear/> position of <unclear/> dolphins to give advice</u>
<u n="679" who="S0058">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how I feel about that</u>
<u n="680" who="S0179" trans="overlap">but they're they're non-human people <unclear/> I don't <unclear/> there's a difference between being cruel to them and not keep them in captivity and giving them human rights</u>
<u n="681" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0179">because they're not human but <unclear/></u>
<u n="683" who="S0058" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's the flaw</u>
<u n="684" who="S0179" trans="overlap">they might be intelligent they may even be more intelligent</u>
<u n="685" who="S0058">and yeah so don't keep them in tiny pools don't mistreat them and</u>
<u n="686" who="S0179">Don't harm them and don't</u>
<u n="687" who="S0058">don't <pause dur="short"/> exactly yeah</u>
<u n="688" who="S0179" trans="overlap">fine but I don't see why that is synonomous <unclear/> applies?</u>
<u n="689" who="S0058">you'd probably have the human right and not to be left out in the ocean you know? Cos that's not suitable for humans you know? Whereas actually</u>
<u n="690" who="S0179">and if we treat them <unclear/> that means they're accountable for actions as humans are so that means that so a human</u>
<u n="691" who="S0058">so</u>
<u n="692" who="S0179">so a dog <unclear/></u>
<u n="693" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> if they kill another animal does that make them murders?</u>
<u n="694" who="S0179">if they kill another dolphin or</u>
<u n="695" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0179">so a dolphin <unclear/> yeah exactly</u>
<u n="697" who="S0058">it doesn't really work</u>
<u n="698" who="S0179">no it doesn't work at all I hadn't thought about it before</u>
<u n="699" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="700" who="S0179">because dolphins are a dolphin is not very nice <unclear/> Well not very nice but they are quite vicious</u>
<u n="701" who="S0058" trans="overlap">well they're animals yeah that that's the point they they hunt</u>
<u n="702" who="S0179" trans="overlap">they're quite good as predators</u>
<u n="703" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> and they're clever</u>
<u n="704" who="S0179" trans="overlap">as are we</u>
<u n="705" who="S0058">and they like play but you know</u>
<u n="706" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="707" who="S0058">your favourite car</u>
<u n="708" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="709" who="S0058">that motorbike <unclear/></u>
<u n="710" who="S0179">it's not my favourite car don't you say that</u>
<u n="711" who="S0058">oh I'm only joking</u>
<u n="712" who="S0179">do you find that funny?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0058">I just like teasing you <pause dur="short"/> it's just cos I don't like it</u>
<u n="714" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="715" who="S0058">it's just cos I don't like it very much</u>
<u n="716" who="S0179" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> low gear <pause dur="short"/> no shit Sherlock</u>
<u n="717" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="718" who="S0179">is this sixty? Oh <unclear/> over there</u>
<u n="719" who="S0058">oh ho feel it on the legs <pause dur="short"/> feel the burn as they say in Body Attack</u>
<u n="720" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="721" who="S0058">yeah that's the way to do it only ever come in at the top <pause dur="short"/> yeah they've got the idea</u>
<u n="722" who="S0179">that's hilarious</u>
<u n="723" who="S0058">yeah well I was looking at the rain I was a bit like oh Sutton Bank and I thought oh there's no reason not to do it it's fine to drive</u>
<u n="724" who="S0179">it's just I've never heard of</u>
<u n="725" who="S0058"><unclear/></u>
<u n="726" who="S0179">shit <pause dur="short"/> I've never heard of this <pause dur="short"/> this is a bit special</u>
<u n="727" who="S0058" trans="overlap">I think cos we've <pause dur="short"/> this is <pause dur="short"/> maybe I should have searched Sutton Bank</u>
<u n="728" who="S0179">I've literally never heard of it</u>
<u n="729" who="S0058">yeah it was quite erm I think maybe it's because I've been spending more time in North Yorkshire you've never really done North Yorkshire whereas we've driven around here a bit <pause dur="short"/> yeah and like I said we used to drive around here in a car that my dad wasn't confident would have coped well</u>
<u n="730" who="S0179">wow</u>
<u n="731" who="S0058">nice isn't it?</u>
<u n="732" who="S0179">it's a bit unnerving actually driving uphill</u>
<u n="733" who="S0058">yeah?</u>
<u n="734" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="735" who="S0058">oh</u>
<u n="736" who="S0179">because you could slip back quite easily <pause dur="short"/> I should not be looking</u>
<u n="737" who="S0058">no</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="738" who="S0179">oh</u>
<u n="739" who="S0058">okay?</u>
<u n="740" who="S0179">yeah but</u>
<u n="741" who="S0058" trans="overlap">right at the top</u>
<u n="742" who="S0179">well that was a a good experience because it went <unclear/></u>
<u n="743" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="744" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="745" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="746" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="747" who="S0179">well if you can then er</u>
<u n="748" who="S0058">yeah fair play to you <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="749" who="S0179">well I wouldn't want to try</u>
<u n="750" who="S0058">mm not so much no</u>
<u n="751" who="S0179">I really lost out on that</u>
<u n="752" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="753" who="S0179"><unclear/> start on that</u>
<u n="754" who="S0058" trans="overlap">nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah while you're doing your driving test from the Thirsk Centre <pause dur="short"/> right Sutton Bank</u>
<u n="755" who="S0179">actually I'm very glad you know after that time in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s old car in Wales with four people in it</u>
<u n="756" who="S0058" trans="overlap">oh yes it was really struggling</u>
<u n="757" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/> trying do anything like that</u>
<u n="758" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="759" who="S0179">and we'll get out and walk</u>
<u n="760" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="761" who="S0179">see you at the top <pause dur="short"/> right so where are we coming up to now?</u>
<u n="762" who="S0058">erm so yeah so er when we get to the end of this road which is kind of</u>
<u n="763" who="S0179">so gosh was that a single gradient mark or a double gradient mark on the map?</u>
<u n="764" who="S0058">double</u>
<u n="765" who="S0179">Good <pause dur="short"/> well I was gonna say if that was a single what the fuck's a double?</u>
<u n="766" who="S0058">okay so erm yeah so when we come to the end <pause dur="short"/> this road is kind of erm the turn off for the B125 one erm it it's on the erm on the map it's kind of the erm the A170 does a sort of sharp left bend like a right hand bend so it might well be a a sort of a T-junction or a a kind of a cross like a</u>
<u n="767" who="S0179">so there's a turn off to the right</u>
<u n="768" who="S0058">to the right for the B152</u>
<u n="769" who="S0179">how far?</u>
<u n="770" who="S0058">erm in about four miles</u>
<u n="771" who="S0179">four miles okay</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="772" who="S0058">we must have a look at the erm the last bit of the <unclear/></u>
<u n="773" who="S0179">Don't miss the turning <unclear/></u>
<u n="774" who="S0058">okay</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="775" who="S0179">the perception is where you might be able to overtake to get into speed</u>
<u n="776" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="777" who="S0179">look at that bit it is like a plateau</u>
<u n="778" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="779" who="S0179">it's like a <unclear/></u>
<u n="780" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="781" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="782" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="783" who="S0179">it makes you think that it could be</u>
<u n="784" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="785" who="S0179">what's that steep bit called again?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0058">Sutton Bank</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="787" who="S0058">okay</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="788" who="S0058"><unclear/></u>
<u n="789" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="790" who="S0058">erm it could well be it <pause dur="short"/> erm no no that's fine <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="791" who="S0179">it's a minor road anyway</u>
<u n="792" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="793" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="794" who="S0058">er yeah it is an actual B road <pause dur="short"/>  Falls is where erm James Brody went <pause dur="short"/> it's a very posh Catholic college by run by monks a very exclusive sort of school</u>
<u n="795" who="S0179">how can it be exclusive when it's run by monks?</u>
<u n="796" who="S0058">er well as in you have to erm it's a kind of a Catholic thing and a lot of people go into the priesthood I think it's all quite erm</u>
<u n="797" who="S0179">wow</u>
<u n="798" who="S0058">but James Brody is quite unusual he's quite erm</u>
<u n="799" who="S0179">unusual</u>
<u n="800" who="S0058">do you know what I mean? He never  he never  seemed like you know you could imagine him not going to a normal school <pause dur="short"/> he didn't seem sort of like he'd been to a normal you know your comp around the corner</u>
<u n="801" who="S0179">no <pause dur="short"/> I suppose I had a moment in my head as Mr University Challenge</u>
<u n="802" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="803" who="S0058">picturesque</u>
<u n="804" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="805" who="S0058">I guess the turn should be coming up pretty soon</u>
<u n="806" who="S0179">picturesque <pause dur="short"/> panoramic <unclear/></u>
<u n="807" who="S0058" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> we're coming down off that er land that time forgot plateau</u>
<u n="808" who="S0179">it's not <unclear/></u>
<u n="809" who="S0058" trans="overlap">oh right so I think it's where that <unclear/> that's where the the <trunc>t</trunc> the road bends around so we want to go right</u>
<u n="810" who="S0179">right <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="811" who="S0058">there isn't no</u>
<u n="812" who="S0179"><unclear/> Scotland this terrain</u>
<u n="813" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="814" who="S0179"><unclear/> it's just wild</u>
<u n="815" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="816" who="S0179">this feels like there could be a town over by the next hill</u>
<u n="817" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's not as bleak</u>
<u n="818" who="S0179">yeah exactly it's it's it's not bleak but it's still remote</u>
<u n="819" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> so yeah so this road bends right round actually erm</u>
<u n="820" who="S0179">wow</u>
<u n="821" who="S0058">more than one actually <pause dur="short"/> more than that anyway sorry <pause dur="short"/> yeah so we want the the left hand one here</u>
<u n="822" who="S0179">I certainly don't want to go to</u>
<u n="823" who="S0058" trans="overlap">sorry no we want the right hand one</u>
<u n="824" who="S0179">yeah yeah I know</u>
<u n="825" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="826" who="S0179">if you were keen and it was clear how quickly <unclear/></u>
<u n="827" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="828" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="829" who="S0058">okay?</u>
<u n="830" who="S0179">I still unfortunately <unclear/></u>
<u n="831" who="S0058">er yeah we're not going er towards them yeah</u>
<u n="832" who="S0179">we're going towards?</u>
<u n="833" who="S0058">we're going towards Morton yes that's that's correct yeah <pause dur="short"/> so basically now we're gonna stay on this B road</u>
<u n="834" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="835" who="S0058">yeah as far as one can tell these things <pause dur="short"/> we're gonna stay on this B road until we get to a town called <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="836" who="S0179">oh look at that</u>
<u n="837" who="S0058">oh a little cottage</u>
<u n="838" who="S0058">so we're gonna go through erm according to this two of the towns first and then we get to a town called <anon type="place"/> which is gonna be in about five miles</u>
<u n="839" who="S0179">so we'll make a turn in a town?</u>
<u n="840" who="S0058">yeah when we get into that town we take a turn onto a minor road which takes us down to Flaxton</u>
<u n="841" who="S0179">I'm glad we're going this way rather than through York <unclear/></u>
<u n="842" who="S0058">mm it is</u>
<u n="843" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="844" who="S0058">yeah presumably you haven't really driven around</u>
<u n="845" who="S0179">no I've never been to Yorkshire</u>
<u n="846" who="S0058">no other than when I dragged you to my convention</u>
<u n="847" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> you owe me a lot for that</u>
<u n="848" who="S0058">I did appreciate it it <trunc>wa</trunc> wasn't really</u>
<u n="849" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="850" who="S0058">I didn't <unclear/></u>
<u n="851" who="S0179"><unclear/> pointless thing in the world and the time and effort into this <unclear/> cure the world of hunger or something <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> evidently time and money to spare I'm sure it could have been better employed</u>
<u n="852" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="853" who="S0179">rather than recreating one page of a book about fifty times</u>
<u n="854" who="S0058">yeah but there there were just loads of black sheets but there <trunc>w</trunc> there was it was the idea</u>
<u n="855" who="S0179" trans="overlap">essentially</u>
<u n="856" who="S0058">some of them were but a lot of them were ideas sparked off by it</u>
<u n="857" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="858" who="S0058">it was interesting <pause dur="short"/> it <trunc>wa</trunc> it wasn't erm sort of the most interesting</u>
<u n="859" who="S0179" trans="overlap">but I mean you can say about you know <unclear/> most people would never even have heard of this <unclear/></u>
<u n="860" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="861" who="S0179">do <unclear/> got to do it anyway?</u>
<u n="862" who="S0058">erm artists I think they'd been involved with sort of <unclear/> yeah there's artists</u>
<u n="863" who="S0179">it would be hilarious <unclear/> two of them actually <unclear/> You'll probably find that was true</u>
<u n="864" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's very funny in the film and Cock and Bull Story you know the one about the filming of Tristram Shandy? And the the the sort of the joke is that a lot of them haven't actually read the book <pause dur="short"/> so like Steve Coogan hasn't read the book and he actually sits down one night and reads the entire book</u>
<u n="865" who="S0179">in one night?</u>
<u n="866" who="S0058">or he he's sort of meant to be yeah</u>
<u n="867" who="S0179">is that possible?</u>
<u n="868" who="S0058">mm no</u>
<u n="869" who="S0179">as in if you can't do it you'd be <unclear/></u>
<u n="870" who="S0058" trans="overlap">so yeah we're sort of bearing left here</u>
<u n="871" who="S0179">ooh Castle Howard</u>
<u n="872" who="S0058">oh yeah so sad when I go to Castle Howard</u>
<u n="873" who="S0179">why?</u>
<u n="874" who="S0058">that's Brideshead</u>
<u n="875" who="S0179">oh right</u>
<u n="876" who="S0058">yeah it it's erm it's very close to here <pause dur="short"/> I didn't realise how close <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> lives to it erm</u>
<u n="877" who="S0179">well we could detour if you want?</u>
<u n="878" who="S0058">not it's fine you need a a good while to appreciate its full glory</u>
<u n="879" who="S0179">oh right <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="880" who="S0058">we should definitely have a trip though and then go to Castle Howard it's just amazing <pause dur="short"/> but you maybe need to watch Brideshead first</u>
<u n="881" who="S0179"><unclear/> stay with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="882" who="S0058">yeah yeah that could be fun actually we'll drive up on Friday night and see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> go to Castle Howard on Saturday <pause dur="short"/> awesome</u>
<u n="883" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="884" who="S0058">we'll got to Herriot World as well</u>
<u n="885" who="S0179">I'm interested as to what that can be? <pause dur="short"/> actually no the World of James Herriot <pause dur="short"/> james Herriot is fictional Christopher Timothy is</u>
<u n="886" who="S0058">ah</u>
<u n="887" who="S0179">is the chap <unclear/></u>
<u n="888" who="S0058" trans="overlap">so it was probably the birthplace of Christopher Timothy then?</u>
<u n="889" who="S0179">probably <pause dur="short"/> er if you've got a minute could you change the CD?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0058">yeah erm yeah we just stay on this road now <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah what would you like?</u>
<u n="891" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="892" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="893" who="S0179">right <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="894" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="895" who="S0179">new places</u>
<u n="896" who="S0058">yeah it's cool</u>
<u n="897" who="S0179">expanding my knowledge of the world</u>
<u n="898" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="899" who="S0179"><unclear/> in general <unclear/> like <unclear/></u>
<u n="900" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="901" who="S0179"><unclear/> jetting off to sort of gap year type places <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="902" who="S0058">and this makes you a bit blas?</u>
<u n="903" who="S0179">yeah you don't know but you don't appreciate particularly where you are</u>
<u n="904" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="905" who="S0179">because you're so busy</u>
<u n="906" who="S0058" trans="overlap"><unclear/> next big thing</u>
<u n="907" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="908" who="S0179">you don't about exploring the country really <pause dur="short"/> actually this is sort of very Robbie Coltrane actually</u>
<u n="909" who="S0058">yeah dear old Britain</u>
<u n="910" who="S0179">even if we are stuck behind <unclear/> go too slow for you</u>
<u n="911" who="S0058">no we're not doing bad</u>
<u n="912" who="S0179">it's got to be nice actually <unclear/> drive through and it's quite relaxed <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="913" who="S0058">no</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="914" who="S0179">I take it this is one of the first of the er <unclear/></u>
<u n="915" who="S0058" trans="overlap">erm I think <trunc>m</trunc> I think this is Stonegrave and we haven't actually had a village sign but I'm fairly certain we are</u>
<u n="916" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="917" who="S0179">it's about <unclear/></u>
<u n="918" who="S0058"><unclear/></u>
<u n="919" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="920" who="S0058">that's very helpful yes we are indeed in Stonegrave</u>
<u n="921" who="S0179">okay so</u>
<u n="922" who="S0058">so yeah so they basically erm we carry on erm to the next town and it's it's <trunc>ju</trunc> just out you know we go right through the next town and it's just the other side of it <pause dur="short"/> and it'll probably be signposted Sherrif Hutton and I'll erm I'll give you a shout for it <pause dur="short"/> it's it's a minor road so it won't have a <pause dur="short"/> it'll probably be similar to that one</u>
<u n="923" who="S0179">sorry say that again?</u>
<u n="924" who="S0058">okay so erm that that was one town and we'll go through the next town and then just at the end of it according to this erm we so once we've been through it</u>
<u n="925" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="926" who="S0058">erm there's a minor road turns off <pause dur="short"/> I haven't got the name of the road erm Potticar Bank</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="927" who="S0179">is this <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="928" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="929" who="S0179">it's almost if the car has the best suspension so all considered</u>
<u n="930" who="S0058">there's lots of halls and houses and things around here it's strange</u>
<u n="931" who="S0179">that should be something hall or something house</u>
<u n="932" who="S0058">yeah yeah sorry yeah</u>
<u n="933" who="S0179" trans="overlap">houses and we've got some church halls and lots of cottages</u>
<u n="934" who="S0058">fair enough</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="935" who="S0179"><unclear/> towns in a bit?</u>
<u n="936" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm so yeah it's not we've just gone over the sort of bridge there and so we've kind of half a mile it's not far along that erm it's called <anon type="place"/> erm yeah carry on through the town <pause dur="short"/> erm I think it'll be just once we get past the town but I'll give you shout you know?</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="937" who="S0179">yeah this is nice smooth road <unclear/></u>
<u n="938" who="S0058">it's a funny name for a place <pause dur="short"/> yeah so we're looking for a signpost for Sherrif Hutton erm</u>
<u n="939" who="S0179"><unclear/> place</u>
<u n="940" who="S0058">yeah it is it's funny</u>
<u n="941" who="S0179"><unclear/> It's quite smart though it's erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="942" who="S0058">nice isn't it? It's all very smart</u>
<u n="943" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="944" who="S0058">oh very nice</u>
<u n="945" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="946" who="S0058">there's a bakery</u>
<u n="947" who="S0179"><unclear/> Well I thought your parents are genuinely excited <unclear/></u>
<u n="948" who="S0058">it's all about zeros</u>
<u n="949" who="S0179">it's not</u>
<u n="950" who="S0058">no it is</u>
<u n="951" who="S0179">it's not <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> a cup of tea <unclear/></u>
<u n="952" who="S0058">yeah which is giving her something</u>
<u n="953" who="S0179" trans="overlap">she didn't do any work</u>
<u n="954" who="S0058">and she doesn't particularly like</u>
<u n="955" who="S0179">it's about like me giving up using a vibrator</u>
<u n="956" who="S0058">okay so according to this it'll be the next right hand bend these are just that's just a drive drive</u>
<u n="957" who="S0179">right here?</u>
<u n="958" who="S0058">yes it's this this one here yes</u>
<u n="959" who="S0179">that was a turn and a half</u>
<u n="960" who="S0058">okay and now we carry on down to Sherrif Hutton erm which I reckon is six miles</u>
<u n="961" who="S0179">oh right so we're now on the actual?</u>
<u n="962" who="S0058">this is the minor road that takes us down to Flaxton</u>
<u n="963" who="S0179">okay <unclear/> I'm interested <unclear/> get there</u>
<u n="964" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="965" who="S0179"><unclear/> Ah wibbly-wobbly</u>
<u n="966" who="S0058">this is Potticar Bank which seems to fit with the er</u>
<u n="967" who="S0179">yeah it's topology yes</u>
<u n="968" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="969" who="S0179"><unclear/> There's a lot of situations that if you can make <unclear/> road <unclear/> a little</u>
<u n="970" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="971" who="S0179"><unclear/> pedestrian</u>
<u n="972" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="973" who="S0179">Jesus it's bumpy <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="974" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="975" who="S0179">we might have a Jaguar</u>
<u n="976" who="S0058">I was just about to say about the Jag <pause dur="short"/> ironic</u>
<u n="977" who="S0179">not really</u>
<u n="978" who="S0058">no I mean the <pause dur="short"/> a jaguar is quite a fast animal</u>
<u n="979" who="S0179">oh right yes the car is however particularly <unclear/> Jaguar often <unclear/></u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="980" who="S0179">right so how far is down here?</u>
<u n="981" who="S0058">how far?</u>
<u n="982" who="S0179">Down here is it?</u>
<u n="983" who="S0058">erm so erm so from where we turned off</u>
<u n="984" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="985" who="S0058">erm we go kind of just three miles so we're not too far off</u>
<u n="986" who="S0179">three miles?</u>
<u n="987" who="S0058">erm well so then the road erm it kind of veers around to the left and then we wanna take a right turn and carry on towards Sherrif Hutton so it'll it'll be signposted</u>
<u n="988" who="S0179">and presumably you'll tell me where that turning is?</u>
<u n="989" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="990" who="S0179">I don't think that the next road we're taking <unclear/> it might do yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> overtaking <unclear/> tend to go a bit faster which makes life more difficult</u>
<u n="991" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="992" who="S0179">so that's Wilkinson's law of overtaking <unclear/></u>
<event desc="sound of music"/>
<u n="993" who="S0179">ooh smoking <pause dur="short"/> it's a lot <unclear/></u>
<u n="994" who="S0058">hmm <pause dur="short"/> okay so erm</u>
<u n="995" who="S0179">it smells good</u>
<u n="996" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> in sort of maybe slightly less than a mile</u>
<u n="997" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="998" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> in slightly less than a mile we're going to erm yeah according to the iPad this road is gonna veer around to the left quite sharply <pause dur="short"/> it could be a T-junction</u>
<u n="999" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0058">depending on what</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0179">less than a mile?</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0179">okay that's original <unclear/></u>
<u n="1004" who="S0058">yeah so either this road is gonna veer around to the left or there's gonna be a T-junction where we wanna go left <pause dur="short"/> then very shortly after that we're gonna take a right <pause dur="short"/> it's just like it's staggered across <unclear/></u>
<u n="1005" who="S0179" trans="overlap">and a more powerful car</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0179">and if he wasn't sort of over the line</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0179">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> and we're here <pause dur="short"/> yes here</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0058">oh right so this is probably the yeah</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0179">right <unclear/> two turnings</u>
</body>
</text>
