<text id="SLDB">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:26:00</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-11</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0041 S0086</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Friendships, exercise, work </topics>
		<activity>Friends eating dinner, chatting </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0041">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Conference and Events Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0086">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cuckfield, West Sussex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year, 9 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0041">I think he's going nuts</u>
<u n="2" who="S0086">I think right well that was pretty crazy what just came out of your mouth <pause dur="short"/> and then he surprises me again <pause dur="short"/> I just don't understand <pause dur="short"/> this whole business about well she invited me to the gig em therefore I'm going to go <pause dur="short"/> yeah but she's now since told you that she doesn't feel there's a connection she doesn't want to pursue anything with you <pause dur="short"/> yeah but it's okay cos I'm not going to tell her <pause dur="short"/> oh right okay so turning up unannounced where she would never expect you to be because you don't live there</u>
<u n="3" who="S0041">yeah that's normal</u>
<u n="4" who="S0086">that's a really good idea drink with crazy horse <pause dur="short"/> that's that's going to go really well <pause dur="short"/> I don't understand why he doesn't see that that's making him sound like a fucking psycho</u>
<u n="5" who="S0041">psycho</u>
<u n="6" who="S0086">and then</u>
<u n="7" who="S0041">I think because he is a psycho so he can't see it</u>
<u n="8" who="S0086">did he tell you think thing about the phone <trunc>get</trunc> her getting a messages <pause dur="short"/> okay well it'll make you want to be sick in your mouth so just prepare yourself <pause dur="short"/> so they were spooning on the bed whatever day it was <pause dur="short"/> so for her to then say that there's no connection is a bit weird because why would you spoon with anyway fine <pause dur="short"/> she's mental</u>
<u n="9" who="S0041">she must be let's be honest</u>
<u n="10" who="S0086">so they're <trunc>sp</trunc> they're spooning she gets a message <pause dur="short"/> she's got a BlueBerry <pause dur="short"/> and they're lying there and he must be hugging her <pause dur="short"/> she gets a message and he says oh it's from someone called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and I said you were reading her messages? And he's like oh well I I had to because I was lying like with my head on her shoulder and I said bollocks you could have looked at the TV <pause dur="short"/> em and he was like oh and I'm sure it said POF in the background of the message <pause dur="short"/> and I was like oh right like waiting for like this big revelation <pause dur="short"/> he said but she told me she wasn't speaking to a <unclear/> I was like but she was speaking to you <pause dur="short"/> and she's single <pause dur="short"/> what the fuck is the matter with you? He's like yeah but she told me I said I wasn't talking to anybody else and she said she wasn't talking to anybody else and I said even if that were true</u>
<u n="11" who="S0041">she only just met him</u>
<u n="12" who="S0086">it's only been a few days <pause dur="short"/> she's only been chatting to you like less than a week <pause dur="short"/> he's like a couple of weeks <pause dur="short"/> no bollocks it's been a couple of weeks <pause dur="short"/> been a couple of days <pause dur="short"/> he's I just I really struggle to talk to the boy because everything he says is mental and I feel like I'm always being contrary <pause dur="short"/> I feel like I'm always disagreeing with everything he says and I feel like he thinks</u>
<u n="13" who="S0041">yeah yeah I do as well</u>
<u n="14" who="S0086">I'm deliberately picking holes in everything he says but I can't help it because everything he says is mental <pause dur="short"/> and I started to think like em <pause dur="short"/> cheers <pause dur="short"/> here's to Wednesdays</u>
<u n="15" who="S0041">Wednesday's hump day of the week</u>
<u n="16" who="S0086">hump day <pause dur="short"/> eh yeah it worries me that well no no it doesn't worry me I mean I just think maybe he thinks I'm being a twat but I can't help it now</u>
<u n="17" who="S0041">I don't think you're being a twat</u>
<u n="18" who="S0086">I can't  I can't  hide me</u>
<u n="19" who="S0041">that that yesterday was just the straw for me final straw <pause dur="short"/> after all the craziness and all the patience I was just like what are you joking <pause dur="short"/> I was actually really looking forward to the opportunity to some in home and saying fuck this</u>
<u n="20" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah well he's gone after the girls <pause dur="short"/> which I don't mean he's going to meet the kids <pause dur="short"/> I mean what is it with these single young mums introducing their kids to the</u>
<u n="21" who="S0041">oh god knows <pause dur="short"/> it just shows you the calibre of person that he's going for if they're willing to introduce their kids to some randomer they've met off the internet and barely know <pause dur="short"/> frigging nuts</u>
<u n="22" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> how's your chilli? Good? Hitting the spot?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0041">I put it in a deceptive bowl though</u>
<u n="24" who="S0086">quite a lot of it</u>
<u n="25" who="S0041">especially considering it's my second dinner</u>
<u n="26" who="S0086">it's not really your second dinner <pause dur="short"/> ham and egg is not really dinner is it? Nutter</u>
<u n="27" who="S0041">and a Fajita</u>
<u n="28" who="S0086">no it's still not dinner</u>
<u n="29" who="S0041">yeah cos I was thinking about it today I thought actually I can't be hacked with trying to organise something to come</u>
<u n="30" who="S0086">that you don't even want to have</u>
<u n="31" who="S0041">yeah that I don't even want to have <pause dur="short"/> for people to come here and I'm going to be concerned about what the hell he's being up <pause dur="short"/> cos I haven't had any part in it cos if I wanted to do it I'd want to decorate the place you know and put neon you know neon linen on the walls or something <pause dur="short"/> you know really do the place out</u>
<u n="32" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0041">not some half-hearted all my mates having a party at my house so yeah let's go</u>
<u n="34" who="S0086">yeah weird <pause dur="short"/> and I think you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have been on at me about having party I think you know we can have one in the summer but one that we've all organised <pause dur="short"/> one that we're all involved in not for your birthday being told well that's what's happening</u>
<u n="35" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I just I don't understand the logic behind it</u>
<u n="36" who="S0086">I know it worries me <pause dur="short"/> and even you do fell embarrassed getting your mates over here cos you don't know what sort of person he's going to be inviting</u>
<u n="37" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> well I don't know who this Mark is but if it's who I'm thinking of he was a weirdo</u>
<u n="38" who="S0086">yeah I think he's that skinny little one</u>
<u n="39" who="S0041">skinny weirdo yeah <pause dur="short"/> like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and crazy horse is one thing to contend with but the whole motley crew</u>
<u n="40" who="S0086">yeah and then that weird one that was with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for a while and the fat one <pause dur="short"/> that was who we though <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was wasn't it?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> no it's just all too it's all too much <pause dur="short"/> to be honest I'd rather just go over the Village for a few drinks and then come into town</u>
<u n="42" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that's the thing it's your prerogative it's your birthday <pause dur="short"/> that's what you get to do <pause dur="short"/> you get to do you get to choose you don't get to be told by your housemate <pause dur="short"/> you've got to have a chavtastic barbecue and like it</u>
<u n="43" who="S0041">fucking <unclear/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0086">I wondered if Grace was cooing round to be like oh are you <unclear/> going I the house</u>
<u n="45" who="S0041">to be honest I'd rather have her back than bloody</u>
<u n="46" who="S0086">noisy feet</u>
<u n="47" who="S0041">noisy feet upstairs <pause dur="short"/> what I was thinking actually is that they've <trunc>sta</trunc> we've started doing packages at the hotel for cocktail making <pause dur="short"/> and we go and it'll be <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that does it basically teaches you how to make a cocktail</u>
<u n="48" who="S0086">fun</u>
<u n="49" who="S0041">and then or teaches you how to make two cocktails and then he gives you loads of ingredients and splits you into two teams and you have to make your own cocktail and then he judges the winner and whatever one wins is the cocktail of the week at the hotel</u>
<u n="50" who="S0086">wow that's such a good idea</u>
<u n="51" who="S0041">yeah and I think  I think  it's like twelve pound a head for one to have one cocktail each out of it or twenty pound head to have two cocktails reach out of it <pause dur="short"/> but we pay half price anyway</u>
<u n="52" who="S0086">winner</u>
<u n="53" who="S0041">Cos I get fifty per cent off at the hotel don't I?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0086">that sounds like a bargain? Does that extend to your friends?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0041">yeah I think I'd book it and pay for the lot</u>
<u n="56" who="S0086">oh right</u>
<u n="57" who="S0041">so as far as they're concerned I pay for everything</u>
<u n="58" who="S0086">it's all on your bill it's your bill</u>
<u n="59" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0086">ah well that sounds pretty exciting</u>
<u n="61" who="S0041">so that would be fun thing to do</u>
<u n="62" who="S0086">yeah it sounds really fun even if it is at work it's whether you want to spend your birthday at work but even</u>
<u n="63" who="S0041">yeah but we'd only be there for an hour or two</u>
<u n="64" who="S0086">yeah and then you're well placed you know for carrying o the festivities</u>
<u n="65" who="S0041">yeah so I thought that would be fun</u>
<u n="66" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0041">something easy you know when I don't <pause dur="short"/> it's easily done it's not expensive and then</u>
<u n="68" who="S0086">yeah and then <pause dur="short"/> and then you know cocktails Aare always nice <pause dur="short"/> see where the night takes us <pause dur="short"/> I can't believe how soon it's come in</u>
<u n="69" who="S0041">I know</u>
<u n="70" who="S0086">yeah we won't talk about dates</u>
<u n="71" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="72" who="S0086">I used to tell <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like when she was finishing off her PhD <pause dur="short"/> I was like don't worry there's only a month to go and she was like fuck like fuck fuck fuck stop saying that <pause dur="short"/> obviously that means you've only got a month to go and you've got to do all this work</u>
<u n="73" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> no I'm not <pause dur="short"/> no no</u>
<u n="74" who="S0086">I think just put your foot down</u>
<u n="75" who="S0041">I'm gonna <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s on holiday this week <pause dur="short"/> when she comes back next week I'm gonna ask her and just make sure that we'll all get it all half price</u>
<u n="76" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0041">Cos they have like life if it's a a deal then you don't get half price or something I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if his counts as an offer <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it is it's standard package <pause dur="short"/> I'll ask her</u>
<u n="78" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's a good idea to do it at the <trunc>he</trunc> hotel <pause dur="short"/> good little money spinner</u>
<u n="79" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has made a video to teach the F and B staff how to like shake the cocktail thing and all the tricks swing it round</u>
<u n="80" who="S0086">ah nice <pause dur="short"/> so what does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0041">everything <pause dur="short"/> he's the one that gets run ragged all the time</u>
<u n="82" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> the one who hasn't ever been employee of the month or something <pause dur="short"/> gone for the special dinner</u>
<u n="83" who="S0041">gone to the dinner <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> sound like a nice guy</u>
<u n="85" who="S0041">yeah he is really nice</u>
<u n="86" who="S0086">is he the one with the funny wife <pause dur="short"/> well not funny wife</u>
<u n="87" who="S0041">even though I'm convinced he's gay</u>
<u n="88" who="S0086">but then where is she Philippines or something</u>
<u n="89" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> malaysia <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if that's different <pause dur="short"/> is it?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's a different country yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0041">oh I wasn't sure if the Philippines was in Malaysia</u>
<u n="92" who="S0086">em no mm <pause dur="short"/> different countries I think <pause dur="short"/> well cos capital of Malaysia is Kuala Lumpur isn't it? Yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I couldn't tell you where it is <pause dur="short"/> I don't know where anything is <pause dur="short"/> I know where I am just <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was telling about some place that she used to go to like the beach <pause dur="short"/> she was like oh it's in Scotland it's near this place and I was like yeah uh-huh and she's like I don't know why I'm telling you <pause dur="short"/> you've got no idea where this is have you?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> no I don't</u>
<u n="94" who="S0086">sounds lovely though</u>
<u n="95" who="S0041">sounds really nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah so</u>
<u n="96" who="S0086">sO how was work</u>
<u n="97" who="S0041" trans="overlap">we shall see <pause dur="short"/> apart from that it just as it just drags  it just drags  and I had to sort out the stupid thing with people who haven't paid again <pause dur="short"/> I had her on the phone</u>
<u n="98" who="S0086">oh god</u>
<u n="99" who="S0041">and the accountants still saying no we're not refunding it until they've provided other card details and I was like but they can't do that</u>
<u n="100" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0041">it's not  It's not  a business card <pause dur="short"/> and he was like so it's the only leverage that we've got</u>
<u n="102" who="S0086">Jesus</u>
<u n="103" who="S0041">I'm just going to go and put the phone down <pause dur="short"/> I never answer it <pause dur="short"/> just pick up the receiver and put it down again</u>
<u n="104" who="S0086">I think it's just recorded messages</u>
<u n="105" who="S0041">if anybody's ever rung they've never got through if I've been in <pause dur="short"/> ah look at this <pause dur="short"/> I've been walking round with no bra on all day</u>
<u n="106" who="S0086">you animal did you leave it at home</u>
<u n="107" who="S0041">yeah I forgot it didn't I?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0086">ah saggy boobs</u>
<u n="109" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> blazer on all day <pause dur="short"/> all day long</u>
<u n="110" who="S0086">at least you've got a bit of em support in the dress though <pause dur="short"/> like there's a bit of material <pause dur="short"/> no nothing?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0041">no no <pause dur="short"/> this I thought well maybe if it was tighter waist band <pause dur="short"/> no the waist and is just half way up my boob <pause dur="short"/> so that's nice that's attractive</u>
<u n="112" who="S0086">wow</u>
<u n="113" who="S0041">that was yum</u>
<u n="114" who="S0086">delish</u>
<u n="115" who="S0041">delishioso</u>
<u n="116" who="S0086">oh I spoke to one of my suppliers this morning</u>
<u n="117" who="S0041">not the three grand one?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0086">huh the three grand?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0041">not the three grand one</u>
<u n="120" who="S0086">no but that's still bumbling along <pause dur="short"/> that stupid bint in finance supposed to give me a cheque today has she fuck</u>
<u n="121" who="S0041">oh no</u>
<u n="122" who="S0086">and so god knows what's happening with that <pause dur="short"/> luckily the supplier hasn't chased though <pause dur="short"/> it's a designer and it's he and his wife had their own little business <pause dur="short"/> and em <pause dur="short"/> I don't I've never met him but I think he's probably from the sound of his voice about fifty in his fifties anyway <pause dur="short"/> to me had sounds like an aging hippy <pause dur="short"/> like he's always really hi how're you doing you alright? Yeah the covers yeah well mm I'll get them to you <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> like he has he's done loads of work for me hasn't sent in any invoices <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how he actually lives <pause dur="short"/> he never remembers to actually request for payment <pause dur="short"/> so I was em I was briefing him to do some more work and I called <pause dur="short"/> he I'd sent him an email he'd called me to like to clarify a few points and he said did you have a good long break over Easter? And I said yeah it was you know really fun quite relaxing how was yours? Oh good yeah went to a party and em I did something I hadn't done in thirty years <pause dur="short"/> and in my head I'm like oh maybe he got home at like three in the morning like you know got really drunk</u>
<u n="123" who="S0041">are you going to tell me he smoked pot?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0086">yeah he's like I got stoned</u>
<u n="125" who="S0041">and I was like oh nice <pause dur="short"/> so the covers em <pause dur="short"/> what the fuck? Client supplier <pause dur="short"/> fifty odd year old man and a <pause dur="short"/> cos what do you say? Did you have a lovely time? He was like yeah it was great <pause dur="short"/> you know totally ruined my weekend but em <pause dur="short"/> you know totally you know cos he was probably really off his face cos he's an old man <pause dur="short"/> but em <pause dur="short"/> but he said yeah we had a lovely time <pause dur="short"/> he's probably still high now to be fair <pause dur="short"/> he wasn't really with it <pause dur="short"/> hilarious</u>
<u n="126" who="S0041">you don't tell someone you work with that</u>
<u n="127" who="S0086">no or work for which is even worse</u>
<u n="128" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0086">so he's very em very relaxed about these things <pause dur="short"/> turns out</u>
<u n="130" who="S0041">yeah it turns out</u>
<u n="131" who="S0086">Cos I told <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> our designer who is you know know him much better than I do <pause dur="short"/> because normally it should fall to them to do the briefing but <pause dur="short"/> funnily enough they said oh we're really busy <pause dur="short"/> can you do it? Well the thing is I'm really fucking busy <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> it's a different story <pause dur="short"/> and I told her and she was like no fucking way <pause dur="short"/> what did you say and obviously there's nothing you can say than lovely</u>
<u n="132" who="S0041" trans="overlap">no there isn't <pause dur="short"/> just acknowledge it yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0086">Good that sound fun <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="134" who="S0041" trans="overlap">oh good yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0086">moving swiftly on <pause dur="short"/> it was so funny <pause dur="short"/> I'd like to meet him now <pause dur="short"/> in my head he is a proper aging hippy like long flowing hair and big cardigans <pause dur="short"/> I think that's probably what he looks like</u>
<u n="136" who="S0041">ah nice <pause dur="short"/> ah I could do with a cardigan <pause dur="short"/> you em aught o message him and say <pause dur="short"/> we need pictures <pause dur="short"/> having ID cards made for if you ever ever come here</u>
<u n="137" who="S0086">huh <pause dur="short"/> he's so funny <pause dur="short"/> so that was the good thing about today <pause dur="short"/> oh and I got loads of contraband teabags</u>
<u n="138" who="S0041">ah brilliant</u>
<u n="139" who="S0086">which was good and then it was juts downhill from there</u>
<u n="140" who="S0041">ah frigging calves <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0086">my bike makes a nice crunching noise now like its going over Coco Pops like over and over</u>
<u n="142" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0086">yeah so that's a new development <pause dur="short"/> but I did superglue on my light <pause dur="short"/> because when I stacked off my bike a few weeks ago the <trunc>l</trunc> the light came you know where it fixes it slots in at the top <pause dur="short"/> underneath the bracket had broken off so it wouldn't stay in the holder so I've glued it on <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> batteries but we'll cross that bridge when we come to it</u>
<u n="144" who="S0041">yeah yeah don't worry about that yet <pause dur="short"/> I saw on Facebook earlier cos I was at work in the office on my own from half five</u>
<u n="145" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="146" who="S0041">yeah I was going to leave but then I thought well if somebody comes in and there's no one here</u>
<u n="147" who="S0086">yeah that might be a sackable offense</u>
<u n="148" who="S0041">yeah so I em I waited <pause dur="short"/> until like five to <pause dur="short"/> em and I was messing around on Facebook ad a couple of girls that I lived with for a little while at uni between houses <pause dur="short"/> one write to the other one hilarious do you remember that time in second year when I thought I had a family of mice living in my wardrobe and it turned out to be a bottle of lemonade? So she heard the rustling of the lemonade <unclear/> itself and thought she'd got a family of ice in her wardrobe</u>
<u n="149" who="S0086">did it want to explode in her wardrobe?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0041">must have done it really made me laugh</u>
<u n="151" who="S0086">that's funny</u>
<u n="152" who="S0041">and her friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wrote alcohol dot dot dot because no good stories start with eating salad <pause dur="short"/> forget how much pleasure I get out of Facebook stalking</u>
<u n="153" who="S0086">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> pretty sure that's what it was invented for so that's fine</u>
<u n="154" who="S0041">yeah yeah I think so</u>
<u n="155" who="S0086">Steve Zuckerman or whatever his name is have bought Instagram hasn't he? From Apple</u>
<u n="156" who="S0041">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0086">for some ridiculous amount of money</u>
<u n="158" who="S0041">yeah and it's gone straight to the top of the apps chart hasn't it? I like Instagram <pause dur="short"/> that's why I wanted to get my phone cos I wanted to have a play on Instagram</u>
<u n="159" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0041">whenever <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that's what I always used to <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s phone for whenever I whenever I'm with him <pause dur="short"/> can I borrow your phone please? I just go through Instagram <pause dur="short"/> I like looking at that <pause dur="short"/> basically because I'm shit at photography</u>
<u n="161" who="S0086">well if you've got things like that everyone's good a photography then <pause dur="short"/> it does all the hard work for you</u>
<u n="162" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> all the different tints and stuff <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why I'm picking his off cos I'm only going to have to repaint it <pause dur="short"/> bu there's there's a lump there <pause dur="short"/> it's too late now</u>
<u n="163" who="S0086">I managed to avoid getting any <trunc>slu</trunc> super glue on my hand but I said to <unclear/> I can't open it <pause dur="short"/> he's like oh you just em you just pierce it with the end of the the nose you turn in back on in itself and I was like okay <pause dur="short"/> so he did it and it squeezed all over his hands and he was like okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> loads of <trunc>s</trunc> that's come out okay well be careful with that <pause dur="short"/> I said okay fine <pause dur="short"/> gluing away on my bike <pause dur="short"/> he's like it's not really em coming coming off yeah it's really not coming off now <pause dur="short"/> okay it's to coming off my hands okay it's not coming off <pause dur="short"/> still on my hand em <pause dur="short"/> and he ran then under the tap and I said just use the wire wool thing rather than get them wet <pause dur="short"/> cos then as soon as he got it wet it went all white like he'd got paint all over his hands <pause dur="short"/> then he tried to scrub it off and it wouldn't come off</u>
<u n="164" who="S0041">so he's got no fingerprints</u>
<u n="165" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0041">ah yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0086">he's like a criminal <pause dur="short"/> well he is a criminal</u>
<u n="168" who="S0041">I always thought that you know if you were going to be a criminal you could put superglue on your fingertips</u>
<u n="169" who="S0086">there you go</u>
<u n="170" who="S0041">gets rid of all your all all that goodness</u>
<u n="171" who="S0086">all those  All those  traceable things</u>
<u n="172" who="S0041">all those <trunc>tra</trunc> all those traceable tips</u>
<u n="173" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0041">of course when I rob a bank I'll be prepared</u>
<u n="175" who="S0086">mm hm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0041">when my plan comes together</u>
<u n="177" who="S0086">it's good that you've given it some thought</u>
<u n="178" who="S0041">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I was trying to guess your email for work today</u>
<u n="179" who="S0086">how did you manage it?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0041">Cos I needed to top my phone up and I'd left my card here <pause dur="short"/> I messages Facebook messaged <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to find it for me <pause dur="short"/> and em so I was like right what's the <anon type="place"/> email? So I was like in Google <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> nothing <pause dur="short"/> but then I saw everybody else's email address at Cambridge dot org and I saw how there's was set up and then just put then guessed yours</u>
<u n="181" who="S0086">no I was em</u>
<u n="182" who="S0041">that's what I thought <pause dur="short"/> if it's not you and it's some other <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I thought wow</u>
<u n="183" who="S0086">I know <pause dur="short"/> I thought you were just taking the piss that's why I wrote back <pause dur="short"/> testing testing</u>
<u n="184" who="S0041">yeah could have been any <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> anywhere <pause dur="short"/> in case there was two of you</u>
<u n="185" who="S0086">that would be pretty weird wouldn't it? There are two <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> actually cos there's another one on Facebook and she's an actress and she's she's like a prettier version of me which is relay annoying <pause dur="short"/> cos if I just got slightly better genes I would be her and have lovely exotic lovely life</u>
<u n="186" who="S0041">right <pause dur="short"/> I think she might have come up when I Googled <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0086">yeah bitch</u>
<u n="188" who="S0041">but I didn't look at her</u>
<u n="189" who="S0086">I think we must be related distantly because I know that sounds mental but it's not a a common name <pause dur="short"/> so I think we're all like all the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>s and all the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>s which is my mum's maiden name we're all related <pause dur="short"/> so it's all quite em quiet em em eh what's the opposite of common? Rare scarcer?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0041">rare</u>
<u n="191" who="S0086">rarer</u>
<u n="192" who="S0041">more rare</u>
<u n="193" who="S0086">more rare</u>
<u n="194" who="S0041">all the rare</u>
<u n="195" who="S0086">not the rare <pause dur="short"/> so but yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's probably some sort of cousin great grandmother twice removed or something <pause dur="short"/> sounds about right</u>
<u n="196" who="S0041">ah <unclear/> when I running round earlier I got half way round I was like ah I've got a snotty nose ah <pause dur="short"/> I I looked really attractive <pause dur="short"/> as you can imagine</u>
<u n="197" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> there's nothing quite like going for a run to make yourself look horrendous</u>
<u n="198" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> came back in sweating and he's just quite normal <pause dur="short"/> buzz off</u>
<u n="199" who="S0086">ah it's good for you</u>
<u n="200" who="S0041" trans="overlap">whatever <pause dur="short"/> so I figure I'm doing nothing this afternoon <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> I was so <trunc>cl</trunc> so tempted to pub so tempted to pub</u>
<u n="201" who="S0086">really?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0086">Good girl though</u>
<u n="204" who="S0041">em</u>
<u n="205" who="S0086">especially on a budget</u>
<u n="206" who="S0041">yeah yeah budget would not stretch</u>
<u n="207" who="S0086">mm mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0041">em and then it's going to have to be Aqua tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> cos otherwise my legs are not going to move <pause dur="short"/> unfortunately</u>
<u n="209" who="S0086" trans="overlap">aqua <pause dur="short"/> aqua tomorrow that sounds good <pause dur="short"/> and I might go for a little run after work cos what time is Aqua? Six forty-five or something?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0041">maybe</u>
<u n="211" who="S0086">one of one of those things</u>
<u n="212" who="S0041">maybe it's six thirty</u>
<u n="213" who="S0086">oh that's fine <pause dur="short"/> so I'll still be home by five <pause dur="short"/> I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was supposed to come over for dinner but I haven't heard from him he's in some sort of work crisis</u>
<u n="214" who="S0041">oh that's a point if it's six-thirty I might not make it in time will I?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0086">no <pause dur="short"/> I wonder if I can give <pause dur="short"/> oh cos you're not driving or walking</u>
<u n="216" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0086">I could pick you up but we won't if it's six thirty we won't get there in time with the traffic <pause dur="short"/> we will have to check this <pause dur="short"/> I thought it was you said it was six forty-five but it might not be <pause dur="short"/> six thirty yeah <pause dur="short"/> I get the old mobile out in a minute</u>
<u n="218" who="S0041">we might make it if I took my swimming stuff with me</u>
<u n="219" who="S0086">it's just getting out of <anon type="place"/> that's the only problem <pause dur="short"/> cos that time</u>
<u n="220" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> once you get to here it's like ten minutes from here</u>
<u n="221" who="S0086">but that that's the problem isn't it? But then at least you know not that it would have been school traffic at the at time any way but the schools aren't in <pause dur="short"/> but then that means that the town traffic like shop closing time that's going to be busy</u>
<u n="222" who="S0041">yeah it didn't take me very long today cos I before I came home which time? What time was I home for <pause dur="short"/> cos I text <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when I got in <pause dur="short"/> I got in at half six and I went from the hotel up <anon type="place"/> Road to see what time the sunbed was open till <pause dur="short"/> parked the car got out walked round to the sunbed walked round back to the car and drove home</u>
<u n="223" who="S0086">okay <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's just that you've got to avoid <anon type="place"/> Road <pause dur="short"/> but that's fine cos I guess form the hotel</u>
<u n="224" who="S0041">oh I drove up <anon type="place"/> Road</u>
<u n="225" who="S0086">oh did you? Was it alright?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0041">I went  I went  from <pause dur="short"/> it looks bad because the traffic's at a standstill <pause dur="short"/> once it moves</u>
<u n="227" who="S0086" trans="overlap">mm but it moves quite quickly</u>
<u n="228" who="S0041">but once it moves you move <pause dur="short"/> went from the hotel down past where the police station use to be or still is <pause dur="short"/> up <anon type="place"/> Road to the other side of the bridge <pause dur="short"/> parked went in the thingy back out again went down <anon type="place"/> Road up <anon type="place"/> Road</u>
<u n="229" who="S0086">oh fine okay</u>
<u n="230" who="S0041"><vocal desc="sneeze"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0086">bless you</u>
<u n="232" who="S0041">so it might be possible</u>
<u n="233" who="S0086">but to be honest <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="234" who="S0041">or if I put my swimming if I take my swimming costume with me put it on under my dress that when we get there I just have to strip off</u>
<u n="235" who="S0086">well that's fine if I if you walk I will run come home get in the car get you em and then this fine <pause dur="short"/> and I'll be at work <pause dur="short"/> is there somewhere that I can wait?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> you won't need to wait though but yes <pause dur="short"/> opposite the hotel there's little road that goes behind <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> used to wait down there <pause dur="short"/> cos otherwise it's theyou can wait on the driveway</u>
<u n="237" who="S0086">but then they might try and park you</u>
<u n="238" who="S0041">they might try and park you but also if another car comes the can't get round you</u>
<u n="239" who="S0086">well I'll try and time it that I'm there at six but I'll probably try and leave a bit early because of the traffic <pause dur="short"/> so if I leave here at quarter to</u>
<u n="240" who="S0041">well I could probably leave early tomorrow if everyone else has left again</u>
<u n="241" who="S0086">that's true</u>
<u n="242" who="S0041">might be able to sneak out</u>
<u n="243" who="S0086">get the old Mobile on the go when I'm on my way <pause dur="short"/> it's looking pretty unhappy</u>
<u n="244" who="S0041">look at that bad boy</u>
<u n="245" who="S0086" trans="overlap">I should have put it outside <pause dur="short"/> I know it's massive <pause dur="short"/> but it just I think it's going to really need repotting and being outside but it's still a bit cold at night</u>
<u n="246" who="S0041">does it know the temperature</u>
<u n="247" who="S0086">it does know the temperature <pause dur="short"/> but the good thing is it's chillies so they grow in like deserts and shit <pause dur="short"/> so in theory you don't you wouldn't need to ever water it <pause dur="short"/> which is obviously what I'm doing</u>
<u n="248" who="S0041">eh yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0086">with that all that whole swimming pool set underneath that there</u>
<u n="250" who="S0041">yeah that little pool yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0086">that little he yeah got a bit carried away</u>
<u n="252" who="S0041">yep</u>
<u n="253" who="S0086">so I might drain that away and give it a bit water actually that's a bit grim <pause dur="short"/> but there is like compost and stiff out there and flower pots so I'm thinking I might do that at the weekend</u>
<u n="254" who="S0041">chuck them in those pots</u>
<u n="255" who="S0086">yeah got a wash my bike cos it's pretty grim <pause dur="short"/> thought about going to pound land and looking for car shampoo</u>
<u n="256" who="S0041">ah yeah that's good <pause dur="short"/> did you go into town thus afternoon then?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0086">yeah but I just took the stiff back to Primark and then left really quickly before I got distracted by all of the things that I need</u>
<u n="258" who="S0041">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's wise</u>
<u n="259" who="S0086">I was going to take things to the charity shop but as much as you know I'm in to charity shops I thought if I go in I'll only buy more stuff <pause dur="short"/> if I'm going to car booty things even if I get a pound you know it's better than a poke in the face</u>
<u n="260" who="S0041">I do like doing the charity shops</u>
<u n="261" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> get some right old bargains but I don't need new things</u>
<u n="262" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna need a new dress</u>
<u n="263" who="S0086">I ne dress yes yeah that's definitely going to happen</u>
<u n="264" who="S0041">I think  I think  that's only fair</u>
<u n="265" who="S0086">I think that is definitely the law</u>
<u n="266" who="S0041">I was planning on losing four pounds again this week and I don't think that's going to happen</u>
<u n="267" who="S0086">you're not eating any food</u>
<u n="268" who="S0041">I am <pause dur="short"/> I had this I've had two teas</u>
<u n="269" who="S0086">well no</u>
<u n="270" who="S0041">I've had to teas</u>
<u n="271" who="S0086">no <pause dur="short"/> you haven't had two teas <pause dur="short"/> the first tea was not a tea</u>
<u n="272" who="S0041">I had two teas I had two sausages for breakfast today <pause dur="short"/> a yoghurt and some tomato soup</u>
<u n="273" who="S0086">it's not a lot <pause dur="short"/> in the grand scheme of things it's not a lot</u>
<u n="274" who="S0041">it's not four <trunc>hu</trunc> four pounds a week though <pause dur="short"/> it's two pounds a week</u>
<u n="275" who="S0086">see what you eat tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> well I mean we've got a short week because there was Easter eggs on Monday</u>
<u n="276" who="S0041">oh yeah frigging Easter eggs</u>
<u n="277" who="S0086">but you will probably surprise yourself</u>
<u n="278" who="S0041">see how tomorrow and Friday goes</u>
<u n="279" who="S0086">aqua fit <pause dur="short"/> I'm really excited about Aqua fit I really liked it last time</u>
<u n="280" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0086">yep</u>
<u n="282" who="S0041">I'm just looking forward to my legs not hurting cos I'm gonna try and run three mile don Friday</u>
<u n="283" who="S0086">why?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0041">for shits and giggles <pause dur="short"/> I just want to see if I can keep how long I can keep going for <pause dur="short"/> I'm not particularly fast just</u>
<u n="285" who="S0086">power on through</u>
<u n="286" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0086">well I suppose now you're relay getting your time down then you can do that can't you? You know you've got <pause dur="short"/> the your end the end is in sight now <pause dur="short"/> if you an lower it again by thirty seconds you're laughing</u>
<u n="288" who="S0041">yeah I don't <pause dur="short"/> if I lowered it by five seconds I'm in</u>
<u n="289" who="S0086">yeah absolutely but you want to have a bit of safety margin</u>
<u n="290" who="S0041" trans="overlap">but we don't yeah <pause dur="short"/> but now I'm getting a bit too competitive now I want thirteen minutes</u>
<u n="291" who="S0086">fine <pause dur="short"/> well you I mean the best you want to be doing the best don't you? You want to be lowering it as much s possible</u>
<u n="292" who="S0041">I didn't text <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and tell him did I? Fucker saying well you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you need to take it more seriously you might need to get a personal trainer ra ra ra <pause dur="short"/> piss off</u>
<u n="293" who="S0086">just give up <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on life <pause dur="short"/> em have you been in touch with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0041">he texted me today saying hello sexy bum <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> and I replied hello sexy man how have you been today and he didn't reply <pause dur="short"/> but I did leave it two and a half hours before relied to him <pause dur="short"/> he likes to play these games so not expecting a reply yet</u>
<u n="295" who="S0086">he's all about the game playing</u>
<u n="296" who="S0041">all he's all about the game playing</u>
<u n="297" who="S0086">that's obviously how you keep a hymn interested is you just play the game <pause dur="short"/> which is fine if you want to play the game <pause dur="short"/> that's fine <pause dur="short"/> it's entertaining to a degree</u>
<u n="298" who="S0041">yeah to a degree <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="299" who="S0086">and then everyone just gets really fucked off</u>
<u n="300" who="S0041">yeah and thinks why the fuck did I start talking to you again? This is exactly why</u>
<u n="301" who="S0086" trans="overlap">you're a knob <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> grace has put a lot of weight on hasn't she? I <trunc>le</trunc> unless I just forgot how big she was before but her legs looked really big</u>
<u n="302" who="S0041">did they?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> like her thighs <pause dur="short"/> maybe those really unattractive trousers</u>
<u n="304" who="S0041">I was going to say do you think they were really the trousers <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="305" who="S0086">might be yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0041">she was really padded up so I couldn't tell <pause dur="short"/> but I remember thinking before to myself that she was bigger than I first thought she was we when she was still here</u>
<u n="307" who="S0086">yeah yeah which is only a month what? Six weeks? Couple of months?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0086">on no hang on <pause dur="short"/> did she move out before? I thought she moved out in January but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> reckons it was before Christmas so</u>
<u n="310" who="S0041">was it?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0086">I thought it was January but who can say</u>
<u n="312" who="S0041">just have been before Christmas cos when we had those strangers round here when I invited he strangers round here</u>
<u n="313" who="S0086">yes absolutely let's take some responsibility there <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was here?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0041">no there was no one here</u>
<u n="315" who="S0086">oh that's right because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>didn't get invited round to her <trunc>f</trunc> her family for Christmas <pause dur="short"/> cos they're really nice</u>
<u n="316" who="S0041">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's normal <pause dur="short"/> well I can hardly talk about normal can I?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0086">well <pause dur="short"/> like yesterday <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like oh so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is coming round tonight <pause dur="short"/> and I was like oh that's <pause dur="short"/> cos then cos obviously I'd said this whole thing about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he was yeah but oh they've broken up and I didn't know <pause dur="short"/> and em he was like yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is coming round tonight and I was like it's so weird like it's all happened on the same day <pause dur="short"/> and I said oh you know this is the second time you'd have seen her <pause dur="short"/> so that's really good then are trying to maybe get your friendship back on track <pause dur="short"/> he's like yeah you know she knows that that's what I was going too <pause dur="short"/> I was always going to cut her out <pause dur="short"/> or I was always going to whatever <pause dur="short"/> and I was like yeah well you know cutting her out was pretty harsh he was I didn't cut her out <pause dur="short"/> and then literally like five minutes later he's like yeah so I had to cut her out <pause dur="short"/> and I was like this is</u>
<u n="318" who="S0041">oh my god</u>
<u n="319" who="S0086">what are you talking about?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0041">do you think? I can't decide whether he's crazy or he's really stupid</u>
<u n="321" who="S0086">bit of both  Bit of both And and just you know not educated really <pause dur="short"/> I think that's what it comes down to <pause dur="short"/> I just I think he forget <trunc>a</trunc> also I think maybe my manners rubs him up with wrong way so if I say to him well you did you were pretty hard pretty speedy to cut her out your life <pause dur="short"/> and he was like I don't cut her out of my life <pause dur="short"/> and then obviously bit later he was like yeah well she can fuck off you know she knew that I was going to cut her out <pause dur="short"/> like he's showing off and you're like <pause dur="short"/> you already know that I think that your behaviour was despicable</u>
<u n="322" who="S0041">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you know what else I think as well <pause dur="short"/> I think sometimes he forgets that we're brighter than he is <pause dur="short"/> like when he's talking I think he like I think amongst other people he's probably his motley crew of nut jobs <pause dur="short"/> he likes to he likes to pontificate a lot</u>
<u n="323" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> he talks a lot of this <pause dur="short"/> he gives it the big I am</u>
<u n="324" who="S0041">and he obviously never gets pulled up on it <pause dur="short"/> so when you do pull him up he's like no brr brr</u>
<u n="325" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="326" who="S0041">frigging idiot <pause dur="short"/> like yeah I've organised <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> party so you organise yours</u>
<u n="327" who="S0086">yeah thanks for that <pause dur="short"/> it's my fucking birthday</u>
<u n="328" who="S0041" trans="overlap">in my house and I said to him it's my house</u>
<u n="329" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0041">he said eh it's my house <pause dur="short"/> that's what he replied</u>
<u n="331" who="S0086">that's what he said it's my house <pause dur="short"/> charming <pause dur="short"/> welcome welcome <pause dur="short"/> oh he's such a knob man</u>
<u n="332" who="S0041">I want to kick him in the head</u>
<u n="333" who="S0086">fair enough don't we all <pause dur="short"/> don't all women want <pause dur="short"/> oh he's such a weirdo</u>
<u n="334" who="S0041">that grill that was here though I'm sure he said sonly twenty <pause dur="short"/> twenty twenty twenty-five twenty-six <pause dur="short"/> twenty-six</u>
<u n="335" who="S0086">yeah twenty-six I think</u>
<u n="336" who="S0041">she looked well older than twenty-six</u>
<u n="337" who="S0086">do you think she's having him on?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I thought she she looks a lot older than you</u>
<u n="339" who="S0086">she does she's got</u>
<u n="340" who="S0041">did you see her wrinkles?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0086">she's got a lot of lines yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0086">she should be getting the old Olay out <pause dur="short"/> that's what you need</u>
<u n="344" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0086">em yeah she did have lines</u>
<u n="346" who="S0041">she looked  She looked  old</u>
<u n="347" who="S0086">yeah I mean maybe she's tired <pause dur="short"/> maybe the kids are young and maybe she's having to get up with the kids <pause dur="short"/> I don't ever have to do that which is good</u>
<u n="348" who="S0041">yeah cos you've got sense</u>
<u n="349" who="S0086">Cos I've got a brain</u>
<u n="350" who="S0041">did I tell  Did I tell  you I was joking to dad about walking round in a bikini</u>
<u n="351" who="S0086">with your dad?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0041">not not with my dad but I was joking with my dad</u>
<u n="353" who="S0086">oh right</u>
<u n="354" who="S0041">I was just like <pause dur="short"/> when he was on the phone before obviously he started talking about women canoodling and obviously that was all too too raw too raw <pause dur="short"/> eh I was walking home and I was saying <pause dur="short"/> he said ooh when could all this take place and I've been through this for him a million times <pause dur="short"/> so if someone else drops out then I can in September that's the plan <pause dur="short"/> the likely hood of that happening is pretty slim but that's what we're hoping for</u>
<u n="355" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0041">he's like right okay and I said em and then obviously there'll be twelve week intensive training then after that it'll be more leadership based <pause dur="short"/> so I just have to get through the twelve week power on through cry every day</u>
<u n="357" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0041">secretly cry</u>
<u n="359" who="S0086">sob</u>
<u n="360" who="S0041">sob secretly</u>
<u n="361" who="S0086">defeat <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was telling me s story about how he had to get into bed like he couldn't move his arms because of the weights training <pause dur="short"/> for three days couldn't move his arms because he was being a pillock probably and doing above what he should have been doing <pause dur="short"/> and they're really really pushing him so he's like yeah of course I can do it of course I can do it because he's like a fucking monkey <pause dur="short"/> and eh he couldn't get it when he got into bed he had to get into bed like that like in the foetal position and then like try and hook the duvet up like with his knee over it because he couldn't extend his arms and then he had to get his leg and like get his leg to extend his arm <pause dur="short"/> and he would cry because his arms hurt that much <pause dur="short"/> that's what they're I just want out to be aware</u>
<u n="362" who="S0041">I won't be having to do that</u>
<u n="363" who="S0086">I would hope not</u>
<u n="364" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="365" who="S0086">and obviously you will not be doing ridiculous things like him like yesterday when he was like it's run a five minute mile and then he literally destroyed himself <unclear/> twenty things</u>
<u n="366" who="S0041">no I won't have to do that <pause dur="short"/> no no no no no no</u>
<u n="367" who="S0086">it's mad <pause dur="short"/> so yes you'll have a twelve week intensive don't break your arms</u>
<u n="368" who="S0041">death <pause dur="short"/> try not to break your arms don't let them see you cry</u>
<u n="369" who="S0086">Don't let them see you cry</u>
<u n="370" who="S0041">want to kill yourself more or less every day</u>
<u n="371" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> don't laugh in their face also <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0041">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0086">turns out they don't like that</u>
<u n="374" who="S0041">not turns out I'm not sure I'll be able to hold that but <pause dur="short"/> if it's going to result in death then I think I'm one be more scared</u>
<u n="375" who="S0086">iron your bed at night</u>
<u n="376" who="S0041">if they seriously do that I'm just going to laugh <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="377" who="S0086">that's what they did <pause dur="short"/> they slept on the floor</u>
<u n="378" who="S0041">that's the problem</u>
<u n="379" who="S0086">they ironed their beds</u>
<u n="380" who="S0041">like if I have to go on with the kids if I have to go in with the kids I'm not going to take it seriously</u>
<u n="381" who="S0086">yeah I know</u>
<u n="382" who="S0041">they'll be shitting themselves and I'll be like are you taking the piss?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0086">have you been in the real world?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0041">yeah like eighteen nineteen twenty twenty-one twenty-two twenty-three twenty-four twenty-five twenty-six <pause dur="short"/> eight years I'll have on these people <pause dur="short"/> eight years of life and I'll be like are you actually having a laugh</u>
<u n="385" who="S0086">do they pit you all in together then people going in as an officer and people going into <unclear/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> officers are all together ratings are all together but obviously you can't be an officer unless you've done you're A-levels so although you would be eighteen the likely hood of anybody that's eighteen years old getting throughout interview bit at the end is very unlikely <pause dur="short"/> they'd probably minimum age twenty</u>
<u n="387" who="S0086">oh good okay</u>
<u n="388" who="S0041">so that's a bit more</u>
<u n="389" who="S0086">that's more bearable <pause dur="short"/> that's only six years</u>
<u n="390" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> em</u>
<u n="391" who="S0086">hilarious <pause dur="short"/> so your dad didn't really realise when you would be going then?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0041">no so when I said this he was like oh right and then twelve weeks training so</u>
<u n="393" who="S0086">and I said yeah and then you get to come and see my pass out parade <pause dur="short"/> note me saying you can come not if you can come cos I might not do it we'll go with yes I will <pause dur="short"/> yes I can <pause dur="short"/> and em he's like oh yes that should  that should  be about December time <pause dur="short"/> and I was like yes obviously by which time after all the running all the time every day I will be so fit I'll be walking round in a bikini and <trunc>everyo</trunc> everyone will be saying Charlie but it's minus one and I'll be saying do my abs give fuck</u>
<u n="394" who="S0086"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0041">and he was like oh yeah I could <pause dur="short"/> he says of yeah I can shut see it now pass out day no one's on the stiff and you've got a bikini on to match your hat <pause dur="short"/> I was like yeah <pause dur="short"/> if you see a blue one while you're out</u>
<u n="396" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0086">yeah I can just see that you maniac</u>
<u n="398" who="S0041">like the photograph you have for your graduation except that I'm bikinied <pause dur="short"/> can you imagine? Do you think they'd throw you out for that?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0086">em I think they'd take it pretty seriously <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a pretty big deal I think you know</u>
<u n="400" who="S0041">I mean I don't think I'm going to tell them hat at the interview</u>
<u n="401" who="S0086">I plan on just wearing a bikini</u>
<u n="402" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0086">I mean you say this now but I think you've forgotten how fucking cold it is when it's minus one <pause dur="short"/> so you might really want to be parading round in your bikini but em no <pause dur="short"/> you might actually you might actually be blue yourself from hypothermia so</u>
<u n="404" who="S0041">match the hat</u>
<u n="405" who="S0086">match the hat yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then the lips go blue and then you die so</u>
<u n="406" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's wrong</u>
<u n="408" who="S0041">probably didn't think that through far enough did I?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0086">mm well it's a plan <pause dur="short"/> it's a definite plan</u>
<u n="410" who="S0041">my eyes feel really dry like there's no eye juice in them</u>
<u n="411" who="S0086">keep blinking</u>
<u n="412" who="S0041">it's like a rave</u>
<u n="413" who="S0086">yeah disco disco <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to go to work tomorrow</u>
<u n="414" who="S0041">I really don't want to go to work tomorrow</u>
<u n="415" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> say it isn't true</u>
<u n="416" who="S0041">ah Ed was saying we had an Apple conference in last week <pause dur="short"/> obviously he does all the helping around the people out there and I hide in the office <pause dur="short"/> em Apple approached him to poach him</u>
<u n="417" who="S0086">really?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0041">and they said you know we we very rarely do recruitment event co we just head hunt people <pause dur="short"/> we go to enough places to spot the people that we want <pause dur="short"/> eh <pause dur="short"/> how much are you on here? So he lied and said twenty <pause dur="short"/> he's not he's probably on what I'm on</u>
<u n="419" who="S0086">really</u>
<u n="420" who="S0041">twenty okay well we can offer twenty-one would you leave?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0086">nice and is he owing time</u>
<u n="422" who="S0041">in the shop I think it's just a sales assistant job</u>
<u n="423" who="S0086">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> you get a wear a T-shirt saying I'm a genius or something don't they?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0041">well yeah yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0086">so that's pretty awesome</u>
<u n="426" who="S0041">but em yeah once you're in Apple apparently it's quite difficult get promoted <pause dur="short"/> cos they're all very yeah we all love everything <pause dur="short"/> frigging nutters <pause dur="short"/> so they're all like there are all the people that are there are very brand eared like they're very we love Apple we all want to progress in the Apple</u>
<u n="427" who="S0086">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah that would cheese you right off</u>
<u n="428" who="S0041">yeah wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0086">oh that's pretty exciting though <pause dur="short"/> it us be nice to be headhunted</u>
<u n="430" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="431" who="S0086">we had em we had an email come round <pause dur="short"/> they do these things called <anon type="place"/> announces <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> I presume I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I've got this instant reflex where I delete it and then everyone's like did you read the <anon type="place"/> announce <pause dur="short"/> no tell me <pause dur="short"/> summarise very quickly in ten seconds and I will have lost interest <pause dur="short"/> em within ELT our business they they're very they had they've had two restructures in the two years that I've been there and then we're also in another restructure <pause dur="short"/> so we're restructuring ourselves into the original structure that was destructured <pause dur="short"/> so we're constantly in a state of flux like no one's ever no one's ever really in one position at all you're just constantly moving</u>
<u n="432" who="S0041">yeah I love that</u>
<u n="433" who="S0086">so that's nice that's you know fluid <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> and they'd create these three heads of business like one for school books one for school publishing one for adult book publishing and one for exams publishing <pause dur="short"/> but exams which is the list I work on is doing its own rogue thing in the corner because they work with <anon type="place"/> Assessment but no one really understands what they do <pause dur="short"/> so there are three but the exams one is over the secret things</u>
<u n="434" who="S0041">A bit mental <pause dur="short"/> secret squirrel things</u>
<u n="435" who="S0086" trans="overlap">nobody would go and talk to them cos they do their own secret thing so <unclear/> no one really understands that but it's fine</u>
<u n="436" who="S0041">yeah <anon type="place"/> Assessment one of our biggest clients</u>
<u n="437" who="S0086">yeah it's cos ESOL an just do what they like because we we need them <pause dur="short"/> so they go oh we're only go to pay you X amount of money <pause dur="short"/> oh okay</u>
<u n="438" who="S0041">nice</u>
<u n="439" who="S0086">but can we still use your <unclear/></u>
<u n="440" who="S0041">I was talking to somebody from <anon type="place"/> <trunc>ases</trunc> <anon type="place"/> actually</u>
<u n="441" who="S0086">oh nice</u>
<u n="442" who="S0041">his name's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> nig <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0086">ah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0041">but we call him in the office and I call him eh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0086"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> the <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> the <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s here <pause dur="short"/> not that I've ever met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I just speak to him a lot on the phone</u>
<u n="447" who="S0086">yeah I don't know what he looks like <pause dur="short"/> I don't think he I wouldn't work with me <pause dur="short"/> but obviously there's a thousand people on site so</u>
<u n="448" who="S0041">well yeah that's what I mean <pause dur="short"/> I see the name and I think ooh Liz might know him and I think how the fucks that going to happen</u>
<u n="449" who="S0086">definitely going to look him up in connections tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> but em so they restructured this restructure about six months ago <pause dur="short"/> and em and obviously now we we're now in in the new restructure <pause dur="short"/> and one of them has been headhunted y the head of <trunc>in</trunc> you know <anon type="place"/> it's like an alternative to A-level <pause dur="short"/> has been head hunted to be the head of <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> she's going to go and work in <anon type="place"/> but she's going to you know</u>
<u n="450" who="S0041">what the fuck? Seriously?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0086">yeah yeah she's going to go and</u>
<u n="452" who="S0041">how the hell did that happen?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0086">create their publishing program in relation to the curriculum <pause dur="short"/> its fucking <trunc>men</trunc> she's going to be on ridiculous money <pause dur="short"/> but she's only just been appointed as this head of em school book publishing literally a matter of months ago <pause dur="short"/> so I read the I actually read this announcement one of the few that I actually do</u>
<u n="454" who="S0041">which you hadn't deleted</u>
<u n="455" who="S0086">yeah yeah cos everyone was like have you heard <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s leaving I was like no hang on wait a minute let me get go through my trash <pause dur="short"/> em and they said yeah she's you know she's been recruited to be head of whatever and we're all very excited blah de blah <pause dur="short"/> okay wow it's amazing <pause dur="short"/> speaking to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it turns out the they that she works in education and I work in ELT that their head of education was headhunted first <pause dur="short"/> she turned it down but said to her boss like the director I've been headhunted I want a better position and I want more money and they went okay oh my god right stay and we'll create this new  this new  role for you which was announced last week and now I know why because that that was her bargaining chip <pause dur="short"/> cos she was the one who was actually headhunted <pause dur="short"/> she turned it down <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she turned it down and now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got it <pause dur="short"/> but it's so good because I mean it's a <trunc>n</trunc> it's a fantastic opportunity for anybody to be em headhunted at that level but it's a woman <pause dur="short"/> like it's a female <pause dur="short"/> it's really good <pause dur="short"/> it's really really good <pause dur="short"/> cos even though publishing is a  is a  real female orientated industry the top jobs are still blokes</u>
<u n="456" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's the same in any industry isn't it? I know it sound really old fashioned but it's true <pause dur="short"/> you hot a certain level and then it's male dominated</u>
<u n="457" who="S0086">well it's disgusting and it shouldn't be the case <pause dur="short"/> so it's nice it's refreshing actually cos even on our senior management team the majority positions are held by men <pause dur="short"/> and that's only middle management</u>
<u n="458" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="459" who="S0086">so yeah it's really it's difficult</u>
<u n="460" who="S0041">I think it's because men are  men are  easier at piggy backing <pause dur="short"/> I've said this for years <pause dur="short"/> a good manager a good CEO is a good piggy backer <pause dur="short"/> they're not good at anything themselves but they're god a seeing who's good at the stuff and using people</u>
<u n="461" who="S0086">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="462" who="S0041">and I think women and less incline to do that</u>
<u n="463" who="S0086">yeah well you you sort of you take a lot of responsibility on your own shoulders I think that's she difficulty</u>
<u n="464" who="S0041">or if you're in a team you want to work with the team not use the team <pause dur="short"/> and I think once you get to a certain level you've got to be able to extract yourself from it</u>
<u n="465" who="S0086">yeah yeah yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="466" who="S0041">and see even above the top line <pause dur="short"/> like my dad was saying and I was debating going in as an officer or a rating I was like I don't really want to I want to be invoked with people <pause dur="short"/> and he was like no no no do you want to be giving the orders or taking the orders <pause dur="short"/> and I was like yeah but it'll be your whole if cos you'll be there all the time <pause dur="short"/> there's no going home from work <pause dur="short"/> and he was like yeah but you're still going to have friends there <pause dur="short"/> they'll just be on a similar level to you <pause dur="short"/> and I said but like he said well I never went home did I? I was on the side I said but were you friends with them? He said no <pause dur="short"/> I said well there you go I want friendships out of it <pause dur="short"/> and he said well I still go out with them but they're more acquaintances <pause dur="short"/> and for him it was very easy and it always has been he's always down the same job <pause dur="short"/> that</u>
<u n="467" who="S0086">he could draw a line</u>
<u n="468" who="S0041">yeah and I think  I think  girls naturally find it more difficult cos you don't <pause dur="short"/> I think girls like to please each other more than man do</u>
<u n="469" who="S0086">yeah yeah absolutely <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah or or you find that you get <pause dur="short"/> I think that's the problem that women then try and adopt male attributes in order to progress <pause dur="short"/> and they're either seen as ah you know she's being a cow or <pause dur="short"/> women get it slightly wrong or they go a bit you know or they just delegate everything and they just piss on their thrones <pause dur="short"/> we like one of our directors is female and she's just a massive twat she doesn't do anything she just delegated everything and the everyone ends up really stressed and motivated as opposed to feeling empowered to do stuff because they're being utilised for their articular skill set <pause dur="short"/> they're not there just becoming digs bodies <pause dur="short"/> de-skilled and demotivated so</u>
<u n="470" who="S0041">oh my god <pause dur="short"/> so today I went on the em website for the company I used to work for</u>
<u n="471" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="472" who="S0041">and before I left I was trying to encourage him to retain to work on his retention but he just he don't <pause dur="short"/> he wanted to do it but he just never really implemented it <pause dur="short"/> and I said well I'm doing all this marketing I need a bigger marketing base <pause dur="short"/> so every time somebody asks for a quote I should have their details I should have their at least their email address whack on marketing list <pause dur="short"/> I said cos as long as it's relevant to them then we're not spamming them</u>
<u n="473" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0041">he's like yeah okay so we should do that and then I said okay encouraging people even just to leave their information if I put if I write some things to go on like a guide to  a guide to  translation or guide to search engine optimisation but in a foreign language <pause dur="short"/> even if it's just like a little bit of information for people that have never done it before <pause dur="short"/> so just like side of A four which some things some people already know <pause dur="short"/> but people don't know about like the software that automatically translates stuff like translation memory <pause dur="short"/> people don't know whether tis <pause dur="short"/> you assume they do cos we've been in this field for a long time <pause dur="short"/> and he's been in it for like twenty years</u>
<u n="475" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="476" who="S0041">well usually people don't know that exists <pause dur="short"/> every time you send something to a translator they put it through a machine basically that remembers <pause dur="short"/> it breaks down the sentences in smaller chunks and remembers it <pause dur="short"/> so if one time you translate and there was and it comes up later as you start to write it auto-populates it and you can see and click yes or no <pause dur="short"/> which is great because especially if you work for say Microsoft and you get stuff from them every month the way they phrase things their terminology is going to repeated through everything they do <pause dur="short"/> it's quicker for you to click yes than it is to translate it <pause dur="short"/> so it speeds it up it makes it more accurate and more consistent and therefore more cost effective <pause dur="short"/> cos you don't get charged for the repetition</u>
<u n="477" who="S0086">okay</u>
<u n="478" who="S0041">they charge you I think it's like five per cent of the unit price for any words that are repeated <pause dur="short"/> so in layman's terms it takes a long time to explain and he didn't really get it but I was telling people and they were like ah <pause dur="short"/> what's that then? I was like you know like in Word when you write the date you write the first two letters and it <trunc>ci</trunc> brings it up and you can put yes or onto <pause dur="short"/> that's basically it <pause dur="short"/> em so I wrote three three different things for him <pause dur="short"/> I said if we put them on the website people want to click to download their free information on whatever it is <pause dur="short"/> and then in order to download it you ask for their email <pause dur="short"/> cos they're getting something cos they're getting free information and we're getting something cos we get their email went on the fucking website today <pause dur="short"/> leven's top tips for something or other <pause dur="short"/> my fucking writing</u>
<u n="479" who="S0086">oh god</u>
<u n="480" who="S0041">as is as if he's done it?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0086">really?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0041">and he's edited some of it relay poorly and the font <pause dur="short"/> oh my god <pause dur="short"/> oh my god <pause dur="short"/> whoever choose the typeface <pause dur="short"/> the typeface isn't the same as the rest of the branding of the company</u>
<u n="483" who="S0086">nice</u>
<u n="484" who="S0041">and it it's all wonky like I don't</u>
<u n="485" who="S0086">have they got a copy writer in to do it or would they just have done it themselves</u>
<u n="486" who="S0041">published it themselves</u>
<u n="487" who="S0086">urgh</u>
<u n="488" who="S0041">but we do have a typesetter <pause dur="short"/> like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> works on InDesign <pause dur="short"/> how the hell she let that go through <pause dur="short"/> I think it's more of a a thing of taste as opposed to anything else</u>
<u n="489" who="S0086" trans="overlap">Jesus <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0041">but yeah as his own not even accredited or nothing</u>
<u n="491" who="S0086">yeah not even a message to say <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thanks again for this idea I'm going to run with it just FYI</u>
<u n="492" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> not even idea I'd written it</u>
<u n="493" who="S0086">oh right its actually the text that you left</u>
<u n="494" who="S0041" trans="overlap">I'd written everything <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'd written three separate things <pause dur="short"/> left them with him</u>
<u n="495" who="S0086">oh god yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0041">and he's taken part of one and part of the other and moshed it together and it's bad</u>
<u n="497" who="S0086">ah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0041">yeah but I was like what the fuck?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0041">gutted</u>
<u n="501" who="S0086">that's shitty that's absolutely shitty</u>
<u n="502" who="S0041">yeah and you can see the difference because I on the website from ages ago when I was there</u>
<u n="503" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0041">there is something still written that says my by <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> marketing manager</u>
<u n="505" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="506" who="S0041">and you can see the difference between the two levels of English <pause dur="short"/> it's so different</u>
<u n="507" who="S0086">that's so shitty <pause dur="short"/> that's really really shady <pause dur="short"/> really shady <pause dur="short"/> but then I mean obviously he is going to do that you know he is going to try and get stuff for free and not have to pay for it</u>
<u n="508" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I've just thought of something <pause dur="short"/> what are you doing now?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0086">em I'm getting a yoghurt</u>
<u n="510" who="S0041">are you?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0086">do you want one?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0041">well I thought I did and then I thought I might want some Fish Food</u>
<u n="513" who="S0086">I do probably need some Fish Food <unclear/> Investigation <pause dur="short"/> why? <unclear/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's pretty secure <pause dur="short"/> blind <pause dur="short"/> disco disco <pause dur="short"/> right and</u>
<u n="514" who="S0041">required <pause dur="short"/> there's not loads lift but there's still a decent amount</u>
<u n="515" who="S0086">em <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> is this your washing in the machine?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0041">it's my towel</u>
<u n="517" who="S0086">ah did it come good?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0041" trans="overlap">my blue towel <pause dur="short"/> eh no it's blue</u>
<u n="519" who="S0086">blue is nice though and as you say at least it's not streaky</u>
<u n="520" who="S0041">put it on the <pause dur="short"/> it is blue <pause dur="short"/> oh last night I wanted to go to sleep and the washing still <unclear/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0086">ah man</u>
<u n="522" who="S0041">I need you for the morning</u>
<u n="523" who="S0086">that's pretty dedicated <pause dur="short"/> how late did you have to stay up?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0041">well I fell fell to sleep at about elven <pause dur="short"/> set my alarm for one <pause dur="short"/> slept like two hours got up took it out and then</u>
<u n="525" who="S0086">that is not fun times <pause dur="short"/> is it called <anon type="place"/> yes?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0086"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0041">but I think it's vaginal</u>
<u n="529" who="S0086"><trunc>Vag</trunc> vaginald yeah <pause dur="short"/> that sounds about right actually <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/>Stop in the name of love<shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> impinge? No</u>
<u n="530" who="S0041">impinge</u>
<u n="531" who="S0086"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> swimming pool <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="532" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="533" who="S0086">that's that's the one <pause dur="short"/> oh blah de blah is that actually the thing <pause dur="short"/> so there not a a <trunc>we</trunc> a age for it?</u>
<u n="534" who="S0041">em yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think it's <anon type="place"/> village college and then you click on the</u>
<u n="535" who="S0086">aH that's swimming club <pause dur="short"/> well the first one that comes up is called swimming <anon type="place"/> village college <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if that's <pause dur="short"/> oh okay <pause dur="short"/> here we go <pause dur="short"/> clubs birthday parties swimming time table</u>
<u n="536" who="S0041">yeah time table</u>
<u n="537" who="S0086">ah thanks mate <pause dur="short"/> this website address is a bit weird <pause dur="short"/> c G U <pause dur="short"/> don't know what that is <pause dur="short"/> while we're young</u>
<u n="538" who="S0041">I wonder if it was six forty-five</u>
<u n="539" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> well it would be nice if it was six forty-five</u>
<u n="540" who="S0041">ah I meant the spoon</u>
<u n="541" who="S0086">bent the spoon</u>
<u n="542" who="S0041">trying to get the ice-cream out</u>
<u n="543" who="S0086">oh well</u>
<u n="544" who="S0041">I was telling everyone at work about this ice cream today</u>
<u n="545" who="S0086">it's pretty good <pause dur="short"/> it's the best invention I think ever</u>
<u n="546" who="S0041">I think it's the best thing I ever tasted under five per cent fat</u>
<u n="547" who="S0086">why are you not working?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0041">I don't think that's the</u>
<u n="549" who="S0086">you don't think that's the thing? Does that not look familiar</u>
<u n="550" who="S0041">no no it doesn't</u>
<u n="551" who="S0086">that's the thing that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> no that might not be the thing <pause dur="short"/> okay that's probably not the thing <pause dur="short"/> no swim guidelines <pause dur="short"/> swim <pause dur="short"/> swimming swimming</u>
<u n="552" who="S0041">that's definitely not</u>
<u n="553" who="S0086">that is  That is  the thing it says swim</u>
<u n="554" who="S0041">that's not the webpage I usually go on</u>
<u n="555" who="S0086">okay abort abort</u>
<u n="556" who="S0041">put in Impington village <pause dur="short"/> did our put in Impington vagina college before</u>
<u n="557" who="S0086">I did no yes <pause dur="short"/> but it didn't come up <pause dur="short"/> village pool <pause dur="short"/> village <pause dur="short"/> impington village centre isn't it?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0041">no college</u>
<u n="559" who="S0086">college yes yes</u>
<u n="560" who="S0041">not <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="561" who="S0086">not vagina centre <pause dur="short"/> who keeps saying that? Not me <pause dur="short"/> it's not me</u>
<u n="562" who="S0041">remind me while we're there to ask them if they've got ropes</u>
<u n="563" who="S0086">what?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0041">ropes</u>
<u n="565" who="S0086">oh you've got to climb the rope yeah <pause dur="short"/> good luck with that <pause dur="short"/> ah here we go I recognise the horrible sign</u>
<u n="566" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="567" who="S0086"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> no not you <pause dur="short"/> adult learning and community <pause dur="short"/> you're what we need <pause dur="short"/> for special people</u>
<u n="568" who="S0041">I think you probably wanted the sport centre bit</u>
<u n="569" who="S0086">ah look at that man getting a good feel on <pause dur="short"/> he was there last week wasn't he?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="571" who="S0086">dirty boy</u>
<u n="572" who="S0041">know your game</u>
<u n="573" who="S0086">yeah know what you're about <pause dur="short"/> filth meister <pause dur="short"/> filth meister general <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> background <pause dur="short"/> stop it <pause dur="short"/> my phone and me we're just not friends <pause dur="short"/> swimming pool <pause dur="short"/> thermal spa <pause dur="short"/> right we need to go to the thermal spa I think</u>
<u n="574" who="S0041">I think we have to be a member to go to the thermal spa</u>
<u n="575" who="S0086">but we are members we have cards</u>
<u n="576" who="S0041">oh does that make us members?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0086">probably not</u>
<u n="578" who="S0041">oh my god I haven't looked from my card</u>
<u n="579" who="S0086">opening times <pause dur="short"/> swimming pool timetable yes</u>
<u n="580" who="S0041">mm hm</u>
<u n="581" who="S0086">go go go <pause dur="short"/> is it with it spring twenty twelve?</u>
<u n="582" who="S0041">eh yes</u>
<u n="583" who="S0086">okay oh no it's downloading something</u>
<u n="584" who="S0041">it's going to open a PDF</u>
<u n="585" who="S0086">does it open on my phone?</u>
<u n="586" who="S0041">mm hm</u>
<u n="587" who="S0086">complete thing go <pause dur="short"/> there's a child on my phone</u>
<u n="588" who="S0041">that's it scroll down</u>
<u n="589" who="S0086">now but be de be <pause dur="short"/> it's challenging me now <pause dur="short"/> did I not tell you I've had a really difficult day <pause dur="short"/> right okay so tomorrow aqua <pause dur="short"/> this find is really not helping my eyes <pause dur="short"/> okay so tomorrow is Thursday we want to go to aqua fit Aaqua fit is green <pause dur="short"/> okay so bright green so you can't even read the numbers <pause dur="short"/> oh six thirty till seven thirty <pause dur="short"/> that's a bit of a bitch isn't it? Well we'll try <pause dur="short"/> I mean do they let you in if you're if you're late</u>
<u n="590" who="S0041">yeah I would have thought so <pause dur="short"/> well just kind of run run in throw the clothes</u>
<u n="591" who="S0086">yeah because we'll already have it on</u>
<u n="592" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> throw the clothes off</u>
<u n="593" who="S0086">yeah chuck them in</u>
<u n="594" who="S0041">and jump in</u>
<u n="595" who="S0086">jump in the pool <pause dur="short"/> probably won't jump in the poo cos I might drown <pause dur="short"/> ladies only</u>
<u n="596" who="S0041">for swimming yeah</u>
<u n="597" who="S0086">Cos they cos men are disgusting</u>
<u n="598" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0086">fifty plus I need to go to that</u>
<u n="600" who="S0041">which by the way is ageist</u>
<u n="601" who="S0086">adult lane <pause dur="short"/> that sex sex lane <pause dur="short"/> adult</u>
<u n="602" who="S0041">porn lanes</u>
<u n="603" who="S0086">porn lane <pause dur="short"/> shag-a-lagging <pause dur="short"/> don't get I the pool you'll catch babies <pause dur="short"/> you'll catch the babies <pause dur="short"/> I don't know where that stores does that? So that goes in downloads or something does it?</u>
<u n="604" who="S0041">eh yeah</u>
<u n="605" who="S0086">it's em I don't know</u>
<u n="606" who="S0041">going to go with yeah</u>
<u n="607" who="S0086">em <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="608" who="S0041">although I haven't looked for my card</u>
<u n="609" who="S0086">you never have your card <pause dur="short"/> they know you now</u>
<u n="610" who="S0041">I know <pause dur="short"/> but I remembered it last time and then I forgot it again and they get annoyed at me</u>
<u n="611" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0041">for forgetting it</u>
<u n="613" who="S0086">they think you're ditzy</u>
<u n="614" who="S0041">what the hell is it? I wonder if it's down the side of the bed? I thought I'd left it</u>
<u n="615" who="S0086">it's probably in the bed <pause dur="short"/> everything's in the bed <pause dur="short"/> if in doubt it's one the bed</u>
<u n="616" who="S0041">Earthier is that</u>
<u n="617" who="S0086">you know this now</u>
<u n="618" who="S0041">but I remember last time I had it was when I went swimming and I don't remember taking it back out of my bag but it's certainly not in there now <pause dur="short"/> which might mean it's gone forever</u>
<u n="619" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> it might have it might be gone then <pause dur="short"/> what will have to happen? Will they issue you with another card?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0041">they'll make me buy another card</u>
<u n="621" who="S0086">maybe they'll just shoot you</u>
<u n="622" who="S0041">I think that might be the option</u>
<u n="623" who="S0086">you know that Norwegian guy that killed seventy-seven people last year</u>
<u n="624" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="625" who="S0086">they found him sane</u>
<u n="626" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's had two medical assessments and the one last year said that he was insane and that he couldn't stand trial and now this one's found him sane <pause dur="short"/> but you do have to wonder are they just finding him sane that he so that he can stand trial even though he's mental <pause dur="short"/> because anyone that kills seventy-seven people and thinks because it's because they're all potential terrorists is probably a bit fucking mental <pause dur="short"/> so he he</u>
<u n="628" who="S0041">he killed them all because he thought they were all potential terrorists? Ah that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="629" who="S0086">he was on a crusade</u>
<u n="630" who="S0041">wow that sounds usual</u>
<u n="631" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean the first one diagnosed him as a paranoid schizophrenic <pause dur="short"/> so I don't know how you could get it so wrong</u>
<u n="632" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="633" who="S0086">how can one one lots of people say yeah he's fucking insane</u>
<u n="634" who="S0041">fucking crazy</u>
<u n="635" who="S0086">and others are like no</u>
<u n="636" who="S0041">he's fine</u>
<u n="637" who="S0086">sound as a penny <pause dur="short"/> put him on trial and then shoot him <pause dur="short"/> no I don't think they have the death penalty in Norway</u>
<u n="638" who="S0041" trans="overlap">they don't do that do they?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0086">I hope not <pause dur="short"/> I think it's just barbaric places like the US</u>
<u n="640" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="641" who="S0086">ah <pause dur="short"/> in a recent letter to a Norwegian tabloid he said being sent to a psychiatric ward would be a fate worth than death <pause dur="short"/> to send a political activist to an asylum is more sadistic and more evil than killing him <pause dur="short"/> says the crazy person</u>
<u n="642" who="S0041">oh so the crazy person says he's not crazy he says he's a political activist</u>
<u n="643" who="S0086">the crazy person thinks that it would be worse to send you to a psychiatric ward</u>
<u n="644" who="S0041">well I suppose they would drug you all the time and keep you in under</u>
<u n="645" who="S0086">and but he refers to himself as a political activist <pause dur="short"/> he's a murdering killed seventy-seven people</u>
<u n="646" who="S0041">although I think I would quite enjoyed being sedated for a little while</u>
<u n="647" who="S0086">em <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="648" who="S0041">think how relaxed it would be</u>
<u n="649" who="S0086">yeah I mean who need is a brain <pause dur="short"/> come on lobotomy <pause dur="short"/> come on get it out</u>
<u n="650" who="S0041">I often think that I should have lobotomy <pause dur="short"/> a temporary lobotomy <pause dur="short"/> you know just for like a day or two</u>
<u n="651" who="S0086">just put it in a jar or something <pause dur="short"/> put it back in</u>
<u n="652" who="S0041">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know like when you have a break up or you've got loads going on and you just think oh for god's sake <pause dur="short"/> you know those days when you can't stop your brain</u>
<u n="653" who="S0086">yeah you can</u>
<u n="654" who="S0041">playing scenarios</u>
<u n="655" who="S0086">maybe not a lobotomy maybe an on off switch</u>
<u n="656" who="S0041">mm <pause dur="short"/> that'd be easier than having the whole thing out and put back in again wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="657" who="S0086">just a bit messy I think bit fiddle some</u>
<u n="658" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="659" who="S0086">and they're attaching like you know nerve endings and stuff</u>
<u n="660" who="S0041">mm</u>
<u n="661" who="S0086">I mean unless we all you know have medical degrees</u>
<u n="662" who="S0041">or that crazy guy we watched the other day <pause dur="short"/> we need to do eight minute abs <pause dur="short"/> I probably should have done that before I had the ice-cream</u>
<u n="663" who="S0086">man my abs today are really killing me <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had me doing scissors kicks and all kinds of shenanigans yesterday <pause dur="short"/> I had to do <pause dur="short"/> I did press ups <pause dur="short"/> let's not get carried away cos I could only od one a time and then I had to collapse <pause dur="short"/> but he was sleek you're doing really well you're do and whether he was just saying that because he was like god she's she's a fool she can't do a press up <pause dur="short"/> but before he was it was really funny actually because I would like give him a bit of cheek like I can't do the number twenty-ones <pause dur="short"/> like when I had to do like that and then that and then the full one <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> I was really hurt <pause dur="short"/> I had to do that <pause dur="short"/> mean and I was like I can't do it <pause dur="short"/> and then he was like right we're going to do press ups now and I was like no I can't do it <pause dur="short"/> and he was like right you've got to do ten now <pause dur="short"/> I was like no honestly I can't do press-ups <pause dur="short"/> well you've got to do twelve now <pause dur="short"/> no but everything is I've tried to do press ups before and I can't do them <pause dur="short"/> well you're doing fifteen now <pause dur="short"/> I said well the thing is <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to start talking now cos you're going to make me do now <pause dur="short"/> and I <trunc>co</trunc> I did ten</u>
<u n="664" who="S0041">you managed to do ten real press ups?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I had I collapsed between each one <pause dur="short"/> cos he was like just dig <pause dur="short"/> and actually what he was saying was quite a good tip that I'd never hear was dig your toes in <pause dur="short"/> if you dig your toes in you've got a you've got something to help you up with <pause dur="short"/> because before I was like how do you or I don't have any upper arm strength so I just can't do it <pause dur="short"/> and what I found was I was always dropping my bum which is why I have trouble swimming I think <pause dur="short"/> I drop my bum rather than be like a plank rather than to be up down up down it would be more like that <pause dur="short"/> so I'd kind of go up as one and then drop and then down so it would be a bit <pause dur="short"/> it was never really even</u>
<u n="666" who="S0041">I really want to try après up but I'm a bit scared now</u>
<u n="667" who="S0086">it's really not a fun time  It's really not a fun time  so tats' why tomorrow I have to go running cos I didn't really do any cardio yesterday <pause dur="short"/> just went to bloody fishing game which is shit by the way</u>
<u n="668" who="S0041">fishing game? Ah</u>
<u n="669" who="S0086">on the rowing <pause dur="short"/> I always kept getting eaten <pause dur="short"/> big fish always came to eat me</u>
<u n="670" who="S0041">hang on a second you actually have a game</u>
<u n="671" who="S0086">on the rowing machine it's called go fish</u>
<u n="672" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="673" who="S0086">you'd think it would be really fun but it's shit</u>
<u n="674" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="675" who="S0086">basically what happens is the more the <trunc>ho</trunc> in theory what happens <pause dur="short"/> the harder you row your fish starts off at the bottom and there are little fish that are smaller than you that you get to eat to accrue points <pause dur="short"/> but there's big fish that will eat you and then you die and then you lose points and depending on how fast you row you move up and down the the space on the screen <pause dur="short"/> so if there's big fish at the top you want to kind of slow it down so you fall back down the screen and then you get to eat the little fish <pause dur="short"/> but then there's a big fish coming out the bottom <pause dur="short"/> you've got to speed up sp that's you're on the top in theory <pause dur="short"/> but even when you're going rowing like a fucking maniac you're not moving very quickly so you just get really annoyed co then you get eaten</u>
<u n="676" who="S0041">oh</u>
<u n="677" who="S0086">but I it's quite it takes your mind off the fact that you're rowing cos that's fucking boring let's be honest <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="678" who="S0041">yeah I don't have that game</u>
<u n="679" who="S0086">it's a really good work out</u>
<u n="680" who="S0041">I really want to see if I can do a boy press up <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I can</u>
<u n="681" who="S0086">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> I think I might actually die if I tried to do one <pause dur="short"/> I'll try and do one in a minute when I've eaten my from you <pause dur="short"/> but today man alive <pause dur="short"/> I tried to get out of bed and I went ah <pause dur="short"/> cos he was getting me to do ones for my top abs and one for my lower abs or something</u>
<u n="682" who="S0041">what did this entail <pause dur="short"/> that's what I think I need an abs workout</u>
<u n="683" who="S0086">it was quite good actually it was em <pause dur="short"/> sit ups and we've got one of those ones where it hold your feet but you have to you're lying down so so gravity is sort of working against you so you have to work harder <pause dur="short"/> but it means that your feet are are trapped so it makes it that bit easier in a way so it's <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit weird but I I don't really like doing those <pause dur="short"/> I can only do like three sets of fifteen on that <pause dur="short"/> and the we did ones one the mat but with em like a kettle bell and you've got to move your body from side to side as you sit up</u>
<u n="684" who="S0041">ah yeah</u>
<u n="685" who="S0086">and that was  that was quite good actually <pause dur="short"/> I found that having something in my hands actually made it easier</u>
<u n="686" who="S0041">ah</u>
<u n="687" who="S0086">like as a sort of way to motivate your body to get up <pause dur="short"/> having this weight and then like put it down on the mat so that you're moving your whole body <pause dur="short"/> cos what he's like you're moving your legs <pause dur="short"/> you're cheating <pause dur="short"/> you're <trunc>ch</trunc> you're still you're cheating now <pause dur="short"/> so he came and sat on my feet which helped <pause dur="short"/> it was put if you put it down on the mat you actually really make your body move <pause dur="short"/> so <unclear/> come and go mm yeah this is fine <pause dur="short"/> he's he was like yeah but your' doing it wring <pause dur="short"/> okay fine</u>
<u n="688" who="S0041">damn <pause dur="short"/> it</u>
<u n="689" who="S0086">yeah and then there was all kind of press ups occurring made want to cry</u>
<u n="690" who="S0041">really want to try it really bad <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I can do it through</u>
<u n="691" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> what he was saying he's got some pads for kickboxing I was like I really like kickboxing from when I went before <pause dur="short"/> he's like well I could take you and try it out for weekend for kickboxing</u>
<u n="692" who="S0041">that sounds fun</u>
<u n="693" who="S0086">which would be really fun <pause dur="short"/> cos when we use to go the guy used to make us like run up and down the room and like do lunges and kick really fast and it was really fast paid and I remember when I used to come home I was really buzzing <pause dur="short"/> I felt so energetic ad so just really buzzing like really pumped <pause dur="short"/> and even when I have like a workout now you know when you're having good run you sort of feel like yeah I could keep going I feel really good and then then you die</u>
<u n="694" who="S0041">well yeah of course</u>
<u n="695" who="S0086">I think like having that the difference with that was just doing yourself and having a class with that person there to motivate you <pause dur="short"/> it really really helps <pause dur="short"/> it's quite nice when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s there cos I just have a bit of a laugh <pause dur="short"/> like every time I laugh he makes me do more so I try not to laugh <pause dur="short"/> cos he's a bastard <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> but he does make me laugh so</u>
<u n="696" who="S0041">sounds fun <pause dur="short"/> yeah to be honest it was really nice having Nick there today <pause dur="short"/> I realised that I would never want to go anywhere with anyone doing anything ever</u>
<u n="697" who="S0086">no</u>
<u n="698" who="S0041">no never ever</u>
<u n="699" who="S0086">I really would like a personal trainer</u>
<u n="700" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="701" who="S0086">so expensive though</u>
<u n="702" who="S0041">yeah if I could afford it I would certainly have personal trainer all the time</u>
<u n="703" who="S0086">mm definitely <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="704" who="S0041">I'd love that</u>
<u n="705" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="706" who="S0041">hey ho <pause dur="short"/> I was thinking I've made no plans for the weekend actually <pause dur="short"/> I quite like it that way <pause dur="short"/> to be honest</u>
<u n="707" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> especially when living in a budget</u>
<u n="708" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="709" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="710" who="S0041">sounds like a granny but I'm really looking forward to sleep tonight <pause dur="short"/> I feel like I've not really slept properly for ages <pause dur="short"/> it's like Kate's been getting me up for doing or <pause dur="short"/> I had a lie in at the weekend and it didn't feel good enough</u>
<u n="711" who="S0086">I woke up I think it must have been <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s boyfriend rattling the bike chains at five o'clock this morning <pause dur="short"/> if he's got to leave at that time then I just don't understand why he has to stay <pause dur="short"/> I mean to be fair I haven't heard him for ages but <pause dur="short"/> it's not and he was I could tell he was trying to be quiet but really <pause dur="short"/> I just think if you're going to be leaving at five why stay?</u>
<u n="712" who="S0041">the thing that I don't understand is that he's an adult <pause dur="short"/> you're not a teenager you know <pause dur="short"/> you're not  You're not  a young person being a little bit selfish <pause dur="short"/> you're a fifty year old bloke <pause dur="short"/> have some self-respect</u>
<u n="713" who="S0086">yeah it's weird</u>
<u n="714" who="S0041">you would never I don't know any man that would knowingly wake up a household <pause dur="short"/> I just don't I mean I just don't know those people <pause dur="short"/> being quiet or not I mean it's just so so childish tapping around like that you just wouldn't degrade yourself in that way <pause dur="short"/> just have some dignity <pause dur="short"/> you're a fully you you're a fully grown man <pause dur="short"/> behave like one</u>
<u n="715" who="S0086">it was like when we <pause dur="short"/> when we had the argument with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> he just sloped of upstairs didn't he?</u>
<u n="716" who="S0041">yeah god you'd be so embarrassed if that was your boyfriend or whatever wouldn't you and he behaved like that</u>
<u n="717" who="S0086">horrendous <pause dur="short"/> like I barely speak to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> these days</u>
<u n="718" who="S0041">no me neither <pause dur="short"/> she was in here earlier and she barely looked up</u>
<u n="719" who="S0086">I just don't really have anything to say to her <pause dur="short"/> it was nice at she took Craig that dinner though</u>
<u n="720" who="S0041">yeah yeah I didn't expect hat</u>
<u n="721" who="S0086">it was really nice but em <pause dur="short"/> I'm just thinking it I appreciate that he's really making an effort to be quiet but I you have it's always hoping to wake us up <pause dur="short"/> cos it's a relay the walls are really thin and the bokes are noisy and if you are owing to be getting up at that time just don't leave your bike out the front <pause dur="short"/> go out the back <pause dur="short"/> because I can hear <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the kitchen <pause dur="short"/> she was up <pause dur="short"/> and that's what fucks you off like why do we wake up just because your boyfriend's staying and</u>
<u n="722" who="S0041">no it's just no</u>
<u n="723" who="S0086">and that's cos we're living on top of each other <pause dur="short"/> you know there's a lot of people in a house that was only really designed for three so <pause dur="short"/> it's hard</u>
<u n="724" who="S0041">yeah it drives me frigging nuts</u>
<u n="725" who="S0086">I'm not particularly careful <pause dur="short"/> like when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s round now not the he ever really stays the night but <pause dur="short"/> bertie beg your pardon <pause dur="short"/> just think <pause dur="short"/> I don't really I worry about his noise levels</u>
<u n="726" who="S0041">I never hear him never hear him</u>
<u n="727" who="S0086">really</u>
<u n="728" who="S0041">never have once heard him at all</u>
<u n="729" who="S0086">that's good <pause dur="short"/> I usually do tell him off in the mornings if he is here because he doesn't have an inside voice <pause dur="short"/> but I notice that <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> doesn't either cos when we got back from</u>
<u n="730" who="S0041"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't</u>
<u n="731" who="S0086">it's weird <pause dur="short"/> when we got back form <anon type="place"/> last Wednesday she was just talking like at this volume but it was one o'clock in the morning and everybody else obviously <unclear/> to talk quietly but no there was none of that <pause dur="short"/> so I was talking really like <vocal desc="misc"/> and show would just be carrying on as if <pause dur="short"/> she must have thought like why are you whispering <pause dur="short"/> or like she goes to the toilet and she doesn't turn the handle so she slams the door behind her and then slams it again when she comes out and leaves the light on <pause dur="short"/> she does it all the time she always leaves the light on <pause dur="short"/> I'm like em you've got to go in and turn the light on when you go in there <pause dur="short"/> we obviously always keep the light off <pause dur="short"/> it's just really the sort of thing that I can imagine <pause dur="short"/> her mum is really a stickler for stuff like that and I can see why her mum would get why they would get on each other's nerves cos the are polar opposites <pause dur="short"/> but then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I guess because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is really relaxed about stuff like that like it doesn't faze her <pause dur="short"/> she's just not bothered about it which is fine <pause dur="short"/> but for people who are a bit worried about you know either saving electricity or</u>
<u n="732" who="S0041">saving the planet</u>
<u n="733" who="S0086">saving the planet <pause dur="short"/> you know just I think that sort of passes her by <pause dur="short"/> and it's hard because she's so scattered like with her mum last Wednesday her mum was like have you got the tickets now are you sure you've got the tickets have you packed the tickets? Cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is really scattered she's like yeah mum fuck's sake I'm not a teenager <pause dur="short"/> it is the sort of thing she would do is get to mine of get to Norwich and realise she hasn't packed them</u>
<u n="734" who="S0041">she hasn't got them <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="735" who="S0086">so she did check like ten times though in her handbag <pause dur="short"/> and she actually made me check can you just check my handbag I've got the tickets I haven't <unclear/> them <pause dur="short"/> yeah no they're definitely there <pause dur="short"/> but it must be really infuriating for your mum not to trust you for your mum to treat you like a child because you are a bit scatty <pause dur="short"/> I think now she's so used to her own space it's the first time she's been living at home since she was what? Twenty-one <pause dur="short"/> so it is going to em it is going to take its toll <pause dur="short"/> even though my budget's shit I really want to go wild this weekend</u>
<u n="736" who="S0041">yep <pause dur="short"/> I definitely do</u>
<u n="737" who="S0086">I feel like we're overdue</u>
<u n="738" who="S0041">I feel like I'm I'm containing the crazy</u>
<u n="739" who="S0086">yeah I'm on the edge <pause dur="short"/> I think that's the problem with today I really feel like I need to have a big blow out</u>
<u n="740" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="741" who="S0086">and usually what happens when I feel like that is I get absolutely plastered by about eight thirty I've passed out in my own bed so <pause dur="short"/> so I am quite a cheap night out <pause dur="short"/> em but I guess your birthday's not so far away <pause dur="short"/> what is it the week after next? Two weeks this Saturday <pause dur="short"/> like your birthday is two weeks today <pause dur="short"/> your birthday's two week today</u>
<u n="742" who="S0041">oh no <pause dur="short"/> god twenty-two again</u>
<u n="743" who="S0086">twenty-two again <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> I love the fact that we can stop time <pause dur="short"/> that's my favourite thing</u>
<u n="744" who="S0041">yeah yeah I can</u>
<u n="745" who="S0086">yeah I think it's like superman when you just fly around the world three times</u>
<u n="746" who="S0041">yeah yes yeah that counts</u>
<u n="747" who="S0086">that's definitely fine <pause dur="short"/> this weekend no plan this weekend <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> sunny old <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="748" who="S0041">sun sunny <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="749" who="S0086">I don't know quite how one gets to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think one might have to brave the M twenty-five but I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> I think it's  I think it's  the <anon type="place"/> side</u>
<u n="750" who="S0041">what's the whole <anon type="place"/> plan?</u>
<u n="751" who="S0086">the whole <anon type="place"/> plan is going to my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house which involves meeting her mum which is quite nice cos I've never met her <pause dur="short"/> cos she's this is the friend that I stayed with when I was in Sydney but only know her through my friend Sophie who is getting married</u>
<u n="752" who="S0041">married</u>
<u n="753" who="S0086">she and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went to university together in <pause dur="short"/> that place beginning with W that one <anon type="place"/> in in the place with the forest</u>
<u n="754" who="S0041">right</u>
<u n="755" who="S0086">the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="756" who="S0041">the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="757" who="S0086">that's not what it's called <pause dur="short"/> it's the one with the ponies <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="758" who="S0041">forest with ponies?</u>
<u n="759" who="S0086">yeah it has like <anon type="place"/> ponies that's what they're called <pause dur="short"/> and they look like little <trunc>Shet</trunc> Shetland ponies <pause dur="short"/> adorable <pause dur="short"/> they've got really long shaggy hair so cute <pause dur="short"/> so yes they went to uni together and every time I went to visit <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'd see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and we became quite good friend which was nice <pause dur="short"/> and then after uni we'd all meet up and go for drinks and stiff and <pause dur="short"/> my plan  my plan  has always been to spend time in Australia and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like right I'm off to spend time in Australia and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like right I'm off <pause dur="short"/> probably because I was just like I'm never actually going to pull my finger out <pause dur="short"/> something always got in the way I was going to New Zealand or I was going away with Will and that also fell through <pause dur="short"/> so and then I was doing my degree my second degree s she went and then</u>
<u n="760" who="S0041">so she moved out there?</u>
<u n="761" who="S0086">she moved out there she's been there for two years <pause dur="short"/> so she did her first year there and she had to do one year's eh three months rural work which was sin the outback</u>
<u n="762" who="S0041">stupid berry picking</u>
<u n="763" who="S0086" trans="overlap">so she went out and did eh <pause dur="short"/> berry picking yeah <pause dur="short"/> eh she twisted her ankle</u>
<u n="764" who="S0041">sweeping everything a million times</u>
<u n="765" who="S0086">sweeping everything open the door the dust comes in again sweep again <pause dur="short"/> em she broke an ankle the flying doctors said no we can't come out today <pause dur="short"/> hold you shit together</u>
<u n="766" who="S0041">I'd love that</u>
<u n="767" who="S0086">we'll be out at some point in the next few days try not to die <pause dur="short"/> so that was really reassuring yeah</u>
<u n="768" who="S0041">yeah thanks yeah mm hm</u>
<u n="769" who="S0086">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what you get when yore's like a hundred K from civilisation <pause dur="short"/> so eh yeah so that's what she did and then she came back this time last year cos she went out in about March two years ago <pause dur="short"/> so she same back this time last year for about a month and then went back out <pause dur="short"/> and I think that's what she's doing now <pause dur="short"/> I think she's back for about six weeks so she gets back <pause dur="short"/> I think she might get ask this weekend <pause dur="short"/> or sometime next week <pause dur="short"/> quite soon anyway within the next week <pause dur="short"/> em she's going to stay at her mums <pause dur="short"/> so there's sort of reunion at hers</u>
<u n="770" who="S0041">Good</u>
<u n="771" who="S0086">next weekend <pause dur="short"/> and then for the weekend after that it's rest weekend after that will be <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s hen party that I'm not going to <pause dur="short"/> and then</u>
<u n="772" who="S0041">you have another rest</u>
<u n="773" who="S0086">then it's the wedding</u>
<u n="774" who="S0041">then it's the real wedding</u>
<u n="775" who="S0086">then it's the wedding and then its  and then its  <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="776" who="S0041">I can't believe haw quick that is</u>
<u n="777" who="S0086">I know <pause dur="short"/> so that's <anon type="place"/> then it's <anon type="place"/> to see my uni friends and the its <anon type="place"/> and then it's sit on your hands so you don't spend any money</u>
<u n="778" who="S0041">sit on your hands</u>
<u n="779" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> stare at the wall <pause dur="short"/> get in the old Tenancy brew because that's all I'll be able to afford Vinegar</u>
<u n="780" who="S0041">mouthwash</u>
<u n="781" who="S0086">drink drink the white wine vinegar <pause dur="short"/> the cider vinegar</u>
<u n="782" who="S0041"><vocal desc="laugh"/> White wine vinegar <pause dur="short"/> cider vinegar <pause dur="short"/> staple</u>
<u n="783" who="S0086">go and meet some friendly crack dealers get hooked on crack</u>
<u n="784" who="S0041">yes yes</u>
<u n="785" who="S0086">eh yeah all of those</u>
<u n="786" who="S0041">all of the above</u>
<u n="787" who="S0086">but then the weekend after that is the Jubilee weekend</u>
<u n="788" who="S0041">I haven't texted him actually <pause dur="short"/> find out what her life is</u>
<u n="789" who="S0086" trans="overlap">yeah see if she's still in the land of the living <pause dur="short"/> and young <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="790" who="S0041">and I need to text the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="791" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="792" who="S0041">she texted me actually over Easter weekend I completely forgot to reply</u>
<u n="793" who="S0086">Cos you're shocking</u>
<u n="794" who="S0041">Cos I really am shocking shopping</u>
<u n="795" who="S0086">I'm shopping now</u>
<u n="796" who="S0041">I'm really shopping</u>
<u n="797" who="S0086">no no it's not possible</u>
<u n="798" who="S0041">no</u>
<u n="799" who="S0086">that's just not going to happen I'm afraid <pause dur="short"/> is this mine? Yeah</u>
<u n="800" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="801" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="802" who="S0041">I just can' be bothered to text anybody <pause dur="short"/> it's just too too much hassle</u>
<u n="803" who="S0086">but it's so hard isn't it because I get a message from someone and I'm like oh that's so nice <pause dur="short"/> and then I put my phone down and it goes completely out of my mind <pause dur="short"/> like last night I <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> texted me on Saturday I think and just said do you want to catch up next week <pause dur="short"/> I was like yeah I haven't spoken to her in about a month so I really wanted to see how she was <pause dur="short"/> I was like yeah well look Tuesday's the next available day I'll call you then <pause dur="short"/> and last night was sat in her with Craig like basically just staring at him like a crazy person</u>
<u n="804" who="S0041">thinking what the fuck happened to your head</u>
<u n="805" who="S0086">what what is with you? What are you <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> I was just thinking oh I really can't be arsed to call anybody <pause dur="short"/> like it gets the the evening after work and I'm either I'm really knackered or I just think it's going to be really hard work which is so weird <pause dur="short"/> it's weird to think that talking to your friend who you care about it going to be hard work but</u>
<u n="806" who="S0041">but it's just the time it takes as well <pause dur="short"/> like I know once I'm on the phone to Sim it's for an hour two hours</u>
<u n="807" who="S0086">yeah easily yeah</u>
<u n="808" who="S0041">just</u>
<u n="809" who="S0086">and it's nice when your once you're on the phone it's fine <pause dur="short"/> but there's always that part of me that's like oh I don't know I don't really want to be on the phone</u>
<u n="810" who="S0041">once I'm on the phone I'm like why have I not called you for so long</u>
<u n="811" who="S0086">mm <pause dur="short"/> and it's nice and it's really easy and you know your realise how much you miss the person but</u>
<u n="812" who="S0041">yeah</u>
<u n="813" who="S0086">I'm really looking forward to the wedding actually <pause dur="short"/> cos I was saying cos her hen party is next I think they leave next Wednesday so it's a week today <pause dur="short"/> em it's the week I was saying oh are you go are you deliberately gone away cos it's the week of the Titanic celebrations <pause dur="short"/> she's like the week are you fucking having a laugh <pause dur="short"/> it's like it's going on all year <pause dur="short"/> like everywhere you go it's Titanic Titanic Titanic</u>
<u n="814" who="S0041" trans="overlap">yeah all the time</u>
<u n="815" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's driving em fucking loopy <pause dur="short"/> must be really bad it's like you'd l think that it would have sailed form Belfast</u>
<u n="816" who="S0041">people are going there on purpose</u>
<u n="817" who="S0086">yeah yeah to go and see them <pause dur="short"/> they've got a new museum haven't they?</u>
<u n="818" who="S0041">yeah apparently it look it's as big as the Titanic like it looks like the front of the building</u>
<u n="819" who="S0086">yeah yeah it looks really awesome I don't know if you've seen a picture of it? It looks really cool?</u>
<u n="820" who="S0041">no I haven't seen a picture of it</u>
<u n="821" who="S0086">I don't know if we'll have time <pause dur="short"/> I mean I'm not really that fussed about seeing the inside but to see that outside</u>
<u n="822" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="823" who="S0086">well we <pause dur="short"/> depending on how dead we feel in the morning <pause dur="short"/> I mean what we could do is just you know sort of power on through and then die <pause dur="short"/> cos the good thing is we're coming back on a Saturday and we've got</u>
<u n="824" who="S0041">we can have a whole dead day of death on Sunday</u>
<u n="825" who="S0086">exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="826" who="S0041">day of death and ice-cream</u>
<u n="827" who="S0086">yeah all of those <pause dur="short"/> yeah all of that <pause dur="short"/> em so yeah so we could  we could  try and fit in some sightseeing <pause dur="short"/> cos at least our flight is not until two or three or something like that <pause dur="short"/> probably should know my flights are</u>
<u n="828" who="S0041">yeah don't at al</u>
<u n="829" who="S0086">I really wish cos I think it was my fault I think I said lets book the flights now while they're cheap and what we should have done is book the Thursday night flights <pause dur="short"/> and stayed an extra night rather than have the hassle of rushing Friday morning <pause dur="short"/> never mind <pause dur="short"/> worse things have happened</u>
<u n="830" who="S0041">at sea</u>
<u n="831" who="S0086">at sea and</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="832" who="S0041">em he said you know we'll probably sell everything up and then I'll be moving up for up to Newcastle</u>
<u n="833" who="S0086">oh my god</u>
<u n="834" who="S0041">like the day the couple of days after I'll be ringing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to come and get his stuff and that will be that <pause dur="short"/> it's like fuck</u>
<u n="835" who="S0086">but then I suppose <pause dur="short"/> I mean did he think that that's an actual option?</u>
<u n="836" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> if she  If she  agrees to everything he's like great let's go</u>
<u n="837" who="S0086">quick quick quick <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="838" who="S0041">I was convinced they're <unclear/></u>
<u n="839" who="S0086">ah it's fine <pause dur="short"/> em well fingers crossed <pause dur="short"/> but then so she he's going to give her both of those options then that you were talking about the other day</u>
<u n="840" who="S0041">yeah and see what</u>
<u n="841" who="S0086">and see what she goes for</u>
<u n="842" who="S0041">see what she says</u>
<u n="843" who="S0086">are they talking at all?</u>
<u n="844" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> he was saying that she went he went into the hearing thing and she was in front of him so she was a person like that had most face time <pause dur="short"/> she didn't even say hello</u>
<u n="845" who="S0086">really?</u>
<u n="846" who="S0041">not alight how are you doing? Just nothing</u>
<u n="847" who="S0086">what is the matter with her? Well as we know she's mental</u>
<u n="848" who="S0041">she's a doosh</u>
<u n="849" who="S0086">she's actually evil <pause dur="short"/> oh don't worry about that it's yeah that's that's what I take my breakfast in</u>
<u n="850" who="S0041" trans="overlap">is this yours? Ha</u>
<u n="851" who="S0086">just leave it on the side honestly <pause dur="short"/> cos you probably smell that as well cos it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="852" who="S0041">it's too late</u>
<u n="853" who="S0086">here you go</u>
<u n="854" who="S0041">ah I've just realised I've got to pour put that soup that I left in the</u>
<u n="855" who="S0086">still?</u>
<u n="856" who="S0041">I left in the fridge</u>
<u n="857" who="S0086">well at least it hasn't got soup in now</u>
<u n="858" who="S0041">no it's not in the fridge now it's my room I brought it home today I haven't dared open it</u>
<u n="859" who="S0086">ah <pause dur="short"/> ah man alive</u>
<u n="860" who="S0041">it was only the first it was edible tomato south went in it <pause dur="short"/> the first lot <pause dur="short"/> so not the cabbage soup</u>
<u n="861" who="S0086">not the cabbage death</u>
<u n="862" who="S0041">not the  Not the  cabbage death</u>
<u n="863" who="S0086">that cabbage was nice though that we had with our roast chicken</u>
<u n="864" who="S0041">yeah I have cabbage in there I keep forgetting <pause dur="short"/> that's for tea tomorrow</u>
<u n="865" who="S0086">yum</u>
<u n="866" who="S0041">Don't know what I'm having with it <pause dur="short"/> cabbage and cabbage</u>
<u n="867" who="S0086">cabbage <pause dur="short"/> bubble and squeak?</u>
<u n="868" who="S0041">what goes in that again potato?</u>
<u n="869" who="S0086">potato and bacon <pause dur="short"/> but you could have ham</u>
<u n="870" who="S0041">I've got bacon in the fridge in the freezer</u>
<u n="871" who="S0086">there you go  There you go  So I think you do some sort of I don't really know how you do it <pause dur="short"/> it's like mashed potatoes cabbage and some sort of fried meat</u>
<u n="872" who="S0041">yeah it just all gets chucked in together doesn't it?</u>
<u n="873" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then I think you fry it <pause dur="short"/> it's sort of like frittata type situ</u>
<u n="874" who="S0041">mosh <pause dur="short"/> comes out looking like mosh</u>
<u n="875" who="S0086">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's got all the good things <pause dur="short"/> all those good things for you</u>
<u n="876" who="S0041">I might just have a plate of cabbage to be fair and then Coco Pops for desert</u>
<u n="877" who="S0086">yeah plate of cabbage <pause dur="short"/> well yeah that's it you know introduce it to the water cover it in black pepper yum <pause dur="short"/> yeah I was actually quite surprised that I like the cabbage</u>
<u n="878" who="S0041">yeah I could get in I think I've got to buy some broccoli in my life again I mean</u>
<u n="879" who="S0086">slowly slowly <unclear/></u>
<u n="880" who="S0041">just a <trunc>li</trunc> baby baby broccoli</u>
<u n="881" who="S0086">you know what that noise means don't you?</u>
<u n="882" who="S0041">did you hear them get in the shower last night at elven o'clock half past eleven?</u>
<u n="883" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> rank <pause dur="short"/> rank as hell</u>
<u n="884" who="S0041">what the fuck?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0086">she must be entertaining tonight then so <pause dur="short"/> let's look forward to getting woken up at fie AM</u>
<u n="886" who="S0041">I was just like what?</u>
<u n="887" who="S0086">I thought someone might have actually been robbing <pause dur="short"/> because he must have come round after we'd gone to bed <pause dur="short"/> cos he wasn't here when we were up</u>
<u n="888" who="S0041">she eh cos last night I got out of the bath and I didn't realise it was like quarter past ten when I got out of the bathroom <pause dur="short"/> maybe a bit earlier than that <pause dur="short"/> maybe it was quarter to ten <pause dur="short"/> I don't remember it was late anyway <pause dur="short"/> later than I thought it was</u>
<u n="889" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="890" who="S0041">and I was like oh shit I was glad I got in the bath and not a shower running for all that time</u>
<u n="891" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="892" who="S0041">so I come downstairs sort my washing out em pin my hair up get my jamas on cover myself in moisturizer get into bed and then <pause dur="short"/> the shower goes on <pause dur="short"/> forty-five minutes after I'd been out the bathroom</u>
<u n="893" who="S0086">no way</u>
<u n="894" who="S0041">yeah so I'm trying to get to sleep eleven o'clock at night half past eleven and she's running the fucking shower <pause dur="short"/> I was like oh my god</u>
<u n="895" who="S0086">there's no need for that</u>
<u n="896" who="S0041">it's not like she'd not been in <pause dur="short"/> and both of then got in so I don't know if it was hit on her or her on her</u>
<u n="897" who="S0086">her on her maybe <pause dur="short"/> maybe that's what's occurring <pause dur="short"/> they are pretty close</u>
<u n="898" who="S0041">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was like time people time</u>
<u n="899" who="S0086">I think they a different idea of time don't they?</u>
<u n="900" who="S0041">yeah well the <pause dur="short"/> I was thinking that I was like I can't be too angry cos I remember when I was living out there and I remember looking back at my friend at home who were in bed for ten and thinking what the hell are you doing? And I remember how far away it was from <unclear/> even though it had always been my lifestyle</u>
<u n="901" who="S0086">yeah sure <pause dur="short"/> but the thing is that's all very well and good if everyone there is doing that <pause dur="short"/> but if you're here and other people aren't doing that <pause dur="short"/> you've got to remember</u>
<u n="902" who="S0041" trans="overlap">that's what I thought to myself <pause dur="short"/> I adapted to them because I was there</u>
<u n="903" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you've just got <pause dur="short"/> it's just who <pause dur="short"/> if you've got people in the house even if you have people there who are going who were you know it was still on British time <pause dur="short"/> on a different time to you you just have to be respectful and it's <trunc>ju</trunc> there's just none of that <pause dur="short"/> there's none of that courtesy</u>
<u n="904" who="S0041">I can only say like stereotypical English people are very courteous but getting the bathroom when people have got to be up for world at half past eleven at night is fucking ridiculous</u>
<u n="905" who="S0086">yeah cos I often feel like at six thirty or whatever that I'm really taking the piss if I have to have a shower in the morning cos I haven't can't be bothered to have one at night <pause dur="short"/> but then at the same time they're up at four thirty in the morning so you can't really <pause dur="short"/> you can't really use that an <trunc>e</trunc> you know you start to feel guilty</u>
<u n="906" who="S0041">yeah like when I hear the shower going off at that time in the morning I just get on with it <pause dur="short"/> I'm like okay well people have to get up for work <pause dur="short"/> people don't have to get in the shower at half past eleven at night</u>
<u n="907" who="S0086">no absolutely <pause dur="short"/> but the thing is the latest they come home in nine o'clock <pause dur="short"/> so it's not like they can't get straight in to the shower <pause dur="short"/> oh sorry love yeah that's my soup</u>
<u n="908" who="S0041" trans="overlap">this <unclear/> here</u>
<u n="909" who="S0086">yeah it probably smells really funny <pause dur="short"/> it's like a sort of stainless steel type affair and em it gives a really weird smell after like the soup's been in it <pause dur="short"/> not altogether pleasant but em nay mind <pause dur="short"/> so all in all we just need to get rid of them</u>
<u n="910" who="S0041">yes that's what needs to happen</u>
<u n="911" who="S0086">they just need to go</u>
<u n="912" who="S0041">they need to go or need to go</u>
<u n="913" who="S0086">well yeah both really</u>
<u n="914" who="S0041">both of those things <pause dur="short"/> all of those things <pause dur="short"/> thanks for that love</u>
<u n="915" who="S0086">that's okay</u>
<u n="916" who="S0041"><unclear/></u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="917" who="S0086">it's alive</u>
<u n="918" who="S0041">I hope it's not alive</u>
<u n="919" who="S0086">I think it is alive <pause dur="short"/> with creepy crawlies</u>
<u n="920" who="S0041">there's soup wandering around the bottom</u>
<u n="921" who="S0086">mm</u>
<u n="922" who="S0041">I realised I must be stinking at the moment cos that soup I made last time had so much garlic in it <pause dur="short"/> so much</u>
<u n="923" who="S0086">that's fine <pause dur="short"/> em I've been stealing tea bags <pause dur="short"/> so have some of these contraband tea bags</u>
<u n="924" who="S0041">contraband</u>
<u n="925" who="S0086">and I'll steal some more tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> there you go <pause dur="short"/> I got a mix of earl Grey and breakfast tea</u>
<u n="926" who="S0041">bit of a selection</u>
<u n="927" who="S0086">bit of that  Bit of that</u>
<u n="928" who="S0041">ah I forgot I could have got more contraband teabags today when was in the office on my own</u>
<u n="929" who="S0086">yeah</u>
<u n="930" who="S0041">oh god I'll get some tomorrow</u>
<u n="931" who="S0086">loves a bit of contraband</u>
<u n="932" who="S0041">just have to wait till there's nobody in the office and that's a rare thing</u>
<u n="933" who="S0086">oh okay</u>
<u n="934" who="S0041">should have pigging thought that one through</u>
<u n="935" who="S0086">well yeah</u>
<u n="936" who="S0041">look <unclear/> there</u>
<u n="937" who="S0086">you ninny grommet <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> we don't have to open it up do we?</u>
<u n="938" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> I feel bit sick now if I'm honest</u>
<u n="939" who="S0086">yeah I think it might all come back up again</u>
<u n="940" who="S0041">yeah I think I'm going to get up in the morning and do it before work though <pause dur="short"/> cos I don't think I'll hack it after rocking around the pool</u>
<u n="941" who="S0086">aqua aqua fit</u>
<u n="942" who="S0041">yeah so if I get my shit together</u>
<u n="943" who="S0086">yeah can you make sure you've got that with you <pause dur="short"/> I mean if you've forgot something just text me cos I think I'm going come home pick up the car <pause dur="short"/> I want to cycled work tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> go for a little run <pause dur="short"/> come home</u>
<u n="944" who="S0041">go for a little run at work?</u>
<u n="945" who="S0086">go for a little run at work</u>
<u n="946" who="S0041">I won't be doing that tomorrow</u>
<u n="947" who="S0086">no but you could do it very well <pause dur="short"/> I'll go for a little run tomorrow and the Friday I'm going to do a different sort of set of resistance training with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> probably do the legs again cos that's fine cos I don't need to walk on Saturday <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> that's nice</u>
<u n="948" who="S0041">nobody likes walking</u>
<u n="949" who="S0086">not on the weekends</u>
<u n="950" who="S0041">no <pause dur="short"/> bed all weekend</u>
<u n="951" who="S0086">well well when you can't spend any money cos it's the week before payday <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="952" who="S0041">yes</u>
<u n="953" who="S0086">it would be good to book to the em <anon type="place"/> hotel</u>
<u n="954" who="S0041"><anon type="place"/> hotel I keep forgetting all about that <pause dur="short"/> I keep thinking in my head that we've already done it that's why</u>
<u n="955" who="S0086">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we can do it at the weekend <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure the rooms won't have all sold out <pause dur="short"/> I mean I hope not <pause dur="short"/> ah death <pause dur="short"/> death by ab</u>
<u n="956" who="S0041">death by carbs <pause dur="short"/> I wish I was death by abs <pause dur="short"/> I always feel better when the abs burn <pause dur="short"/> I like that feeling</u>
<u n="957" who="S0086">yeah when you breathe in and out <pause dur="short"/> that's normal <pause dur="short"/> go and have a little stretch in your bed <pause dur="short"/> that'll make you feel good</u>
<u n="958" who="S0041">ah bed</u>
<u n="959" who="S0086">I think hats' what everybody needs <pause dur="short"/> everybody just needs to go to bed <pause dur="short"/> god we're just old nannies <pause dur="short"/> it's <trunc>eigh</trunc> it's eight twenty-five and everyone is going to bed</u>
<u n="960" who="S0041">granny Vegas <pause dur="short"/> I'm surprised I've made it this far if I'm <trunc>no</trunc> if I'm really honest</u>
<u n="961" who="S0086">yeah my eyes are about to fallout my head <pause dur="short"/> and I had a snooze when I got home</u>
<u n="962" who="S0041">that's definite Granny Vegas</u>
<u n="963" who="S0086">dude</u>
<u n="964" who="S0041">I'm going to go to sleep and sleep all the way through to like quarter to eight tomorrow</u>
<u n="965" who="S0086">Good twelve hour stint</u>
<u n="966" who="S0041">yeah it's just required</u>
<u n="967" who="S0086">it's probably necessary</u>
<u n="968" who="S0041">pretty standard</u>
<u n="969" who="S0086">alright night love</u>
<u n="970" who="S0041">night</u>
</body>
</text>
