<text id="SLDD">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:42:47</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-08-24</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0439 S0441</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Home - Kitchen</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Holiday, Barcelona, Paris, future plans, the weekend, tv shows, food, family, boyfriends, </topics>
		<activity>Catch-up with house-mate after a weekend away in Barcelona.  </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, inviting, announcing, anecdote telling, making arrangement</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0439">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern - Non-accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0441">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridgeshire - Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Mental Health Nurse</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0439">no erm so what? yeah we turned up obviously on the Thursday night and we got in at about <pause dur="short"/> one and the well no about twelve and the taxi driver we've got a taxi from the airport to the place cos we don't wanna be wandering around in the dark erm and then we once we arrived like on the street where we were staying there was a police car <pause dur="short"/> and them like dealing with some <vocal desc="misc"/> scruffians or whatever you wanna call them ruffians so we were like great this is the entrance to our street and then you walk down the street and there were bars open and stuff but a lot of it was closed and a lot of it just had like graffiti all down the sides so it was like okay in the daytime it was really pleasant but at night everything just seemed a bit erm yeah just unloved and vandalised and erm but it was it was nice but erm like unlike Paris where like you know the Eiffel Tower and Notre Dame and and the Louvre are all kind of like really close to each other in Barcelona they're not like one's like up here by five kilometres the next one is like down here by another how many kilometres and you just end up walking around trying to find everything so you spend more time walking than actually sightseeing but erm you can get like a tour bus and everything like that but because we were there for such a short period of time like none of us had really <trunc>rea</trunc> researched how to use the public or what public transport to use</u>
<u n="2" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0439">so we just kind of end up walking everywhere which was fine for me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were not used to the amount of walking <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="5" who="S0439">so erm <pause dur="short"/> but it was really <trunc>ni</trunc> it was nice the first day we arrived and we went to like we wandered round and we found this like festival thing</u>
<u n="6" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0439">erm and then went to in the evening went to this erm massive light erm fountain exhibition like they have the beautiful it's it's not a stately home it's now the national museum but it looks like it used to be palace or a stately home and it's like up erm up a hill with like fountains and like beautiful steps and at the bottom there's this massive fountain and they had this music and water display and that was again miles away so you had to walk all the way there and you know when like you're in a city with people who like none of you know where you're going but you're the one who's kind of vaguely suggested doing this and you end up being in charge? so I was like okay let's walk this way and then when you kind of get the wrong way they're like <vocal desc="sigh"/> you know it's not my fault I've never been here before</u>
<u n="8" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0439">erm <pause dur="short"/> and then but we did see the er Sagrada Familia and that was amazing like really really impressive you've got to walk in and you're just like <pause dur="short"/> wow like it was incredible but it certainly is like a city definitely worth going to but it wasn't as pretty as some of the other cities I've been to well the beach was actually okay it's well quite a lot of people slag off the beach <pause dur="short"/> well I <trunc>th</trunc>thought it was fine</u>
<u n="10" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0439">like I didn't think it was a bad beach although oh my god I've never seen so much nakedness in my life</u>
<u n="12" who="S0441">oh wow</u>
<u n="13" who="S0439">like <pause dur="short"/> yeah I've never seen so many penises flopping around</u>
<u n="14" who="S0441">oh</u>
<u n="15" who="S0439">I know erm yeah how was your weekend? how was it here? or er not here or you how was it for at home?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0441">I was at home it was fine it was good no it was good <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0439">get up to much?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0441">went out on Friday which was nice</u>
<u n="19" who="S0439">oh did you? that's nice</u>
<u n="20" who="S0441">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then work went out there <pause dur="short"/> but it was good</u>
<u n="21" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's good</u>
<u n="22" who="S0441">yeah it was fun</u>
<u n="23" who="S0439">how was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0441">fine</u>
<u n="25" who="S0439">did you go out for dinner or do anything like that or just?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0441">well we were gonna get a takeaway but then we just got I made a curry and stuff</u>
<u n="27" who="S0439">oh nice</u>
<u n="28" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0439">I love a good curry</u>
<u n="30" who="S0441">it was good actually <pause dur="short"/> didn't eat for ages though it took for ages <unclear>to make</unclear></u>
<u n="31" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0439">how come? was it just that it took ages to cook?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0441">well we sort of were um and ahing for ages about whether or not to get a takeaway and then it just got became quite late</u>
<u n="34" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0441">and then it just took quite a while to cook cos I forgot to defrost the chicken <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0439">oh no</u>
<u n="37" who="S0441">it was fine though it tasted good</u>
<u n="38" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0441">just long</u>
<u n="40" who="S0439">and when did he go back?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0441">Saturday</u>
<u n="42" who="S0439">Saturday</u>
<u n="43" who="S0441">Saturday <pause dur="short"/> midday</u>
<u n="44" who="S0439">okay that's cool</u>
<u n="45" who="S0441">yeah it was nice <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0439">mm and you you worked?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0441">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I did</u>
<u n="48" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0441">which was good</u>
<u n="50" who="S0439">gonna say is that I haven't done very much today at work today at work to be honest we haven't had much to do though <pause dur="short"/> but I'm just like I'm so tired</u>
<u n="51" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> really busy day it seems</u>
<u n="52" who="S0439">mm they're just <pause dur="short"/> well yesterday was just nearly not a whole day travelling like we didn't leave till two or something</u>
<u n="53" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and then we got to the airport so it wasn't actually a whole day but it just because we went out until three in the morning the day before</u>
<u n="55" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0439">it and then we got up at eight it genuinely seemed like the longest day of my life</u>
<u n="57" who="S0441">it probably yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> what did you do for your actual birthday?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0439">er well yesterday was my actual birthday and then erm</u>
<u n="59" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0439">and then erm so we stayed out until we went to <trunc>wa</trunc> to watch England versus France in the rugby on Saturday night</u>
<u n="61" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0439">and so it I was in the pub at midnight so that was cool</u>
<u n="63" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0439">and then we went for drinks then we went back and made food and wandered around a bit and then we played Cards Against Humanity</u>
<u n="65" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0439" trans="overlap">for a while and then on my actual birthday we got er well I got up early actually everybody else was kind of dying in bed</u>
<u n="67" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0439">but erm we didn't drink very much but because it was so hot</u>
<u n="69" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0439">and you dehydrate <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah you just end up not drinking enough</u>
<u n="71" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0439" trans="overlap">so then when you do have alcohol it's like it hits you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you're like oh crap erm and then we just went to this like main tourist strip erm and went to this market</u>
<u n="75" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0439">and then walked down to the port and saw this antique little fair and then went to the sea and then got a taxi to the airport</u>
<u n="77" who="S0441">nice <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0439">so wasn't it wasn't a bad birthday</u>
<u n="79" who="S0441">good better than last year</u>
<u n="80" who="S0439">yes</u>
<u n="81" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah definitely better than last year <pause dur="short"/> er yeah so at least now I can tick Barcelona off my list of places I've been and stuff</u>
<u n="83" who="S0441">you can <pause dur="short"/> it's a very informative bottle that you've got here <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0439">I know I know it's like mum bought it didn't she? well my mum</u>
<u n="85" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0439">it's my mum's my mum mum always buys loads of shit and always buys <unclear>mulled</unclear> wine she just loves it so <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0441">has it got water in it?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0439">yeah it's a water bottle <pause dur="short"/> yeah what is it? water bottle in French</u>
<u n="89" who="S0441">can't remember</u>
<u n="90" who="S0439">me neither</u>
<u n="91" who="S0441"><foreign lang="fre">bouteille</foreign></u>
<u n="92" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no don't think so</u>
<u n="93" who="S0441">isn't it?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0439">dunno is it? I don't think so it doesn't sound right maybe it is I take it back</u>
<u n="95" who="S0441">let me look at it <pause dur="long"/> <unclear>water's there</unclear></u>
<u n="96" who="S0439">yeah I'm thinking <foreign lang="fre">tasse</foreign> but that's cup isn't it?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0441">yes</u>
<u n="98" who="S0439"><foreign lang="fre">tasse</foreign> is the</u>
<u n="99" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0439">what did I say?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0441"><unclear>reply</unclear></u>
<u n="102" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="103" who="S0441"><unclear>in Thai</unclear> probably</u>
<u n="104" who="S0439">is it? oh god <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is obviously Australian and he is so Australian though like</u>
<u n="105" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0439">when you know like when you go to a foreign country and you kind of try to say how they would pronounce it? or</u>
<u n="107" who="S0441" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you kind of you know say <foreign lang="spa">hola</foreign> and stuff stuff he literally walked into any every shop didn't even try and suss out whether the person spoke English he was just like I want one of those and I want one of those and I think I might want like a Coke</u>
<u n="109" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0439">and I was like oh god and then when we went to a restaurant he didn't even say <foreign lang="spa">hola</foreign> he was like hello we want to order this and I want to order this and then I want to order that and a bottle of water please <pause dur="short"/> which is perfectly fine you know like it was like obviously the waiters and everybody understood English and it it was fine but it was just how he did it was just so</u>
<u n="111" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0439">tourist like it was</u>
<u n="113" who="S0441" trans="overlap">very tourist</u>
<u n="114" who="S0439">and then we went to the German erm we went to the <trunc>G</trunc>German airport and I asked for a cup of coffee in German because it's not too <trunc>har</trunc> it's just you know like I want and then you just say whatever's on the sign so it was really easy and really straightforward and he was like that's really cool of you I want a coffee please</u>
<u n="115" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0439">I was like oh no cos you can just see them</u>
<u n="117" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="118" who="S0439">with the German woman dying inside slightly</u>
<u n="119" who="S0441" trans="overlap">German women <trunc>s</trunc> Germans <trunc>li</trunc> German women? German people <pause dur="short"/> hate that anyway <unclear/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I know she was just like right okay cos like she obviously knew that I wasn't German but at least I tried and I said it right and she was like that's fine but he just <pause dur="short"/> oh bless him it was hilarious</u>
<u n="121" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0439">and the weather was so nice it was twenty-nine degrees and</u>
<u n="123" who="S0441" trans="overlap">nice</u>
<u n="124" who="S0439">it was just remembering to drink constantly is really hard</u>
<u n="125" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0439">remembering just to keep drinking is a bit difficult but <pause dur="long"/> oh what are your plans for the rest of this week?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0441">erm <vocal desc="sigh"/> I might go on Wednesday I'm going home tomorrow I've got my <unclear/> I'll probably be home quite early tomorrow</u>
<u n="128" who="S0439">your what?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0441"><unclear/> day</u>
<u n="130" who="S0439">oh okay</u>
<u n="131" who="S0441">and Thursday and Friday work Friday I'm going home again cos I need to I got me and mum are having a pedicure on <trunc>Sa</trunc>Saturday morning</u>
<u n="132" who="S0439">oh nice where are you having that?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0441">in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0439">uhu</u>
<u n="135" who="S0441">it's like well I'd go home</u>
<u n="136" who="S0439">that's cool</u>
<u n="137" who="S0441">yeah I've got my mum and her best friend coming here for afternoon tea it'll be nice</u>
<u n="138" who="S0439">oh yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0441">and then it's a nice barbeque the next day <pause dur="short"/> and yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0439">that's cool</u>
<u n="141" who="S0441" trans="overlap">then it's the bank holiday weekend then I'm going</u>
<u n="142" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's the bank holiday weekend</u>
<u n="143" who="S0441" trans="overlap">on holiday</u>
<u n="144" who="S0439">so I would I get back on the Monday</u>
<u n="145" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0439">and you leave on the</u>
<u n="147" who="S0441"><trunc>sh</trunc> the Tuesday evening no Wednesday evening</u>
<u n="148" who="S0439">oh okay so I'll see you for one day</u>
<u n="149" who="S0441">it's confusing me because I it's a bank holiday so I keep thinking that Tuesday is Monday</u>
<u n="150" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0441">but yeah we'll go on Thursday</u>
<u n="152" who="S0439">okay so then you're working the Wednesday?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="155" who="S0441">well I'll just drive straight from <trunc>th</trunc> well I don't know whether to drive or not cos the like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said that my car will be a hindrance on his family for the whole time <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0439">do you think they'll mind?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0441">well <trunc>th</trunc>they have the they they've only got er two spaces on their drive well I don't know</u>
<u n="158" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh I see</u>
<u n="159" who="S0441">I'll I'll ask</u>
<u n="160" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0441">that's what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said</u>
<u n="162" who="S0439" trans="overlap">they probably won't mind</u>
<u n="163" who="S0441">it'll be fine</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="164" who="S0439">they love you so I'm sure it'll be fine <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's exciting are you all packed?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0441">partially I need to buy some like not clothes but toiletries and stuff</u>
<u n="166" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you always end up having to like take stuff and then when you get there you never use it anyway</u>
<u n="167" who="S0441">no luckily at least mum's got us some like mosquito repellent and stuff like that</u>
<u n="168" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh that's good</u>
<u n="169" who="S0441">I I need to buy that cos I really don't wanna get bitten</u>
<u n="170" who="S0439">no no I know what you mean it's a pain in the arse getting bitten we got I didn't actually get too badly eaten this weekend</u>
<u n="171" who="S0441">that's good</u>
<u n="172" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I got the odd bite but nothing major which was really good</u>
<u n="173" who="S0441">that is good</u>
<u n="174" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got bitten on her forehead <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0441">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got bitten on her forehead the other day</u>
<u n="176" who="S0439">did she?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0441">yeah unfortunate like right in the middle of her forehead <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s was like nearly right in the middle it was just like oh bless you dear</u>
<u n="179" who="S0441">that sucks</u>
<u n="180" who="S0439">mm <pause dur="long"/> it looked it looked quite funny to be honest not gonna lie but</u>
<u n="181" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she got a lot of stick for hers as well people kept asking her if she was getting married <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0439">oh really? how come? oh</u>
<u n="183" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0439">like an Indian wedding wasn't it like</u>
<u n="185" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> no I'm not getting married</u>
<u n="186" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0441">it's a bite that is a shit place to have a bite though</u>
<u n="188" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I got one near well on my leg and that was about it and it wasn't too itchy or anything either so</u>
<u n="189" who="S0441">that's good <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's good yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0439">so are you having a girly bonding with your mum on Saturday then?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0441">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I am</u>
<u n="192" who="S0439">a nice little pedicure <unclear/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0441" trans="overlap">have to I'm going to bake on Friday night</u>
<u n="194" who="S0439">oh are you?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0439">what to get ready for Saturday</u>
<u n="197" who="S0441">afternoon tea</u>
<u n="198" who="S0439">oh are you doing afternoon tea here or at home?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0441">here</u>
<u n="200" who="S0439">what so you're going to <anon type="place"/> and then coming back here?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0441">yeah because the whole point was that we were going to <trunc>s</trunc> she wanted to see my new house so</u>
<u n="202" who="S0439">oh I see okay <pause dur="long"/> fair enough chuck</u>
<u n="203" who="S0441">but to be fair it would make sense though like cos I guess I can bring my mum and then she can stay in the flat with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so</u>
<u n="204" who="S0439">yeah yeah cos you've gotta come back here anyway haven't you?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0441">exactly I'll be here tomorrow and Saturday night so <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0439">mm hot cross buns then</u>
<u n="207" who="S0441">teacake</u>
<u n="208" who="S0439" trans="overlap">teacake</u>
<u n="209" who="S0441">I'm really hungry</u>
<u n="210" who="S0439">I'm so hungry like I've eaten the thing is like when you're on holiday you always end up eating lots of like shit you know like just not bad food but just like lots of like carbs like lots of bread and so I was like today I just wanted a salad at lunchtime but then the problem with having a salad that you end up feeling really hungry</u>
<u n="211" who="S0441" trans="overlap">exactly that's what I had and I was absolutely starving well I ate my apple and wasn't really very satisfied with that either</u>
<u n="212" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0441">and I had a teacake it's a vicious circle</u>
<u n="214" who="S0439">it's a vicious circle yeah I think I want to <unclear/> though is like you eat a salad to try and be healthier and then you</u>
<u n="215" who="S0441" trans="overlap">and you're just frigging starving</u>
<u n="216" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you end up eating more because you're hungry</u>
<u n="217" who="S0441">and it fruit doesn't fill me up either so</u>
<u n="218" who="S0439">I know</u>
<u n="219" who="S0441" trans="overlap">if I have an apple I'm just like well great <pause dur="short"/> fantastic that didn't do anything</u>
<u n="220" who="S0439">it's not the same satisfying like feeling as a erm</u>
<u n="221" who="S0441">toasted teacake</u>
<u n="222" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0439">as a as a big carbohydrate loaded cake <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0441">mm that looks really good</u>
<u n="226" who="S0439">it should be alright I hope</u>
<u n="227" who="S0441">mm <pause dur="short"/> so it's like payday tomorrow</u>
<u n="228" who="S0439">is it?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0439" trans="overlap">payday that's good I love payday so payday makes my life</u>
<u n="231" who="S0441">it makes my life too although</u>
<u n="232" who="S0439" trans="overlap">but then I kind of feel bad that I'm living for the payday <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0441">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0439">kind of like mm this is what my life has become</u>
<u n="235" who="S0441">I will transfer you <pause dur="short"/> I suppose <unclear/> but I'm here anyway on the first plus the bills isn't it on the first?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0439">yeah all the bills come out on the first</u>
<u n="237" who="S0441">and I'll be back <pause dur="short"/> by the time the rent comes out anyway so</u>
<u n="238" who="S0439">by the time what sorry?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0441">the rent comes out I'll be back</u>
<u n="240" who="S0439">oh yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0441">so that's all isn't it? that's all I transfer you isn't it? bills and the rent</u>
<u n="242" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I always love how I emailed <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and did has she replied?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0441">oh yeah she's</u>
<u n="246" who="S0439"><unclear/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I think I think you should ring her</u>
<u n="248" who="S0439">no cos she hates me</u>
<u n="249" who="S0441">so?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0439">well ringing her is just gonna make her hate me even more</u>
<u n="251" who="S0441">does it matter in the in the grand scheme of things whether your estate agent hates you?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0439">nah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0441">I mean she's a douchebag anyway</u>
<u n="254" who="S0439">true but they're all in the control of our deposits and shit aren't they? oh no no okay they're not</u>
<u n="255" who="S0441">not I don't think it's <trunc>d</trunc> I I think she's probably got a manager hasn't she so if she's been that shit then just tell her manager she's been shit</u>
<u n="256" who="S0439">that's what I was thinking and I tried to actually have a look if I could make a formal complaint erm I couldn't find a way of doing it</u>
<u n="257" who="S0441">it's a shit estate agency anyway</u>
<u n="258" who="S0439">yeah but she's just er exceptionally poor she makes <trunc>m</trunc> being like a bad estate agent just on a whole new level of shitness</u>
<u n="259" who="S0441">I just can't work out still to this day why why not replying helps her problem</u>
<u n="260" who="S0439">exactly <pause dur="long"/> it just</u>
<u n="261" who="S0441" trans="overlap">ouch</u>
<u n="262" who="S0439" trans="overlap">doesn't are you alright?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0439">yeah it just doesn't make her look any better and it doesn't solve the problem</u>
<u n="265" who="S0441">no makes her look like an even bigger twat if anything</u>
<u n="266" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0441">like</u>
<u n="268" who="S0439" trans="overlap">like I don't understand why she can't just take the fifteen pounds off the rent</u>
<u n="269" who="S0441">why don't you just next time just</u>
<u n="270" who="S0439" trans="overlap">just suggest that</u>
<u n="271" who="S0441">or just don't pay fifteen pounds? I I I don't even think they freaking check anyway</u>
<u n="272" who="S0439">no true</u>
<u n="273" who="S0441">when was the last time we actually like <vocal desc="laugh"/> got a receipt or something back saying we've paid?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0439">that's true actually I've never had a confirmation that we've paid</u>
<u n="275" who="S0441">exactly so for all we know we could never have paid anyway</u>
<u n="276" who="S0439">it's true maybe maybe that's the case <pause dur="short"/> mm it's weird isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> weird</u>
<u n="277" who="S0441">it is weird <pause dur="short"/> whoops</u>
<u n="278" who="S0439">and it's just like in my job like sometimes yeah it just takes me a while to get back to people but I always get back and when I do I'm like I'm so sorry you know</u>
<u n="279" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I'm like busy with something else or</u>
<u n="281" who="S0441">doesn't take you weeks and weeks to reply</u>
<u n="282" who="S0439">no not at all</u>
<u n="283" who="S0441">she's just a douchebag</u>
<u n="284" who="S0439">so many douches in the world</u>
<u n="285" who="S0441">exactly and we have one of them as our estate agent</u>
<u n="286" who="S0439">exactly exactly</u>
<u n="287" who="S0441">unfortunately</u>
<u n="288" who="S0439" trans="overlap">damn them <pause dur="short"/> but at least at least I get to see my sister this weekend</u>
<u n="289" who="S0441">oh</u>
<u n="290" who="S0439">I'm excited you know when you're like sitting there and you're like I actually miss her</u>
<u n="291" who="S0441">ah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I just wanna see her <pause dur="short"/> wanna see my big sister</u>
<u n="293" who="S0441">bless her <pause dur="short"/> send her a big cuddle from me</u>
<u n="294" who="S0439">I will</u>
<u n="295" who="S0441">can I grab some butter to go on my <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0439">yeah go ahead</u>
<u n="297" who="S0441">midway through</u>
<u n="298" who="S0439">buttering</u>
<u n="299" who="S0441" trans="overlap">buttering which is sad</u>
<u n="300" who="S0439">disaster <pause dur="short"/> I sent my nan a postcard from Barcelona</u>
<u n="301" who="S0441">ah <pause dur="short"/> nice that she sent you a card as well</u>
<u n="302" who="S0439">she's seriously the weird she has the weirdest taste in cards</u>
<u n="303" who="S0441">I found it a little bit strange but it's fine it's the thought that counts</u>
<u n="304" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no but that's like a standard nan card from her</u>
<u n="305" who="S0441">oh okay</u>
<u n="306" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's like it kind of looks like they're for children doesn't it?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0441">a little bit</u>
<u n="308" who="S0439" trans="overlap">they're like girly children like teddy bears and the pink and stuff and</u>
<u n="309" who="S0441">perhaps where she goes she can't find a granddaughter card that's old maybe</u>
<u n="310" who="S0439">yeah maybe</u>
<u n="311" who="S0441" trans="overlap">maybe she doesn't <pause dur="short"/> maybe she doesn't branch out to different card shops</u>
<u n="312" who="S0439">it's just they're funny they're always funny and they've always been like that it you genuinely now like me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have like a</u>
<u n="313" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0439">which card from nan is better?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0439">they're just brilliant they're just so <pause dur="short"/> ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> but at least she cares and at least she sends them</u>
<u n="317" who="S0441">exactly bless her <pause dur="short"/> she's sweet</u>
<u n="318" who="S0439">she is I do love granny <pause dur="short"/> and she's so much better now now she hasn't got like</u>
<u n="319" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah it's really good</u>
<u n="320" who="S0439">mental problems</u>
<u n="321" who="S0441">that's good <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="322" who="S0439">how's your grandma by the way?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0441">fine</u>
<u n="324" who="S0439" trans="overlap">how's she doing? is she good?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0441">all good</u>
<u n="326" who="S0439">can't believe how long has she been in recovery now for? like two or no</u>
<u n="327" who="S0441" trans="overlap">only just because she <unclear/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0439" trans="overlap">in recovery</u>
<u n="329" who="S0441">recently</u>
<u n="330" who="S0439">oh okay that's good though</u>
<u n="331" who="S0441" trans="overlap">there's no rationale anyway</u>
<u n="332" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0441" trans="overlap">all good <pause dur="short"/> all good in the hood</u>
<u n="334" who="S0439">yay <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="long"/> that's really good</u>
<u n="335" who="S0441">it's good bless her bless everyone</u>
<u n="336" who="S0439">bless the world</u>
<u n="337" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="339" who="S0441">oh <pause dur="short"/> I have to mow the freaking lawn</u>
<u n="340" who="S0439">damn the lawn</u>
<u n="341" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> damn the</u>
<u n="342" who="S0439" trans="overlap">curse the world damn the lawn <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0441">I wonder what the weather's like tomorrow</u>
<u n="344" who="S0439">oh yeah it started raining today when I went out this morning it seemed okay obviously not <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0441">rain</u>
<u n="346" who="S0439">rain</u>
<u n="347" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh no it's not actually at that time but it's gonna <trunc>rai</trunc> oh gosh</u>
<u n="348" who="S0439">what?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0441">gonna rain all the <pause dur="short"/> forever</u>
<u n="350" who="S0439">oh well I hope you'll hopefully it'll lay off your barbeque a bit no?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0441">it's saying it is raining off the barbeque but <pause dur="short"/> things change</u>
<u n="352" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> England this is England we're talking about</u>
<u n="353" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="354" who="S0439">how many people have you got coming?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0441">erm about six</u>
<u n="356" who="S0439">oh that's cool</u>
<u n="357" who="S0441">six or seven</u>
<u n="358" who="S0439">that's a nice number</u>
<u n="359" who="S0441">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> did you invite <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the end?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0441">no <pause dur="short"/> she was getting on my nerves yesterday <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0439">oh really? what was she doing?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0441">being bossy</u>
<u n="364" who="S0439">like fuck off then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0441">fuck off <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when I have actually well not that it matters but you know when you just think well I've actually worked here longer than you so why are you telling me</u>
<u n="366" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0441">what to do? <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'd I I'd really accepted her telling me what to do <trunc>y</trunc>you know if that was my first shift or something that's fine</u>
<u n="368" who="S0439">mm <pause dur="short"/> I hate it when people do that</u>
<u n="369" who="S0441">it's really annoying</u>
<u n="370" who="S0439">like tell you what to do and you're just like why do you have any right? and then because they tell you to do something you automatically want to do the opposite</u>
<u n="371" who="S0441">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's what <trunc>ha</trunc> that's kind of that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0439">I got a erm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0441" trans="overlap">she smokes as well which surprises me</u>
<u n="374" who="S0439">really?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0439">that really surprises me</u>
<u n="377" who="S0441">like <pause dur="short"/> needs to go out for a fag break smokes</u>
<u n="378" who="S0439">wow <pause dur="long"/> that is strange</u>
<u n="379" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I would never put <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as a smoker</u>
<u n="381" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I always put her she I mean she smokes rollies I suppose you're you know cool</u>
<u n="382" who="S0439">yeah yeah well</u>
<u n="383" who="S0441">still weird so everyone that that I was working with er smokes so they all kept like going away to have fags I was like for fuck's sake</u>
<u n="384" who="S0439">that really annoys me like at work when people leave to have a cigarettes breaks it's like no cos if I went out for ten minutes every time like if I had as many breaks as you did I would not get <trunc>mu</trunc> you know like</u>
<u n="385" who="S0441">you wouldn't get away with it</u>
<u n="386" who="S0439">no <pause dur="short"/> they because they have a legitimate reason for cos they're going out for a cigarette break it's like mm okay</u>
<u n="387" who="S0441">sounds stupid to me</u>
<u n="388" who="S0439">but talking about people telling you to do stuff and erm not being very happy with it I had erm a birthday text message from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at half past ten last night I got in had a really good day got a text message and I was like great he said happy birthday <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I hope you had an amazing day and you're you're like sending my wishes please don't reply to this text but just know that I care</u>
<u n="389" who="S0441">mm fuck off</u>
<u n="390" who="S0439">I was like please don't reply what the fuck? what what?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0441"><trunc>wha</trunc> that</u>
<u n="392" who="S0439">I mean</u>
<u n="393" who="S0441" trans="overlap">that to me says reply</u>
<u n="394" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0441">I hope you didn't reply</u>
<u n="396" who="S0439">no of course I didn't no</u>
<u n="397" who="S0441">good</u>
<u n="398" who="S0439">not at all I was</u>
<u n="399" who="S0441" trans="overlap">that to me says don't reply so I know that you're so angry that you reply</u>
<u n="400" who="S0439">yeah he kind of was like don't reply so I'm making your birthday about me because I don't want you to reply</u>
<u n="401" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0439" trans="overlap">because my girlfriend might find out that that you sent me a text message</u>
<u n="403" who="S0441">remember me</u>
<u n="404" who="S0439">remember yeah don't reply though because it'll make it like awkward</u>
<u n="405" who="S0441">oh</u>
<u n="406" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0441" trans="overlap">he's such a dick</u>
<u n="408" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I was just I know I was just like as if you just made my birthday text message</u>
<u n="409" who="S0441">about</u>
<u n="410" who="S0439" trans="overlap">about you</u>
<u n="411" who="S0441">that just really says it all doesn't it?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> please don't reply well then don't fucking text me</u>
<u n="413" who="S0441">easy</u>
<u n="414" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0441">that that that solves that problem</u>
<u n="416" who="S0439">text messaging because I care</u>
<u n="417" who="S0441">no you don't</u>
<u n="418" who="S0439">care about yourself</u>
<u n="419" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0439">it's like well what a knob</u>
<u n="421" who="S0441">it's</u>
<u n="422" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well the first part was fine and then it just went downhill from there</u>
<u n="423" who="S0441">an actual knob</u>
<u n="424" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I know just don't reply you know well okay then I won't reply <pause dur="short"/> no I definitely did not</u>
<u n="425" who="S0441">well don't like he's a dickhead</u>
<u n="426" who="S0439">I know just a stupid message from a stupid dick <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> men men men</u>
<u n="427" who="S0441">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0439">yeah I was like I need some vitamins and minerals and salad in my life <pause dur="long"/> are you all packed? no I already asked you are you all packed for holiday? no</u>
<u n="429" who="S0441" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="430" who="S0439" trans="overlap">nearly no</u>
<u n="431" who="S0441">partially</u>
<u n="432" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I already asked that didn't I?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0441">partially</u>
<u n="434" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you haven't got the toiletries</u>
<u n="435" who="S0441">no but I will</u>
<u n="436" who="S0439">you will you'll get there</u>
<u n="437" who="S0441">I'll get there in the end</u>
<u n="438" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="439" who="S0441">I'm I'm pretty much done to be fair</u>
<u n="440" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh thank you I forgot about the tea</u>
<u n="441" who="S0441">did you?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0439">damn it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0441">well I've just got <pause dur="short"/> so I reordered my missing item from my bag from Asos</u>
<u n="444" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0441">so that's annoying me cos my address my home address is</u>
<u n="446" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0441">attached to the account and it's gone there</u>
<u n="448" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="449" who="S0441">which is annoying but I'll try it <pause dur="short"/> and then gonna order another bikini top to replace the bikini top that I sent back</u>
<u n="450" who="S0439">oh yeah did they not have a bigger size or a different size?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0441" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> but it's fine though cos I think gonna find that the other one was better</u>
<u n="452" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="453" who="S0441">so it's fine</u>
<u n="454" who="S0439">just a better top or better bottoms as well?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0441">I like their bottoms so I'm keeping them</u>
<u n="456" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0441">but the top I think I found an er let me see if it's still available actually that would be really <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> what?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0439">I do love Asos Asos like <pause dur="short"/> I mean sometimes I'm nervous about buying things online without being able to try them on but once you kind of know your size in a like a certain brand it's quite good</u>
<u n="459" who="S0441">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="460" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0441">yeah it's still</u>
<u n="462" who="S0439">is it still there?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0441">erm <pause dur="short"/> that's the one I bought</u>
<u n="464" who="S0439">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="466" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I love how easy it is to order offline off your phone? it's so dangerous</u>
<u n="467" who="S0441">very dangerous of there it is oh is it that? <pause dur="long"/> no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0439">that's a good shape</u>
<u n="469" who="S0441">mm flattering</u>
<u n="470" who="S0439">I always prefer like chunkier straps I think they</u>
<u n="471" who="S0441" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="472" who="S0439">I think they are more flattering than those</u>
<u n="473" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="474" who="S0439" trans="overlap">skinny ones <pause dur="short"/> and it gives you more support round your boobs</u>
<u n="475" who="S0441">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>exact</trunc> yeah I think it's available</u>
<u n="476" who="S0439">how much is it?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0441">sixteen pounds it's a fuller bust one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0439">fuller bust <pause dur="short"/> cos we all know that you need a bit of a</u>
<u n="479" who="S0441">fuller bust</u>
<u n="480" who="S0439" trans="overlap">fuller bust <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0441">you know if I could get thirty-two E? that but it doesn't work like that does it?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0439">I think it depends doesn't it? like is it too small where is it like too small? you know it was definitely a bit or you were like definitely a bit too small in the cup wasn't it?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0441">the cup was too small</u>
<u n="484" who="S0439">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0441">there's no I would roughly get a thirty-four E</u>
<u n="486" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0441">but</u>
<u n="488" who="S0439">do they not have that?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0441">they don't have it</u>
<u n="490" who="S0439">what sizes do they have?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0441">thirty-four F I think that's too big</u>
<u n="492" who="S0439">well at least you can always tighten the straps</u>
<u n="493" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0439">if it is slightly too bit you can just tighten the straps and it'll</u>
<u n="495" who="S0441">yeah I suppose</u>
<u n="496" who="S0439">be fine</u>
<u n="497" who="S0441">I suppose that's adjustable isn't it?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="499" who="S0441">doesn't matter so much <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0439">I guess it's better to go slightly too big</u>
<u n="501" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="502" who="S0439">and be able to tighten it than to go too small and</u>
<u n="503" who="S0441" trans="overlap">not</u>
<u n="504" who="S0439">not be able to to loosen it</u>
<u n="505" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah okay</u>
<u n="506" who="S0439">erm when we go to Paris<anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants to go er <anon type="place"/> and erm the <anon type="place"/> and we were having a look at <trunc>ta</trunc> tickets today to pre book and then discovered that because I am between eighteen and twenty-five and a European citizen I can get in for free</u>
<u n="507" who="S0441" trans="overlap">woo hoo</u>
<u n="508" who="S0439">and she has to she has to pay fourteen euros <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0439">I was like gutted</u>
<u n="511" who="S0441">gutted</u>
<u n="512" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0441">hey that's a I didn't know it was like that</u>
<u n="514" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0441">can't remember what it was though</u>
<u n="516" who="S0439">I think a lot of the museums are like that</u>
<u n="517" who="S0441">mm <pause dur="short"/> encouraging young people to</u>
<u n="518" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="519" who="S0441">embrace their culture</u>
<u n="520" who="S0439">oh my god erm in Barcelona me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went down to the bakery to get breakfast and erm <pause dur="short"/> we were onto the the third floor so we had a balcony and I was like oh we could like shout up and say something he was like yeah like Stella I was like oh from Streetcar Named Desire he was like <pause dur="short"/> yes I was like yeah A Streetcar Named Desire that's what that scene's from he was like <pause dur="short"/> yes exactly I was like</u>
<u n="521" who="S0441">well what did he mean?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you have no idea what I'm talking about do you? he goes he was like I do it's about that guy Stanley I was like yes he was like I saw it on The Simpsons once</u>
<u n="523" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like oh no <pause dur="short"/> and like he was like I've never seen it I don't actually know what it is I've just seen that one scene in The Simpsons about like the like the section in The Simpsons about a Streetcar Named Desire parody I was like <pause dur="short"/> right okay then</u>
<u n="525" who="S0441">what did he mean?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0439">it was the same scene but it was</u>
<u n="527" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="528" who="S0439">it was like a Simpsons version of Streetcar Named Desire</u>
<u n="529" who="S0441">I see</u>
<u n="530" who="S0439">so he was like I was like yeah like you know and there's Blanche he's like who's Blanche? I was like the main person in A Streetcar Named Desire along with Marlon Brando who plays Stanley he was like oh okay <vocal desc="laugh"/> and he was like who's it written by? I was like oh no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="531" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="532" who="S0439">but erm <pause dur="short"/> I guess he's Australian so they wouldn't really know about Tennessee Williams would they?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0441">perhaps not so much</u>
<u n="534" who="S0439">maybe they don't study that</u>
<u n="535" who="S0441">they just study Neighbours <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0439">mm <pause dur="short"/> talking about Neighbours Neighbours is on in a minute</u>
<u n="537" who="S0441">it's on now isn't it?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0439">mm I've not caught up with Neighbours since <pause dur="short"/> last week and they</u>
<u n="539" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I watched it last week</u>
<u n="540" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="541" who="S0441">and <pause dur="long"/> and <pause dur="short"/> what happened? oh <pause dur="short"/> paul's trying to make Kyle go away from the</u>
<u n="542" who="S0439">oh yeah and <trunc>Am</trunc> Amy?</u>
<u n="543" who="S0441" trans="overlap">the kid</u>
<u n="544" who="S0439">oh the kid</u>
<u n="545" who="S0441" trans="overlap">he keeps hanging out with the kid cos the kid likes him</u>
<u n="546" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0441">so he was like don't hang out with her cos you'll make <trunc>e</trunc> I don't want her to leave or something because of you</u>
<u n="548" who="S0439">yeah but they can't have Kyle have another affair cos he already had an affair on Georgia and then he's just got married so he can't like have another one</u>
<u n="549" who="S0441" trans="overlap">he can't do it again that's just</u>
<u n="550" who="S0439">he can't do it again</u>
<u n="551" who="S0441">really bad</u>
<u n="552" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="553" who="S0441">very bad form <pause dur="short"/> what else happened? erm</u>
<u n="554" who="S0439">it's a poor storyline</u>
<u n="555" who="S0441">Imogen and Daniel</u>
<u n="556" who="S0439">oh did they get together in the end?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0441">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he sung to her and oh</u>
<u n="558" who="S0439">oh grim if someone sung to me I'd die</u>
<u n="559" who="S0441">me too and they had sex</u>
<u n="560" who="S0439">oh Amber's not gonna be very happy</u>
<u n="561" who="S0441">he's er he's weird and I think if if I was Imogen I'd be really not okay with it</u>
<u n="562" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="563" who="S0441">I'd literally just feel like he had just broken up with Amber and then just</u>
<u n="564" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="565" who="S0441">I'd feel pretty <pause dur="short"/> shit</u>
<u n="566" who="S0439">yeah cos apparently down the erm <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="567" who="S0441"><unclear/> yeah he said</u>
<u n="568" who="S0439">he was like you would <trunc>ne</trunc> I would never go for you or something</u>
<u n="569" who="S0441" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="570" who="S0439" trans="overlap">like that</u>
<u n="571" who="S0441">mm cos she asked about her about that and he was like</u>
<u n="572" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="573" who="S0441">well back then I was just thinking about fate and how fate put me and Amber together and could <trunc>nev</trunc> couldn't think of it but erm just kidding myself and I thought what a stupid like that</u>
<u n="574" who="S0439" trans="overlap">grim</u>
<u n="575" who="S0441">me and you are really meant to be</u>
<u n="576" who="S0439">yeah that's what he said to Amber like over and over again like a month ago I never thought we'd get so involved in a TV soap it's ridiculous <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>it's time we got real</unclear></u>
<u n="578" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="579" who="S0441">it is real</u>
<u n="580" who="S0439">no we ought to ask</u>
<u n="581" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="582" who="S0439">Toadie celebrated his twentieth anniversary or something this week as well</u>
<u n="583" who="S0441">yeah but then I just also saw a picture on Facebook that well literally looked like he got carried away by a bouncy castle that's not even a joke and then there was something like erm all ends badly for Toadie or something</u>
<u n="584" who="S0439">Toadie can't die</u>
<u n="585" who="S0441">he can't die on his twentieth anniversary week by a bouncy castle <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="586" who="S0439">death <vocal desc="laugh"/> death by bouncy castle good god</u>
<u n="587" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> just looks it looks like he's been</u>
<u n="588" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that is the worst death ever</u>
<u n="589" who="S0441">taken away by a bouncy castle it's very odd and then Sonya's like ah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> do you know that Sonya annoys the fuck out of me as well</u>
<u n="591" who="S0441" trans="overlap">she's really annoying they need to change her opening credit scene cos it's clearly when she was pregnant and she's just got a ridiculous cushion like on her for no reason and it looks stupid <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0439">mm you know with the whole storyline with erm what the hell's her name? Lauren lusting after Brad again it's just like</u>
<u n="593" who="S0441">oh no</u>
<u n="594" who="S0439">I think the</u>
<u n="595" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh that's another thing</u>
<u n="596" who="S0439">oh god what?</u>
<u n="597" who="S0441">Amy is now employed as Paul's PA</u>
<u n="598" who="S0439">oh yeah er</u>
<u n="599" who="S0441">so she was asked to send some email and you could just see it coming you know they just build it up like you could just see what was gonna happen so they were like okay you need to send this person a letter saying that we don't want their services anymore cos they're crap and this person and send the letter</u>
<u n="600" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and she mixed it up?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah basically</u>
<u n="602" who="S0439">so she fired the wrong person</u>
<u n="603" who="S0441">she fired the wrong person</u>
<u n="604" who="S0439">what a twat <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="605" who="S0441">and then Paul blamed Terese for that</u>
<u n="606" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> even though it was Amy's fault</u>
<u n="607" who="S0441">well Terese is meant to check the letters but Amy said that she just leave she was fine she could do it on her own</u>
<u n="608" who="S0439">well Amy should erm tell the truth then what a bitch</u>
<u n="609" who="S0441">what a bitch</u>
<u n="610" who="S0439">what a skank <pause dur="short"/> no well Amy's a builder Amy isn't a PA</u>
<u n="611" who="S0441">exactly but I think Paul's trying to get her away from Kyle</u>
<u n="612" who="S0439">again Kyle can't do that they cannot redo that storyline again</u>
<u n="613" who="S0441">who did he cheat on with who before?</u>
<u n="614" who="S0439">Kate</u>
<u n="615" who="S0441">oh yeah</u>
<u n="616" who="S0439">I mean Kate died did you ever see her death scene? it was the worst death scene ever she got shot and there was no blood anywhere</u>
<u n="617" who="S0441">oh it's family television you can't have blood in family TV</u>
<u n="618" who="S0439">wasn't even a speck not even a tiny bit <pause dur="short"/> you know just with her and Mark had got together</u>
<u n="619" who="S0441">was there not splatter on the grass? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="620" who="S0439">not even a splatter Mark was perfectly white her dress which was white and blue was still perfectly white and blue</u>
<u n="621" who="S0441">she just died?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0439">yeah there was no dribble of blood from her mouth</u>
<u n="623" who="S0441" trans="overlap">so no blood then</u>
<u n="624" who="S0439">it was just</u>
<u n="625" who="S0441">looked like an <pause dur="short"/> just an undisclosed death</u>
<u n="626" who="S0439">pretty much it was just having <trunc>li</trunc> I <trunc>lo</trunc> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="627" who="S0441">oh god really?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0439">and then she died</u>
<u n="629" who="S0441">that's dramatic</u>
<u n="630" who="S0439">well she got shot and then collapsed and then she died and then Mark was just like oh oh oh cos he'd just literally proposed</u>
<u n="631" who="S0441">very dramatic scene</u>
<u n="632" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it was it was one of those overly dramatic scenes and everybody in Edinburgh apparently was there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="633" who="S0441">Edinburgh?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it was just like <vocal desc="laugh"/> not Edinburgh <pause dur="short"/> edinburgh what is it?</u>
<u n="635" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>Er</trunc> they they took a flight</u>
<u n="636" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it was</u>
<u n="637" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><trunc>Eri</trunc></u>
<u n="638" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it <vocal desc="laugh"/> they took a flight to <unclear/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> had the scene there</u>
<u n="640" who="S0439">my god what is it?</u>
<u n="641" who="S0441">Erinsborough</u>
<u n="642" who="S0439">Erinsborough there we go</u>
<u n="643" who="S0441" trans="overlap">close</u>
<u n="644" who="S0439">close I'm tired</u>
<u n="645" who="S0441">remember the scene where Toadie got married with Dee and then they</u>
<u n="646" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh they drop they drop</u>
<u n="647" who="S0441" trans="overlap">they drove into a</u>
<u n="648" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="649" who="S0441" trans="overlap">the sea</u>
<u n="650" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> off a cliff didn't they?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0441" trans="overlap">that was really sad</u>
<u n="652" who="S0439">yeah Dee died</u>
<u n="653" who="S0441">she did poor Toadie</u>
<u n="654" who="S0439">Toad has some really bad luck with women</u>
<u n="655" who="S0441">so bad who else was he with?</u>
<u n="656" who="S0439">didn't he get with Libby for a while?</u>
<u n="657" who="S0441">I just thought that but I don't think so</u>
<u n="658" who="S0439">no I think they did</u>
<u n="659" who="S0441">did they?</u>
<u n="660" who="S0439">he was with Steph for ages and then Steph turned into</u>
<u n="661" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0439" trans="overlap">a psycho what did Steph do? was it cos she had a baby and miscarriage or something?</u>
<u n="663" who="S0441">no she ran Ringo over by accident <pause dur="short"/> and she went to prison</u>
<u n="664" who="S0439">what him and? no she was married to Max when she did that wasn't she? <pause dur="long"/> cos she was married to Max for ages well not for ages ages in terms of soap life</u>
<u n="665" who="S0441">mm oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember</u>
<u n="666" who="S0439">cos who was it? it was Summer and Boyd</u>
<u n="667" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0439">Boyd drove up into the distance didn't he?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="670" who="S0439">Summer went to <trunc>sw</trunc> went to a school and never came back <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="671" who="S0441">she did come back</u>
<u n="672" who="S0439">oh did she?</u>
<u n="673" who="S0441">she was a different person though</u>
<u n="674" who="S0439">oh I hate it when they do that it's so annoying and she has like it was like when they changed the person who played Declan that was just stupid</u>
<u n="675" who="S0441">that was stupid and you just always missed old Declan</u>
<u n="676" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="677" who="S0441">new Declan was shit</u>
<u n="678" who="S0439">and Bridget Bridget died as well didn't she?</u>
<u n="679" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="680" who="S0439">did she die giving birth?</u>
<u n="681" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0439">and Declan's baby as well wasn't it?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="684" who="S0439">they were like sixteen years old or something stupid like that</u>
<u n="685" who="S0441">the baby was okay though</u>
<u n="686" who="S0439">where did the baby go?</u>
<u n="687" who="S0441">Declan</u>
<u n="688" who="S0439">no I no I didn't watch it then I think having like a massive break from it <pause dur="short"/> no cos that's why <pause dur="short"/> who was the blonde? Jeanette Jeanette Janae</u>
<u n="689" who="S0441">yeah Janae no Janae was the</u>
<u n="690" who="S0439">was the daughter</u>
<u n="691" who="S0441" trans="overlap">Boyd's girlfriend</u>
<u n="692" who="S0439">yeah or and the mum Jeanette or what is that word?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0441">Jenelle</u>
<u n="694" who="S0439">Jenelle oh <pause dur="short"/> oh they were an awful awful family and Bree Bree would be like the daughter who wasn't really their daughter was she? cos they got</u>
<u n="695" who="S0441" trans="overlap">she's was their blind daughter</u>
<u n="696" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="697" who="S0441" trans="overlap">they got swapped at birth or something didn't they? I'm sure they got swapped at birth</u>
<u n="698" who="S0439">they did they got swapped at birth something dramatic like that</u>
<u n="699" who="S0441">lol</u>
<u n="700" who="S0439">but how many sisters were there? there was Janae Bree</u>
<u n="701" who="S0441" trans="overlap">Bree Scotty and Stingray no they're the same person</u>
<u n="702" who="S0439">oh Dylan</u>
<u n="703" who="S0441">Dylan and Stingray</u>
<u n="704" who="S0439">cos then Sky like got was like in going out with Dylan for ages and then ended up going out with Scott</u>
<u n="705" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="706" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><trunc>St</trunc>Stingray for ages then had a</u>
<u n="707" who="S0441" trans="overlap">then he but he died of an aneurism</u>
<u n="708" who="S0439">didn't she have a baby with him? and then Dylan helped to raise it?</u>
<u n="709" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="710" who="S0439">god er and she had a lesbian phase do you remember the lesbian phase with Lana?</u>
<u n="711" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah I do</u>
<u n="712" who="S0439">while she was in like going out with Boyd?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0441">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she got around didn't she?</u>
<u n="714" who="S0439">Scott was a hussy and a half <pause dur="long"/> he was only what? sixteen not</u>
<u n="715" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I just remember them getting it on in the sauna once cos that boy who used to work in the gym</u>
<u n="716" who="S0439">I know do you remember when like when they suddenly brought the gym into it?</u>
<u n="717" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="718" who="S0439" trans="overlap">as a place to hang out? it was like oh god they've clearly run out of places to go</u>
<u n="719" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="720" who="S0439">oh love it</u>
<u n="721" who="S0441">they don't really go to school anymore do they? there's not really any characters</u>
<u n="722" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="723" who="S0441" trans="overlap">in school I think they've tried to grow up a bit</u>
<u n="724" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/> it out a bit yeah</u>
<u n="725" who="S0441">cos there used to be loads of scenes in school like</u>
<u n="726" who="S0439" trans="overlap">who does go to school? <pause dur="short"/> the only people who go to school are</u>
<u n="727" who="S0441">Mason not Mason what's his face Bailey is he in it anymore?</u>
<u n="728" who="S0439">no Bailey wanted to go and stay with a family cos he couldn't deal with the fact that his dad died</u>
<u n="729" who="S0441">oh right</u>
<u n="730" who="S0439">I know that sounds really harsh cos obviously he shouldn't be able to deal with the fact that his dad died but <pause dur="short"/> so <unclear/></u>
<u n="731" who="S0441" trans="overlap">did he go to reba <trunc>re</trunc> reba? rehab</u>
<u n="732" who="S0439">no he went to stay with a family Lou took him he went with Lou</u>
<u n="733" who="S0441">okay cos Lou's quit now well</u>
<u n="734" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="735" who="S0441" trans="overlap">he's gone part time now</u>
<u n="736" who="S0439">do you remember how Mason left to Darwin? and then so it's like oh Mason's coming back for the wedding oh no it's okay cos it's been cancelled so Mason's gonna fly back now oh Mason's coming oh no Mason isn't coming anymore</u>
<u n="737" who="S0441">his flight's delayed</u>
<u n="738" who="S0439">yeah oh Mason's coming oh you know like his his flight you know ended up crashing into the ocean <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's so</u>
<u n="739" who="S0441" trans="overlap">Mason isn't coming anymore</u>
<u n="740" who="S0439" trans="overlap">Mason is not coming Mason Mason is never gonna come back ever again</u>
<u n="741" who="S0441">Mason's disowned his family <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="742" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> for Darwin it's just so funny how the characters leave and then they kind of like crop up in conversation cos you've got to make it seem real but</u>
<u n="743" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="744" who="S0439">it's just not <vocal desc="laugh"/> but Mason's the only <trunc>g</trunc>good looking guy in it</u>
<u n="745" who="S0441">not really that good looking</u>
<u n="746" who="S0439">oh I thought he was I thought he was I thought Mason was a bit of a hottie</u>
<u n="747" who="S0441">Ronan's better</u>
<u n="748" who="S0439">Ronan's hot but like in a more adulty way</u>
<u n="749" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="750" who="S0439">Mason was like hot in like a twenty-one year old kind of way</u>
<u n="751" who="S0441" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="752" who="S0439">I do think he was older than that</u>
<u n="753" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="754" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I hope he was older than that I was lusting after a younger boy</u>
<u n="755" who="S0441">I think he was</u>
<u n="756" who="S0439">damn it oh good</u>
<u n="757" who="S0441" trans="overlap">no older than that</u>
<u n="758" who="S0439">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="759" who="S0441">erm <pause dur="short"/> I liked it when it was <pause dur="short"/> I think my my favourite years were when it was Declan and that that was good that's when I was interested in it</u>
<u n="760" who="S0439">yeah and I liked it when like Boyd and Sky and stuff really</u>
<u n="761" who="S0441">mm that was a bit before wasn't it?</u>
<u n="762" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="763" who="S0441">I quite liked it with Rachel and Zeke and</u>
<u n="764" who="S0439">oh yeah</u>
<u n="765" who="S0441" trans="overlap">Donna and Ringo</u>
<u n="766" who="S0439">I didn't really watch it that much when Donna and Ringo were in it</u>
<u n="767" who="S0441">she's really famous now isn't she?</u>
<u n="768" who="S0439">yeah she is Margot whatever her name is</u>
<u n="769" who="S0441">Margot Robbie</u>
<u n="770" who="S0439">that's the weird thing like the odd person really gets famous and then the rest of them just kind of <pause dur="short"/> fade away</u>
<u n="771" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="772" who="S0439">but then the girl who played Rachel is now like she likes</u>
<u n="773" who="S0441" trans="overlap">a topless person</u>
<u n="774" who="S0439">yeah a topless person who's</u>
<u n="775" who="S0441" trans="overlap">feminist</u>
<u n="776" who="S0439">posts loads of pictures of her boobs everywhere</u>
<u n="777" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="778" who="S0439">Zeke came back into a bit didn't he recently</u>
<u n="779" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="780" who="S0439" trans="overlap">but I can't remember what his storyline was about</u>
<u n="781" who="S0441">I can't either</u>
<u n="782" who="S0439">amazing I loved it when Drew and Libby were today</u>
<u n="783" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh Drew</u>
<u n="784" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and they broke up because</u>
<u n="785" who="S0441">did he fall off a horse?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0439">yeah they broke up because she found out she couldn't they were together and they found out she couldn't have children and she went really like depressed and wouldn't see him and he was like Libby and she was like no go away and so they broke up for ages and then she turned up at his garage one night and he made her that green Beetle</u>
<u n="787" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="788" who="S0439" trans="overlap">like he'd <trunc>r</trunc>redone the whole car and made that</u>
<u n="789" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="790" who="S0439">Beetle and she just turned up and she was like oh you <trunc>li</trunc></u>
<u n="791" who="S0441" trans="overlap">didn't Sky have it afterwards?</u>
<u n="792" who="S0439">yeah I think so he was like he was like I don't care if you can't have children</u>
<u n="793" who="S0441">then she had Ben</u>
<u n="794" who="S0439">then she had Ben yeah Ben was the ugliest child</u>
<u n="795" who="S0441">yeah he was</u>
<u n="796" who="S0439">he was so ugly <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="797" who="S0441">really ugly</u>
<u n="798" who="S0439">well did you not love it how suddenly like Ben changed didn't he? he went from being like a baby</u>
<u n="799" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="800" who="S0439">to sort of like a toddler within like a a month or something <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="801" who="S0441">he grew up really fast</u>
<u n="802" who="S0439">he <unclear>do</unclear> he was speedy growth <unclear>bird</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> no oh Neighbours</u>
<u n="803" who="S0441">oh Neighbours <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="804" who="S0439">I don't watch any British soaps anymore</u>
<u n="805" who="S0441">I don't either</u>
<u n="806" who="S0439">used to watch a bit of Hollyoaks but even that</u>
<u n="807" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I watched Hollyoaks but I got disinterested in that as well</u>
<u n="808" who="S0439">I got massively disinterested</u>
<u n="809" who="S0441" trans="overlap">massively</u>
<u n="810" who="S0439">I just used to love</u>
<u n="811" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I think I literally stopped stopped watching that when do you remember Amy and Ste? and then</u>
<u n="812" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="813" who="S0441" trans="overlap">they had a baby and he was really violent towards her and</u>
<u n="814" who="S0439">didn't he isn't he gay now?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0441">mm yeah that's why he was so violent</u>
<u n="816" who="S0439">maybe he was in denial I used to I only used to watch it when erm John Paul and</u>
<u n="817" who="S0441">Craig</u>
<u n="818" who="S0439">Craig got together I used to love those two</u>
<u n="819" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="820" who="S0439">Craig was always so horrible to him and John Paul was always the over emotional one who kept</u>
<u n="821" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="822" who="S0439" trans="overlap">crying all the time and he was like but I love you it's like whoa okay</u>
<u n="823" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="824" who="S0439">okay calm down calm down John Paul it's fine no I think I stopped it watching it after they left</u>
<event desc="sound of phone"/>
<u n="825" who="S0439">oh is that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="826" who="S0441">oh</u>
<u n="827" who="S0439">have fun</u>
<u n="828" who="S0441">hello?</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
