<text id="SLJ5">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:47:44</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-12-02</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0679 S0681</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>living room, Hardwick Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Discussing the past day, Wicken Fen nature reserve, Online banking, Savings and interest, Housing and issues, Issues about Dave’s front door and door keys, Mapping genotypes, Planning the next day, Christmas cards, Choosing and delivering a Christmas present to friend, Issues with my mobility rollator, Changing battery in electric candle, Christmas lists</topics>
		<activity>Chatting about our day</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, requesting, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0679">
				<exactage>54</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kent, Margate</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None/Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>31 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired (University manager)</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0681">
				<exactage>69</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Surry</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Dutch -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0679">so <trunc>h</trunc>how's your day gone?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0681">well I I it was good that I left early this morning because I erm it was a bit further than I anticipated and so I had to <vocal desc="laugh"/> skate get my skates on erm when I arrived at the <trunc>c</trunc> pub carpark everybody was there fortunately nobody else had got there desperately early so erm it wasn't a big deal in the end although I was panicking towards the end of the journey</u>
<u n="3" who="S0679">you weren't leading it?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0681">no no no I wasn't the leader erm I can't remember who was <trunc>l</trunc> oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was the leader <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was the leader yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0679" trans="overlap">and was it <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/>? you seemed to be a bit</u>
<u n="6" who="S0681" trans="overlap">it was</u>
<u n="7" who="S0679">undecided</u>
<u n="8" who="S0681">well we went to the village of <anon type="place"/> cos we went to the pub in <anon type="place"/> but we were walking around <anon type="place"/> but we went round a different direction than we'd done before so I didn't recognise any of it</u>
<u n="9" who="S0679">well there's quite a bit of it</u>
<u n="10" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0679">I mean we went up here years ago</u>
<u n="12" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0679">that may be the last time I went do you remember there was a snowy weekend?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="15" who="S0679">one January?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0681">I don't <trunc>rea</trunc> the things the place we walked round I don't recall remembering any of it from that trip though</u>
<u n="17" who="S0679">well it is kind of a bit difficult to</u>
<u n="18" who="S0681"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0679">I mean it's all kind of flat and looks the same really</u>
<u n="20" who="S0681">yeah <trunc>d</trunc> we did we go past the <anon type="place"/> centre?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0679">I don't think they had a <anon type="place"/> centre</u>
<u n="22" who="S0681" trans="overlap">well they've got a cottage which is a <anon type="place"/> centre it's only open at the weekends but the we went past that certainly but we didn't go past a er a a major sort of show building or anything like that at all</u>
<u n="23" who="S0679">well did you go to the main entrance? I'd have thought there was only one</u>
<u n="24" who="S0681" trans="overlap">no we didn't no no no er somebody else said we think we're sneaking in the back door</u>
<u n="25" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="26" who="S0681">we seemed to go through lots of fields and things the one that's really nice there was okay winter it was fairly low sun but because there wasn't much cloud there was the sun behind all the <unclear>reeds</unclear> you have the flags that wave about so they really looked quite spectacular oh and we saw some horses we saw some horses the funny horses in the</u>
<u n="27" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh now that the funny horses we saw from a walk from the walk from <anon type="place"/> didn't we?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0681">yeah was that with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0679">yeah is that the same place?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0681">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0679">I don't really know the geography but you said you might head for <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0681">yeah well yeah I got there via <anon type="place"/> so it's quite a bit further out from <anon type="place"/> yeah yes these are Przewalski horses or something</u>
<u n="33" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0681">but that quite happy on the quite coarse grazing there we saw some highland cattle as well both were quite a long way away the horses looked very suspicious they were watching us go there was about twelve of them they were <trunc>qui</trunc> about well I dunno six seven hundred metres away but they were watching us very suspiciously <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0679">I wonder if you'd gone into <anon type="place"/> proper would you not have to show your National Trust membership?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0681">I don't know I don't know I don't</u>
<u n="37" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well did you?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0681">no not at all there was no we didn't go through any barriers or gates or anything</u>
<u n="39" who="S0679">and not even at the <anon type="place"/> centre?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0681">no no that was at the side of the public road you know?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0679">mm was that part of <anon type="place"/> or not?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0681">it <trunc>w</trunc> it <vocal desc="misc"/> it may have been I'm not entirely sure</u>
<u n="43" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0681">it seemed to be a <trunc>cer</trunc> well there was a sign on their fence that said <anon type="place"/> National Trust that way with an arrow</u>
<u n="45" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="46" who="S0681">you know but I don't know if that was actually a National Trust building at all</u>
<u n="47" who="S0679">mm and you had your lunch in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0681">yeah the pub was very nice the <anon type="place"/> I think it was yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0679">does do they just have one do you think? is it that sort of place?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0681" trans="overlap">yes I think so it's not a big place but the the funny thing was just as we were about to set up another walking group arrived and they were having lunch at the pub as well so we <vocal desc="laugh"/> checked the times fortunately they weren't eating till one o'clock and we were we'd set to twelve thirty but when we left after the meal the pub was actually stuffed to the gunnels</u>
<u n="51" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0681">there wasn't a spare space anywhere for food so they obviously they the food was very good so they've obviously got quite a reputation</u>
<u n="53" who="S0679">what did you have?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0681">oh I had stroganoff</u>
<u n="55" who="S0679">uhu</u>
<u n="56" who="S0681">which was superb somebody else had a sandwich which came a doorstep sandwich which came with a load of chips and green stuff and they were only expecting a thin <unclear>girly</unclear> sandwich</u>
<u n="57" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0681"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so they were a bit</u>
<u n="59" who="S0679">so everyone was happy with that one?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0681">oh yeah oh yeah I think everybody did well you know so what have you been up to?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0679">well erm largely sorting out my online accounts which I made sure I could access them properly I also just wanted to update my well I wanted to be sure I knew what sort of interest I was getting on accounts</u>
<u n="62" who="S0681"><vocal desc="laugh"/> bugger all I imagine</u>
<u n="63" who="S0679" trans="overlap">because when my pension comes through I'll have the opportunity of putting some more money in</u>
<u n="64" who="S0681" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="65" who="S0679">an interest <trunc>a</trunc></u>
<u n="66" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0679" trans="overlap">er in a a savings sort of account</u>
<u n="68" who="S0681"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0679">erm and also setting up an ISA for the year</u>
<u n="70" who="S0681">have you have you found anything worthwhile for</u>
<u n="71" who="S0679">erm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0681">interest-wise?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0679">well I know where I'm going to put my money initially because it's always easier to open another account with a building society</u>
<u n="74" who="S0681" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0679">you're already with</u>
<u n="76" who="S0681">but we the National <pause dur="short"/> savings pensioner bonds were quite a good interest rate</u>
<u n="77" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0681">but they may have gone down after the first year all of these things seem to go down</u>
<u n="79" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0681">after a year</u>
<u n="81" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0681" trans="overlap">don't they?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0679">and erm oh there is <pause dur="short"/> yeah I saw something that had twelve months of interest on it interesting interest</u>
<u n="84" who="S0681">interesting interest?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0679">I think it was a Tesco account</u>
<u n="86" who="S0681">yeah I had some money in that but they've they sent me a letter saying they're reducing the interest rate to the square root of bugger all you know?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0679">oh is that their current account?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0681">no no no I had erm I just had a a a savings account</u>
<u n="89" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="90" who="S0681" trans="overlap">of some description I think it was kind of at two percent</u>
<u n="91" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well have a look again</u>
<u n="92" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0679">and cos I think you can get if you do an internet one you can one point seven five for the first year</u>
<u n="94" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0679">so I'm going to work on the current account cos you said you get some interest on that</u>
<u n="96" who="S0681">from from which which <trunc>comp</trunc></u>
<u n="97" who="S0679" trans="overlap">Tesco</u>
<u n="98" who="S0681">mm no I didn't say you get interest on the current account from Tescos</u>
<u n="99" who="S0679">oh I think you did cos you told me you've got one</u>
<u n="100" who="S0681">no I haven't got a current account with Tescos</u>
<u n="101" who="S0679">well anyway I have well I'm in the process of getting one and then I've <trunc>g</trunc> obviously I won't open the the one where you only get the high interest for a year until I've actually got the money to put in it</u>
<u n="102" who="S0681">well</u>
<u n="103" who="S0679">erm but I ought to <trunc>d</trunc> I I mean you don't get very much at all but I've got to do something with it and depending on how much money I get you know that rate has gone down to er the protection is seventy-five thousand</u>
<u n="104" who="S0681">mm yes yes you of course if you're gonna get a big lump sum you're gonna have to spread it around ain't you?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0679">well I've it's not gonna be so large I have to spread it very far</u>
<u n="106" who="S0681"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0679">but because of the way I</u>
<u n="108" who="S0681" trans="overlap">well you're a moneyed woman aren't you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0679">the way I've got erm accounts set up erm I do need to fiddle around with my Nationwide one to make sure that's a legit</u>
<u n="110" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0679">erm and they will Nationwide will let you take ten thousand pounds out of any erm account if it helps you get your you know without a penalty if it helps you get your money down</u>
<u n="112" who="S0681">oh gets you under the er is it</u>
<u n="113" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0681">eighty-five thousand now?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0679">well it was eighty-five it's gonna go down to seventy-five from January</u>
<u n="116" who="S0681" trans="overlap">oh right oh that's <unclear>fine</unclear></u>
<u n="117" who="S0679">and there's a on one of the sites it talked about and after April I think it is all erm interest account is gonna pay er without tax being deducted so</u>
<u n="118" who="S0681" trans="overlap">so is that</u>
<u n="119" who="S0679">you have to</u>
<u n="120" who="S0681" trans="overlap">is that</u>
<u n="121" who="S0679" trans="overlap">declare your own tax presumably</u>
<u n="122" who="S0681" trans="overlap">oh that's</u>
<u n="123" who="S0679">but</u>
<u n="124" who="S0681">well that's bloody stupid isn't it? because that means</u>
<u n="125" who="S0679" trans="overlap">seems it's it's likely to cause more employment opportunities in the er the the tax department</u>
<u n="126" who="S0681" trans="overlap">in the tax well more <trunc>opp</trunc> or opportunities with accountants as well I suspect</u>
<u n="127" who="S0679">well it makes it a bit more complicated I I I can't see any good reason for it erm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0681">no I'd have thought it would have been easier for the Inland Revenue because it was all done corporately so they got a big wodge of money from each bank and they didn't have to pursue it</u>
<u n="129" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0681">now they're gonna get little dribbles of money from or little dribbles of sort of tax demands from that millions of people</u>
<u n="131" who="S0679">unless they think it's a way of checking if you give so much interest one year and give get a lot more interest the next year perhaps that's a way of sussing out who's got more who's you know who's got money they haven't declared but I mean don't</u>
<u n="132" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="133" who="S0679" trans="overlap">unscrupulous people won't actually declare it will they? I mean</u>
<u n="134" who="S0681" trans="overlap">well no quite yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0679" trans="overlap">you'd only <trunc>dec</trunc> er declare it at whatever you're allowed to have every year</u>
<u n="136" who="S0681">because</u>
<u n="137" who="S0679">so it's a bit strange really</u>
<u n="138" who="S0681">yeah cos when you fill in a tax return you still have to declare interest but they crosscheck that against what they've returned cos I used to get that when I did the detailed tax return <unclear>they they would think</unclear> they would mash their figures to mine</u>
<u n="139" who="S0679">uhu</u>
<u n="140" who="S0681">and often they weren't exactly the same but as long as they were fairly close they didn't seem to worry too much about it</u>
<u n="141" who="S0679">and have you erm heard about the second home business?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0681">no what's gonna happen on that?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0679" trans="overlap">if you buy a second home or potentially if you buy <pause dur="short"/> a new house before you've sold your old house or anything like this</u>
<u n="144" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0679">erm you have to pay higher rates of stamp duty</u>
<u n="146" who="S0681">oh yeah I've heard about that I'm not I wasn't sure of the erm how it was hedged about with erm advantages and restrictions so cos you know sometimes you don't sell them by at the same time and so</u>
<u n="147" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well I don't know I mean apparently they're gonna have to have a month or two months to suss out what it might mean</u>
<u n="148" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0679">but I think it's an attempt to try and share the houses round more people</u>
<u n="150" who="S0681">well which is not that</u>
<u n="151" who="S0679" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="152" who="S0681">I still like Westminster Council's idea that if you're not registered to vote there you pay a lot more tax</u>
<u n="153" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0681">I think that's a brilliant idea</u>
<u n="155" who="S0679">well</u>
<u n="156" who="S0681" trans="overlap">because it catches empty property as well</u>
<u n="157" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0681">that's the thing that so often escapes the net</u>
<u n="159" who="S0679">and they might be going to charge people from abroad more</u>
<u n="160" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0679">er well at least as much as everyone else has to pay</u>
<u n="162" who="S0681">charge them what? stamp <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="163" who="S0679">well <trunc>h</trunc> the the <trunc>m</trunc> even if they've only even when they buy their first one</u>
<u n="164" who="S0681">mm yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0679">but it might</u>
<u n="166" who="S0681"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0679">it will make it a bit more expensive for erm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0681">inward investment</u>
<u n="169" who="S0679">landlords to buy</u>
<u n="170" who="S0681" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0679">multiple properties</u>
<u n="172" who="S0681">yes I did recall</u>
<u n="173" who="S0679" trans="overlap">but I mean unless it's expensive it's not gonna make a huge difference</u>
<u n="174" who="S0681">no it'll just push the prices back up again wouldn't it? which is not</u>
<u n="175" who="S0679">well it may depress prices for a while it may just put rents up</u>
<u n="176" who="S0681">I think the only thing that'll depress prices is building a hell of a sight more houses</u>
<u n="177" who="S0679">well</u>
<u n="178" who="S0681" trans="overlap">well I think the government</u>
<u n="179" who="S0679" trans="overlap">we don't really want that do we?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0681">well I don't know you know</u>
<u n="181" who="S0679">well if we want it but it's not in our back garden</u>
<u n="182" who="S0681">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's right yes</u>
<u n="183" who="S0679">but probably living in the houses in the parts of the country where there aren't jobs would help</u>
<u n="184" who="S0681">well that's right yeah and <unclear/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0679" trans="overlap">and why build on any more of the countryside? why make <anon type="place"/> three times as big? because there might be people living here and then</u>
<u n="186" who="S0681">mm why <trunc>d</trunc> why did <anon type="place"/> move from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/>? you know they said <unclear>nominally</unclear> was to be near the university but I these days with communication and things like that good grief you don't really need to be physically near anywhere do you? they're not physically near their manufacturing plants which are all in the Far East</u>
<u n="187" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="188" who="S0681">so there must be another reason</u>
<u n="189" who="S0679">well I mean maybe it's easier to get the labour down here</u>
<u n="190" who="S0681">mm the skilled labour?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0679">the skill</u>
<u n="192" who="S0681" trans="overlap">I wouldn't have thought so we are maybe like yeah I don't know I know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was erm could get I'm fairly certain she could get a job there but <vocal desc="cough"/> they're not a good company to work for apparently</u>
<u n="193" who="S0679">well if she doesn't absolutely need a job but could have a job then that puts her in a good position</u>
<u n="194" who="S0681" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah she's very highly skilled</u>
<u n="195" who="S0679">anyway she may be doing enough with what she's got</u>
<u n="196" who="S0681">yeah she's not earning big money but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s earning good enough so</u>
<u n="197" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0681">and they've paid off their mortgage so they're quite they're sitting pretty really</u>
<u n="199" who="S0679">anyway how how are we left with this front door?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0681">erm we have to lock it from the inside to lock it the cos you can open it from the outside now if you've not locked it with a key from the inside you can just open it from the outside</u>
<u n="201" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0681">yeah? because it hasn't got as there's a thing called a split <pause dur="short"/> barrel? no it's not a barrel a split something or other which we've not got at the moment cos that's part of the problem the locksmith has ordered the part we need and when it comes in he will phone me to let me know</u>
<u n="203" who="S0679">I take it he didn't really like the lock you took in?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0681">no he was he was quite amenable he says it's a he says it's a bit unusual he says erm it's not a standard lock because when I looked on the web on to find out it's all a great thing you can actually look on the web and look this all up</u>
<u n="205" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0681">the standard locks are seventeen millimetres wide and you can buy whole replacement locks for about a hundred pounds you know having said that the barrels and handles are all separate again you know? and the handles are twenty quid</u>
<u n="207" who="S0679">mm you fitted a very stylish erm door <trunc>ha</trunc> door handle on your door</u>
<u n="208" who="S0681" trans="overlap">it's it's the only one they had <vocal desc="laugh"/> in the right size</u>
<u n="209" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="210" who="S0681">the and erm the</u>
<u n="211" who="S0679" trans="overlap">it doesn't no <unclear/> I haven't seen it very closely</u>
<u n="212" who="S0681">it's it's very carefully fitted because it</u>
<u n="213" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="214" who="S0681">cos it's much narrower than the old one but when he gets the part he'll phone me and I'll go in and collect it it's gonna be a lot of money could be up to a hundred quid for this part and then I had to ring back take the whole mechanism off again and replace the bit the lock behind the centre</u>
<u n="215" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0681">and he says it's a bit fiddly to do he says but but he seemed to be quite confident I could do it so they were very busy when I was in there really busy cutting keys like men possessed they were</u>
<u n="217" who="S0679">oh what's mm it's not a particularly <trunc>s</trunc> time of the year for students to be starting</u>
<u n="218" who="S0681">no no these were <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>locals</unclear></u>
<u n="219" who="S0679" trans="overlap">would it be a good opportunity or would it be a not a good opportunity to take the keys round when you go back?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0681">take the key round? where?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0679" trans="overlap">you know I need some keys cutting cos we decided one of the keys we only had one of didn't we?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0681">oh which? the front door or back door?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0679">I don't know perhaps you found some more for the patio door in the end one of the doors there was only one of them</u>
<u n="224" who="S0681">no for the back doors we've certainly got a we've got two sets complete sets of keys for everything</u>
<u n="225" who="S0679">mm well I think we ought to no I think have we got more than <trunc>t</trunc> one one each for the front door?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0681">well I don't know where was the key you gave me? is that your normal front door key?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0679">are we talking about here?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0679">I'm not</u>
<u n="230" who="S0681">ah that</u>
<u n="231" who="S0679" trans="overlap">so okay</u>
<u n="232" who="S0681" trans="overlap">actually changes the issue yes right carry on</u>
<u n="233" who="S0679" trans="overlap">that that key</u>
<u n="234" who="S0681" trans="overlap">reset</u>
<u n="235" who="S0679">okay let's talk about keys here then first the key that is in the front door is the one that lives in my my belt so if I go out</u>
<u n="236" who="S0681" trans="overlap">is that your main key?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0679">my main key is slightly bent and belongs with my</u>
<u n="238" who="S0681" trans="overlap">right so</u>
<u n="239" who="S0679" trans="overlap">with my car key</u>
<u n="240" who="S0681">you've got two keys and I've got one so we've got three keys basically</u>
<u n="241" who="S0679">okay so I've got a slightly bent key and I've got a key that isn't bent the reason I've got the other one is because I don't always take my car keys out when I go out at the moment cos I quite often go in your car and but I have also got a spare key upstairs</u>
<u n="242" who="S0681">so we've got four keys one of which is bent okay and you're holding on to three of them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0679">well it hangs it's it's hanging on the chest of drawers upstairs</u>
<u n="244" who="S0681" trans="overlap">alright okay</u>
<u n="245" who="S0679">on a long loop of string and I put it there in case I had to throw it out the window for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> if I if I couldn't get down <trunc>t</trunc> you know if I needed her to come in</u>
<u n="246" who="S0681">oh right</u>
<u n="247" who="S0679">that's how we got up there</u>
<u n="248" who="S0681">okay fine</u>
<u n="249" who="S0679">but I'll bring that one down and</u>
<u n="250" who="S0681" trans="overlap">no no <unclear>you can use that</unclear></u>
<u n="251" who="S0679" trans="overlap">use it in the front door because I'd rather have one in my</u>
<u n="252" who="S0681">okay</u>
<u n="253" who="S0679" trans="overlap">in my belt</u>
<u n="254" who="S0681" trans="overlap">yeah we'll in while we're messing about for the next two days do that swap them round yeah erm now did you want to say there was something about the keys that <unclear/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0679">yeah I'm sure</u>
<u n="256" who="S0681" trans="overlap">I'm not sure what sets of keys we had we had hundreds of keys and most of them didn't fit anything you know</u>
<u n="257" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah but I'm sure there was one door we only had one key for is it actually a good time to actually go round is it good when you go back to collect it to have keys cut? or or is it better to keep that transaction simple?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0681">well I can do the same fine yeah I'm er I've half a mind to take take the whole thing off and take it with me and get them to do it</u>
<u n="259" who="S0679">well if you do</u>
<u n="260" who="S0681" trans="overlap">he <trunc>s</trunc> he seemed er I said do you need me to take door? oh no he says it's quite easy you can do it yourself he says yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0679">well that's up to you</u>
<u n="262" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0679">if it when are you going to do it?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0681" trans="overlap">actually well when he gets the part in probably</u>
<u n="265" who="S0679" trans="overlap">and when when</u>
<u n="266" who="S0681" trans="overlap">Friday he says day or two</u>
<u n="267" who="S0679">Friday okay well</u>
<u n="268" who="S0681" trans="overlap">oh what day is it?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0679" trans="overlap">if you're going to take</u>
<u n="270" who="S0681" trans="overlap">do we have to put the bins out tonight?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0679">it's your black bin this week</u>
<u n="272" who="S0681" trans="overlap">oh I put it out it's got quite a lot in it</u>
<u n="273" who="S0679">oh have you been throwing things away?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0681">yeah I've been throwing lots of things away I will not let you look cos you'll wanna keep everything</u>
<u n="275" who="S0679">what are have you been throwing away?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0681">no nothing of any weight or <trunc>impor</trunc></u>
<u n="277" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="278" who="S0681"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0679">erm I have put a smelly fish thing in it</u>
<u n="280" who="S0681">a smelly fish thing?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0679">you know that under</u>
<u n="282" who="S0681" trans="overlap"><unclear>what's</unclear></u>
<u n="283" who="S0679">under sort of under thing you get in</u>
<u n="284" who="S0681">ah right</u>
<u n="285" who="S0679" trans="overlap"><unclear/> fish</u>
<u n="286" who="S0681">from where you bought it from er</u>
<u n="287" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="288" who="S0681">the <trunc>supermar</trunc> yeah okay packing it's called I think</u>
<u n="289" who="S0679">yes it's a sort of I think it's meant to absorb any nasties but it can certainly absorb a lot of fish smell</u>
<u n="290" who="S0681">so we could have the cat in the bin tonight then?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0679">no it's not that strong I gave it a wipe over</u>
<u n="292" who="S0681">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> I haven't seen any of next door's cats for a while</u>
<u n="293" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="294" who="S0681">cos they don't like the wind <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="295" who="S0679">so erm now tomorrow you said you'd got you've got something in the morning</u>
<u n="296" who="S0681">I'm going to the genome project in the morning</u>
<u n="297" who="S0679">are you? you've been saying for weeks you're going there is this</u>
<u n="298" who="S0681" trans="overlap">yeah <trunc>ye</trunc></u>
<u n="299" who="S0679" trans="overlap">the time you really go?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0681" trans="overlap">they kept moving it around yeah yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0679">have you been there before?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0681">yeah I have I have I didn't realise well that's some the thing I remember from <pause dur="short"/> er somebody was trying to get some concept of how much data is involved in having a complete genotype</u>
<u n="303" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0681">and somebody said well you need about a terabyte hard drive to hold it</u>
<u n="305" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="306" who="S0681">so that gives you a pretty good idea how much information is involved rather a lot <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0679">yeah I mean it depends how they've got it stored really I mean</u>
<u n="308" who="S0681">they've got a lot of</u>
<u n="309" who="S0679" trans="overlap">do you just mean a terabyte as in my <trunc>har</trunc> my <pause dur="short"/> my removable</u>
<u n="310" who="S0681">drive yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0679">yeah I mean I</u>
<u n="312" who="S0681" trans="overlap">per person</u>
<u n="313" who="S0679">oh per person?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0681">per person <pause dur="short"/> so <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah you can imagine the amount of storage they've got to</u>
<u n="315" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well it's a lot of messages to get you know</u>
<u n="316" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="317" who="S0679">you don't want your left leg coming out like your right leg do you?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0681">no</u>
<u n="319" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I mean you need them different</u>
<u n="320" who="S0681">I might actually take my er my genotype my the little bit of information I've got with me</u>
<u n="321" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="322" who="S0681">and if there's time ask the question you know so they almost certainly the guide won't be able to tell give me anything tell me anything but <pause dur="short"/> but er I I</u>
<u n="323" who="S0679" trans="overlap">make your own up with</u>
<u n="324" who="S0681"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0679">coloured shapes</u>
<u n="326" who="S0681">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>m</trunc>my I get the impression they did the four genotype because the research panel expressed an interest cos</u>
<u n="327" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0681">when the erm cardiac specialist saw it it wasn't room <trunc>f</trunc> it was the other one her boss I think he says we'll have a bit of a job justifying actually running the genotype cos they've got it's about seven thousand quid it reckoned it cost although on my information now it's down to about two now</u>
<u n="329" who="S0679">well isn't that the price <unclear>to do things</unclear>?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0681">yeah and erm then I said oh I'm on the er on the the research <trunc>pane</trunc> oh he said then in that case there might be some quite a lot of advantages for <trunc>doi</trunc> for getting you to do it if we do you</u>
<u n="331" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="332" who="S0681">then we can store it and use it for as part of the research panel as well so</u>
<u n="333" who="S0679">so are you going to have your your erm your drive done in coloured bricks to</u>
<u n="334" who="S0681"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0679">follow you er</u>
<u n="336" who="S0681">TCA TCAFF I think</u>
<u n="337" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="338" who="S0681" trans="overlap">or whatever it is yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0679">I was thinking of the path you know</u>
<u n="340" who="S0681">oh right oh that would be fun wouldn't it? <trunc>st</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0679" trans="overlap">imagine by get a longer path but it's quite long</u>
<u n="342" who="S0681" trans="overlap">the <trunc>ye</trunc></u>
<u n="343" who="S0679" trans="overlap">isn't it?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0681">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's never gonna be long enough though is it?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0679">no and you could do a little bit of it</u>
<u n="346" who="S0681">mm mm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0679"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might not be up for it</u>
<u n="348" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0679">oh the</u>
<u n="350" who="S0681" trans="overlap">oh he'll be up for anything if you pay him enough money</u>
<u n="351" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0681">yeah but I think we might end up with Ashfelt actually</u>
<u n="353" who="S0679">so</u>
<u n="354" who="S0681" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="355" who="S0679">so erm just think you're so you're doing that in the morning</u>
<u n="356" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0679">and then you're coming back</u>
<u n="358" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0679">and that's the afternoon you can take the my my reserve rollator</u>
<u n="360" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="361" who="S0679">to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0679">and I <trunc>h</trunc> I thought really I should go first and sort my clothes out before collection</u>
<u n="364" who="S0681">uhu</u>
<u n="365" who="S0679">but I could A either make a start on doing that just for a few minutes <pause dur="short"/> I see I don't <trunc>kno</trunc></u>
<u n="366" who="S0681" trans="overlap">all your all your all your boxes of clothes are carefully labelled are they?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0679">well all the ones in the wardrobe are labelled</u>
<u n="368" who="S0681">uhu</u>
<u n="369" who="S0679">so they're they're fine it's the ones that erm are <pause dur="short"/> it's you know those big plasticy ones that are red yellow and blue with wheels?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0681">oh boxes not big plasticky clothes?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0679">no no you know the big ones</u>
<u n="372" who="S0681">yeah yeah yeah ones the ones that look like treasure chests?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="374" who="S0681" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0679">exactly erm and possibly could be yeah I don't know I suppose they plastic goes a bit brittle cos I could probably</u>
<u n="376" who="S0681" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="377" who="S0679">sell them otherwise couldn't I?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0679">on Gumtree and buy something probably a little more appropriate</u>
<u n="380" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0679">or indeed possibly eliminate them now I've got the other ones erm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how much they've got in and they're quite bulky</u>
<u n="382" who="S0681">mm so what I need to do is before I go is to fold all the back of the car down</u>
<u n="383" who="S0679">well you're gonna have the rollator in anyway don't worry about doing it before you go</u>
<u n="384" who="S0681">no it makes more sense to do it before you go cos it means I can take the cover off and it's a lot easier to do here</u>
<u n="385" who="S0679"><trunc>oka</trunc> is it? cos I thought</u>
<u n="386" who="S0681" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="387" who="S0679">you could be doing it at <anon type="place"/> while I'm sorting out</u>
<u n="388" who="S0681" trans="overlap">no it doesn't take very long but if I'm gonna take things out the car it's a lot easier to do it here cos I shove it all in the garage then</u>
<u n="389" who="S0679">okay <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0681">I need a few minutes cos I've got when I went on the walk I I <vocal desc="laugh"/> I put the big thick sweater on where you know it was glorious weather this morning</u>
<u n="391" who="S0679" trans="overlap">it was wasn't it?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0681">and I sort of rummaged through my bag of bad weather clothes and just took the neck warmer with me</u>
<u n="393" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="394" who="S0681">so I've emptied the bag out on the back seat so it all needs to go back in the bag again</u>
<u n="395" who="S0679">and you've got a few things in the corner I don't know what status they are</u>
<u n="396" who="S0681" trans="overlap">have I? no I did not have things in the corner</u>
<u n="397" who="S0679">well where have you got your coat from? it was with those</u>
<u n="398" who="S0681">yeah but I was cos you had it no because I had it</u>
<u n="399" who="S0679">no they were all the things that were on the <trunc>so</trunc></u>
<u n="400" who="S0681" trans="overlap">ah is this the one where you tidy up by hiding things under the settee?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0679">well I had to put them somewhere when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came so I put them there</u>
<u n="402" who="S0681">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0679">I think it was when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came cos that was a little while ago but I thought you'd have worn it since then don't you take it when you go walking?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0681">yes I do take it when I go walking</u>
<u n="405" who="S0679">well did you not go walking <pause dur="short"/> two week ago?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0681">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there was obviously I didn't think it was necessary to take</u>
<u n="407" who="S0679">ah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0681">but I thought this is the last one I'd better be fully equipped</u>
<u n="409" who="S0679">so you don't so do anything for Christmas?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0681">mm what?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0679" trans="overlap">in not doing a special Christmas</u>
<u n="412" who="S0681" trans="overlap">no we've got the Christmas the <anon type="place"/> Christmas lunch</u>
<u n="413" who="S0679">oh are they coming to it?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0681">er <pause dur="short"/> at least five of them are</u>
<u n="415" who="S0679">uhu</u>
<u n="416" who="S0681"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> er Indian lady whose name's I've completely forgotten</u>
<u n="417" who="S0679">I know I've seen I've met I haven't really met her though</u>
<u n="418" who="S0681">the <trunc>li</trunc> the little jolly one that's really very nice and and there's another person's <trunc>c</trunc> er one of her friends is coming</u>
<u n="419" who="S0679" trans="overlap">oh that's quite a nice group then</u>
<u n="420" who="S0681">yeah and the erm there was an older couple that the end of our table today and we mentioned something about it and they said what's that about?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="422" who="S0681">so I explained it and they're quite keen to come <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> asked to he asked to buy erm one of my poetry anthologies</u>
<u n="423" who="S0679">oh that's good</u>
<u n="424" who="S0681" trans="overlap">for it</u>
<u n="425" who="S0679">have you got any left?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0681" trans="overlap">he actually gave me the money well I'm running out now</u>
<u n="427" who="S0679">oh well make sure you keep enough for yourself</u>
<u n="428" who="S0681">yeah because erm er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> asked for copies last time so I took them</u>
<u n="429" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="430" who="S0681">and they coughed out the money and this guy was I don't know if this older couple are a bit on the periphery of the group cos they didn't seem to know a lot of what was going on I think they've not come for a few</u>
<u n="431" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="432" who="S0681">and erm he was looking through it and he says I have you got I want one if you've got one I said oh</u>
<u n="433" who="S0679">oh</u>
<u n="434" who="S0681" trans="overlap">I've got them all with me</u>
<u n="435" who="S0679">well I mean maybe you could email around the others and see if they've got any <trunc>d</trunc> that they don't want to sell</u>
<u n="436" who="S0681" trans="overlap">mm yeah if I get</u>
<u n="437" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I mean</u>
<u n="438" who="S0681" trans="overlap">numbers very low I will but they didn't have very many you know normally I print ten and give <trunc>everybo</trunc> sell everybody ten</u>
<u n="439" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="440" who="S0681">but I've told them to tell me their numbers this year</u>
<u n="441" who="S0679">oh I see</u>
<u n="442" who="S0681">but as much</u>
<u n="443" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I thought they had to have the same number</u>
<u n="444" who="S0681" trans="overlap"><trunc>m</trunc> no no it's much lower numbers this year so that's why the price went up a little bit because I needed a print run of eighty</u>
<u n="445" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="446" who="S0681" trans="overlap">instead of the usual hundred hundred and twenty</u>
<u n="447" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="448" who="S0681">so</u>
<u n="449" who="S0679">and tell me now er you're you're you're you've said something about your family history you've made some progress</u>
<u n="450" who="S0681" trans="overlap">oh oh no you're you're talking about tomorrow</u>
<u n="451" who="S0679">oh yes of course</u>
<u n="452" who="S0681">I've got this IT meeting tomorrow and I can't remember if it's a lecture or a committee meeting</u>
<u n="453" who="S0679">I think it's at six</u>
<u n="454" who="S0681">then it's a committee meeting then it should be a committee meeting then that's not so much of a problem it will be useful tomorrow afternoon if I did the rolling display for the next erm lecture then I can <trunc>gi</trunc></u>
<u n="455" who="S0679" trans="overlap">so you won't be free tomorrow afternoon?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0681">er no it's not that I can email it to to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> no no that doesn't matter</u>
<u n="457" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well I will have to go to <anon type="place"/> tomorrow because I'm fairly sure let me just look cos the box is here I've found a few more pills because you know I make up those threes in a strip</u>
<u n="458" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0679">that I keep if I'm <trunc>g</trunc> carrying about? oh I may actually I may I could possibly even go over on Friday</u>
<u n="460" who="S0681">uhu</u>
<u n="461" who="S0679">to collect them so</u>
<u n="462" who="S0681" trans="overlap">I I've got I can go on Thursday if you like?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0679">okay well are you you're coming back here anyway are you?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0681">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0679">you're not having lunch with these people?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0681">no we don't usually have lunch</u>
<u n="467" who="S0679">well if you</u>
<u n="468" who="S0681" trans="overlap">not not as sociable as you</u>
<u n="469" who="S0679">if you did have lunch with them <pause dur="short"/> you'd be over in roughly the right area wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0681" trans="overlap">no no I we'd never have lunch <trunc>tog</trunc></u>
<u n="471" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no? no?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0681" trans="overlap">never had lunch <unclear>together</unclear></u>
<u n="473" who="S0679">okay so you'll come back and have some lunch here will you?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0679">and then we can <event desc="sound of computer"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0679">decide whether it's</u>
<u n="477" who="S0681" trans="overlap">what was that?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0679">best to erm <pause dur="short"/> I think it means an email message has come on my computer</u>
<u n="479" who="S0681">oh right</u>
<u n="480" who="S0679">erm we can decide how we play it</u>
<u n="481" who="S0681">right okay</u>
<u n="482" who="S0679" trans="overlap">because</u>
<u n="483" who="S0681">that's fine</u>
<u n="484" who="S0679">er my timing for going over to <anon type="place"/> is pharmacy-dependent</u>
<u n="485" who="S0681">yes okay and if I get spare time and the library's open I shoot across to the library <pause dur="short"/> oh I've gotta do erm try and do <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s fairy lights as well</u>
<u n="486" who="S0679">okay</u>
<u n="487" who="S0681">I'm very very close to throwing them in the bin now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0679">I think that might be the most time time-effective thing to do with them really</u>
<u n="489" who="S0681">well I it's got personal now because I haven't been able to to suss the problem but I think it's either one of two things there's either an internal break in one of the wires in the control unit or it's a crack in the printed circuit board controller so what I think I'm going to do I'm gonna replace all the wires in the control unit one by one and then cos what happens is I get it working then as I start closing it up it stops working but if that happens I'll just say to them you know fine all the lights work alright or I can make all the lights work er but yes they're running off a four and a half volt battery you know or</u>
<u n="490" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="491" who="S0681">three triple A cells or something</u>
<u n="492" who="S0679">are they putting them outside?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0681">er I I don't know they might oh yeah I promised I've got I've got a little cheap set I picked up at the pound shop I said I'd let them use them at the erm <anon type="place"/> Christmas fair</u>
<u n="494" who="S0679">which erm which er because I'm needing to buy my secret Santa present <pause dur="short"/> and I Netto had a pound lights for a pound</u>
<u n="495" who="S0681">Netto?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0679">Netto the one that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> calls the dog and basket</u>
<u n="497" who="S0681">oh right I know what you mean</u>
<u n="498" who="S0679">yellow and black</u>
<u n="499" who="S0681" trans="overlap">we haven't got one of them in <anon type="place"/> have we?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no we haven't but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got one</u>
<u n="501" who="S0681">oh right</u>
<u n="502" who="S0679">cos it it it's owned by Sainsbury and it's actually on the same site as Sainsbury</u>
<u n="503" who="S0681" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="504" who="S0679">which seems a bit strange really</u>
<u n="505" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="506" who="S0679" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> anyway they had them for a pound but we didn't get round to going er well no er well I wasn't sure cos I've done lights before</u>
<u n="507" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="508" who="S0679">but I do think they're a nice thing to <pause dur="short"/> normally you can</u>
<u n="509" who="S0681"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0679">you can stick a few extra lights up somewhere can't you? <trunc>any</trunc>anybody can</u>
<u n="511" who="S0681" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0679">I think erm</u>
<u n="513" who="S0681">I still haven't made my giant Christmas tree I was always gonna make mm</u>
<u n="514" who="S0679">well let's not let's let's let's leave it for this year perhaps</u>
<u n="515" who="S0679">Christmas cards</u>
<u n="516" who="S0681">yes Christmas cards erm <pause dur="short"/> so we're we're talking about tomorrow and we've got basically please don't point at me I hate people pointing erm and it's obvious you're talking to me cos there's nobody else in the room <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> tomorrow we've got tomorrow you're going out to your whatever it is and we're working out we're doing something in the afternoon so that's alright</u>
<u n="517" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="518" who="S0679">erm <pause dur="short"/> friday I think you're free on Friday so</u>
<u n="519" who="S0681" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="520" who="S0679">we could do it on Friday if not</u>
<u n="521" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="522" who="S0679">erm or if it seemed a I could go over to <anon type="place"/> and then we could go over together and pick things up erm have you insulated the tap at erm?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0681">no isolated</u>
<u n="524" who="S0679">insulated is the word the application of</u>
<u n="525" who="S0681">wrapped it with bubble wrap no I haven't</u>
<u n="526" who="S0679" trans="overlap">in in the old days it used to be the old sock</u>
<u n="527" who="S0681">no I haven't</u>
<u n="528" who="S0679">father was very keen on the old sock approach</u>
<u n="529" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0679">but actually erm bubble wrap is what I used last year</u>
<u n="531" who="S0681">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0679" trans="overlap">okay ah er we need to take some with us although there's probably gonna be some there erm</u>
<u n="533" who="S0681" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="534" who="S0679">and there might even be the thing I used last year if had to <unclear>blame my</unclear> how how it got pulled off erm <pause dur="short"/> okay erm you you mentioned Christmas cards did you see that I've got the first Christmas card of the year arrived?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0681">oh was that? yeah I guessed it might be</u>
<u n="536" who="S0679" trans="overlap">the little square one</u>
<u n="537" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0679">it's from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who if he's in the country and he often goes to erm Vietnam or somewhere at Christmas cos he has Vietnamese in his in his blood</u>
<u n="539" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="540" who="S0679">erm I think with his sister they both sometimes go over erm <pause dur="short"/> but that that's arrived he always seems to like posting them on the thirtieth of November which he may have done and he'd <trunc>ma</trunc> and I always think I'd really like to have my cards out as early as his but I'm not competing this year because I know I can't erm what <pause dur="short"/> what thoughts have you had about Christmas cards?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0681">no just none I thought I'd just panic for a bit <trunc>ye</trunc></u>
<u n="542" who="S0679">okay I maybe we'll put some thought into that tomorrow morning</u>
<u n="543" who="S0681">uhu</u>
<u n="544" who="S0679">because alongside the Christmas card is what we say in a letter and I need to be a little bit thoughtful about what I'm putting in</u>
<u n="545" who="S0681">oh I think I might leave that to you I'll I'll do some late night tonight I'll do some looking around see if I can find find a picture</u>
<u n="546" who="S0679">so you're thinking about making some in some way?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0681">well that's a possibility yeah but</u>
<u n="548" who="S0679">uhu</u>
<u n="549" who="S0681">it that depends on it depends on a lot of things it depends on the picture it depends on could I get some half decent paper which I probably can't anyway</u>
<u n="550" who="S0679">you'll probably only get packs of ten or something</u>
<u n="551" who="S0681">well it's either packs of ten or a ream you know <pause dur="short"/> but erm</u>
<u n="552" who="S0679">if you can get anything <trunc>dece</trunc> what's a ream?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0681">five hundred sheets</u>
<u n="554" who="S0679">one pack?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0681">five hundred sheets</u>
<u n="556" who="S0679">five five packs?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0681">no five hundred individual sheets in a</u>
<u n="558" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="559" who="S0681" trans="overlap">ream</u>
<u n="560" who="S0679">how many <trunc>d</trunc> how many do you get in <pause dur="short"/> a photocopying pack?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0681">a ream</u>
<u n="562" who="S0679">we normally buy possibly up to a hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="563" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="564" who="S0679">so if you could get good paper</u>
<u n="565" who="S0681">yeah well it'll be worthwhile buying a ream to keep us going for a couple of years</u>
<u n="566" who="S0679">if you think there might be two times your you want to do it again even if it's not next year it's worth thinking about if you could get something good</u>
<u n="567" who="S0681">I haven't seen it I I'll it's worth maybe on Friday I'll have a stroll around <anon type="place"/> cos there aren't that number of places there's Staples Rymans</u>
<u n="568" who="S0679">I don't</u>
<u n="569" who="S0681" trans="overlap">and that's oh Paperchase I suppose but their stuff tends to be very expensive</u>
<u n="570" who="S0679">well it tends to be in in small packets</u>
<u n="571" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0679">but I'd do web research rather than walk round <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="573" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="574" who="S0679">then if anybody does have anything decent you can go and have a look at it</u>
<u n="575" who="S0681">yeah I suppose so</u>
<u n="576" who="S0679">erm</u>
<u n="577" who="S0681">so do I look for ornamental paper or something?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0679">well just look up er everybody you know in <anon type="place"/> Paperchase the other ones you mentioned and just see what they sell</u>
<u n="579" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="580" who="S0679">erm or or I don't know if there's some more wholesale paper sort of place</u>
<u n="581" who="S0681">I could actually I could go and see my mates at <anon type="place"/> road couldn't I? the printers I use</u>
<u n="582" who="S0679">could ask the printers about it</u>
<u n="583" who="S0681">yeah that's an idea cos they can get paper at ultra-short notice as well</u>
<u n="584" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="585" who="S0681" trans="overlap">they literally phoning up and have it delivered the next day</u>
<u n="586" who="S0679">we may not need that much but I mean</u>
<u n="587" who="S0681" trans="overlap">well we <unclear>don't</unclear> have a minimum of a ream I'm sure</u>
<u n="588" who="S0679">well yes <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="589" who="S0681">yeah but they're quite friendly and quite helpful I've put a lot of work their way</u>
<u n="590" who="S0679" trans="overlap">it's worth thinking er it's worth thinking about I think even if</u>
<u n="591" who="S0681" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="592" who="S0679" trans="overlap">you don't do it</u>
<u n="593" who="S0681">that's a good idea actually</u>
<u n="594" who="S0679">okay so it looks as though you'll be I bought some cards cos I always send some of</u>
<u n="595" who="S0681" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="596" who="S0679">some individual cards and the first individual card I might be writing is one to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="597" who="S0681">uhu</u>
<u n="598" who="S0679">that we can take over if we go and see her sometime in the next few days with a poinsettia</u>
<u n="599" who="S0681">uhu</u>
<u n="600" who="S0679">can you think of any reason why it wouldn't be good to take her a poinsettia yet?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0681">well have we done it before?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0679">yes which sort of traditional</u>
<u n="603" who="S0681" trans="overlap">it sounds sounds fairly boring</u>
<u n="604" who="S0679">it's sort of traditional</u>
<u n="605" who="S0681">oh right okay</u>
<u n="606" who="S0679">well er she's got a lovely home and</u>
<u n="607" who="S0681" trans="overlap">she does have a lovely</u>
<u n="608" who="S0679" trans="overlap">she <trunc>de</trunc> she does tend to decorate it for Christmas whether she will as much this year I wanted to get it early so she could enjoy it before Christmas</u>
<u n="609" who="S0681">oh</u>
<u n="610" who="S0679">well they you know</u>
<u n="611" who="S0681" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="612" who="S0679" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said well I bought one of those already but the one I bought died so it was quite nice you brought me another one</u>
<u n="613" who="S0681"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="614" who="S0679">but she's got you know different rooms and</u>
<u n="615" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="616" who="S0679">you know she's well not different rooms but</u>
<u n="617" who="S0681" trans="overlap">and a cat does the cat eat poinsettia?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0679">I don't know I imagine if if we take it round you would like to come</u>
<u n="619" who="S0681">oh yes I'd like to <unclear>play with the cat</unclear></u>
<u n="620" who="S0679" trans="overlap">only <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I it's nice it's a shame that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wasn't able to visit when we were down last time cos we had it on a long list of things we might do because I do feel a little bit bad that we didn't talk to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> individually</u>
<u n="621" who="S0681"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0679">about coming to the funeral</u>
<u n="623" who="S0681">uhu</u>
<u n="624" who="S0679">cos she's not our friend more than <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friend but as things turned out erm it I I do feel I wish I'd checked in with her</u>
<u n="625" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="626" who="S0679">but I didn't and</u>
<u n="627" who="S0681">I I I wouldn't have thought of doing it so</u>
<u n="628" who="S0679">mm cos you know I although you know it's it's difficult because er perhaps perhaps <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> ought to take the lead on her friends</u>
<u n="629" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="630" who="S0679">but there was a bit of a slip-up over some relatives</u>
<u n="631" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="632" who="S0679">which could have been a misunderstanding on my part perhaps but I suspect it was on a list of things that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was going to do but erm and she may not have done well it appeared she didn't do erm <pause dur="short"/> but anyway er I don't know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> may not have wanted to come to the funeral I don't know</u>
<u n="633" who="S0681">I don't think she knew <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> particularly well</u>
<u n="634" who="S0679">no but just</u>
<u n="635" who="S0681" trans="overlap">she'd met him or you think she might liked to have come out in solidarity with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sort of thing?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0679">well only that she has been involved in the family for fifty or more years</u>
<u n="637" who="S0681" trans="overlap">oh yes that's true isn't it? indirectly via <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as well yeah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0679" trans="overlap">it's via <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0681">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="640" who="S0679">so</u>
<u n="641" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="642" who="S0679">I don't know when somebody in the family dies</u>
<u n="643" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="644" who="S0679">do you go? I don't know if you're a longstanding family friend</u>
<u n="645" who="S0681">I think typically you do yeah</u>
<u n="646" who="S0679">but you would if it was in <anon type="place"/> would you necessarily</u>
<u n="647" who="S0681" trans="overlap">if it was local local you certainly</u>
<u n="648" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="649" who="S0681">you certainly would go but <trunc>bei</trunc> that much further away makes it makes it a bit more difficult I dunno</u>
<u n="650" who="S0679">I don't know anyway we can't do anything about that but</u>
<u n="651" who="S0681" trans="overlap">no no water under the bridge</u>
<u n="652" who="S0679">I feel I'd still like to maintain contact with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="654" who="S0679">and in that she sent you a card</u>
<u n="655" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="656" who="S0679">admittedly it was you a card rather than me a card but it looks as though she's keen to keep</u>
<u n="657" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="658" who="S0679">a card going obviously it was your birthday</u>
<u n="659" who="S0681" trans="overlap">it's was my birthday so she can hardly send you a card you prawn is she? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="660" who="S0679">no but you know</u>
<u n="661" who="S0681"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="662" who="S0679">I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sent you a card but I wouldn't expect she'd send me one</u>
<u n="663" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="664" who="S0679">for example</u>
<u n="665" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="666" who="S0679">erm and just because you know she's done it to you it doesn't mean</u>
<u n="667" who="S0681">well whatever</u>
<u n="668" who="S0679" trans="overlap">she wants to do it for me but anyway I think one if we go early it will also set what we're doing</u>
<u n="669" who="S0681"><trunc>ye</trunc> right I need to put the bin out and do the washing up erm</u>
<u n="670" who="S0679">okay well I'm I will assist I can do the washing up or I could probably</u>
<u n="671" who="S0681" trans="overlap">oh oh</u>
<u n="672" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I could do the drying up with the use</u>
<u n="673" who="S0681" trans="overlap">do you wanna put the bin out?</u>
<u n="674" who="S0679">no won't do the</u>
<u n="675" who="S0681" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="676" who="S0679">put <trunc>th</trunc> put the bin out</u>
<u n="677" who="S0681">no right</u>
<u n="678" who="S0679">I <trunc>ye</trunc> and we were going to do the servicing of the <unclear>Troja</unclear> this afternoon</u>
<u n="679" who="S0681">the servicing?</u>
<u n="680" who="S0679">you said you would service it</u>
<u n="681" who="S0681">oh right okay <unclear>just give it a brush</unclear></u>
<u n="682" who="S0679" trans="overlap">you said when I come back</u>
<u n="683" who="S0681">I'll give a brush with the scrubbing brush</u>
<u n="684" who="S0679">no not not a clean er it has the servicing instruction for</u>
<u n="685" who="S0681">oh</u>
<u n="686" who="S0679" trans="overlap">check the brakes and things</u>
<u n="687" who="S0681" trans="overlap">oh right oh I didn't know about that</u>
<u n="688" who="S0679">well on that instruction leaflet it's very thorough</u>
<u n="689" who="S0681">oh right okay</u>
<u n="690" who="S0679">erm</u>
<u n="691" who="S0681">does it need re-greasing like like six thousand kilometres?</u>
<u n="692" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no it's the one that ends with you need it if you want it disinfected it had to be done by a professional</u>
<u n="693" who="S0681" trans="overlap">oh you read that part out for me but you didn't read out the</u>
<u n="694" who="S0679"><trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="695" who="S0681">servicing this</u>
<u n="696" who="S0679" trans="overlap">the the only thing is that erm it is a little bit stiff to</u>
<u n="697" who="S0681">which? where?</u>
<u n="698" who="S0679">when you unclip it and when you try and</u>
<u n="699" who="S0681">to open it out you mean?</u>
<u n="700" who="S0679"><trunc>y</trunc>you can open it out when you try and close it you have to almost yank the</u>
<u n="701" who="S0681" trans="overlap">right just</u>
<u n="702" who="S0679" trans="overlap">handle up</u>
<u n="703" who="S0681">it just sounds to me it's not been used for a long time</u>
<u n="704" who="S0679">well I'd just like you to check it cos I don't want to be pulling it inappropriately</u>
<u n="705" who="S0681">yes you can</u>
<u n="706" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I did</u>
<u n="707" who="S0681" trans="overlap">tend to rip door handles off and things can't you? or <unclear/></u>
<u n="708" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I did check to make sure that I was erm I understood the mechanism</u>
<u n="709" who="S0681">uhu</u>
<u n="710" who="S0679">but I just wondered whether if it hadn't been used for a long time although I don't know quite I don't quite understand that er but it does look a bit dusty in places that it just might need lubricating a little or something</u>
<u n="711" who="S0681">mm I won't do that this evening but I will</u>
<u n="712" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="713" who="S0681">I'll dust it over</u>
<u n="714" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no no no you shouldn't do any more cos you've done enough with that erm <pause dur="short"/> with that door</u>
<u n="715" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="716" who="S0679">but</u>
<u n="717" who="S0681">bit of a pain that actually</u>
<u n="718" who="S0679">yeah but it does need to go back on the list of things that to do because I would like it looked at</u>
<u n="719" who="S0681">uhu</u>
<u n="720" who="S0679">I'd also like your opinion on when or <trunc>m</trunc> you know I've got three small candle lights they're not candles as in real flames you just put a battery and they light up</u>
<u n="721" who="S0681">oh yeah I know yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0679">one of them doesn't anymore but I think I I can't remember if it even came they may not <trunc>m</trunc> the batteries may have been separate oh the batteries would have been in place probably one of those pieces of plastic you pull out</u>
<u n="723" who="S0681" trans="overlap">that you pull out yeah</u>
<u n="724" who="S0679">but there's a little screw and I think you might be able to get the battery out</u>
<u n="725" who="S0681">oh well that's fairly simple</u>
<u n="726" who="S0679" trans="overlap">and I would like you to show me if that is the case</u>
<u n="727" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="728" who="S0679">cos you I and we may er even have some batteries to fit on your big board</u>
<u n="729" who="S0681" trans="overlap">it might might be another one of this CR2032s which I the ones I got for my car key</u>
<u n="730" who="S0679">oh right</u>
<u n="731" who="S0681">cos I bought eight of those in one go from the pound shop</u>
<u n="732" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well if you've got a spare one of those then that would be</u>
<u n="733" who="S0681">got a spare seven actually</u>
<u n="734" who="S0679">yes erm well one of the others might need a go soon but</u>
<u n="735" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="736" who="S0679">if if if you've got a small screwdriver I'd like I think</u>
<u n="737" who="S0681" trans="overlap">I have many small screwdrivers</u>
<u n="738" who="S0679" trans="overlap">I think it's erm something I could do myself</u>
<u n="739" who="S0681">oh</u>
<u n="740" who="S0679">but I need instruction</u>
<u n="741" who="S0681">oh</u>
<u n="742" who="S0679">I didn't haven't got on very well with the watch battery thing yet but I think I should be able to do that</u>
<u n="743" who="S0681" trans="overlap">I've gotta do <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s watch he's given me a watch to put back in unfortunately it's a it's a very peculiar strap cos normally I pin the bracelet off</u>
<u n="744" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="745" who="S0681">so you've got good access to the back but it's a funny one if you oh I don't really see it at Aldi once they did a watch repair kit</u>
<u n="746" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="747" who="S0681">which was something silly like three pound fifty or something like that and I wish I'd bought one now because it had three or four it had an adjustable spanner a pin a push pin and for for just the odd funny little tools you need</u>
<u n="748" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="749" who="S0681">which might have been quite useful <pause dur="short"/> mm I might even look at the web see if there's one on the web</u>
<u n="750" who="S0679">might be it's always possible</u>
<u n="751" who="S0681">or I'll put it on my Christmas card list you never know</u>
<u n="752" who="S0679">yeah I don't know well not on your Christmas card list cos you're not gonna send them a Christmas card but you might put it on your</u>
<u n="753" who="S0681">Amazon wish list</u>
<u n="754" who="S0679" trans="overlap">Christmas present list</u>
<u n="755" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="756" who="S0679">erm</u>
<u n="757" who="S0681">oh damn I must phone <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> up <pause dur="short"/> I just remembered</u>
<u n="758" who="S0679">I am really at a loss as to what to put on my Christmas card list er oh you've got me saying it now my Amazon wish list</u>
<u n="759" who="S0681">I <trunc>f</trunc> er books is yours a good thing I think</u>
<u n="760" who="S0679">I well I don't I <trunc>d</trunc> I mean I'm not getting round to reading</u>
<u n="761" who="S0681">neither am I</u>
<u n="762" who="S0679">books you know if I I'm not going to want to just get them and throw them away</u>
<u n="763" who="S0681">no have you seen any DVDs you want films?</u>
<u n="764" who="S0679">well</u>
<u n="765" who="S0681" trans="overlap">cos there were a few you you you've acquired a few that you particularly wanted haven't you? are there any more that you could put on?</u>
<u n="766" who="S0679" trans="overlap">well if unless they're <trunc>rea</trunc></u>
<u n="767" who="S0681" trans="overlap">cos DVDs are easy to get you know</u>
<u n="768" who="S0679">unless some really special one I'd rather borrow them to be honest</u>
<u n="769" who="S0681">okay fine</u>
<u n="770" who="S0679">because erm I don't really want to keep them</u>
<u n="771" who="S0681">well the other issue is</u>
<u n="772" who="S0679" trans="overlap">you see</u>
<u n="773" who="S0681">if you don't choose something something will be imposed upon you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="774" who="S0679">well I I did choose things last year and I still was given something</u>
<u n="775" who="S0681">well I think they've bought that much earlier on with you in mind you know</u>
<u n="776" who="S0679">well maybe</u>
<u n="777" who="S0681">yeah yeah they had bought it</u>
<u n="778" who="S0679" trans="overlap">no they said no they said they'd bought it and they and they hadn't quite decided who to give it to</u>
<u n="779" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="780" who="S0679">and they</u>
<u n="781" who="S0681">they bought it cos they liked it</u>
<u n="782" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="783" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="784" who="S0679">erm would it be if I mean the thing that I might like is a smartphone</u>
<u n="785" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="786" who="S0679">I mean in a way it would be nice</u>
<u n="787" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="788" who="S0679">it would suit my purposes more</u>
<u n="789" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="790" who="S0679">if they could give you a small contribution</u>
<u n="791" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="792" who="S0679">towards my smartphone</u>
<u n="793" who="S0681">mm yeah think it would cost you about sixty quid for <unclear>wire three thousand</unclear> <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="794" who="S0679">cos I mean they</u>
<u n="795" who="S0681" trans="overlap">which is quite good</u>
<u n="796" who="S0679" trans="overlap">they give awfully generous presents and if there are things that you want it's <trunc>int</trunc> but I I mean I'd sort of been putting things on a wish list at the moment unless I'm get great inspiration</u>
<u n="797" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="798" who="S0679">I mean I don't I mean I'm I my my life is quite you know I've got I would have needed an MP3 player</u>
<u n="799" who="S0681">well we sorted that</u>
<u n="800" who="S0679">but I needed to get one and that's quite a big thing to put on even so isn't it?</u>
<u n="801" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0679">erm</u>
<u n="803" who="S0681">yeah I can have a word with the two of them they're quite they're quite amenable to suggestion they'll much rather give you something you want</u>
<u n="804" who="S0679">well it just seems like that would be something I'd I'd like</u>
<u n="805" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="806" who="S0679">I mean I'd rather they didn't buy me a present anyway to be honest</u>
<u n="807" who="S0681">well you can't avoid that I'm afraid they're like that mm</u>
<u n="808" who="S0679">erm <pause dur="short"/> well I I I could <trunc>poss</trunc> I mean if they want to buy me something I could try and put some very small things on there</u>
<u n="809" who="S0681">mm</u>
<u n="810" who="S0679">do you think that would be helpful?</u>
<u n="811" who="S0681">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah we've got a present I think we've got a present from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s folks at their house</u>
<u n="812" who="S0679">tea or jam?</u>
<u n="813" who="S0681">I don't see the point of that but she's very erm <pause dur="short"/> oh I think she's she feels I look after <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know so I think cos I see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> quite a lot quite often</u>
<u n="814" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="815" who="S0681">I think she and I think the way I looked after when she was very ill when she was</u>
<u n="816" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="817" who="S0681">she's got <unclear/></u>
<u n="818" who="S0679">so do you think we better make a start on this washing up?</u>
<u n="819" who="S0681">no I'll make a start on taking the bin out</u>
<u n="820" who="S0679">oh bin out and then washing up</u>
<u n="821" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="822" who="S0679">have you had something for supper?</u>
<u n="823" who="S0681">yeah</u>
<u n="824" who="S0679">oh I <trunc>did'n</trunc> missed that happening</u>
<u n="825" who="S0681">you were too busy watching television</u>
<u n="826" who="S0679">okay</u>
<u n="827" who="S0681"><foreign lang="fre">avez servez vous</foreign>?</u>
<u n="828" who="S0679">oh yes</u>
<u n="829" who="S0681" trans="overlap">a plate</u>
<u n="830" who="S0679">of course</u>
<u n="831" who="S0681">and a glass</u>
<u n="832" who="S0679">yeah okay righty-o</u>
<u n="833" who="S0681">have we <event desc="abrupt end"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
