<text id="SLLC">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:23:59</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-12-06</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0439 S0440</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Car</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Family, cars, family friends, weddings, housing situations, boyfriend problems.</topics>
		<activity>Catch-up with mum, part 2</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, ancedote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0439">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern - Non-accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0440">
				<exactage>58</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich, Norfolk</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Norfork</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Thrapston (Northants)</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>26</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Examinations Manager in Secondary School</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0439"><unclear>good</unclear></u>
<u n="2" who="S0440">cos dad was getting panicky <unclear>when he was</unclear> going around there <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> she hadn't even been out all day</u>
<u n="3" who="S0439"><trunc>sh</trunc> they're just</u>
<u n="4" who="S0440">she was still in her</u>
<u n="5" who="S0439">they're just</u>
<u n="6" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0439">fuckers</u>
<u n="8" who="S0440">I know</u>
<u n="9" who="S0439">fucking hate them</u>
<u n="10" who="S0440">I was I was <pause dur="short"/> bloody annoyed I really was to be honest</u>
<u n="11" who="S0439">like <pause dur="short"/> you can't choose your family but <pause dur="short"/> I already have you know like <pause dur="short"/> my friends are so much closer to me and I do so much more for them than what I ever do for my extended family <pause dur="short"/> they just don't care they're just not nice people</u>
<u n="12" who="S0440" trans="overlap">it'll be very interesting to <trunc>s</trunc> it'll be no they're not it'll be very interesting to see how many of them ever bother to come and see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0440">and if they say oh well are you bringing him up? can you bring him round?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0439">no piss off</u>
<u n="16" who="S0440" trans="overlap">no yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you can meet us in town if you want to not gonna drive to all your individual houses</u>
<u n="18" who="S0440">no you know what'll happen is I'll bring him up and I'll drop him off at for you for four days I said to him I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says oh we need to are you bringing dad over this weekend? we need to see him it'll be yeah I'll bring him over on Monday and you can bring him back on Thursday</u>
<u n="19" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well they can't be like well we've got children we can't see him you had children</u>
<u n="20" who="S0440">I had children</u>
<u n="21" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you know?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I had children and I worked</u>
<u n="23" who="S0439">and you brought and you know? we've <trunc>s</trunc> we saw him when we were little we like not religiously but we saw him like well nearly every few months? and you had to drive us up when we were little so <pause dur="short"/> and we stayed with grandma and grandad and stuff like there's no children don't stop you from doing stuff so</u>
<u n="24" who="S0440">no</u>
<u n="25" who="S0439">has <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got two now? now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s only got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hasn't she?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0440" trans="overlap">one yeah <pause dur="short"/> well but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> won't go and see him won't come and see him <pause dur="short"/> this is what annoys me about you know?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0439">our family is just horrible people</u>
<u n="28" who="S0440"><unclear>mm</unclear></u>
<u n="29" who="S0439">well they aren't <pause dur="short"/> I dunno they're not horrible they just don't <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>like about</unclear> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just <pause dur="short"/> don't get me wrong I don't see my grandparents as much as I should do <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> I don't live fifteen minutes away from them you know if I if I lived as close to nana as what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does I'd go up and see her every week</u>
<u n="30" who="S0440" trans="overlap">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> absolutely piss me off</u>
<u n="31" who="S0439">like it's because we don't live close to our grandparents if we lived round the corner <pause dur="short"/> you'd make an effort to go see them every week wouldn't you? <pause dur="short"/> you just would</u>
<u n="32" who="S0440" trans="overlap">well I mean I got really angry with er with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when we were talking about the erm <pause dur="short"/> we were talking about the <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> thirty thousand she wanted to borrow for her house</u>
<u n="33" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0440"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had already asked her do you want?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I know <unclear>I know</unclear> I know yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0440" trans="overlap">he thought <pause dur="short"/> and and that annoys me intensely <unclear>but</unclear></u>
<u n="37" who="S0439" trans="overlap">cos then she's like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would give it to me fuck off <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0440" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wouldn't give it to me <pause dur="short"/> no we said go and see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and let <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> get some out of the bank for you</u>
<u n="39" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> dad isn't holding the money <unclear>ransom</unclear> I mean he's not</u>
<u n="40" who="S0440" trans="overlap"><unclear>but</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> no no I know</u>
<u n="41" who="S0439">he's not making preventing you from doing it</u>
<u n="42" who="S0440" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> but he he told her he was making a an investment</u>
<u n="43" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's just investing it <pause dur="short"/> he's looking after it he's not <pause dur="short"/> spending it <pause dur="short"/> like that's why I think like <trunc>gr</trunc>grandad <trunc>gr</trunc>grandad just trusts dad I wouldn't trust <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> with the money</u>
<u n="44" who="S0440"><unclear>there's er</unclear></u>
<u n="45" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and I think the difference is because dad has money <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't have the money <pause dur="short"/> and therefore there's that always that element of</u>
<u n="46" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0439">like lack of trust</u>
<u n="48" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0439">but cos dad's got his own money</u>
<u n="50" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's erm a <trunc>s</trunc> a system now <pause dur="short"/> where <pause dur="short"/> parents can give a deposit and <pause dur="short"/> children can have a deposit <pause dur="short"/> and you can get a <pause dur="short"/> preferential loan for buying a house so <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="51" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0440">your father wants you to look into that if you're staying in Cambridge for any length of time <pause dur="short"/> so that</u>
<u n="53" who="S0439" trans="overlap">he could look into that anyway just rent it out</u>
<u n="54" who="S0440">no you can't rent it out</u>
<u n="55" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="56" who="S0440">but you you could have it and rent it out <pause dur="short"/> rent a room out that's not a problem</u>
<u n="57" who="S0439">I dunno how long I want to live in Cambridge</u>
<u n="58" who="S0440">I know you don't but you don't have to rent the room out permanently you can just say to someone you know till I'm living in Cambridge and then you can sell it after that</u>
<u n="59" who="S0439">yeah but I don't know if I even wanna stay in Cambridge I don't know how long I want to be <unclear>that much</unclear></u>
<u n="60" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I know I know but the thing is <pause dur="short"/> look at it <pause dur="short"/> because if eventually it would then mean that we could buy it off you <pause dur="short"/> okay?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="62" who="S0440">but you can get preferential <anon type="place"/> rate <pause dur="short"/> mortgage rates and everything <pause dur="short"/> and savings rates <pause dur="short"/> it's really erm you know <unclear>it's good</unclear></u>
<u n="63" who="S0439" trans="overlap">so <trunc>y</trunc> well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s bought a house in London <pause dur="short"/> and obviously that's London so different but like <pause dur="short"/> her council tax is really high her erm <pause dur="short"/> everything's really high she has to pay content insurance <pause dur="short"/> like owning a house is a lot of money</u>
<u n="64" who="S0440">owning a house is a lot of money but it's also <pause dur="short"/> if you don't get in this erm <pause dur="short"/> if you don't get into the housing market some time you'll never get in</u>
<u n="65" who="S0439">quite negative view but okay</u>
<u n="66" who="S0440">it isn't that's the true deal with it nowadays <pause dur="short"/> it's really getting difficult</u>
<u n="67" who="S0439">I don't I wouldn't wanna house that I couldn't rent because I don't know how long I wanna stay</u>
<u n="68" who="S0440">no you can't rent it out immediately <pause dur="short"/> okay? <pause dur="short"/> you can rent it out eventually but you can't rent it out immediately</u>
<u n="69" who="S0439">well then find a house you want and I'll buy it under <trunc>you</trunc> under my name but you have it</u>
<u n="70" who="S0440" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="71" who="S0439">can have it as like an investment property then</u>
<u n="72" who="S0440">mm <pause dur="short"/> but you'd have to move into it</u>
<u n="73" who="S0439">well yeah yeah fine</u>
<u n="74" who="S0440" trans="overlap">and then you can leave<unclear/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and I could leave when I want to</u>
<u n="76" who="S0440">and then you could rent a room out to someone as well while you you know while <pause dur="short"/> if you got a two bedroom house</u>
<u n="77" who="S0439" trans="overlap">how long will I have to live in it till I could leave <unclear>eventually like</unclear>?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0440" trans="overlap">probably a probably a year</u>
<u n="79" who="S0439">I can do that</u>
<u n="80" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0439">if you and dad found a house you wanted and you can buy it under my name and use that scheme</u>
<u n="82" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0439">that doesn't bother me but I don't I'm not buying a property for me</u>
<u n="84" who="S0440">I know you're not</u>
<u n="85" who="S0439">like if you and dad want a <pause dur="short"/> retirement <trunc>pro</trunc> you know? <pause dur="short"/> I think property is a good thing to do <pause dur="short"/> property is a great thing to do it's what the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>s did <pause dur="short"/> the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>s took <pause dur="short"/> some <trunc>m</trunc> a lump sum out of their pension or something and they brought two flats in <anon type="place"/> to rent to students</u>
<u n="86" who="S0440" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0439">I think they make er something <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying something like her mum charges nine hundred pounds a month or something for her that person to live in that house</u>
<u n="88" who="S0440">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0439" trans="overlap">so but like <pause dur="short"/> it's <trunc>g</trunc> it's a good place to buy a house like housing will go up in Cambridge like you won't have any problem ever reselling</u>
<u n="90" who="S0440" trans="overlap">absolutely</u>
<u n="91" who="S0439">or making money on it <pause dur="long"/> but yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I'll take my <trunc>u</trunc> my <unclear>car</unclear> back <unclear>today</unclear></u>
<u n="92" who="S0440">why?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0439">cos it's my car</u>
<u n="94" who="S0440">alright okay fine</u>
<u n="95" who="S0439">I don't need it any I don't <pause dur="short"/> I don't need yours at the moment do I?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0440">well yeah you're still trying to slash the mileage on yours aren't you?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0439">yeah? <pause dur="short"/> but I'm only gonna be driving to and from work this week <pause dur="short"/> I'm not gonna be driving anywhere else <pause dur="short"/> I'm not gonna be <trunc>doi</trunc>doing any long distances <pause dur="short"/> I'm not doing any long distances next weekend</u>
<u n="98" who="S0440">okay how many miles is it to your office from your house?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0439">er eight</u>
<u n="100" who="S0440">oh that's alright then <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0439">sixteen miles a day same as what you're doing</u>
<u n="102" who="S0440" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0439">I've got <trunc>n</trunc> I haven't got any long distances planned over the next few weeks so <pause dur="short"/> cos the weekend after so this weekend I don't really have anything planned I can come home and <pause dur="short"/> help you clean on the Saturday if you want</u>
<u n="104" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0439">the weekend after that I'm coming home I'm not doing I'm not going anywhere so I don't need <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I don't need your car I don't need I'll just erm I'll just use mine <unclear/> paying off for it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="106" who="S0440">the other thing I need to do is call into <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0439">oh why?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0440">cos we've gotta choose a toilet and stuff for the <unclear/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0439" trans="overlap">not today</u>
<u n="110" who="S0440">oh alright</u>
<u n="111" who="S0439">do it another day do it next weekend do it next Sunday</u>
<u n="112" who="S0440">alright</u>
<u n="113" who="S0439">if we do it today we'll never get into town</u>
<u n="114" who="S0440">alright</u>
<u n="115" who="S0439">cos I know how long you spend in <anon type="place"/> so you say you'll be there for five minutes and five hours later you finally come out <trunc>b</trunc> having bought absolutely nothing</u>
<u n="116" who="S0440">oh no I'm not buying it now anyway <unclear/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0439" trans="overlap">exactly so don't do it</u>
<u n="118" who="S0440">they've got a sale on in erm the end of January</u>
<u n="119" who="S0439">look online <pause dur="short"/> it's what the world is made of today mum is looking online <pause dur="long"/> er <pause dur="short"/> horrible weather oh England <pause dur="short"/> but erm no I was thinking this about Germany when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> isn't gonna be there I thought he was having I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was having problems getting a job in <anon type="place"/> and stuff</u>
<u n="120" who="S0440">she is</u>
<u n="121" who="S0439">then why are they staying in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0440">cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> works there doesn't he?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0439">yeah true <pause dur="short"/> true true <pause dur="long"/> but <pause dur="short"/> if she can't get a job there that's not very good for them is it?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0440">no <pause dur="long"/> but then she's not exactly the the er light at the end of the tunnel is she when it comes to? she's not exactly</u>
<u n="125" who="S0439">she's not a laugh a minute but</u>
<u n="126" who="S0440" trans="overlap">spark no <trunc>spark</trunc> bit <unclear>sparkly</unclear> is she?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0439">you know he's <pause dur="short"/> I think he's settled I think he's gonna</u>
<u n="128" who="S0440"><unclear>mm</unclear></u>
<u n="129" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I think they'll probably get married and Bob's your uncle</u>
<u n="130" who="S0440" trans="overlap"><unclear>I think so</unclear></u>
<u n="131" who="S0439">that's them <pause dur="short"/> done and dusted really isn't it?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0439">how they how long have they been together now for? four years?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0440" trans="overlap">five five years something like that yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0439">so <pause dur="short"/> they're obviously happy together I assume so <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/> let it be</u>
<u n="136" who="S0440">she's always such a misery though isn't she?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0439" trans="overlap">she is she's a pain in the arse</u>
<u n="138" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0439">but he's always gone for girls who are just a bit weird</u>
<u n="140" who="S0440">why've I come this way for?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0439">no idea <pause dur="short"/> but you can go into town this way but I don't know what you're doing I don't know what your plan is</u>
<u n="142" who="S0440" trans="overlap">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I I just automatically came this way by mistake I should've gone back to the M6 <pause dur="short"/> gone into town the other way <pause dur="short"/> never mind</u>
<u n="143" who="S0439">yeah yeah you came off didn't you? yeah true <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I always carry on actually I always make the mistake of carrying on and then</u>
<u n="144" who="S0440" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0439">having to come back and turn round <pause dur="short"/> I always missed that bloody turning</u>
<u n="146" who="S0440">could always turn and go back up that way <unclear/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's up to you I don't <trunc>c</trunc> I don't mind what you do <pause dur="short"/> I don't mind <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I won't get to see him anyway <unclear>not unless er</unclear></u>
<u n="148" who="S0440">mm?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0439">I won't get to see him anyway <pause dur="short"/> they're going back to <anon type="place"/> on the twenty-eighth they're not even gonna be there</u>
<u n="150" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0439">so <pause dur="short"/> see what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s doing</u>
<u n="152" who="S0440"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s coming with us</u>
<u n="153" who="S0439">is she?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0440"><unclear>mm</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> shall I turn round and go round</u>
<u n="155" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I don't mind mum do what you wanna do</u>
<u n="156" who="S0440">oh I'll go back I'll go through <anon type="place"/> <unclear>my way</unclear></u>
<u n="157" who="S0439">okay <pause dur="short"/> and dad'll be like did you park at <unclear/> to get the bus in? <pause dur="short"/> like fuck off dad <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> horrible weather</u>
<u n="158" who="S0440">ghastly isn't it?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0439">absolutely ghastly <pause dur="short"/> so how you've only got two weeks left of work now haven't you?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0439">and then you're out of there</u>
<u n="162" who="S0440">I'm out and that's it I've got to return all the goods that I've got in good condition little do they know <pause dur="short"/> oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sent <unclear>a card got laughing</unclear> the other day <pause dur="short"/> well I tell you what we'll do we'll go round by the station see whether we can park at the station free of charge if we can then get the train in</u>
<u n="163" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0440">if we can't we'll drive in alright?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="166" who="S0440">yeah we were laughing at erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying oh she says <pause dur="short"/> I'll miss things like <pause dur="short"/> take pencils home for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I said well take a box of pencils home for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0440">so we made her a box up with er calculator and er stuff like that</u>
<u n="169" who="S0439">yeah they're not gonna miss a calculator are they?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0440" trans="overlap">the calculators haven't even been opened they're brand new we've</u>
<u n="171" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0440">had them for <trunc>wee</trunc> for years brand new ones never opened so like they can have a she's having a calculator</u>
<u n="173" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0440">and she's having erm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0439">who cares? yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0440" trans="overlap">pencils <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has <trunc>pencil</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> she got a pencil case with all bits of equipment in it you know?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0439">who obviously gives a shit?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0440">well I I don't no</u>
<u n="179" who="S0439" trans="overlap">at the end of the day</u>
<u n="180" who="S0440">considering she's done so much extra for them you know <pause dur="short"/> oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in our library you know the one who was oh <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> the one who's having erm IVF treatment?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0440">she had a miscarriage</u>
<u n="183" who="S0439">oh shit</u>
<u n="184" who="S0440">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so she's been off whether she'll ever come back again I don't know</u>
<u n="185" who="S0439">it's weird that some I think a lot of women miscarriage though don't they? like you miscarriaged three times? twice?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0440">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum cos I remember talking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum miscarriaged a few times as well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> miscarriaged I think it's a common thing isn't it? it's not</u>
<u n="188" who="S0440" trans="overlap">of course it is <pause dur="short"/> it's not</u>
<u n="189" who="S0439">it's not like</u>
<u n="190" who="S0440">no</u>
<u n="191" who="S0439">it's just obviously <trunc>horr</trunc> it's it's a double blow when you can't when you're struggling to conceive anyway</u>
<u n="192" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0439">then you conceive a miscarriage but normal <trunc>u</trunc> women who don't have problems miscarriage</u>
<u n="194" who="S0440">course they do</u>
<u n="195" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> miscarriaged didn't she?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0440">they think that I miscarriaged because they were boys</u>
<u n="197" who="S0439">really?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0439">oh sorry about that</u>
<u n="200" who="S0440">no</u>
<u n="201" who="S0439">you're stuck with girls <unclear/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0440">I like them</u>
<u n="203" who="S0439" trans="overlap">gutted for you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0440" trans="overlap">no I like girls who wants a boy?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0439">dad</u>
<u n="206" who="S0440">no he <unclear>wouldn't</unclear></u>
<u n="207" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I don't even dad dad didn't give a shit did he?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0440">dad didn't give a shit no</u>
<u n="209" who="S0439" trans="overlap">dad didn't want kids to begin with so</u>
<u n="210" who="S0440">he loved his two girls and he still does love his two girls</u>
<u n="211" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> I know yeah I remember him telling us like I didn't want children but then I got you so I have to look after you I was like oh thanks dad that's nice <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> nice being honest with me <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> but yeah no <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got two boys though hasn't she?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0440">mm mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0439">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got two boys</u>
<u n="214" who="S0440">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had</unclear></u>
<u n="215" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></unclear> wanted a girl</u>
<u n="216" who="S0440">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0439">huh?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0440">er is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> forty?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0439">mm I don't know thirty-eight</u>
<u n="220" who="S0440" trans="overlap">thirty-eight? thirty-nine? yeah?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0439">she won't have any more kids though will she?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0440">no</u>
<u n="223" who="S0439">she wanted a little girl didn't she? but <trunc>i</trunc></u>
<u n="224" who="S0440" trans="overlap">she can't <pause dur="short"/> she can't afford it but I think her and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> aren't haven't got any money haven't got much money at all</u>
<u n="225" who="S0439">no <pause dur="short"/> it's a forty mum</u>
<u n="226" who="S0440">I know it is <pause dur="short"/> and I'm doing forty</u>
<u n="227" who="S0439">good</u>
<u n="228" who="S0440">yeah I don't think they've got much money at all</u>
<u n="229" who="S0439">maybe they shouldn't've gone to <trunc>f</trunc> bloody <anon type="place"/> for their wedding then should they?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="231" who="S0439">I realise that was a few years ago and I am just picking hairs but you know <unclear>it's a point</unclear></u>
<u n="232" who="S0440">it is he's absolutely <unclear>wrong</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> there's no point in spending money well that's like when they said to us about going over there to the wedding</u>
<u n="233" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="234" who="S0440">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said no <pause dur="short"/> and and what we can't afford it and the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was really <pause dur="short"/> of course you can afford this</u>
<u n="235" who="S0439">well my worry is that</u>
<u n="236" who="S0440" trans="overlap">but we don't want to use our holiday up</u>
<u n="237" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> to go visit <unclear>their thing</unclear></u>
<u n="238" who="S0440" trans="overlap">to go visit them</u>
<u n="239" who="S0439">I don't even like them</u>
<u n="240" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0439">like if I really worry <unclear>well I don't I don't I don't</unclear></u>
<u n="242" who="S0440" trans="overlap">why would we? we can have a two week family holiday</u>
<u n="243" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/> well I use the word worry but if I ever get married I don't <trunc>w</trunc> I'm not inviting them</u>
<u n="244" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0439">I don't want to pay to have these people at my wedding who I don't even like and don't like me just because I've got the same blood as them <pause dur="short"/> fuck off do I</u>
<u n="246" who="S0440">no <trunc>d</trunc> if I if I if you <pause dur="short"/> if I was getting married now I would have a very very small wedding</u>
<u n="247" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I'm gonna have <trunc>t</trunc> the smallest wedding you can imagine</u>
<u n="248" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0439">to be fair me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were joking about this we were trying to count who we would have at our wedding <vocal desc="laugh"/> and it came to something like twenty people <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0440" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's all we had twenty-four at ours</u>
<u n="251" who="S0439">I just wouldn't care why would I want them?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0440" trans="overlap">and six of them were kids what I'll <trunc>l</trunc> one of those was erm what's his name? rent a crowd <pause dur="short"/> er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and rent a mob</u>
<u n="253" who="S0439">yeah so</u>
<u n="254" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0439">I don't want people I don't <trunc>w</trunc> I don't want to pay to have people at my wedding who I don't want to see</u>
<u n="256" who="S0440">no</u>
<u n="257" who="S0439">it's my day you can piss right off <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>we'll probably have</unclear> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they're alright <pause dur="short"/> get on better with them than what I do <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I don't want them I don't want them at my wedding if I get married so they're not gonna come</u>
<u n="258" who="S0440">they won't give you a bloody <trunc>pre</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> wedding present so</u>
<u n="259" who="S0439">don't wanna wedding present <pause dur="short"/> I don't want their stuff I don't want anything from them</u>
<u n="260" who="S0440">oh Volkswagen are having to give money off cars now</u>
<u n="261" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I can imagine yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0440"><unclear/> to existing customers are getting double the discount</u>
<u n="263" who="S0439">really?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0440" trans="overlap">double the <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0439">they <trunc>kee</trunc> they did keep trying to ring me to they spoke to me asked for a car I was like no fine thank you I like my car <pause dur="short"/> go away <pause dur="short"/> finishes in June anyway so <pause dur="short"/> do love it though it's so cute</u>
<u n="266" who="S0440">mm I know it is it's beautiful <pause dur="short"/> so if you don't want it we'll take over another one and get rid of my smart car <pause dur="short"/> or you can have the smart car for good and I'll take over your</u>
<u n="267" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah I think while yeah we wouldn't keep the <pause dur="short"/> we wouldn't keep the Up cos I don't have five grand to</u>
<u n="268" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I'll swap it</u>
<u n="269" who="S0439">we don't have five we just swap the Up back</u>
<u n="270" who="S0440">swap the Up <pause dur="short"/> yeah swap the up back for a er</u>
<u n="271" who="S0439" trans="overlap">another Up or another Volkwagen yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0440">another Up yeah <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't want <trunc>f</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to me he said is that big enough for your dad and I said absolutely</u>
<u n="273" who="S0439" trans="overlap">course it is yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0440">I said I don't want anything bigger than that <pause dur="short"/> so that's what we do swap it in for another Up</u>
<u n="275" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos you get five grand off the Up</u>
<u n="276" who="S0440">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> then you can erm yeah <pause dur="short"/> by which time by the time it came to it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll be dead and we pay the five grand</u>
<u n="277" who="S0439">bless him</u>
<u n="278" who="S0440">it will be</u>
<u n="279" who="S0439">it will be yeah I know</u>
<u n="280" who="S0440" trans="overlap">will be</u>
<u n="281" who="S0439">he's <trunc>g</trunc> I think he's got about another two or three</u>
<u n="282" who="S0440">I I</u>
<u n="283" who="S0439">two years</u>
<u n="284" who="S0440">two years <pause dur="short"/> but mum has now got to the stage where she can't swallow properly</u>
<u n="285" who="S0439">oh that's <unclear>so horrible</unclear></u>
<u n="286" who="S0440">erm <pause dur="short"/> she's choking on her food</u>
<u n="287" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well this is this this again is a really morbid thing to say but if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> if when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> dies</u>
<u n="288" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can live there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0440">I know that's what we've already said</u>
<u n="291" who="S0439">like you can rent out nan's house</u>
<u n="292" who="S0440">that's what we said</u>
<u n="293" who="S0439">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can live with you</u>
<u n="294" who="S0440">that's what exactly what we've said</u>
<u n="295" who="S0439">so you</u>
<u n="296" who="S0440" trans="overlap">we can rent out <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house we wouldn't bother selling it we'd rent it out</u>
<u n="297" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no you'd rent it out</u>
<u n="298" who="S0440">we rent it out</u>
<u n="299" who="S0439" trans="overlap">cos there isn't a mortgage on it is there? she <trunc>pai</trunc> they paid it off</u>
<u n="300" who="S0440" trans="overlap"><unclear>no</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> but er</u>
<u n="301" who="S0439">so</u>
<u n="302" who="S0440">yeah there's no mortgage on it</u>
<u n="303" who="S0439">you know? that's a what? that's a hundred and fifty grand sitting there</u>
<u n="304" who="S0440">absolutely so you would rent it out</u>
<u n="305" who="S0439">rent it out</u>
<u n="306" who="S0440">erm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0439">you and dad and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would just have a <pause dur="short"/> bank account with the money going to <pause dur="short"/> if anybody needed to take money out of it they could you know you'd be <trunc>f</trunc> wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0440">you'd rent that out you could easily rent that out for <pause dur="short"/> five six hundred pounds a month</u>
<u n="309" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> after a year you'd have what? seven grand that's three grand each for dad and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0439">nice little money earner really isn't it so?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0439">there's no point selling it when you can make money out of it</u>
<u n="314" who="S0440" trans="overlap">and you've still got <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> you've still got your capital</u>
<u n="315" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0440">no absolutely <trunc>u</trunc> you know it's that is</u>
<u n="317" who="S0439">it'd be <trunc>fooli</trunc>foolish of them to sell it</u>
<u n="318" who="S0440">absolutely</u>
<u n="319" who="S0439">but if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't want it I guess dad could buy her half but still quite a bit of money isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> you wouldn't be able to afford that</u>
<u n="320" who="S0440" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> you wouldn't sell it you wouldn't <trunc>s</trunc> no he wouldn't buy <pause dur="short"/> while <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is alive <pause dur="short"/> you wouldn't sell it anyway</u>
<u n="321" who="S0439">no no no no <pause dur="short"/> of course not</u>
<u n="322" who="S0440"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> couldn't have any money out of it <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can't have any money out of it at all until erm</u>
<u n="323" who="S0439">she's dead yeah I know</u>
<u n="324" who="S0440" trans="overlap">until <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dead</u>
<u n="325" who="S0439">but that'll be <trunc>s</trunc> it'll be fine wouldn't it? er</u>
<u n="326" who="S0440">yeah course it will</u>
<u n="327" who="S0439">technically it'd be nan earning the <trunc>mo</trunc> nan would earn more money <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> seven thousand pound income she'd be paying tax in the end</u>
<u n="329" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she actually would</u>
<u n="330" who="S0440">I get a tax rebate as well by the way</u>
<u n="331" who="S0439">yeah but christ how much is that gonna be?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0440">about two hundred three hundred quid four hundred quid maybe</u>
<u n="333" who="S0439">good god</u>
<u n="334" who="S0440" trans="overlap">do you know what I'm doing with that?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0439">what?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0440" trans="overlap">do you know what I'm gonna do with that? I'm gonna buy myself a ring from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0439">you already have a ring from <anon type="place"/> mum</u>
<u n="338" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna buy myself a piece of jewellery from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0439">but you don't need to</u>
<u n="340" who="S0440" trans="overlap">on my tax back</u>
<u n="341" who="S0439">why?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0440" trans="overlap">not <trunc>f</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> why? just <pause dur="short"/> for me</u>
<u n="343" who="S0439">but you've got it</u>
<u n="344" who="S0440">I know but I want <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="345" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you don't even wear it</u>
<u n="346" who="S0440">I do <pause dur="short"/> well I <trunc>c</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I want one that I can wear all the time you know a <trunc>g</trunc> a general one that I can wear</u>
<u n="347" who="S0439" trans="overlap">why can't?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0440" trans="overlap">don't want an expensive one I want a silver one</u>
<u n="349" who="S0439">how much was the one you bought?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0440">three hundred quid</u>
<u n="351" who="S0439">so why would gonna buy another one for three hundred quid?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0440">I'm not gonna buy one for three hundred quid I'll buy one of her silver ones they're <trunc>n</trunc> about ninety aren't they?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0439">yeah well just <pause dur="short"/> that's all I want</u>
<u n="354" who="S0440">but I just want to buy something for myself</u>
<u n="355" who="S0439">you buy everything for yourself</u>
<u n="356" who="S0440">I do not</u>
<u n="357" who="S0439">that's why you've got four handbags <pause dur="short"/> you and your money</u>
<u n="358" who="S0440">I was gonna give you that brown one but if you don't want <unclear>it then</unclear></u>
<u n="359" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I don't need a handbag I use my pockets I told you this</u>
<u n="360" who="S0440">I know <pause dur="short"/> things get lost in pockets</u>
<u n="361" who="S0439">things get lost in handbags</u>
<u n="362" who="S0440"><vocal desc="sigh"/> anyway <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0439">but no they went so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came last Thursday before we went to Naples I picked her up from the park and ride</u>
<u n="364" who="S0440">mm?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0439">she got out the car she went ah don't know where my phone is I was like oh god what? <pause dur="short"/> and she so she made me wait at the park and ride for the next bus to come which was twenty minutes</u>
<u n="366" who="S0440" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0439">then it <trunc>dr</trunc> the bus drove straight past cos she wanted to try and stop and ask the driver</u>
<u n="368" who="S0440" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0439">cos <trunc>eigh</trunc> <trunc>n</trunc>no it must've been half eight at night so nothing was open</u>
<u n="370" who="S0440" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="371" who="S0439">then she asked me to drive to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> to chase the bus I was like you're kidding me</u>
<u n="372" who="S0440">you didn't do it? cos oh fucking hell</u>
<u n="373" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah we drove we drove to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0439">she spoke to the bus driver got a number <pause dur="short"/> of someone to call to find lost property <unclear>and stuff</unclear></u>
<u n="376" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0439">she like she gave me petrol money and stuff like that wasn't the point though the point was just <pause dur="short"/> she's taking the piss <unclear>love for her</unclear> phone the only reason she wanted it is so she could text <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> all weekend anyway <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> drove to Tesco's picked her up a SIM card gave her my old phone just to cos I wasn't sure if it was gonna work or not it might've got blocked so I don't know if it'll work but we'll give it a go luckily it didn't it not blocked so we can reuse it for you if you want it</u>
<u n="378" who="S0440">yes please</u>
<u n="379" who="S0439">pop a SIM in it</u>
<u n="380" who="S0440">yes please</u>
<u n="381" who="S0439">erm <pause dur="short"/> it's just like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just <pause dur="short"/> we didn't get home till half ten <vocal desc="sigh"/> I was like I've gotta get up at three to drive us to the airport <pause dur="short"/> you're taking the piss <pause dur="short"/> I just <pause dur="short"/> seriously</u>
<u n="382" who="S0440">yeah so she never got it back obviously</u>
<u n="383" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no no someone nicked it or</u>
<u n="384" who="S0440" trans="overlap"><unclear/> someone</u>
<u n="385" who="S0439"><trunc>s</trunc>someone found it didn't hand it in I don't know</u>
<u n="386" who="S0440" trans="overlap">what sort of phone was it?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0439"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh it was only a <pause dur="short"/> it was <trunc>b</trunc> it was a bit like yours think it was an HTC it wasn't like a great phone it</u>
<u n="388" who="S0440">no</u>
<u n="389" who="S0439">but it had data and <pause dur="short"/> and like she just rang up her cos her contract was the same as her parents' contract it was all</u>
<u n="390" who="S0440" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="391" who="S0439">built in to the same it's cheaper if you get your oh actually we could do that when you get my phone when people ring up and ask for a deal actually</u>
<u n="392" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="393" who="S0439">oh I could do that okay <pause dur="short"/> erm sort that out next weekend oh no I forgot to get the phone off her damn it <pause dur="short"/> well I'm gonna get the phone off her</u>
<u n="394" who="S0440" trans="overlap"><unclear>okay</unclear></u>
<u n="395" who="S0439">I'll ring up O2 and we can try and get a double deal thing <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> anyway and I <trunc>d</trunc> it wasn't a great phone but it's just because she wanted to contact <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and I was just like <pause dur="short"/> and apparently that was another thing he had a go at her saying you've been weird with me the last two days it's like yes cos she hasn't had a phone <pause dur="short"/> well she has a phone but it doesn't have data so she can't message you every minute of every fucking day you <pause dur="short"/> controlling <pause dur="short"/> possessive <trunc>c</trunc> twat face <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="396" who="S0440"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0439">she's <trunc>annoy</trunc> she's</u>
<u n="398" who="S0440">I do I do <pause dur="short"/> get so pissed off with people</u>
<u n="399" who="S0439">I know I just</u>
<u n="400" who="S0440">I really do</u>
<u n="401" who="S0439">I just <pause dur="short"/> like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we're here this weekend having a great time going to one of the one of the wonders of the world Pompeii</u>
<u n="402" who="S0440" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so where else are we gonna go then?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear>but</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> budapest</u>
<u n="404" who="S0440">Budapest yeah <pause dur="short"/> and where else?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0439">Budapest</u>
<u n="406" who="S0440">yeah well that's good</u>
<u n="407" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and <trunc>w</trunc> that's kind of that's kind of my limit at the moment I don't know where else to go</u>
<u n="408" who="S0440">Budapest Berlin</u>
<u n="409" who="S0439">Budapest Berlin <pause dur="short"/> new York</u>
<u n="410" who="S0440">yeah want to New York</u>
<u n="411" who="S0439" trans="overlap">wanted to go to New York</u>
<u n="412" who="S0440">yeah we can still go to New York <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> for christ sake <pause dur="short"/> just let them go</u>
<u n="413" who="S0439">he did actually flash him he just didn't go</u>
<u n="414" who="S0440"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0439">the the woman just wasn't looking</u>
<u n="416" who="S0440">and this dude <pause dur="short"/> ah <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0439">god they're both women you're letting down the side loves <pause dur="short"/> come on <pause dur="short"/> learn to drive a car <pause dur="short"/> that's one thing about your car I don't like <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> about your car <pause dur="short"/> is the turning circle you have a really big turning circle</u>
<u n="418" who="S0440">I know because I haven't got <trunc>day</trunc> I haven't got er whatnot I can't go in that in that side oh <unclear>I did</unclear> oh go in that way er I haven't got yeah there's loads of parking spaces here for fuck's sake</u>
<u n="419" who="S0439">yeah we're trying it here then?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0440">yeah we'll try it here that'll be the easiest thing perhaps okay?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0439">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0440"><trunc>loa</trunc>loads of parking spaces</u>
<u n="423" who="S0439" whoConfidence="low"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="424" who="S0439">do you have to pay on a Sunday?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0440">no idea <pause dur="short"/> expect so</u>
<u n="426" who="S0439">bloody Sunday drivers it's only Saturday <pause dur="short"/> er Sunday</u>
<u n="427" who="S0440"><unclear>can you can</unclear></u>
<u n="428" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mum that's not a space <unclear>that's a space</unclear></u>
<u n="429" who="S0440">er got space there haven't I?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0439">just about <pause dur="short"/> uh <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0440"><unclear>I'll take</unclear> clear all this so it doesn't</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
