<text id="SLNV">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:33:04</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-02-13</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0618 S0619</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A bistro in Tarnow, Poland</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Discussing students, politics, student loans, pensions, MOT, working abroad, Netflix, consent, agreeing where to drive.</topics>
		<activity> Two friends talking about various topics (see 9 above) in a bistro in Tarnow, Poland.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0618">
				<exactage>42</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge/Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months on and off</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>unemployed/ Some part-time private TEFL teacher/ Semi-retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0619">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury, Lancashire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Nort West: Lancs, Greater Manchester</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>nearly 4 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher of English as a foreign Language</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0618">hi <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0619">hello</u>
<u n="3" who="S0618">a little bit above a speaker there do you think that'll just be nice</u>
<u n="4" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I know I'm not sure</u>
<u n="5" who="S0618" trans="overlap">nice groovy background music for the people doing the transcripts</u>
<u n="6" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I don't know how they'll feel about it but</u>
<u n="7" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> they'll not be able to hear us</u>
<u n="8" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm sure it'll be okay</u>
<u n="9" who="S0618">I'm sure it'll be okay cool so</u>
<u n="10" who="S0619">yeah so obviously <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I absolutely adore him</u>
<u n="11" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0619" trans="overlap">he's just very very sweet er <pause dur="short"/> and who else?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0618">there's a</u>
<u n="14" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I liked her as well</u>
<u n="15" who="S0618">I think she just started she came late to the class</u>
<u n="16" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm mm mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0618">and on the other side of the table there's naughty boy who used to wear always wear the sweatshirt saying do I give a fuck? or something like that</u>
<u n="18" who="S0619">is he the one with the <trunc>s</trunc> er what's his name? what does he look like? weird like</u>
<u n="19" who="S0618">oh crumbs erm quite a chunky young man <pause dur="short"/> you wouldn't want to meet him in a dark alley of an evening erm</u>
<u n="20" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="22" who="S0618">or maybe you would I don't know but er he used to sit next to and mess around a little bit with another young woman whose name I also can't remember she was a little bit emo <pause dur="short"/> but not quite</u>
<u n="23" who="S0619">I don't know I don't think I met <pause dur="short"/> met them <pause dur="short"/> but some of them <pause dur="short"/> were really nice</u>
<u n="24" who="S0618" trans="overlap">no yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0619">confident and very sure of themselves very good at English and some just so shy</u>
<u n="26" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0619">and I can I can understand it but <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I don't know how you can help them to that extent</u>
<u n="28" who="S0618">what were you doing with them? was it speaking exams?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0619">speaking exams no the actual speaking <trunc>mo</trunc> well the mock exam</u>
<u n="30" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh the actual mock okay</u>
<u n="31" who="S0619">erm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0618"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s actually really good but incredibly shy</u>
<u n="33" who="S0619">yeah he yeah I could tell</u>
<u n="34" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0619">erm <pause dur="short"/> but he you know <pause dur="short"/> they get a mark for their ability to interact with the partner</u>
<u n="36" who="S0618">oh dear</u>
<u n="37" who="S0619">and if they don't look at each other in the eye when they're talking or it doesn't seem kind of genuine and they're going so what do you think? yes well I like you know like robots</u>
<u n="38" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0619">erm they get marked down for it they've got to be like normal people having a conversation</u>
<u n="40" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0619">erm and like I know the stress affects them but you can tell like when they get on well anyway outside of class but in the exam they can be with anyone</u>
<u n="42" who="S0618" trans="overlap">aha <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah it might actually help them in the exam to be with a complete stranger</u>
<u n="43" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0618">in a strange environment I wonder if part of the shyness is a worry about being judged by people that they know</u>
<u n="45" who="S0619">yep <pause dur="short"/> because you're really on the spot erm and there's this feedback at the end so you know you can tell quite clearly who's got more who's <trunc>ma</trunc> who made <trunc>m</trunc>more mistakes</u>
<u n="46" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0619">than the other person so <pause dur="short"/> I don't know but it's very it was it was nice anyway</u>
<u n="48" who="S0618">yeah good they're nice group</u>
<u n="49" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I was with <trunc>Mo</trunc> I was with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her stomach was rumbling for three hours straight I <trunc>thou</trunc> I was like we really you need food</u>
<u n="50" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0619">and there's this bit in the exam where it's just silence for like fifteen seconds while they read whatever they're reading</u>
<u n="52" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0619">er and it was at that point every single group of people that her stomach would start and she would be like oh I'm so sorry I was like he he he</u>
<u n="54" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0619">oh it was just so funny ha ha ha <pause dur="short"/> I enjoyed that</u>
<u n="56" who="S0618">you need to keep some emergency oatcakes or a banana in your pocket for them her</u>
<u n="57" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like oh can I get you anything? and I was like</u>
<u n="58" who="S0618">feed this woman</u>
<u n="59" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I was like do you have any food?</u>
<u n="60" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0619">and she'd like brought back like two biscuits I was like mm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0618">ah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay I'm gonna solve the situation?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0618">ha</u>
<u n="65" who="S0619">I didn't even know what I expected her to do <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh I'll just whip up a banquet in the back <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0618">just pop down Maccy D's</u>
<u n="67" who="S0619">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0619">oh dear</u>
<u n="70" who="S0618">oh well</u>
<u n="71" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah it was funny it was very funny though <pause dur="short"/> very nice and good <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came last night with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> from the school so they well had a couple of beers not me er and nice we talked about er the holocaust ISIS British politics er <pause dur="short"/> sort of every kind of controversial topic that you could</u>
<u n="72" who="S0618">and how was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s outlook? I can imagine she's not so judgmental and racist as a lot of <pause dur="short"/> the folks in town</u>
<u n="73" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no she's not <pause dur="short"/> she said couple of things that I thought oh that's I'm not sure because you know we were talking about Polish politics and this new government and she was like well it's just so hard to vote because <pause dur="short"/> I mean we don't want to vote for these but you don't want to vote for the last lot</u>
<u n="74" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0619">but somehow these are sort of erm the lesser of two evils and I thought oh well that's telling unless like she just voted for something completely different</u>
<u n="76" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0619">erm away from these two parties</u>
<u n="78" who="S0618">yeah most of my students have pretty much said with the election that there's just no choice</u>
<u n="79" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0618">do you want you know which of well which of the two evils there is no party that they would vote in <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I can kind of see it and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said <vocal desc="laugh"/> ah and I'm still like a little bit I don't think I can look at you properly er he was like well I think my friends me and my friends have very different political views to you and a your friends and he was like my friends me and my friends sort of <trunc>al</trunc> are all conservatives or UKIP and I guess and I guess that you're sort of erm Labour Lib Dem</u>
<u n="82" who="S0618" trans="overlap">holy fuck <pause dur="short"/> was he serious?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0618">wow</u>
<u n="85" who="S0619">and I was like but he was like but it's okay cos we get along in the house we're not sort of arguing all the time</u>
<u n="86" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0619">I was like I was like oh my god well that's sort of like</u>
<u n="89" who="S0618">wow</u>
<u n="90" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you know it's so kind of erm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0618">wow</u>
<u n="92" who="S0619">I just sort of can't look at him properly and like how I <pause dur="short"/> you know I <trunc>ju</trunc> I wouldn't admit that my friends vote UKIP not that I have any but I wouldn't sort of admit it <vocal desc="laugh"/> er to a group of people</u>
<u n="93" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> my family all voted for the Tories</u>
<u n="94" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0618">which really shocked and surprised me</u>
<u n="96" who="S0619">my two of my closest friends <pause dur="short"/> say <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>we</trunc> separately were economic Tories</u>
<u n="97" who="S0618">what?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0619">they're like we're left no but but I don't agree with the sort of welfare side of things</u>
<u n="99" who="S0618">oh my god</u>
<u n="100" who="S0619">it's like what are you talking about? <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm it's I don't know</u>
<u n="101" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0619">so and <pause dur="short"/> as I've <trunc>sa</trunc> I think I've said before I mean we've talked about this before you know you sort of lose touch with or you just presume everyone thinks the same as you because you surround yourselves with people who think the same as you</u>
<u n="103" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and your Facebook feed is full of the same stuff</u>
<u n="104" who="S0619">yeah yeah yeah and the same people</u>
<u n="105" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0619">and you know when I was on Twitter on the election er night or the night of the elections and all these exit poles my whole stream was people going oh my god what's happening? I can't believe that this de de de de</u>
<u n="107" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0619">erm <pause dur="short"/> and I was like well so who's voting for these people?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0618">yeah my family sorry and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s and his family and friends sorry yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="110" who="S0619">yeah so I was like these people do exist in our society I just don't know them</u>
<u n="111" who="S0618" trans="overlap">it just makes you think you know there's a whole other Facebook newsfeed out there that's full of this oh David Cameron oh Jeremy Hunt hooray</u>
<u n="112" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> how can anybody how can people be like oh well I just think this is a great idea Jeremy? but <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0618">I know</u>
<u n="114" who="S0619">it's rather worrying all my friends were out <pause dur="short"/> with their banners and signs</u>
<u n="115" who="S0618">good for them</u>
<u n="116" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0618">oh I do like a good march</u>
<u n="118" who="S0619">oh I do like a good march</u>
<u n="119" who="S0618">oh I do I do like a good banner wave <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it was you know they were putting all these pictures of themselves on Instagram and stuff and erm their the consultants who weren't striking had ordered them like loads of takeaway pizza and stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0618">ah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0619">so my friend was like weighed down with like twenty pizzas</u>
<u n="123" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0619">you know it was just sort of</u>
<u n="125" who="S0618">that's sweet</u>
<u n="126" who="S0619">yeah it was good <trunc>s</trunc>spirit around it</u>
<u n="127" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0619">but I read something the other day that oh no it's not in it's in like trust hospitals or foundation hospitals they can decide whether to implement the new contract or not <pause dur="short"/> so there's like some hospitals where they won't have to implement it <pause dur="short"/> but all my doctor friends er are applying to jobs abroad so</u>
<u n="129" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0619">and I was thinking about this if they all move abroad it means they won't have to pay their student fees so that's fifty thousand pounds per doctor er per person who's graduated in the last few years who just won't pay back their fees</u>
<u n="131" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> wow <pause dur="short"/> good on them</u>
<u n="132" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0619">I'm not paying my fees back er but I've not been kind of forced out of country because er you know what I mean</u>
<u n="135" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> is there a time limit on it? I mean if you if you're in the UK and start earning at aged fifty-five for example would you be expected?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0619" trans="overlap">er twenty-five years</u>
<u n="137" who="S0618">twenty-five years hey that's not bad <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0619">I think so I think it's <pause dur="short"/> I think it's twenty-five years cos</u>
<u n="139" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0619">we're we're taught this erm <pause dur="short"/> at school or at uni</u>
<u n="141" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0619">if you're out of the country for twenty-five years they wipe it</u>
<u n="143" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that's cool handy hint for you though if you think you might want a UK pension you can ring the tax office every year and say how much do I owe you in national insurance contributions?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0618">and it's a few hundred quid a year I can't remember the figure I did I was a year short er more than a decade ago and I think I had to pay seven hundred quid and that was that year with a tick in a box</u>
<u n="146" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0618">I mean there are no guarantees of course I think you needed something like twenty-five qualifying years to be able to draw a pension but that's as things stand today</u>
<u n="148" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0618">the government by the time I retire might have decided to do away with pensions entirely you never know so</u>
<u n="150" who="S0619">yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> so erm what erm what was I going to say? mm mm mm yeah and er and pay national insurance for that time that I'm in England so for about five weeks</u>
<u n="151" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0619">erm and it is quite a lot of national insurance and it's quite a lot of tax but I can get the tax back</u>
<u n="153" who="S0618">yeah it won't be enough for the year</u>
<u n="154" who="S0619" trans="overlap">er <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0618">but yeah it's just something worth considering you might want to sort of factor it into your annual budgetary equations <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="156" who="S0619">mm <pause dur="short"/> so we'll see <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="157" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0619">but it was you know it was just such a shock and then he started a sentence that was something like oh I just don't get that about gay marriage and me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0619">no no no no no no</u>
<u n="161" who="S0618">oh</u>
<u n="162" who="S0619">he's like I just don't believe that people you know are so against it and I was like thank fuck for that I was going to have to kick you out and go to Mrs <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and say</u>
<u n="163" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh my god <pause dur="short"/> I can't live with this man</u>
<u n="164" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I can't live with this man I'm sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0619">we were like er this was sort of after the UKIP <trunc>revel</trunc> er revelation</u>
<u n="167" who="S0618">yeah mind you David Cameron voted for equal marriage <pause dur="short"/> there's still big problems it's a big issue in Northern Ireland still erm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="169" who="S0618">with er the DUP vetoing it all the Stormont executive has said yes let's have equal marriage and the DUP er have this petition of concern</u>
<u n="170" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0618">which is a a legal thing that they can use to block legislation from being passed if they believe that it's gonna unfairly disadvantage either the Protestant community or the Catholic community so they've used it <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and it's a nonsense so there are you know big petitions trying to get their petition overturned to bring it in to to law that still hasn't happened</u>
<u n="172" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="173" who="S0618">I do wonder you know if it does come in if my legal rights of marriage <trunc>w</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> might get backdated because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I had a civil partnership in Northern Ireland</u>
<u n="174" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0618">so I don't have equal rights you know financially and that's going to affect me in later life even if it doesn't now but I wonder if that might get sort of wiped out <pause dur="short"/> and changed I don't know</u>
<u n="176" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="177" who="S0618">I suppose once it eventually goes through I need to be asking that question</u>
<u n="178" who="S0619">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't think the coffee's as good here as it was last time</u>
<u n="180" who="S0619">it's too hot to drink that's the problem <vocal desc="laugh"/> with black well we can have a little wander</u>
<u n="181" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> can we manage a little</u>
<u n="182" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0618" trans="overlap">air?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0619">I was thinking yeah I need to get out of the house</u>
<u n="185" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure it's driving you stir crazy we can just drive around in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for a little while if you like? <pause dur="short"/> open the window when you want some air try not to cough on anything or touch anything</u>
<u n="186" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm joking</u>
<u n="188" who="S0619">you know it's been better today I took the I took the rubbish out and then I was like fuck that was a bad idea</u>
<u n="189" who="S0618" trans="overlap">good <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0619">erm but <pause dur="short"/> in general <pause dur="short"/> stuff's starting to clear up but we'll see</u>
<u n="191" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0619">it well I suppose it should be doing <pause dur="short"/> by now</u>
<u n="193" who="S0618">and have you noticed how clean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0619">she's very clean I hadn't noticed but she's clean</u>
<u n="195" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she's very shiny I've been putting off going to one of these erm <pause dur="short"/> wash places cos there are five numbers</u>
<u n="196" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0618">and I have no idea what they all say <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I asked <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he said oh start with number two and then go for number three and that's you just ignore the other numbers so I was on number two for most of the time getting six months worth of shite off of her and then I started to wonder after these streaky lines were appearing am I actually taking off the top layer of polish here?</u>
<u n="198" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0618">I mean there's there's a certain amount of potential for that I'm not sure so when I'm over in England in March for the pre MOT checks and things I'll get an opinion of an expert and we'll see <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0619">oh no</u>
<u n="201" who="S0618">I know I'm not sure though because</u>
<u n="202" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> naked</u>
<u n="203" who="S0618">no then I rubbed bits with my hand and then the streaks disappeared and everything went whiter</u>
<u n="204" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0618">so I wonder if you know the the super heated soapy jet wash of number two gets a certain level of shit off of it and then I need to actually rub with a sponge or something to get the next layer of cack off</u>
<u n="206" who="S0619" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0618">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0619">but it was easy to do?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0618">yeah really easy to do cost about ten zlotys about a pound seventy-five something like that</u>
<u n="210" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0618">and I was there for fifteen minutes with the various</u>
<u n="212" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0618">jets number two and number three so yeah it went very well so I'll do that again and I think any future wash will only cost about five so I should do it in half the time</u>
<u n="214" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0618">yeah it's good</u>
<u n="216" who="S0619">good for you</u>
<u n="217" who="S0618">yeah so I'm writing out my itinerary at the moment and erm checking with various people that it's okay to stay on whatever dates</u>
<u n="218" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="219" who="S0618">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah and I've just been in touch with the van man see if he's free to do a check on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> pre MOT check and you know with a vehicle you can get thirteen months' worth of MOT</u>
<u n="220" who="S0619">right</u>
<u n="221" who="S0618">so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s due on the sixteenth of April</u>
<u n="222" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="223" who="S0618">but if I have her tested on the sixteenth of March or after then the certificate is still valid to sixteenth of April next year</u>
<u n="224" who="S0619">ah ha okay</u>
<u n="225" who="S0618">so it's a naughty way of getting thirteen months I suppose</u>
<u n="226" who="S0619">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="227" who="S0618" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah so I'm trying to do that and trying to figure in all of the the the dates and allow time for if she does need any parts or need any work doing</u>
<u n="228" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="229" who="S0618">so <pause dur="short"/> yeah but we'll see but I'm quite excited really and I've finally asked my aunty and uncle if I can leave all my shite at their house <pause dur="short"/> and my aunty weren't keen</u>
<u n="230" who="S0619">oh no</u>
<u n="231" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh shit so my uncle wasn't there he was working late last night he's the one he'll say oh yes mate whatever you need no no worries but my aunty's I don't know I think she's quite stressed because her youngest son and his wife who both have fairly severe disabilities have been staying with them for the past few months</u>
<u n="232" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="233" who="S0618">she's pushing seventy and she's just stressed out a lot of the time so I think anybody asking anything of her <vocal desc="laugh"/> is gonna be met with a ah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah mm</u>
<u n="235" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0618">so I dunno <pause dur="short"/> so I quickly followed that up with an email to my uncle just to say I had a chat with my aunty and this is what I asked and this is the volume of crap I wouldn't mind keeping in your spare room and it's really genuinely honestly not that much</u>
<u n="238" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0618">it will fit in the spare room and all go away in drawers wardrobe cupboards</u>
<u n="240" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0618">I mean easily it's not like boxes everywhere erm <pause dur="short"/> I mean you know if you look at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> there she was full on the way over</u>
<u n="242" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0618">I'm keeping some stuff to travel with giving a load of stuff away I'm ready to let go of now it's not really that much so</u>
<u n="244" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> good</u>
<u n="245" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0619">good for you</u>
<u n="247" who="S0618">and I've been on the work away website and the help X website I'm getting really really really really excited</u>
<u n="248" who="S0619">so what's how's the what's the plan today? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0618">well</u>
<u n="250" who="S0619">as it stands</u>
<u n="251" who="S0618">there's actually there's a place in Portugal where</u>
<u n="252" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="253" who="S0618">I think erm they they're looking for people from I think it's mid April to December</u>
<u n="254" who="S0619">ah ha</u>
<u n="255" who="S0618">they accept people and I I don't know I kind of get the feeling I could go live with them for the whole duration</u>
<u n="256" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0618">but <pause dur="short"/> heat might be a problem in Portugal in the summer</u>
<u n="258" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="259" who="S0618">and then there are some Poland projects I really like the look of as well</u>
<u n="260" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="261" who="S0618">erm one of them has they look like <unclear/> horses</u>
<u n="262" who="S0619">ah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0618"><trunc>li</trunc>little ponies they're stumpy little things erm not quite like the things that go up and down beaches but</u>
<u n="264" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="265" who="S0618">you know a bit bigger than that and a bit more grown up looking than that I suppose a bit more horsey looking than that but erm yeah they got twenty of them and part of the job obviously will be shovelling shit</u>
<u n="266" who="S0619" trans="overlap">cute <pause dur="short"/> oh my god</u>
<u n="267" who="S0618">and I think in the profile they talk about shovelling shit or clearing shit and thought ah that's honest I like that</u>
<u n="268" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0618">erm but you'd also have an opportunity to learn to ride and they talk about erm cos they're all hippies being in kind of being one with the horse and learning how like <pause dur="short"/> raw ride in a</u>
<u n="270" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> horse whisperer</u>
<u n="271" who="S0618">yeah ride in a horse sensitive kind of a way <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I really like that</u>
<u n="272" who="S0619">well that's nice</u>
<u n="273" who="S0618">so that might be a wonderful opportunity</u>
<u n="274" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah be really nice</u>
<u n="275" who="S0618">yeah haven't found much with bees <pause dur="short"/> unfortunately</u>
<u n="276" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="277" who="S0618">I am keen to learn about bees there's lots on biodynamic farming and organic farming and permaculture so I'm not going to have problems there <pause dur="short"/> and then <pause dur="short"/> and then I looked at a map and I thought I'm you know I'm thinking now about this drive back to the UK and I'm staying with friends in <anon type="place"/> and I'm staying with two lots of friends in the Netherlands</u>
<u n="278" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0618">and I'm thinking if I'm driving form Poland to Portugal surely it makes sense to stay in some projects in Czech Republic in Austria</u>
<u n="280" who="S0619">nice</u>
<u n="281" who="S0618">and maybe Italy in France in Spain before I get down to Portugal</u>
<u n="282" who="S0619">oh</u>
<u n="283" who="S0618">so I'm thinking maybe I'll just do like a month or six weeks in Poland and then maybe you know a month Czech Republic a month Austria a month Spain and then get down to Portugal and kind of bed in there for winter I don't know</u>
<u n="284" who="S0619">nice</u>
<u n="285" who="S0618">there's projects everywhere it's amazing can't believe I've never discovered this world before <pause dur="short"/> and you can tell from the feedback and the reviews that <pause dur="short"/> well not everybody but if you pick the right ones based on reviews they treat you like part of the family and</u>
<u n="286" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="287" who="S0618">in they can be having a traditional whatever meal with that mum or grandma's cooked and be at the table with the whole family and other volunteers so it's exciting can't wait really</u>
<u n="288" who="S0619">good for you <pause dur="short"/> I'm kind of well I'm not jealous of the sort of opportunity to move so much <pause dur="short"/> but er</u>
<u n="289" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="290" who="S0619">it's nice</u>
<u n="291" who="S0618">I think to each their own you know I think some people <pause dur="short"/> er I was talking to my Holland friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about this she's very much a home body</u>
<u n="292" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="293" who="S0618">and she's a home maker and she's been put sending me Whatsapp pictures of she's bought a new sofa and a new coffee table and a new TV unit and new net curtains and asks me my opinion on does this knick knack go well in this window with these curtains? I mean as if I have an opinion</u>
<u n="294" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="295" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like it's not my department not where my skills lie I'm afraid I don't know it's another dust <unclear>ball</unclear></u>
<u n="296" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0618">and yeah so <pause dur="short"/> that's her and that brings her joy and happiness and she's a feeder and a you know a mother and a nurturer</u>
<u n="298" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0618">and for me I love wandering and I love finding out about people and about their culture</u>
<u n="300" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="301" who="S0618">and learning new skills when I'm going about it and there's no right or wrong it's just different</u>
<u n="302" who="S0619">mm m mm mm yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0618"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s eldest son is going around erm around Asia for three months and she's shitting a brick worrying already that he's gonna die or get into some sort of difficulties and <pause dur="short"/> I dunno she says she takes comfort in knowing me because we talk about</u>
<u n="304" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="305" who="S0618">my plans sort of step by step whereas I think with her and her son it's just a case of he's going and she doesn't know</u>
<u n="306" who="S0619">where he'll be</u>
<u n="307" who="S0618">yeah she doesn't know the detail of what he's up to and who he's meeting and how safe he is <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> just watching if these people slip cos the last two have <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="308" who="S0619">no no no</u>
<u n="309" who="S0618">navigated that slope quite successfully</u>
<u n="310" who="S0619">oh <pause dur="short"/> okay what do you fancy doing?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0618">well I don't want another coffee cos that was a bit rank I'm surprised at that I'm sure we had a nicer one before</u>
<u n="312" who="S0619">and it was the same girl</u>
<u n="313" who="S0618" trans="overlap">anyway <pause dur="short"/> was it?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0618">cor you're so observant <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> what you mean the skinny brown haired one? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0619">yes the skinny brown haired rather pretty one yes</u>
<u n="317" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's how all Polish women look yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> funny <pause dur="short"/> I don't know do you need anything from any particular shop or do you want to go for a little random drivette or?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0619">mm <pause dur="short"/> let me think? <pause dur="short"/> I could do with shopping but I can't be bothered</u>
<u n="319" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="320" who="S0619">erm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0618">if you want to write a list and then sit where you're sitting I'll run into Lidl and get a few bits</u>
<u n="322" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh no no no <pause dur="short"/> erm I'm trying to think what we could do or where we could go</u>
<u n="323" who="S0618">don't forget you can use your trolley as a Zimmer frame</u>
<u n="324" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I've got legs</u>
<u n="325" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0619">this isn't like the problems of two three weeks ago when I didn't have legs but I had an upper body</u>
<u n="327" who="S0618">I know</u>
<u n="328" who="S0619">this week I seem to not have an upper body but I do have the legs the legs are fine</u>
<u n="329" who="S0618" trans="overlap">you have no lungs</u>
<u n="330" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> don't know which is worse <pause dur="short"/> I think the no legs is actually worse than the no lungs</u>
<u n="331" who="S0618">yeah well the no lungs could potentially kill you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="333" who="S0618">whereas the no legs you just <vocal desc="laugh"/> might be a bit bored but you're not dead</u>
<u n="334" who="S0619">it was it was more painful though it was more painful</u>
<u n="335" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="336" who="S0619">whereas this is kind of just sort of frightening <vocal desc="laugh"/> but not that painful <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="337" who="S0618">oh yes USA Netflix</u>
<u n="338" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="339" who="S0618">more joys to behold they've got <pause dur="short"/> I mean we're talking inane Hollywood bollocks it's just good to stare at of an evening doesn't really tax the brain cells too much they've got all of the Mission Impossibles all of them <pause dur="short"/> one through four</u>
<u n="340" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh have they? I've not seen any Mission Impossible ever in my whole life no</u>
<u n="341" who="S0618" trans="overlap">have you not? <pause dur="short"/> oh number one's the best number two's pretty good yeah I really like them they're all on there they've got all of the modern day Batmans</u>
<u n="342" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="343" who="S0618">I've seen none of those</u>
<u n="344" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh I like some of them</u>
<u n="345" who="S0618">they've got all of the Matrix films</u>
<u n="346" who="S0619">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> not seen the Matrix either</u>
<u n="347" who="S0618" trans="overlap">and I I got number one completely number two lost me about half way through and I didn't get number three so I'd like to have a little <pause dur="short"/> you know a bit of analysis I think</u>
<u n="348" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0618">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah what else was on there? they've got Broadchurch</u>
<u n="350" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="351" who="S0618">they've got the Bletchley something or others</u>
<u n="352" who="S0619" trans="overlap">circle</u>
<u n="353" who="S0618">Bletchley Circle did you see that?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0619">no</u>
<u n="355" who="S0618">it was excellent erm strong female leads</u>
<u n="356" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="357" who="S0618">so you'd probably enjoy that bit of girl power going on yeah which reminds me Happy Valley</u>
<u n="358" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0618">I mean great but it's not very happy is it?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0619">well no I know er but</u>
<u n="361" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> although I did laugh a lot in the first five minutes</u>
<u n="362" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="363" who="S0618">while they're sat outside smoking fags and she's relaying the story about the goat <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0619">I know I really enjoyed</u>
<u n="365" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0619">I really enjoyed it er <pause dur="short"/> I started watching before this one was released I started watching the season one last week and in the first episode I was just like ah I just can't be bothered with all of the rape <vocal desc="laugh"/> all of the time</u>
<u n="367" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0619">erm <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> yeah I abandoned it</u>
<u n="369" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I think the twist to this one will be a woman done it it'll probably be the woman who was Moaning Myrtle</u>
<u n="370" who="S0619">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0619">erm <pause dur="short"/> yes another thing we were talking about last night we were talking about erm <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember it was something to do with sort of <pause dur="short"/> not rape culture exactly but it was sort of erm <pause dur="short"/> er sort of like victim shaming or educating <trunc>gi</trunc> oh no we were talking about having children and then we said I were so worried about erm <pause dur="short"/> if I had a daughter cos I'd just feel so protective all the time if she ever left the house I'd be worrying like what would happen to her <pause dur="short"/> er and you know well I sort of said but you know it's not her responsibility to learn how to sort of er protect herself it should be sort of the responsibility of or the education of young men saying</u>
<u n="373" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0619">stop attacking people please <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> er and I <trunc>fe</trunc>feel quite strongly about this</u>
<u n="375" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think we have a <pause dur="short"/> a lot of that in UK culture in particular is teaching women in particular to be afraid and that just sucks</u>
<u n="376" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="377" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0618">and teaching parents to be afraid and a lot of that's you know it's nonsense</u>
<u n="380" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="381" who="S0618">statistically what's the probability of you know a paedophile attacking your child or</u>
<u n="382" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="383" who="S0618">erm a rapist attacking your daughter I mean statistically it's tiny but the fear can be enormous</u>
<u n="384" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm but <pause dur="short"/> no I well I think sort of if you're talking about like rapists in the sense of like a man dragging you into an alley</u>
<u n="385" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0619">it's tiny</u>
<u n="387" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0619" trans="overlap">but if it's like erm going home with someone on a night out</u>
<u n="389" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah and you've had too much to drink and whatever yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0619">yeah that's</u>
<u n="391" who="S0618">that's more likely</u>
<u n="392" who="S0619">way more likely so there sort of needs to be some education for both young men and women <pause dur="short"/> about sort of consent or</u>
<u n="393" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> there was a fantastic thing on Facebook</u>
<u n="394" who="S0619" trans="overlap">the tea thing</u>
<u n="395" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0619">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="397" who="S0618">on tea</u>
<u n="398" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah and if a woman you've gone home with is too drunk to agree to cup of tea she doesn't want tea</u>
<u n="400" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="401" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0619">well I read this</u>
<u n="403" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I like that</u>
<u n="404" who="S0619">I read this book about <pause dur="short"/> no it was sort of a fiction book for young <pause dur="short"/> people erm about a sort of group of friends and this girl erm in this community and she's like really really beautiful and she's a proper bitch to her friends and she knows that she's pretty and de de de and sort of for the first half of it you don't really like her and you're not sort of very sympathetic towards her erm <pause dur="short"/> and she's always going out and getting drunk er and sleeping around and then she's <pause dur="short"/> er at a party and she's sort of gang raped by this group of footballers from the local football team and they take pictures and put it on the internet and all of this stuff <pause dur="short"/> erm and <pause dur="short"/> well it's sort of about these issues of consent and about social media and er the impact of social media and all of <pause dur="short"/> these <pause dur="short"/> things and I think my point is that it should be sort of not not necessarily read in schools but sort of recommended to young people young men</u>
<u n="405" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah the issues should be addressed</u>
<u n="406" who="S0619">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't remember having any form of school education over sex or rape or consent nothing</u>
<u n="408" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="409" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0619">I don't know</u>
<u n="411" who="S0618">look at all the birds on the lamppost they've all paired off <pause dur="short"/> this lamppost</u>
<u n="412" who="S0619" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0618">they're quite close next lamppost above <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think they've had a row</u>
<u n="414" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="415" who="S0618">lamppost further over they're a mile apart I don't think they're talking</u>
<u n="416" who="S0619">strange isn't it?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="418" who="S0619"><unclear/> friends</u>
<u n="419" who="S0618">the life of <unclear/> anyway sorry</u>
<u n="420" who="S0619">no it's okay no it's okay anyway right plan plan</u>
<u n="421" who="S0618" trans="overlap">so let's do something <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0619">I don't know what it's just</u>
<u n="423" who="S0618" trans="overlap">would you like another beverage somewhere to be out and to <pause dur="short"/> feel an engaged and active part of society?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="425" who="S0618">be that consumer society or otherwise</u>
<u n="426" who="S0619" trans="overlap">you're really selling it to me <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm</u>
<u n="427" who="S0618">oh I know</u>
<u n="428" who="S0619">I don't know where we can go though</u>
<u n="429" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="430" who="S0619">that's not sort of in the city centre</u>
<u n="431" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm we could just <pause dur="short"/> I know if it was warm we could go and sit in a park or something</u>
<u n="432" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="433" who="S0618">we can just go for a random drive see where we end up</u>
<u n="434" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0618">let's do that will we?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0619">yeah I'm just trying to think of this</u>
<u n="437" who="S0618" trans="overlap">basically it's just nice for you not to be in your flat for a little while</u>
<u n="438" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I know I just need a bit of <pause dur="short"/> scenery erm <pause dur="short"/> I'm trying to I don't know where we could go though that's kind of local</u>
<u n="439" who="S0618" trans="overlap">we could do a sort of head out west of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="440" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0618">and there are all sorts of little villages around there might end up on the motorway I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'll try not to</u>
<u n="442" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="443" who="S0618">and then you can sort of come in to the south of <anon type="place"/> again <pause dur="short"/> I'm not really sure how that would work but I could drive in that general direction and</u>
<u n="444" who="S0619">or we could go I don't know how far away it is <pause dur="short"/> maybe it's quite far <pause dur="short"/> the place where when we went to the place with the church</u>
<u n="445" who="S0618">mm mm</u>
<u n="446" who="S0619">and there's like that town</u>
<u n="447" who="S0618"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> there's a bloody great church thing there <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> that describes most of the towns in Poland but</u>
<u n="448" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether that's the one and I said oh that this looks pretty</u>
<u n="449" who="S0618">and it's got a cute little square</u>
<u n="450" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="451" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0619">how far away is that is that too far?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0618" trans="overlap">erm no no not at all from here probably less than twenty K <pause dur="short"/> what's that about twelve miles or something?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0619">I don't know is it Saturday afternoon? I don't know what'll be open probably nothing</u>
<u n="455" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0618">well we could go park in the square there's bound to be a coffee shop or something we could get a herbal something or not bother</u>
<u n="458" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0618">erm if you want you can even come to my house and have a green tea or a peppermint tea or whatever <pause dur="short"/> just for a change of scenery</u>
<u n="460" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yes anything anything</u>
<u n="461" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah I haven't hoovered in a more than a week so the <pause dur="short"/> I have what do you call those things?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0619">I don't know dust balls?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0618" trans="overlap">dust things sort of dust balls yeah like in an old western movie</u>
<u n="464" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="465" who="S0618">kind of circling across my living room and hall but</u>
<u n="466" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="467" who="S0618">if you can put up with that then great</u>
<u n="468" who="S0619">I will survive</u>
<u n="469" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0619">erm <pause dur="short"/> anything else? anything else? I can't think of anything that we could possibly do that would be <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know I don't know erm don't know</u>
<u n="471" who="S0618">yeah I suppose I'm thinking about you and walking I mean we could</u>
<u n="472" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="473" who="S0618">do a circuit of <anon type="place"/> but then that's walking</u>
<u n="474" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="475" who="S0618">which probably isn't so good and inside a shopping centre it's gonna be fake air</u>
<u n="476" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0618">which won't be so good and then sunset will be in another <pause dur="short"/> hour</u>
<u n="478" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah mm mm</u>
<u n="479" who="S0618">and once that happens it'll start getting cold quickly <pause dur="short"/> so I think if you can do any outside walking I'd do it now <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> quick circuit of the <anon type="place"/> car park</u>
<u n="480" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0618">that's enough take me home <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0619" trans="overlap">erm erm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0618">yeah but I'm happy enough to just drive aimlessly and see where we end up <pause dur="short"/> we could drive for twenty minutes in one direction and then ask Sally sat nav to bring us home <pause dur="short"/> or Simon sat nav</u>
<u n="484" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah okay</u>
<u n="485" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0619">I'd like to go to a village</u>
<u n="487" who="S0618">let's aim for <anon type="place"/> it's probably about I don't know a twenty minute drive that away <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="488" who="S0619">shall we try it?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0618" trans="overlap">erm yeah we can do a quick tour of the square and then a twenty minute drive back</u>
<u n="490" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh it's a square congratulations it looks exactly like every square <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0618" trans="overlap">hooray <pause dur="short"/> yeah let's do that then</u>
<u n="492" who="S0619">yes okay is that okay? do you agree?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0618">that's okay let me turn this thingy off so bye</u>
<u n="494" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> bye</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
