<text id="SLRD">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:03:00</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-11-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>5</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0282 S0283 S0647 S0648 S0649</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>At the home of speakers X and X in Balham, South London</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Process of getting a valuation. Extending lease or buying into freehold.  The process of recording for Corpus. Turner exhibition and film. Artist called Marie Spartali. Pre-Raphaelite artists. Labour Party fundraising dinner. Politics and politicians. Europe and immigration. Grandparent duties. ANON having a baby. Getting a parking ticket, illegal parking and attitude of police.</topics>
		<activity>Family members discussing property matters and politics</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, requesting, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0282">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Stratford-upon-Avon</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>self employed</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0283">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Civil servant</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0647">
				<exactage>82</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>80_89</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Calver</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>21 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>PR director</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_1</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0648">
				<exactage>45</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>45</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Radio Producer</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0649">
				<exactage>79</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Aldershot, Hampshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Received Pronunciation</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Calver, Derbyshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>21 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0283">erm okay so</u>
<u n="2" who="S0647">just get the original documentation</u>
<u n="3" who="S0648">those are the ones that I</u>
<u n="4" who="S0647">okay that goes with the move but when we talked to them</u>
<u n="5" who="S0648">yes</u>
<u n="6" who="S0647">it was about the company not not erm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0649" trans="overlap">sorry</u>
<u n="8" who="S0647" trans="overlap">just not about <unclear/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0649" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0648" trans="overlap">I explained both</u>
<u n="11" who="S0283">okay good</u>
<u n="12" who="S0648">I'll I'll forward you the email that I sent to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0283" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="14" who="S0647">but if you look at these <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got this <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cover</u>
<u n="15" who="S0648">yeah for example erm do you know what your current ground rent is?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0647">yeah twenty-five pounds</u>
<u n="17" who="S0648" trans="overlap">yeah because erm for my reading what I've got erm worked out is that erm if you deal direct with Dorrington's sometimes they erm they there's a sort of established route of doing things whereby you ask for evaluation you go through the process of <unclear/> okay that's a way of doing it is that you pay X amount of money for or you can do it informally like you do where what you do is then you write to them they come back to you they give you a price and you just arrange it with them for a certain amount of money and in this particular case there's <trunc>ch</trunc> I think they quoted seven hundred and fifty pounds for lawyers' fees</u>
<u n="18" who="S0283">and that's they normally do</u>
<u n="19" who="S0647">yeah and they their thing is seven thousand if you want it</u>
<u n="20" who="S0648">yeah but but also what they might do is what as they have done there is change the <trunc>t</trunc> conditions so that the ground rent is two hundred pounds rather than twenty-five pounds that's okay it's not it's <trunc>ma</trunc>manageable and impose a clause</u>
<u n="21" who="S0647">and this is it he said to me that Dorrington are you going to protect their protect themselves</u>
<u n="22" who="S0648">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0647">and maybe the others will press <trunc>pre</trunc>press for erm certain changes but I don't know which with you you have to make a judgement</u>
<u n="24" who="S0648" trans="overlap">I think it's much too much this</u>
<u n="25" who="S0647">we have to take a judgement will it be easier to go through Dorrigton's even though it might cost a bit more because it's all <unclear/> house or is it better to go to the company?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0283">who is the freeholder?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0648">Dorrington's</u>
<u n="28" who="S0283">Dorrington's the freeholder and who's the managing agent?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0647">oh erm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0648">Aron?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0647">Aron yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0283">okay so Aron are not part of this conversation</u>
<u n="33" who="S0648">no</u>
<u n="34" who="S0283">and whether or not you get a lease extension with Dorrington they'll still be paying Aron on your behalf to manage the building</u>
<u n="35" who="S0647">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0283">so it remains</u>
<u n="37" who="S0647">the rent is outside the rent's outside</u>
<u n="38" who="S0282">no the lease holders can have can influence that</u>
<u n="39" who="S0647" trans="overlap">the rent's outside of</u>
<u n="40" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0648">yeah but that's</u>
<u n="42" who="S0283">yeah I was thinking that</u>
<u n="43" who="S0282">yeah often that's what that's what the impetus often this it's er oh no that's not it's not enfranchised you're not enfranchising are you? you're just extending the lease</u>
<u n="44" who="S0283">which is <unclear/> for erm is there a question of buying the freehold?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0648">no the freehold you could only buy en masse everybody getting together and we don't want the freehold of this building it's all about er</u>
<u n="46" who="S0283">fine</u>
<u n="47" who="S0648">mobile fine masts it's a huge building</u>
<u n="48" who="S0283">yeah yeah no fine</u>
<u n="49" who="S0648">you know this is a this is a you can't <trunc>a</trunc> my understanding and I may have got this wrong is that you can't just get the freehold to</u>
<u n="50" who="S0283">no you have to buy the freehold to the land and all of the tenants would have to have an equal</u>
<u n="51" who="S0648">yeah so yeah they they've given me an explanation of how that would work but that's not really what's on the table and not really what anyone's interested in</u>
<u n="52" who="S0282">yeah that would be a headache and a half</u>
<u n="53" who="S0283">are they offering differential extensions or is it standard extension?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0648">well this is the other thing is that erm er I mean this is what it says in this leaflet which is obviously not totally impartial but what they've explained is erm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0649">interruption for tea</u>
<u n="56" who="S0648">what's this?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0649">who wants their teabag taken straight out?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0282">me please</u>
<u n="59" who="S0647"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> likes it brew too would you?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0648">yes me please yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0649">one?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0648">one</u>
<u n="63" who="S0649"><unclear/> are a bit too strong milk for everybody?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0282">yes please <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0283">I do like those dry roasted nuts</u>
<u n="66" who="S0649">sugar for anybody?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0282">no thanks</u>
<u n="68" who="S0283">it is true that food that you eat outside of your own house doesn't count with the calorific value</u>
<u n="69" who="S0282">it so does</u>
<u n="70" who="S0648">yes basically erm <pause dur="long"/> erm <pause dur="long"/> the there's they the if you did it direct with the these people they might try and get you a shorter <trunc>le</trunc>lease although in this particular case they're going for a <trunc>cl</trunc> a new term of a hundred and twenty-five years from twenty ten which is reasonable</u>
<u n="71" who="S0649" trans="overlap">that's right that's alright</u>
<u n="72" who="S0648">what you don't want is for them to offer you like ninety-five years or something</u>
<u n="73" who="S0283">no no</u>
<u n="74" who="S0648">because you're looking for a much bigger extension than that</u>
<u n="75" who="S0283">yes</u>
<u n="76" who="S0648">erm but the usually the freehold will not be for an additional and that you want yeah so you'll want an additional ninety years but sometimes they offer an extension up to a hundred and twenty-five years you don't want that really</u>
<u n="77" who="S0283">no</u>
<u n="78" who="S0648">I mean there's noting wrong with that but erm it's not you'd rather have ninety plus eighty</u>
<u n="79" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0648">than a hundred and twenty-five</u>
<u n="81" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0648">but in fact they have offered up to a hundred and seventy-five here so that's not an issue either</u>
<u n="83" who="S0283">okay well</u>
<u n="84" who="S0648">so I <trunc>thi</trunc></u>
<u n="85" who="S0647">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying something like oh I I'll protect the the stuff I've got</u>
<u n="86" who="S0283">and do you have a view as to whether or not to just go and do it direct? or whether to go through their scheme?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0648">all the only thing I think really that needs finding out now is how much additional solicitors' fees would we pay to make this work erm and it</u>
<u n="88" who="S0283">about a thousand quid</u>
<u n="89" who="S0648">then I'd probably go with this</u>
<u n="90" who="S0283">okay</u>
<u n="91" who="S0647">what's this?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0648">this is the direct to Dorrington's</u>
<u n="93" who="S0647">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0648">it's straightforward and you know exactly what you're getting into whereas this I don't think it's a rip-off but it <unclear/> equally doesn't seem to be offering a particular bonus either</u>
<u n="95" who="S0283">no and are they and who brought them in?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0648">they approached us because they've leafleted everybody in the building</u>
<u n="97" who="S0283">oh they've not they've made an arrangement</u>
<u n="98" who="S0647" trans="overlap">yes I <unclear>called it I called it</unclear></u>
<u n="99" who="S0648">no they they no they're they're they're not acting on Dorrington's behalf they're acting then then they would be doing what we're doing to Dorrington but just en masse</u>
<u n="100" who="S0283">okay yeah okay</u>
<u n="101" who="S0648">they're a <unclear/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0647" trans="overlap">that's er that's one of the points isn't it? <trunc>m</trunc>me</u>
<u n="103" who="S0648" trans="overlap">which one is mine?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0649" trans="overlap">that one</u>
<u n="105" who="S0648">thank you</u>
<u n="106" who="S0647" trans="overlap">I don't know how many people</u>
<u n="107" who="S0648">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0647">it <unclear/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0283">oh okay</u>
<u n="110" who="S0647">we don't know how many people are in the chain</u>
<u n="111" who="S0283">okay well how?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0647">let me finish</u>
<u n="113" who="S0283">okay</u>
<u n="114" who="S0647">we don't know how many people in the chain have have signed on</u>
<u n="115" who="S0648">yeah but</u>
<u n="116" who="S0647" trans="overlap">the problem is the more than sign on the cheaper it gets because of <trunc>sha</trunc>shared costs</u>
<u n="117" who="S0648">yeah and you can talk to them</u>
<u n="118" who="S0647">whereas here there is no question of sharing the costs</u>
<u n="119" who="S0648">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0647">erm but we'll have a conversation presumably both sets of them</u>
<u n="121" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0647">er to establish</u>
<u n="123" who="S0648">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0647">erm what what erm and I don't know if we'll be penalised for not joining in the private one as opposed to Dorrington one</u>
<u n="125" who="S0283">but the</u>
<u n="126" who="S0647">which has been going for some months now</u>
<u n="127" who="S0648">well erm my guess is not I mean it it's a slightly chicken and egg because you can ask erm you can ask the private one to do a valuation on your behalf now I think you'd have to pay three hundred and ninety-five pounds for them to do that</u>
<u n="128" who="S0647">but they yeah go on</u>
<u n="129" who="S0648">and I can't remember if that's refundable whether you go ahead or not</u>
<u n="130" who="S0647">I don't know but I honestly think it's that price they said it was that price because of shared costs</u>
<u n="131" who="S0648" trans="overlap">yeah yeah and is that still available to us? is that your question?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0647">mm</u>
<u n="133" who="S0648">yeah I mean I think have a phone call with I've given <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the contact <trunc>de</trunc> the person who's dealing with this the Ducane class action</u>
<u n="134" who="S0647">mm well she's listed there</u>
<u n="135" who="S0648">that that's the Dorrington's one but I've given you the the the</u>
<u n="136" who="S0647">the private what we call the private</u>
<u n="137" who="S0648">the private one they've got a named person who's dealing with it as well</u>
<u n="138" who="S0647">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0283">okay</u>
<u n="140" who="S0647">this this is only tells you that they don't know <unclear>have a meeting</unclear></u>
<u n="141" who="S0648">I know it sounds</u>
<u n="142" who="S0647" trans="overlap">well I actually said to you this is what happened in the end</u>
<u n="143" who="S0648">I know it sounds like a great enormous hassle</u>
<u n="144" who="S0649" trans="overlap">are you cold?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no no I'm fine I was just rearranging my</u>
<u n="146" who="S0649" trans="overlap">yourself</u>
<u n="147" who="S0648" trans="overlap">but I honestly don't think it is I think it's making a few phone calls to make the decision and then once you get in that it's a sort of process</u>
<u n="148" who="S0647">again I I'm I ought to <unclear/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0649" trans="overlap">we ought to turn this up I think</u>
<u n="150" who="S0283">okay good</u>
<u n="151" who="S0648">good</u>
<u n="152" who="S0283" trans="overlap">no that's fine I think we we do it <unclear/> difficult process but only because we were selling it to a lunatic</u>
<u n="153" who="S0648">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0283">erm and they had to form their own company and</u>
<u n="155" who="S0648">there won't be any of that I think there'll be various papers that you need to preside over but I</u>
<u n="156" who="S0282" trans="overlap">get over their racial prejudice to do so</u>
<u n="157" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0648">and I but I'm embarrassed now that I've asked you to do it cos I actually think it is quite straightforward</u>
<u n="159" who="S0283" trans="overlap">alright it's alright I I'll see if I can help</u>
<u n="160" who="S0648">it's more embarrassing to ask you to do something easy than it is to ask you to do something difficult</u>
<u n="161" who="S0283">that's fine</u>
<u n="162" who="S0648">er right I'd better go I'm afraid but does it make sense thus far? you probably need to re read my email and all of that</u>
<u n="163" who="S0283">yeah that's fine I'll do that</u>
<u n="164" who="S0648" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0649">do you want me to ring <anon type="place"/> and tell them to hold onto everything?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0648">no I'm going to do it</u>
<u n="167" who="S0282">can I get you to fill in a form? cos you're on this tape now so I either have to tape it again or</u>
<u n="168" who="S0648">er you can how long's it gonna take? cos I really have to go and pick up <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0282" trans="overlap">two minutes two minutes literally</u>
<u n="170" who="S0648">okay</u>
<u n="171" who="S0282">but I have to do it again because erm just the top just one of them</u>
<u n="172" who="S0648">this?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0649">we you recording all that then then?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0649">oh <pause dur="short"/> I didn't realise that I wouldn't have chipped in with</u>
<u n="177" who="S0282">no it's supposed to be erm normal conversation so</u>
<u n="178" who="S0283" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0649">how interesting it'd be interesting to know how how they analyse it</u>
<u n="180" who="S0282">I think they do it every ten years</u>
<u n="181" who="S0649">do they?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0282">they've said and they have linguists who listen to the tape and listen to how English is being spoken</u>
<u n="183" who="S0283" trans="overlap">do you think? do you think that roughly two thirds of all of the language that they analyse is discussing the project?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0282">er mm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0283">I know</u>
<u n="186" who="S0648">yeah so what I am doing here is I'm actually yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0283">good</u>
<u n="188" who="S0649">so who are they talking about?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0282">the erm topic that seems to raise most interesting query is what is your accent?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0649">the other one that's intriguing me at the moment is pronunciation</u>
<u n="191" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0649">that certain things the only one I can think of at the moment is respite and respite always I'd never heard of respite I always said respite it's both of course respite</u>
<u n="193" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="194" who="S0649">but but now erm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0648">is this enough do I have to do the?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0282" trans="overlap">er no just a signature on page two</u>
<u n="197" who="S0283">see I've I've it's always respite care</u>
<u n="198" who="S0649">it's respite care but I don't think we talked about respite care when I was little</u>
<u n="199" who="S0648" trans="overlap">will that do?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and a contact thank you</u>
<u n="201" who="S0649">I mean respite was where the weather gave you no <trunc>re</trunc> there was no respite from the <trunc>res</trunc> no respite from the autumn gales but respite care erm <pause dur="long"/> is one a noun and one an adjective?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0282">thank you</u>
<u n="203" who="S0648">if I haven't done enough I'll give it to you another time</u>
<u n="204" who="S0282">okay</u>
<u n="205" who="S0283" trans="overlap">thank you see you soon</u>
<u n="206" who="S0648" trans="overlap">right bye thank you okay erm <pause dur="long"/> I'll see you tomorrow</u>
<u n="207" who="S0283" trans="overlap">are we going out <unclear/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0648" trans="overlap">yeah I'll go and pick up <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it'll be about three yeah?</u>
<event desc="0648 leaves"/>
<u n="209" who="S0283">good so how was the Turner?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0649">erm yeah good</u>
<u n="211" who="S0647" trans="overlap">er well well some of it was brilliant and some of it was</u>
<u n="212" who="S0649" trans="overlap">good and interesting but yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0647">ordinary erm <unclear/> I certainly he's been he's <trunc>al</trunc> it's all all later</u>
<u n="214" who="S0283">see you</u>
<u n="215" who="S0648">bye</u>
<u n="216" who="S0647">bye bye</u>
<u n="217" who="S0647">it was all late Turner and er I think there's some question of he he sort of got ill and difficult and he may have taken in in some things in his work he sort of goes from one one <unclear/> it it says it's a boat in water but you think you get the feeling of a boat in water but you don't often see any boat</u>
<u n="218" who="S0283">yes</u>
<u n="219" who="S0647">and you hardly see the water but he's also got some classical references</u>
<u n="220" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="221" who="S0647">diadem and someone or other erm we're talking about Turner in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0649">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0647">er yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0649">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0647">and they were almost boring cos erm the sort of thing that you've seen done a million times</u>
<u n="226" who="S0649">they looked also the <trunc>thi</trunc> you know how you could search for ten years to find an outline normally in Turner it was just</u>
<u n="227" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0649">but all the figures had very clear outlines and looked to me like artist's models sitting there doing that or doing that</u>
<u n="229" who="S0283">oh interesting</u>
<u n="230" who="S0647">it was only some of them</u>
<u n="231" who="S0649">and may well have been</u>
<u n="232" who="S0647">only some of them were like that they were some absolutely amazing</u>
<u n="233" who="S0649">but there were some very interesting</u>
<u n="234" who="S0647" trans="overlap">some magnificent ones</u>
<u n="235" who="S0649">erm background both written and on the audio</u>
<u n="236" who="S0282">they were saying that erm they'd been or there was an article I read and article with Timothy Spall lately and they were saying they've been working on it for a couple of years and then that they'd all gone away and done research and that Timothy Spall had actually had painting classes erm and that they hadn't set out with a particular cast but the cast had kind of emerged as they all read background materials on Turner and stuff like that</u>
<u n="237" who="S0283">what's this?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0282">it's this film Turner Mr Turner</u>
<u n="239" who="S0649">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0282">I presume that's what you've been you've seen you've been to see the film? not</u>
<u n="241" who="S0649">no no no no</u>
<u n="242" who="S0282">oh no no the the oh I see right we're at cross purposes then</u>
<u n="243" who="S0649">we would have liked to have seen the film which would be tomorrow but it's not going to fit in but</u>
<u n="244" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh right you went to the <trunc>exhibi</trunc> there's an exhibition as well is there on?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0649">oh yeah at the Tate all the late Turners</u>
<u n="246" who="S0282">oh right okay oh sorry I was completely I was under the misapprehension you'd been to the cinema</u>
<u n="247" who="S0649">no we tried to fit it in but it doesn't quite work so there's actually some quite</u>
<u n="248" who="S0283" trans="overlap">so this is more sort of an artistic kind of</u>
<u n="249" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah it <unclear/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0647">some quite nice what we expected Turner</u>
<u n="251" who="S0649">but he was very he was very misunderstood obviously the impressionist had a <trunc>terri</trunc> owe him a terrific debt</u>
<u n="252" who="S0283">mm</u>
<u n="253" who="S0649">but he's been misunderstood but also apparently there was a great erm</u>
<u n="254" who="S0283">Turner</u>
<u n="255" who="S0649">the the the feeling of the age was a part had to be expressive of</u>
<u n="256" who="S0283">mm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0649">morality and it had to be learned you had to learn lessons for history you couldn't just have a nice picture it had to be a a learning experience</u>
<u n="258" who="S0282">no <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0649">what you looking for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0647">mm?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0649">what are you looking for?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0647">erm your <unclear/></u>
<u n="263" who="S0649">that's there</u>
<u n="264" who="S0647">that's mm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0282">thank you</u>
<u n="266" who="S0647">this was some some of the better pictures in in there</u>
<u n="267" who="S0649">but the man was clearly <trunc>obsess</trunc>obsessed with mist and sea and when he just allows himself to <unclear>od</unclear> that it's absolutely wonderful</u>
<u n="268" who="S0283">mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0649">and there's one you'll come across it in there <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> there's another wonderful one where it does work with the figures</u>
<u n="270" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="271" who="S0649">and that's I I think it's called The Exile</u>
<u n="272" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="273" who="S0649">is that the one you've got at the moment?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0282">no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0647">I don't remember that one</u>
<u n="276" who="S0649">yes you do</u>
<u n="277" who="S0647">I don't remember the title I'm sure I remember the picture</u>
<u n="278" who="S0649" trans="overlap">I think it's called yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0648">War the Exile and the Rock Limpet that one? with a figure in the middle of it</u>
<u n="280" who="S0649">mm with a big Welsh <unclear/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0647" trans="overlap">oh yes yes oh of course</u>
<u n="282" who="S0283">well it's different</u>
<u n="283" who="S0647">oh yes yes yes it's the soldier coming back</u>
<u n="284" who="S0649">well it's Napoleon</u>
<u n="285" who="S0647">oh well he's a soldier</u>
<u n="286" who="S0649">it's <trunc>mea</trunc> surely it's meant to be Napoleon</u>
<u n="287" who="S0647">it is yes no I was joking</u>
<u n="288" who="S0649" trans="overlap">exile</u>
<u n="289" who="S0282">he hasn't got his hand up his jumper</u>
<u n="290" who="S0649">and and an amazing shadow of him in the water and the presumably a a minder in the background</u>
<u n="291" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="292" who="S0649">and then behind that the usual <trunc>turn</trunc>Turner mist it's absolutely wonderful and that was the only one I think where the figure is successful</u>
<u n="293" who="S0283">how did you find it? is it for?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0282">cos some people can't paint in fact actually I think</u>
<u n="295" who="S0649" trans="overlap">tell tell <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what page it is</u>
<u n="296" who="S0282">erm it is on page it's on opposite four Square in the Circle <unclear/> formats from eighteen forty <pause dur="short"/> erm is there</u>
<u n="297" who="S0283">okay</u>
<u n="298" who="S0282">erm have is <trunc>we</trunc> what was it when did you go to that stately home and they had a painting that was by somebody who usually usually did landscapes and it was a picture of a woman leaning on a do you remember? a woman leaning on a erm window sill looking out of the window and it's really really really crass and it's like a really amateurish painter painting and it's painted by a really famous artist</u>
<u n="299" who="S0283">I don't know could it be Watts or?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0282">no it wasn't Watts</u>
<u n="301" who="S0649">sounds like sounds like it might have been</u>
<u n="302" who="S0282" trans="overlap">it wasn't no it might be erm it might be Turner I can't remember exactly but erm it just shows that just cos you can paint one thing you can't necessarily paint another thing</u>
<u n="303" who="S0649">well I think he could paint them but he couldn't kind of paint him in the superlative way that he painted these these uncertainties</u>
<u n="304" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="305" who="S0649">these miasmas of it's as if if there was a certainty he kind of didn't add to it and if it was a a a mist he he just put it into and bring it right to you</u>
<u n="306" who="S0282">it's not like Monet who went blind and couldn't actually see at the end</u>
<u n="307" who="S0649">no he wasn't well I think this is the last five or six years of his life</u>
<u n="308" who="S0282" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="309" who="S0649">and he wasn't well and he was fading and ailing but he was painting like mad like mad erm partly to earn money</u>
<u n="310" who="S0282">so is it a coincidence this film is out at the same time as the originals on or?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0283">it it's yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0649">I think so yeah they were running the counter yes</u>
<u n="313" who="S0647" trans="overlap">it must be I think I think it must be</u>
<u n="314" who="S0282">mm is there a a bicentenary or a tri-centenary? or a</u>
<u n="315" who="S0649">he died in sixty or eighteen sixty-one that's not I forget when he was born</u>
<u n="316" who="S0282">he was sixty in eighteen thirty-five</u>
<u n="317" who="S0649" trans="overlap">I think I think it's a crest the crest has just ripened isn't it? somehow didn't they just get a lot more Turners?  <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="318" who="S0283">I'd like to know which Turner it was that was hanging in our house</u>
<u n="319" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0282">yeah no I know</u>
<u n="321" who="S0647">was it real?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0647">oh what happened to it?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0282">no we don't know well erm there was a letter</u>
<u n="326" who="S0647" trans="overlap">it's not there not there now</u>
<u n="327" who="S0282"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wrote to er not <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s brother <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> after her husband died and said what a comfort it had been to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to be able to look at the Turner over his fireplace in his bedroom while he was dying and that he had got a lot out of being able to look at this Turner painting</u>
<u n="328" who="S0649">but this was somebody who lived in your house?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="330" who="S0649">this a brother of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0282">no no no sorry other people who lived in our house were <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was the more famous of the two at the time probably he was a journalist and he was also an American counsel but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who grew up in <anon type="place"/> and was a member of a big Greek commercial clan went on was a <trunc>y</trunc> as a young woman was a model for for Rossetti and Ben James and erm other pre-Raphaelites she was taught by Fort Maddox Brown to paint</u>
<u n="332" who="S0649">er</u>
<u n="333" who="S0282">she was one of the what they called the three graces who are one of the subjects of the paintings and erm and erm so but her husband was called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and she met he was much older than her and her sort of sad old stick but she got married to him anyway and lots of people were very intrigued about why she'd married I'm what there could be between them but she had a lot of freedom as a married woman and did a lot of painting and became a painter in her own right so so possibly <pause dur="short"/> it it might have been a marriage of convenience I suppose but certain she had a lot of freedom to be an artist</u>
<u n="334" who="S0649">and <pause dur="short"/> and how did you come by the connection with your house?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0282">well somebody er somebody who's related to both of them or a descendent of both of them wrote a book about their lives and erm and this letter which was written from our house</u>
<u n="336" who="S0283">it's all</u>
<u n="337" who="S0282">and it says was was written the day after <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> died I E her husband was left <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> saying you'll be sad to hear that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has died</u>
<u n="338" who="S0283" trans="overlap">this this all came about</u>
<u n="339" who="S0649"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0282">and you know it gave the huge amount of comfort to him to be able to look at the Turner you lent us</u>
<u n="341" who="S0649">I see</u>
<u n="342" who="S0283">this all came about cos someone knocked at the door selling tickets for the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0649">oh I I heard I heard of that that was a long time ago</u>
<u n="344" who="S0283" trans="overlap">society and he said your house is on Ebay</u>
<u n="345" who="S0649" trans="overlap">and then all your research started</u>
<u n="346" who="S0282">mm yes</u>
<u n="347" who="S0649">wow wow wow erm</u>
<u n="348" who="S0282">erm so we scoured the house <pause dur="short"/> and we have found other paintings and things in the loft but no Turners</u>
<u n="349" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0649"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has got a pre-Raphaelite exhibition in the National Portrait Gallery</u>
<u n="351" who="S0282">yes we need to go back to that because</u>
<u n="352" who="S0649">you've been to that</u>
<u n="353" who="S0282">there was a little there was a little <trunc>e</trunc>exhibition a while ago about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s friends and associates and and I just dropped in there one day by chance because I was I had been to a breakfast meeting which I felt erm terribly aggrieved about because I'd had to get up really early to go to this I never understand why people have breakfast meetings cos I think it's really uncivilised anyway I thought do you know what? I'm going to go to the National Portrait Gallery so I went in there there's this little exhibition of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s friends and there were pictures of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> photographs of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in that</u>
<u n="354" who="S0649">oh</u>
<u n="355" who="S0282">so I do want to go back and have a look at this exhibition in case there's more photographs on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in that</u>
<u n="356" who="S0649"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who is well anyway I was sitting next to her at something</u>
<u n="357" who="S0282">oh really <vocal desc="gasp"/> wow</u>
<u n="358" who="S0649">the really exciting thing was that she was doing this exhibition and she was allowed to put photographs in as well as pictures yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="360" who="S0649">I don't think we could quite procure you an introduction I don't think we'd have to go via <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="361" who="S0282">oh dear</u>
<u n="362" who="S0283">his <unclear/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0649">which is a no no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0282">but er oh that's exciting but then they had this fantastic thing in National Portrait Gallery in the shop where you there's a screen you tap in the name of anybody and it comes up if National Portrait Gallery's got an image of them <pause dur="short"/> and if they have you can pay and have a print of this photograph or a reproduction of the of the painting then and there so you just cough up your money and then a man goes behind the counter and takes it out of a big photocopier and gives it to you so you can have a reproduction you want this size this size or this size</u>
<u n="365" who="S0649">ah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0282">it's really exciting</u>
<u n="367" who="S0649" trans="overlap">wonderful I would so like to go and see that before it it goes off</u>
<u n="368" who="S0647">we'll go tomorrow morning</u>
<u n="369" who="S0282">well why not?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0649" trans="overlap"><unclear/> we could go tomorrow and see if we're not going to see Turner we could go and see pre-Raphs</u>
<u n="371" who="S0282">and certainly <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has stayed in our house</u>
<u n="372" who="S0647">what's that what is the actual exhibition that's on at the National Portrait Gallery now?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0282">it's something about William Morris a retrospective of William Morris William Morris' life loves work and everything</u>
<u n="374" who="S0649">I can't remember I didn't <trunc>n</trunc><trunc>n</trunc> erm we didn't have a long conversation it was at a the East Midlands Labour party fundraising dinner <pause dur="short"/> say no more the nicest thing about it was Fiona MacCarthy</u>
<u n="375" who="S0282">mm and who was giving the speech?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0649">Ed</u>
<u n="377" who="S0282">oh really? how did he do?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0647">this is er one year ago</u>
<u n="379" who="S0649">very well it must be about a year ago</u>
<u n="380" who="S0647">it is cos er we've just been asked or we've been invited to buy a ticket for this yea's last year's we were</u>
<u n="381" who="S0282">have they got Ed again?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0647">we were guests right?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0282">have they got Ed again or?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0647">er I think it's no I think they've got Kinnock</u>
<u n="385" who="S0283">oh right</u>
<u n="386" who="S0282">oh god</u>
<u n="387" who="S0283">that's okay</u>
<u n="388" who="S0649">if it's at the same place you'd better start now do you remember how hard it was to find?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0647" trans="overlap">same place same place yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0283">why don't you just donate and not listen to Neil Kinnock?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0647">that's what we're doing</u>
<u n="392" who="S0649"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0647">but it it's not just listening to Kinnock er you buy a very expensive ticket for this rather boring event</u>
<u n="394" who="S0282">how much is the ticket?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0647">yes and the speech is fine but the speech is half an hour out of <trunc>thre</trunc> two and a half hours</u>
<u n="396" who="S0649">the rest is all fundraising active and proactive fundraising except the meal which was adequate erm</u>
<u n="397" who="S0282">so what they do a raffle or something? what?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0649">oh every kind of game</u>
<u n="399" who="S0647" trans="overlap">oh they had had all sorts of games and</u>
<u n="400" who="S0283">oh god</u>
<u n="401" who="S0649">yes erm</u>
<u n="402" who="S0647">give you envelopes to put money in</u>
<u n="403" who="S0649">we were asked at the last minute to to to to fill two people two places on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s table and we discovered that the later that the people who we were replacing had died</u>
<u n="404" who="S0282">oh that's nice</u>
<u n="405" who="S0283">what both of them?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0649">well the she one was I don't I don't know or whatever it was anyway we were guests but how much would he have paid for us then?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0647">quite a lot</u>
<u n="408" who="S0282">oh he paid he paid for you?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0647" trans="overlap">he buys no he buys he buys a table he buys a table and</u>
<u n="410" who="S0282" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0649" trans="overlap">well actually he would have</u>
<u n="412" who="S0647" trans="overlap">er and invites eight people</u>
<u n="413" who="S0649">the the woman the gap woman she would have paid up already</u>
<u n="414" who="S0647">no it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> buy</u>
<u n="415" who="S0649">all of us?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0647"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> buys a table</u>
<u n="417" who="S0649">oh</u>
<u n="418" who="S0647">and then and then invites people</u>
<u n="419" who="S0283">mm so you were one of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s invited guests</u>
<u n="420" who="S0647">mm</u>
<u n="421" who="S0283">substitute invited guests</u>
<u n="422" who="S0649" trans="overlap">no we were we were</u>
<u n="423" who="S0282" trans="overlap">do you owe him after that? does he expect favours in return?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0647">er er I don't think so</u>
<u n="425" who="S0282">ten hours of canvassing</u>
<u n="426" who="S0649">well I'm not a fan of his in fact</u>
<u n="427" who="S0282">oh no? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0649">no no</u>
<u n="429" who="S0282">but there's erm did you see the article in the Observer about what they're calling the red princes? the red princes of the Labour party who are erm young young Dramy young Straw young Kinnock young Prescott young Blair young Gould</u>
<u n="430" who="S0647">what about them?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0282">well they're all standing for seats so they're all getting ushered</u>
<u n="432" who="S0647">oh I see you mean the oh right no listen</u>
<u n="433" who="S0649" trans="overlap">really? I thought they were</u>
<u n="434" who="S0647" trans="overlap">but they're all</u>
<u n="435" who="S0649">I knew young Straw was</u>
<u n="436" who="S0647">there there was a big article about the Carol Cadwaledon or I don't know what her name is but had gone to the Labour party conference was moaning about how fake it all was</u>
<u n="437" who="S0649">how what?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0647">fake</u>
<u n="439" who="S0649">oh</u>
<u n="440" who="S0282">and how it wasn't genuinely political and how the Labour party was being <trunc>tak</trunc>taken over by <unclear/> chicks erm like the Tory party was and so they were all PPE erm and erm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0649"><unclear/></u>
<u n="442" who="S0282">had gone into research and <unclear>spad</unclear> jobs and had never their feet hadn't ever touched the pavement and then she had gone around to all these fringe meetings and met all these sort of ordinary member show would love to be Labour party candidates had it not been that young Straw young Kinnock young Prescott etcetera had been parachuted into the seat and swept in over their heads so she was she was moaning about how Labour party was you know? sort of meaningless these days because</u>
<u n="443" who="S0649">oh dear oh dear</u>
<u n="444" who="S0647">oh dear</u>
<u n="445" who="S0649">Labour party does love to have grievances</u>
<u n="446" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but you did feel like writing and saying dear Carol if you erm if you're interested in politics why don't you do something political? because after all</u>
<u n="447" who="S0649">she she this is the column she's written somewhere is it?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0282">yeah no it was double page spread</u>
<u n="449" who="S0649">mm</u>
<u n="450" who="S0282">and er but you just sort of say well you know don't go around moaning that nobody else is interested in politics do something and if you're interested in politics why don't you get political?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0649">and what on earth with the Labour party do if you deprived it of it's grievances?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0283">yeah well the Labour party always belongs to someone else doesn't it? everyone thinks it belongs to them but it always belongs to someone else someone's always taking it over</u>
<u n="453" who="S0649">I don't know</u>
<u n="454" who="S0283">I thought that it is it's actually a product of its current membership rather than its hundred year history</u>
<u n="455" who="S0282">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0649">erm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0283">they haven't got very active erm <anon type="place"/> Labour party</u>
<u n="458" who="S0649">we've got</u>
<u n="459" who="S0282">well it's hardly worth it is it? I mean really honestly</u>
<u n="460" who="S0283">or a very active <anon type="place"/> Labour party</u>
<u n="461" who="S0647">no</u>
<u n="462" who="S0649">no</u>
<u n="463" who="S0647">alright don't be don't be deflated by by all those terrible things that you keep reading about in certain newspapers</u>
<u n="464" who="S0282">no no it's not so much that it's that erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is our MP</u>
<u n="465" who="S0647">oh</u>
<u n="466" who="S0282">so his majority is fairly unassailable</u>
<u n="467" who="S0283">yes and we've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0649">who's your MP?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0282"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0649">oh</u>
<u n="471" who="S0647">and then who is <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0283"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> next door</u>
<u n="473" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0647">oh well</u>
<u n="475" who="S0282">he's very bad very bad</u>
<u n="476" who="S0647" trans="overlap">well ensure that you get a quick train to London and I'm sure that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would would be would be er very happy to</u>
<u n="477" who="S0282" trans="overlap">we'd go out and lobby for Sadiq yeah</u>
<u n="478" who="S0283" trans="overlap">we like Sadiq we like Sadiq</u>
<u n="479" who="S0649">yes that'd be good</u>
<u n="480" who="S0282">old Chaka I'd be more keener on erm going up to <anon type="place"/> and lobbying for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0283" trans="overlap">actually if they if they got together then it would be Chaka Khan wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="482" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="483" who="S0282">the new dream team at the top of the Labour party</u>
<u n="484" who="S0647">look out look out</u>
<u n="485" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0647">that is what you do you go <trunc>fi</trunc> and find someone useful</u>
<u n="487" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="488" who="S0647">but it has <pause dur="short"/> erm it's been awful a massacre <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's been awful</u>
<u n="489" who="S0283">massacre of?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0647">of Ed</u>
<u n="491" who="S0283">oh right yeah I <pause dur="long"/> I don't I don't warm to him I don't</u>
<u n="492" who="S0647">no no no I I</u>
<u n="493" who="S0649" trans="overlap">you don't what?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0647">I don't warm to him but but but but but we do</u>
<u n="495" who="S0649" trans="overlap">I do I absolutely do</u>
<u n="496" who="S0647">actually he this erm the speech that he did the other day er one of the news did quite an extended bit of it and it was</u>
<u n="497" who="S0649">yes</u>
<u n="498" who="S0647">a very good speech and actually the the Times sketch writer said it was a good speech</u>
<u n="499" who="S0283">what was that called?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0647">the Times article about it was all about erm a problem about this a problem about that and and after eight or nine inches it gave two paragraphs to the speech er even you know</u>
<u n="501" who="S0649">I I do warm to Ed I think I warm to him particularly because I think everything that ever comes out of Cameron's mouth sounds scripted and prepared and second hand and everything that comes out of Ed it absolutely from his heart absolutely genuine person and I would rather have my country run by him than by Cameron I mean as people part before we start on policies so that's what I mean by warming to him I don't necessarily agree with everything he says</u>
<u n="502" who="S0283" trans="overlap">yeah I <trunc>do</trunc> he feels like a bit of a geek</u>
<u n="503" who="S0649">er?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0283">he's a bit of a geek</u>
<u n="505" who="S0649">don't say such rubbish he's not a geek</u>
<u n="506" who="S0647" trans="overlap">no no no no no come on it's true</u>
<u n="507" who="S0649">I don't</u>
<u n="508" who="S0647">in it well I know no I would amend it not that he is but people have been <trunc>mi</trunc> people have been persuaded that's what he is I mean the word is written</u>
<u n="509" who="S0283" trans="overlap">he looks like he he looks like a geek</u>
<u n="510" who="S0649">oh bollocks absolute bollocks</u>
<u n="511" who="S0647" trans="overlap">I think he</u>
<u n="512" who="S0649"><vocal desc="laugh"/> sorry we're being recorded</u>
<u n="513" who="S0282">it's fine I'm sure that they need to know the pronunciation of the word bollocks</u>
<u n="514" who="S0649"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="515" who="S0647">well now they</u>
<u n="516" who="S0282">in fact in fact I I did a tape the other day about gynaecological cancer</u>
<u n="517" who="S0647">I wonder if it's use whether it's used erm a lot</u>
<u n="518" who="S0282">mm I did a tape with a friend the other day about gynaecological cancers so they've probably got a lot of language there that they didn't anticipate getting</u>
<u n="519" who="S0649"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="520" who="S0283">that's that's Latin though isn't it?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0282">yeah that's true actually</u>
<u n="522" who="S0283">erm yes no when I was at the prime minister's strategy unit</u>
<u n="523" who="S0282">la de da</u>
<u n="524" who="S0283">erm</u>
<u n="525" who="S0647">oh oh oh oh</u>
<u n="526" who="S0283">and Ed Miliband was the</u>
<u n="527" who="S0649">oh you've got I can't hear I can't hear what she says I'm so old</u>
<u n="528" who="S0283">well I</u>
<u n="529" who="S0282">that's cos he's mumbling into his beard</u>
<u n="530" who="S0649">that's true anyway</u>
<u n="531" who="S0283">when I was in strategy Ed Miliband was the cabinet office minister erm I used to say should we run this past the minister? who was supposed to be running the cabinet office and others would just say no I'll tell him next week erm so he was the minister but he didn't have a strong grip and we didn't really know what his role was as he didn't either and I thought if you're going to be a minister you should know what you're there to do</u>
<u n="532" who="S0649">what stage in his career in yours in your career was this?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0283">I <trunc>we</trunc> I went on a secondment to the prime minister's strategy unit for six months</u>
<u n="534" who="S0649">why didn't we know about that?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0283" trans="overlap">erm you did know about that</u>
<u n="536" who="S0649">no we didn't</u>
<u n="537" who="S0647" trans="overlap">I don't remember anything about that no</u>
<u n="538" who="S0283">no it was when I when I said the prime minister's strategy unit it wasn't in number ten it the strategy unit is part of cabinet office but it's called the prime minister's strategy unit it was at the time it was at the time when Gordon Brown didn't call the election</u>
<u n="539" who="S0649" trans="overlap">mm yeah? ah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0647">ah</u>
<u n="541" who="S0283">er I remember being there when Gordon Brown didn't call the election I just thought what?</u>
<u n="542" who="S0649"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0283">and I wanted him to call the election cos it meant that I <trunc>co</trunc> I would stop the work that I was doing which I thought was a very stupid piece of work and I was disappointed that he didn't call the election firstly because he didn't call the election firstly because he didn't call the election second because it meant I had to carry on doing that piece of <trunc>wo</trunc> I'm sure we spoke about it</u>
<u n="544" who="S0649">no absolutely not</u>
<u n="545" who="S0647" trans="overlap">no no I can't remember I can't remember that</u>
<u n="546" who="S0649" trans="overlap">I'd remember that</u>
<u n="547" who="S0283" trans="overlap">it was a piece it was a piece of work that was all about how to improve the quality of life in communities and it was a it was a</u>
<u n="548" who="S0647" trans="overlap">oh right yes yes yes that rings a very strong bell</u>
<u n="549" who="S0649" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="550" who="S0283">and it was a it was a typical piece of strategy work where we sat around drawing graphs and looking at the internet for data and deciding how to make people's lives better</u>
<u n="551" who="S0647">yeah I'm sure that <trunc>ri</trunc> that rings very strong bells</u>
<u n="552" who="S0283">but erm</u>
<u n="553" who="S0647">I didn't know it was called the prime minister</u>
<u n="554" who="S0283">I might have called it cabinet office rather than prime minister's strategy I was just showing off for the tape</u>
<u n="555" who="S0649" trans="overlap">I don't know</u>
<u n="556" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="557" who="S0647">no no this is this is a point about the observer being observed</u>
<u n="558" who="S0282" trans="overlap">was that <trunc>gen</trunc> was that genuinely?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0647">how it it's a terrible problem you really have to record people in secret</u>
<u n="560" who="S0649" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="561" who="S0282">no no it's not that I mean I if we</u>
<u n="562" who="S0647">if you actually tell them you're recording everybody's thinking about what shall I say?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0282" trans="overlap">you if we all started if we all started speaking terribly properly and denouncing you know erm about things erm and pronouncing and being very very formal and more tea vicar then that wouldn't really help them so people talking ordinarily is what they wants so so they say don't do soliloquys and don't do reading and don't do all that sort of stuff do have to put at the bottom what people were dong on the tape so I don't think there was a box for bragging actually</u>
<u n="564" who="S0283">what about nibbling nuts?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0282">well that's the other thing your crunching is going to turn out really loud</u>
<u n="566" who="S0283">oh no</u>
<u n="567" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="568" who="S0283">nice nuts</u>
<u n="569" who="S0282">are they good?</u>
<u n="570" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0649">well erm yes it's a pity you weren't there when Ed didn't mention the erm economy then</u>
<u n="572" who="S0283">yes</u>
<u n="573" who="S0649">that would have that would have matched nicely</u>
<u n="574" who="S0283">yes yeah no that was I remember being I remember <trunc>do</trunc> I remember where I was when Gordon Brown didn't call the election</u>
<u n="575" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="576" who="S0647">but who remembers? <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh interesting he might have won</u>
<u n="577" who="S0283">I think he would have won in two thousand and nine</u>
<u n="578" who="S0647">yeah?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0282">so did the audience warm to Ed on that occasion that you saw him?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0649">oh very much so</u>
<u n="581" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="582" who="S0649">very much so</u>
<u n="583" who="S0647" trans="overlap">well it it well yes <trunc>a</trunc>agreed except for the fairly substantial minority who who didn't want him in the first place</u>
<u n="584" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="585" who="S0647">who who who all <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> fans and and they're not capable of saying that was a good speech they they were <unclear/></u>
<u n="586" who="S0649">I don't remember well certainly not round our table there was nobody who didn't warm to him on that occasion</u>
<u n="587" who="S0647">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> voted for Ed Ed against against David</u>
<u n="588" who="S0649" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was yeah I can't I can't I can't I'd be surprised if there were many people who would have paid good money to go there if they weren't Ed supporters</u>
<u n="589" who="S0647">erm</u>
<u n="590" who="S0283">I don't know</u>
<u n="591" who="S0647">no no I don't know I mean they they would have been Labour British midlands Labour party people</u>
<u n="592" who="S0649" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="593" who="S0647">erm</u>
<u n="594" who="S0283">it's fund raiser I my first I remember my first er <anon type="place"/> CLP meeting I the pub on <anon type="place"/> corner and at the beginning of the meeting I walked in and some bloke called Eddie said er do you want a ticket for the raffle? I said no thanks he said are you sure? I said yeah no thanks he said oh okay well we all normally buy tickets for the raffle cos we're raising funds for oh okay I'll have one then one?</u>
<u n="595" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="596" who="S0283">it was</u>
<u n="597" who="S0647">yeah well no it's</u>
<u n="598" who="S0282">this is an obligatory time</u>
<u n="599" who="S0649" trans="overlap">he came round and shook everybody's hand</u>
<u n="600" who="S0282">oh wow</u>
<u n="601" who="S0649">yeah and I don't think anybody actually wiped him off afterwards</u>
<u n="602" who="S0282">who is that minister who got erm the woman pregnant was it Cecil Parkinson?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0283">he did get a woman pregnant yeah</u>
<u n="604" who="S0649">yeah</u>
<u n="605" who="S0282">oh was that when I when I worked for this this company?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0649" trans="overlap"><unclear/> all owned up</u>
<u n="607" who="S0282">yeah that's yeah that erm yeah tried to pretend it wasn't his</u>
<u n="608" who="S0649">yes</u>
<u n="609" who="S0282">and I was out I was out</u>
<u n="610" who="S0647" trans="overlap">he made he made a very good big fuss and succeeded in <unclear/></u>
<u n="611" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah I was out I was out at a works do so I was with my work colleagues and we were at the RSA and he was the speaker and he came up and he put his hand out and I so I had this terrible moral dilemma cos I felt like saying bastard <vocal desc="laugh"/> how dare you do this? and er and yet I was with my work colleagues and I thought so I had to shake his hand so it was just like oh oh I don't want to do this</u>
<u n="612" who="S0283">mm</u>
<u n="613" who="S0649">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="614" who="S0282">but there was another occasion when we were did you go to that dinner Business in the Community dinner where Tony Blair was the speaker? and it was long before he was anything in the Labour party really he he wasn't even leader of the Labour party at that point and he was an after dinner speaker and and he just charmed everybody nearly everybody in the room was utterly charmed by the time he'd finished they all started off really suspiciously who is this bloke? and you know wrong politics wrong colour you know oh he's not not I mean wrong political colouration</u>
<u n="615" who="S0283">I went to a different one I went to one with Blair and Brown and Smith was supposed to turn up but didn't so this was when Smith was the leader of the party and Blair and Brown were the were the number twos er and they were fantastic they were brilliant</u>
<u n="616" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="617" who="S0649">I think we went to a a meeting in <anon type="place"/> by that time Tony Blair was leader of the party and then we went there and I thought he was absolutely inspirational</u>
<u n="618" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="619" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="620" who="S0649">mm</u>
<u n="621" who="S0283">yes and yeah as I say I went to</u>
<u n="622" who="S0649">do you remember going there?</u>
<u n="623" who="S0282">there was there's something very engaging about the way he talks</u>
<u n="624" who="S0649" trans="overlap"><unclear/> very sorry?</u>
<u n="625" who="S0282">there's something very engaging about the way he talks there's something about</u>
<u n="626" who="S0649">also the way he looks</u>
<u n="627" who="S0647">yeah but the people who who oppose him don't like him they're again another group erm who cannot be influenced</u>
<u n="628" who="S0649">no</u>
<u n="629" who="S0647">they cannot concede for a minute</u>
<u n="630" who="S0283">no</u>
<u n="631" who="S0647">and this is not just Iraq war although that that increased it</u>
<u n="632" who="S0282" trans="overlap">a lot of it comes from there</u>
<u n="633" who="S0647" trans="overlap">increased the number and and but but and still the case and the same sort of people that will decide whether Ed's a good person or not</u>
<u n="634" who="S0649">a lot of scales fell from my eyes over Iraq and various other things that happened since but I I yes I think Tony Blair did inspire extremes of approval and disapproval</u>
<u n="635" who="S0283">which is unfair because I think the people who disapproved of him forgot that the Labour party had not been in government for seventeen or eighteen years because the Labour party was like it was when it wasn't in power</u>
<u n="636" who="S0282">but no the other thing is that nobody knows about you know the they the sort of cheap plans for policy that we were involved with the general population knows nothing about</u>
<u n="637" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0282">erm and and has no knowledge of and there was erm you know the mistake they made where they said they were going to reduce child poverty but that they were going to measure it comparatively</u>
<u n="639" who="S0283">which never win</u>
<u n="640" who="S0282">yeah and so therefore there was there was erm an upswing in general prosperity which meant that the level of child poverty proportionately went up as well so you know you still see newspapers today that Tony Blair presided over an increase of child poverty which is not er not true</u>
<u n="641" who="S0283" trans="overlap">yeah yeah more more children had more money but there was an increase in child poverty</u>
<u n="642" who="S0282">yeah I know well there was yeah that was because of the gap between the haves and the have nots got bigger but the have nots have got more</u>
<u n="643" who="S0649">statistical games</u>
<u n="644" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="645" who="S0649">yes</u>
<u n="646" who="S0282">but you know people will still say that well you know you know Labour party had absolutely no effect whatsoever because you know people were poorer at the end of it <pause dur="short"/> and erm <pause dur="short"/> and people just say that and don't question what they're even saying and it's very upsetting when you think about the amount of money and effort that went into various policies</u>
<u n="647" who="S0283">I'd quite like to see a chart of er growth in GDP over these last several erm <pause dur="short"/> parliaments</u>
<u n="648" who="S0282">well well of course you know that's why we're having to pay all this extra money to Europe cos our economy is doing so really well</u>
<u n="649" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="650" who="S0649">what a storm in a teacup that was what a bit of</u>
<u n="651" who="S0647">yes</u>
<u n="652" who="S0649">what a shaming and embarrassing incident</u>
<u n="653" who="S0283">but also again it's typical Cameron you know you get one point seven billion pound bill</u>
<u n="654" who="S0647">oh god</u>
<u n="655" who="S0283">and he says there is no way that I'm going to pay all of this</u>
<u n="656" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="657" who="S0283">all of this on the due rate and he's saying oh okay I can't really spot the get out clause there can I? I mean jesus who does he think we are?</u>
<u n="658" who="S0282">Nigel Farage was very quick to point that out</u>
<u n="659" who="S0649">it would be beyond <trunc>be</trunc>beyond my credibility now if we actually managed to land with Cameron for a second term</u>
<u n="660" who="S0282">but but I generally</u>
<u n="661" who="S0649">beyond my <trunc>credi</trunc> credulity</u>
<u n="662" who="S0647" trans="overlap">I don't erm this erm <pause dur="short"/> the reporting of the fact that he only had to pay half was was a rebate in in <unclear/> and I was thinking the only Joe guy walking down the road does he know what they're talking about there's a rebate?</u>
<u n="663" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="664" who="S0647" trans="overlap">no no no one no one no one there must be other words that you could use to communicate</u>
<u n="665" who="S0649" trans="overlap">I think the <unclear/> think think</u>
<u n="666" who="S0283">I I still don't understand whether there was any reduction in the money that we whether whether the negotiation reduced the amount of money that we would l have had to pay</u>
<u n="667" who="S0647">no no</u>
<u n="668" who="S0649">no</u>
<u n="669" who="S0647">it it it <trunc>abs</trunc> no absolutely not</u>
<u n="670" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0647">we we had to pay the money but yes erm</u>
<u n="672" who="S0283">but there was a supplement</u>
<u n="673" who="S0647" trans="overlap">but we're we're but we've got a quite separate issue erm we've got the rebate</u>
<u n="674" who="S0282">actually what they did achieve was they put off the payment date for the</u>
<u n="675" who="S0649">yes</u>
<u n="676" who="S0282">for the <unclear/> until the date of the rebate</u>
<u n="677" who="S0649">and they didn't <unclear/> rebate</u>
<u n="678" who="S0282" trans="overlap">so they have to pay it now the first of December they don't have they don't have to pay the balance</u>
<u n="679" who="S0649">cos they were told they were going to have to pay the <unclear/> rate didn't they?</u>
<u n="680" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="681" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0647">but most people won't understanding what the slight of hand was</u>
<u n="683" who="S0283">no so it's like going into Sainsbury's and erm saying I'm not paying twelve pounds fifty for a bottle of wine and I refuse to pay it absolutely and then using your club card to get six pounds forty-two off bacon and then saying that my bottle of wine costs less it's just it's yeah oh right I haven't explained that very well</u>
<u n="684" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no that's a very torturous example really</u>
<u n="685" who="S0649"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="686" who="S0647">and I think the I think the majority of people have no idea what</u>
<u n="687" who="S0283">oh okay the I suppose the point is that we pay a huge amount of money into the EU every year and we get some back</u>
<u n="688" who="S0647">mm</u>
<u n="689" who="S0283">and so what what they've said is that we have to pay more in but we're not getting any more back that's the point and what the government have said is that they they've used the money that we were already getting back to say that we're paying less which is just nonsense</u>
<u n="690" who="S0282">I think I think most people jumped on it I think you would have to be that type to have left the country not to hear the second story</u>
<u n="691" who="S0647">no I'm sorry if you if you read the the Sun and Telegraph erm I just wonder how sympathetic the reporting would be there</u>
<u n="692" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="693" who="S0647">and and it it's quite difficult and I mean I had to have two goes at at explaining it it's it's quite difficult to understand</u>
<u n="694" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="695" who="S0283">have you ever read the <trunc>To</trunc> the Telegraph?</u>
<u n="696" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="697" who="S0647">not very <unclear/></u>
<u n="698" who="S0282">yeah the Telegraph comes into our house every day now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="699" who="S0283">well I often buy it cos of the <unclear/></u>
<u n="700" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="701" who="S0283">buy it a couple of time just to read it because what as Guardian readers it's all a bit loopy lefty and it's a bit floppy the Times is sort of fairly dry and analytical</u>
<u n="702" who="S0647">it's it's it's getting very right actually</u>
<u n="703" who="S0283">oh is it?</u>
<u n="704" who="S0647">mm</u>
<u n="705" who="S0283">well I was going to say was that actually you can you can trust other Guardian and the Times to have an element of fact in their factual reporting whereas the Telegraph is pure propaganda it's not it's not</u>
<u n="706" who="S0649" trans="overlap">no but I don't count them</u>
<u n="707" who="S0647" trans="overlap">yeah and the Daily Mail too</u>
<u n="708" who="S0283">mm</u>
<u n="709" who="S0647">which I if I go to a a dental appointment or something I look at the Daily Mail and it it's quite astonishing</u>
<u n="710" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0282">but the Telegraph is just my parents live in a state of constant alarm because the Telegraph is just this sort of it's like a penny dreadful it's everything oh it's all bad for you everything's going to go wrong</u>
<u n="712" who="S0647">the Times the Times has got a comparatively new editor and it's well I said to you before the erm erm what was the story erm the the speech their coverage of the speech started with a couple of negative things about the speech and it was eight inches later that they actually reported on the speech so</u>
<u n="713" who="S0649" trans="overlap">but the but they've been sniping at Ed right since this new editor came in</u>
<u n="714" who="S0283" trans="overlap">yeah I don't I don't mind a paper being right wing what's different about the Torygraph is that it's not news it's not facts it's opinion based around</u>
<u n="715" who="S0649" trans="overlap">it's very smart fact I mean they're suppose to tell us the facts</u>
<u n="716" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="717" who="S0282">well and but then they stances you see like climate change the the Telegraph believe there is no such thing as climate change so that's it's starting point on every single story about the environment of course climate change is nonsense erm</u>
<u n="718" who="S0649">I have to say the Telegraph just dropped off my consciousness I think with the the demise of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who was a Telegraph reader</u>
<u n="719" who="S0283">was she?</u>
<u n="720" who="S0649">I think so I think so</u>
<u n="721" who="S0283">but there are hundreds of thousands of people who read it and believe it and that's frightening</u>
<u n="722" who="S0647">I think you'll find the Daily Mail presents <trunc>f</trunc><trunc>f</trunc>f quite a serious threat er erm</u>
<u n="723" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="724" who="S0282">well Paul Dacre is our secret prime minister really isn't he?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0283">I was I was in the head</u>
<u n="726" who="S0282">he's the man who really runs the country</u>
<u n="727" who="S0283">I was in the hairdresser this evening it's run by two women from the old Eastern Europe I don't I have no idea where erm and one of their sons</u>
<u n="728" who="S0282">can they cut hair?</u>
<u n="729" who="S0283">well no but one of their sons was in there he's about eight or nine and he was reading the front page of the Daily Express which said facts proven there are underlined too many immigrants and I just thought how how does that person feel aged eight or nine reading a newspaper which says fact there are too many immigrants? I just think it's horrible</u>
<u n="730" who="S0649">well you wouldn't think he would believe a child of eight or nine</u>
<u n="731" who="S0283" trans="overlap">well you probably <trunc>w</trunc>well actually probably what he would think is yeah there are they should send them send them all back send the new ones back</u>
<u n="732" who="S0649" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="733" who="S0647">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="734" who="S0283">oops sorry</u>
<u n="735" who="S0282">well I don't know I don't know where this is going to end up the xenophobia is just appalling it's just like they've opened a a kind of</u>
<u n="736" who="S0647">a Pandora</u>
<u n="737" who="S0282">take the lid off the box and then all this stuff comes out and it's disgusting it doesn't makes me it makes me so distressed</u>
<u n="738" who="S0649">where did I pick up a fag end? yesterday I can't remember it must have been the radio on one of the questions they were asking is would you feel afraid would you feel afraid if you lived next door to immigrants?</u>
<u n="739" who="S0282">afraid?</u>
<u n="740" who="S0649">mm</u>
<u n="741" who="S0283" trans="overlap">what what do they mean by immigrants</u>
<u n="742" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm <trunc>Trans</trunc> what Transylvanians or French people?</u>
<u n="743" who="S0283" trans="overlap">Americans</u>
<u n="744" who="S0649">well I told you the question as I heard it with a quarter of an ear on the radio did you hear it?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0647">erm I heard it as part of Ed's speech Ed Ed Ed erm</u>
<u n="746" who="S0649" trans="overlap">oh is that where I heard it?</u>
<u n="747" who="S0647">listed a whole lot of terrible things like</u>
<u n="748" who="S0649" trans="overlap">like not true not true yeah</u>
<u n="749" who="S0647" trans="overlap">that that UKIP censor UKIP UKIP are he said that UKIP actually asked whether you'd be fearful of a foreigner or immigrant lived next door he listed a whole lot of things that UKIP espoused</u>
<u n="750" who="S0283">well the British prime minister is now er speaking against the free movement of people in the European Union which presumably means he doesn't want British people to go and work in France or Germany</u>
<u n="751" who="S0647">yeah he he</u>
<u n="752" who="S0649" trans="overlap">he doesn't know the answer himself</u>
<u n="753" who="S0647" trans="overlap">he won't get that but what will happen is more and more cut back on whether they can get benefits or not</u>
<u n="754" who="S0283">which which will be fine until such time British people can't get benefits or jobs abroad and then we'll complain about it</u>
<u n="755" who="S0282">yeah when all those erm OAPs in Spain won't get treated on the Spanish health system and get sent home or get charged huge amounts of money or whatever no cos apparently there's about a million of us</u>
<u n="756" who="S0647" trans="overlap">but but but they're afraid of Labour I mean it is now a Labour policy that we shouldn't get benefits for X months</u>
<u n="757" who="S0282">oh that makes that I think that's disgraceful quite frankly</u>
<u n="758" who="S0647">yeah</u>
<u n="759" who="S0282">absolutely disgraceful</u>
<u n="760" who="S0647">erm what you want to know is if someone is actually starving to death</u>
<u n="761" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="762" who="S0647">you still get not getting not getting any benefits</u>
<u n="763" who="S0282">but then there are controls anyway but nobody will believe it nobody will believe the numbers it's one of those things where they say when they go out to people and they do a questionnaire they say how many immigrants come into this country a year? oh three or four million it's like er no you know how many? and there was a they did a whole survey where they <trunc>wr</trunc> what people believed you know how many teenage girls get pregnant? you know how many immigrants come into this country how many people in this country come from a minority people's estimates area just bizarrely out of they're really out of proportion</u>
<u n="764" who="S0647" trans="overlap">this last thing I saw was I think you mentioned where where people were asked to say how many what percentage of people were immigrants?</u>
<u n="765" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="766" who="S0647">and the percentages were way up there and the answer is very low</u>
<u n="767" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="768" who="S0649">it's seven per cent or something</u>
<u n="769" who="S0647">yes about yeah I can't remember what no maybe a bit more</u>
<u n="770" who="S0283">well you've met my</u>
<u n="771" who="S0647">the they cos we we we had the thing as well that in fact people coming from the the <trunc>re</trunc><trunc>re</trunc> people coming from EU numbers have reduced I think but one of the increase were people coming from outside of the EU</u>
<u n="772" who="S0649">perhaps out of EU yeah</u>
<u n="773" who="S0282">out of the EU well the the floods of which who was the latest ones that they were afraid of?</u>
<u n="774" who="S0647">Romania and</u>
<u n="775" who="S0282">Romanians didn't add up to the numbers that anybody thought they were going to</u>
<u n="776" who="S0647">in fact it was something he said the other day that their numbers have increased quite erm er it's a problem I mean it it would be ridiculous to suggest that it isn't a problem</u>
<u n="777" who="S0282">but then on the other hand they say that erm immigrants are worth more more to the economy than than native British people</u>
<u n="778" who="S0649">they say yes</u>
<u n="779" who="S0282">they they actually bring more in in terms of income and erm earnings and things like that so they're a net benefit</u>
<u n="780" who="S0649">it depends how old they are but they're useful when they're young and they get expensive when they're old</u>
<u n="781" who="S0282">that's the</u>
<u n="782" who="S0649">well it is so that that those are the arguments I we've heard whenever it was</u>
<u n="783" who="S0647">by the time they got old they will have paid lots of money in</u>
<u n="784" who="S0283">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="785" who="S0282">and they're not allowed to bring their grannies with them</u>
<u n="786" who="S0647">no</u>
<u n="787" who="S0282">not automatically anyway <pause dur="short"/> so erm</u>
<u n="788" who="S0647">I don't know erm the economics of it they come here because wages are very high but so is the cost of living in their country they pay little but the cost of living is very low I don't know how that how that balances out</u>
<u n="789" who="S0649">they send back a bit of money which is worth great deal more when it gets there</u>
<u n="790" who="S0283">I suppose you they live in they live in shacks they live in shanty towns they live in hostels</u>
<u n="791" who="S0649" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="792" who="S0282">well even if they send back twenty-five quid a month or something that's probably worth a lot there</u>
<u n="793" who="S0649">is that your machine or has <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> left hers behind?</u>
<u n="794" who="S0282">no that's mine</u>
<u n="795" who="S0649">oh that's</u>
<u n="796" who="S0283">that's what's recording your every word</u>
<u n="797" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="798" who="S0647">oh alright it's a long conversation</u>
<u n="799" who="S0282" trans="overlap">it's on my phone now I know fifty-three minutes so far we need to do another seven months before we can shut up</u>
<u n="800" who="S0647" trans="overlap">oh golly we're going for the we we've got to go for the hour have we? oh</u>
<u n="801" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="802" who="S0282">well it has got dead on to the hour but erm but they like it to be fifteen minutes half an hour or a hour a close as possible you see</u>
<u n="803" who="S0647">oh right right</u>
<u n="804" who="S0649">it must their commitment to analysing it must be very high I don't quite I wonder what they do be interesting to know</u>
<u n="805" who="S0282">I know no I don't know enough about the detail actually</u>
<u n="806" who="S0649" trans="overlap">how they how they extract</u>
<u n="807" who="S0282">somebody said to me the other day do they do it by computer or so people do it? well I don't know that</u>
<u n="808" who="S0283">you could ask</u>
<u n="809" who="S0282">I could ask couldn't I? they paid me ninety-nine pounds in November</u>
<u n="810" who="S0649">CUP is it?</u>
<u n="811" who="S0282">yeah and Lancaster University</u>
<u n="812" who="S0649">I don't know if I know about Lancaster University <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="813" who="S0283">it's a university where</u>
<u n="814" who="S0649">is it CUP with a with a a with a erm intention of feeding it into a new dictionary?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0282">erm they haven't said anything about a dictionary</u>
<u n="816" who="S0649">mm</u>
<u n="817" who="S0283">we should get hold of the last report</u>
<u n="818" who="S0649">yeah</u>
<u n="819" who="S0283">and see what that said</u>
<u n="820" who="S0282">yes that's true</u>
<u n="821" who="S0283">must have been published so yeah so what are your plans now you've got erm you're going to watch the beginning of the sleepover tomorrow are you?</u>
<u n="822" who="S0647">yeah</u>
<u n="823" who="S0282">well that sounds interesting</u>
<u n="824" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="825" who="S0647">yeah this is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> er going to have a sleepover with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the sleepover has always been around but it's now er very very popular</u>
<u n="826" who="S0649"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does does does does launch on her sleepovers yes</u>
<u n="827" who="S0282">right is that a way of saying that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are going out for the evening?</u>
<u n="828" who="S0649">I think they were going to a party and then they were and then she said she didn't know what they were doing and then she had to go and collect erm I don't know</u>
<u n="829" who="S0647">I I don't think the sleepover was arranged so they could have a night off</u>
<u n="830" who="S0649" trans="overlap">no no no no I mean I I think there was a party and well I know that the sleepover has been talked of for some time and time was as <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said last time the end rope is getting smaller</u>
<u n="831" who="S0283">that's the only thing that's getting smaller</u>
<u n="832" who="S0649">no when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came up the other day and to <anon type="place"/> we went for nice <trunc>wa</trunc>walk along the river and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were in front and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I were behind and suddenly <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were in floods and peals and peals of laughter and when I caught up with them it's because they'd come to a squeezer you know what squeezers are the work in the stone walks they have gaps that you just walk through but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> couldn't</u>
<u n="833" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh right oh no</u>
<u n="834" who="S0649">she's huge I don't know when you last saw her</u>
<u n="835" who="S0282">must be a month ago or something wasn't it?</u>
<u n="836" who="S0283">it was your birthday so</u>
<u n="837" who="S0649" trans="overlap">there's a good deal of her</u>
<u n="838" who="S0282">a good month ago</u>
<u n="839" who="S0283" trans="overlap">well I heard she's got she's got two she's got two weeks to <trunc>per</trunc> before she goes to Tottenham so I hope she I hope she manages to stay <unclear/></u>
<u n="840" who="S0649">I knew there was supposed to be a that there was going to be at Tottenham erm gathering of you erm and how many and how many seats has she got?</u>
<u n="841" who="S0647">we saw we saw bits of the last one that was disastrous wasn't it?</u>
<u n="842" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="843" who="S0647">what's wrong what's wrong?</u>
<u n="844" who="S0283">I don't know I don't know it's season of transition the Kinnock years</u>
<u n="845" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="846" who="S0647">erm oh god yes so where what's the next one?</u>
<u n="847" who="S0283">er the thirtieth er I'll er of November</u>
<u n="848" who="S0647">crikey that's very close to the event</u>
<u n="849" who="S0283">no I know well we've got two seats but they're on the end of the row</u>
<u n="850" who="S0647"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="851" who="S0649">two for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="852" who="S0283">no just one for her but it's on the end of the row so</u>
<u n="853" who="S0282">near the exit</u>
<u n="854" who="S0283">it's not that near the exit it's right at the top</u>
<u n="855" who="S0282">near the St John's Ambulance</u>
<u n="856" who="S0647">is there a doctor in the stadium?</u>
<u n="857" who="S0283">if erm</u>
<u n="858" who="S0282">I don't er no honestly you should give her something to induce it while you're there you'll get free tickets for life you'll get their baby will get a life pass life membership</u>
<u n="859" who="S0283">yeah well last time that they had a doctor in the house was Fabrice Muamba so we don't we don't want to repeat that</u>
<u n="860" who="S0649">no thank you very much</u>
<u n="861" who="S0647">what was it?</u>
<u n="862" who="S0282">there's bound there's bound to be a gynaecologist there somewhere or an obstetrician</u>
<u n="863" who="S0283" trans="overlap">Fabrice Muamba the the the yeah</u>
<u n="864" who="S0282">or a midwife or a</u>
<u n="865" who="S0283">yeah well there was there was a world class heart surgeon thank goodness on the way so there's probably a gynaecologist there somewhere</u>
<u n="866" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="867" who="S0283">yeah but no I think as long as as long as she doesn't have a problem at half time or at full time then we're alright cos she can probably get out</u>
<u n="868" who="S0649"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="869" who="S0283">but any time other than that</u>
<u n="870" who="S0282">I think if you start if she goes into labour you need to encourage her to stay there</u>
<u n="871" who="S0647"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="872" who="S0282">because people people who give birth in Sainsbury's or Marks and Spencer's whatever always get really good</u>
<u n="873" who="S0649">is there a midwife in the house? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="874" who="S0647"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="875" who="S0282">lifetime contributions or whatever from the supermarket they get so they get so mushy about these things so if you <trunc>st</trunc> if she starts going oh you've got to make sure she doesn't leave</u>
<u n="876" who="S0647">who is going with you?</u>
<u n="877" who="S0283">just the two of us</u>
<u n="878" who="S0649">just you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="879" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="880" who="S0649">I'm amazed that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/> enough to leave her</u>
<u n="881" who="S0282" trans="overlap">could you could you <unclear/> on what's happened just in case</u>
<u n="882" who="S0283">I'm sure she'll know</u>
<u n="883" who="S0282">I suppose she does know yeah</u>
<u n="884" who="S0649">what what what what?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0283">what to happen just in what would happen just in case</u>
<u n="886" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> running around saying boiling water I need boiling water and a towel</u>
<u n="887" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="888" who="S0283">I would probably say I need a midwife</u>
<u n="889" who="S0649">he would say dressing room dressing room we need the dressing room</u>
<u n="890" who="S0283">yes we couldn't be much further from the dressing room</u>
<u n="891" who="S0649">or is there a midwife in the house? is probably what you need to say</u>
<u n="892" who="S0647">I think that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is perfectly capable where is she where where is she having it?</u>
<u n="893" who="S0649">erm well yeah <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="894" who="S0283">oh really? oh what in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="895" who="S0649"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="896" who="S0283"><anon type="place"/>? I thought <anon type="place"/> was <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="897" who="S0647">yeah</u>
<u n="898" who="S0649">oh it's a bit up from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="899" who="S0282">it's in the block</u>
<u n="900" who="S0283">oh so just by <anon type="place"/> road yes</u>
<u n="901" who="S0647">it's just at the top of? it's it's the junction of <anon type="place"/> road and <anon type="place"/> road</u>
<u n="902" who="S0649" trans="overlap">where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was did you  go and see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="903" who="S0647">yeah</u>
<u n="904" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="905" who="S0283">no</u>
<u n="906" who="S0282">we did go and see a man about my ears there didn't we? was it about my ears?</u>
<u n="907" who="S0283">well I've been to <anon type="place"/> several times but I know where it is</u>
<u n="908" who="S0649">yes</u>
<u n="909" who="S0282">it is between <anon type="place"/> road and <anon type="place"/> and</u>
<u n="910" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="911" who="S0649">opposite <anon type="place"/> really isn't it?</u>
<u n="912" who="S0283">yeah no it just off</u>
<u n="913" who="S0647">no no no not</u>
<u n="914" who="S0282">no a bit further down</u>
<u n="915" who="S0647">further er erm</u>
<u n="916" who="S0283">it's just it's by the <anon type="place"/> road</u>
<u n="917" who="S0647">when when we come back when we come back from when we come back from the north we keep following the <anon type="place"/> signs and what happens is instead of taking us to <anon type="place"/> it takes us to that junction where you can't go out to <anon type="place"/> road you've got to go left or right and you don't want to do either of those things</u>
<u n="918" who="S0649" trans="overlap">we all know where it is we all know where it is we all know where <anon type="place"/> is</u>
<u n="919" who="S0647">and cos we want to get to</u>
<u n="920" who="S0282">and you should have gone down the other path</u>
<u n="921" who="S0647"><anon type="place"/> grove so we need to know to ignore one of the <anon type="place"/> signs</u>
<u n="922" who="S0649">yes this we drove a long time ago anyway never mind</u>
<u n="923" who="S0283">we all know where it is</u>
<u n="924" who="S0282">but nobody can get to it</u>
<u n="925" who="S0649">more more to the point <anon type="place"/> knows where it is</u>
<u n="926" who="S0283">yeah has it got a car park?</u>
<u n="927" who="S0282">probably not</u>
<u n="928" who="S0649">we've never been with our car <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="929" who="S0283">it's very inconvenient of her to be living in north London especially</u>
<u n="930" who="S0647">you got</u>
<u n="931" who="S0283">mm</u>
<u n="932" who="S0647">you you never park just to come here you never park inside the place do you? no we they suddenly got hot on punishing people who are not displaying their disk properly or might not have a disk and they've taken on a commercial firm who will change a hundred pounds</u>
<u n="933" who="S0282">well if they can catch you</u>
<u n="934" who="S0647">if you park</u>
<u n="935" who="S0283">I thought that was illegal I thought that was the</u>
<u n="936" who="S0282">no you can fine you can't clamp and you can't tow anymore you can go get somebody to give you a ticket but you're not obliged legally to tell them anything you're not obliged to reply you're not obliged to confess that you were driving or that your car was there you can ignore any fine that they get and then they have to take you through the courts so it's</u>
<u n="937" who="S0649">how do you know all that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="938" who="S0282">because I've got a car park at the <anon type="place"/> and we have the devil's own job trying to people out of it because people think oh free parking so and then we have fights about people about the bollards and people have there's the the guy who runs the nightclub opposite has Super Glued our bollards four times now to punish us for locking him out of the car park</u>
<u n="939" who="S0647">what's he done four time?</u>
<u n="940" who="S0282">Super Glued our bollards</u>
<u n="941" who="S0647">good god</u>
<u n="942" who="S0282">mm it would be funny if it wasn't so annoying</u>
<u n="943" who="S0647">you can't take some action about that</u>
<u n="944" who="S0282">the police aren't interested we go to the police and they go oh antisocial behaviour we say no it's not it's criminal damage and they say no no no no it's just antisocial behaviour we don't record that</u>
<u n="945" who="S0647">mm</u>
<u n="946" who="S0649">so he has to have a <unclear>U pen</unclear> or whatever it is a new</u>
<u n="947" who="S0282">no they can't be bothered they say unless you know who it is we're not gonna</u>
<u n="948" who="S0283">what's a <unclear>U pen</unclear>?</u>
<u n="949" who="S0649">it's something that used to be a <unclear/></u>
<u n="950" who="S0283">oh right okay</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
