<text id="SLTU">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:03:36</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-24</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0058 S0179</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's car</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Jobs, education</topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T04</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0058">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Corpus Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0179">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harpenden, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years, 7 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Consultant engineer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0179">okie dokie</u>
<u n="2" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> right seriously</u>
<u n="3" who="S0179">what are you doing?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0058">taking their coat off</u>
<u n="5" who="S0179">truly special</u>
<u n="6" who="S0058">that's really special <pause dur="short"/> I'm just going to stop on the slip road <pause dur="short"/> fine</u>
<u n="7" who="S0179">going now</u>
<u n="8" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0179">you stupid woman</u>
<u n="10" who="S0058">that was quite spectacular</u>
<u n="11" who="S0179">oh she's now moving</u>
<u n="12" who="S0058">oh good</u>
<u n="13" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="14" who="S0058">right <pause dur="short"/> after that er brief diversion</u>
<u n="15" who="S0179">debacle</u>
<u n="16" who="S0058">debacle</u>
<u n="17" who="S0179">I like that word</u>
<u n="18" who="S0058">debacle is a lovely word isn't it?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> er I think we were talking about circuits just before we went in <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah I mean do you think we should go around all three of us together or think?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what was the alternative?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0058">er one of us <pause dur="short"/> yeah all all three of us go around separately we could do</u>
<u n="23" who="S0179">yes but one of us going around separately would be me</u>
<u n="24" who="S0058">or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0179">sorry?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0058">or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0179">so you're honestly going to send her off to do it by herself?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0058">you know it's not necessarily a communal thing circuits</u>
<u n="29" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="30" who="S0058"><unclear/> by myself last week <pause dur="short"/> but erm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0058">all three of us yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay cool</u>
<u n="33" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0058">you can request it I'm sure</u>
<u n="35" who="S0179">which makes life better</u>
<u n="36" who="S0058"><unclear/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0179"><unclear/> always making it better</u>
<u n="38" who="S0058">it was hard work erm you know was er</u>
<u n="39" who="S0179">it's going <unclear/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0058">no no I mean it was erm harder than normal I think and as you say it was at the hardest year and not a lot of people said yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0179">and not a lot of people said yeah?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0058">no they did a lot of people did <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0179">you actually did say not <pause dur="short"/> you said a lot of people?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm so it worked quite well <pause dur="short"/> I loved his er slightly terse response <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="45" who="S0179">oh <pause dur="short"/> I didn't and it made me feel very bad</u>
<u n="46" who="S0058">Don't feel bad <pause dur="short"/> he'll have laughed and then been like I can't see <unclear/> Like I said I think he's just very kind of conscious that he wants to be a complete professional</u>
<u n="47" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/> talking about makes me feel <unclear/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0058">oh I'm really sorry chuck <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0179">I'm looking forward to that</u>
<u n="50" who="S0058">well to a certain extent it's generally</u>
<u n="51" who="S0179">A circuit</u>
<u n="52" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it should be good <pause dur="short"/> and er yeah we'll have a chat to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when she gets here on Sunday night and we'll sort of plan the week on Sunday night</u>
<u n="53" who="S0179" trans="overlap">so <unclear/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0058">no that's the one I couldn't <pause dur="short"/> they can't book an induction until she's on the system so and she so she needs to go down on the Monday night erm he said just call in <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah we can go straight from work call in and fill the form in then they can book her in for an induction</u>
<u n="55" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="56" who="S0058">and she can use the gym straightaway kind of thing</u>
<u n="57" who="S0179">okay well we'll do that <pause dur="short"/> well I think if we do the same default then when we'll</u>
<u n="58" who="S0058">go down later Monday</u>
<u n="59" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0058">yeah so I mean</u>
<u n="61" who="S0179">kind of first time go down</u>
<u n="62" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so yeah we could either call in straight from work or just come back and just she can just sign up when we go <unclear/> kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> but erm yeah it should be good <pause dur="short"/> we could try and book in to body pump on Tuesday</u>
<u n="63" who="S0179">on on Monday <unclear/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0058">okay well I mean</u>
<u n="65" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0058">even if just <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes though</u>
<u n="67" who="S0179">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> or even meet me afterwards</u>
<u n="68" who="S0058">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> it works out quite well</u>
<u n="69" who="S0179">okay <pause dur="short"/> erm what else?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0058">I think the thought was moving out and stay out the way of the</u>
<u n="71" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0058">lane</u>
<u n="73" who="S0179">but but fundamentally</u>
<u n="74" who="S0058">but then if I could <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0179">it could mean I was going to cause an accident and you don't do it <pause dur="short"/> people don't</u>
<u n="76" who="S0058" trans="overlap">well you didn't <pause dur="short"/> yeah you didn't really though you kind of stayed in the middle <pause dur="short"/> so you know obviously just not working it out properly</u>
<u n="77" who="S0179">well to be fair if I had thought a bit more ahead I would have given him more room to do it but on the other hand</u>
<u n="78" who="S0058">yeah yeah he was definitely in the wrong</u>
<u n="79" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0058">A bit of a <unclear/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0179">and it's er what was it a Peugeot thingamabob?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0058">thing</u>
<u n="83" who="S0179">A tall thing</u>
<u n="84" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> wind catcher <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if I told you erm my grandpa said he's going to get rid of the car he's not going to drive anymore so he's planning what he's going to do with his garage</u>
<u n="85" who="S0179">does he want to give you the car?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0058">I doubt it <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure I want it <pause dur="short"/> as in it's a fairly old automatic Ford <pause dur="short"/> yeah I should think so</u>
<u n="87" who="S0179">well bearing in mind I was half contemplating that an automatic might be good for you for some drivers</u>
<u n="88" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0179">just getting used to the experience on the road without having to bother to bother you about gears</u>
<u n="90" who="S0058">yeah and then put them in at the end <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0179">because you you've been troubled with the clutches and it's just your ability to select gears at the appropriate junction is problematic</u>
<u n="92" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0179">with an automatic you wouldn't have to worry about that</u>
<u n="94" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and just concentrate on erm what I was doing yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0179">you know it's not <unclear/> holding it like that and you're <unclear/></u>
<u n="96" who="S0058">sorry</u>
<u n="97" who="S0179">you've just hurt my eyes and it's really distracting</u>
<u n="98" who="S0058">sorry yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0179"><unclear/> point out but it's your job to talk to me</u>
<u n="100" who="S0058">yeah yeah sorry</u>
<u n="101" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0058">erm I imagine he'll just sell it to one of the <pause dur="short"/> er but I don't think it's erm but it a sort of mobility one <pause dur="short"/> actually I don't know if he can sell it he's got it through a scheme thing erm because of a grant so he might have to just give it back</u>
<u n="103" who="S0179">fair enough</u>
<u n="104" who="S0058">I don't really know how <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if he gets it free or just very reduced or I don't really know what the deal is but it might just have to go back to them <pause dur="short"/> erm because it's not adapted in any way it's just I think it's just a sort of payment scheme thing</u>
<u n="105" who="S0179">so but he doesn't want at sixty?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0058">er no <pause dur="short"/> well I think it's still more than one erm I think he's decided it's maybe er he's past his time driving</u>
<u n="107" who="S0179">possibly wise</u>
<u n="108" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah I think it's a sensible er decision <pause dur="short"/> but yes I said you know when my mum and dad was talking about it and they said well that's a good thing he's thinking about the future he's planning he's working out what his life is going to be like which is good you know?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0179">yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0058">and it's maybe a <unclear/> and they'll maybe get a bit more help in <pause dur="short"/> because I think my dad really has been doing quite a lot</u>
<u n="111" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="112" who="S0058">and I think maybe <trunc>s</trunc> you know just a little bit of extra help if my grandpa really can't care for my gran and just accepting somebody coming in and doing a bit more for them</u>
<u n="113" who="S0179">well it's not yeah it's not entirely unreasonable to expect families to do</u>
<u n="114" who="S0058">no I mean I think my dad's been doing it willingly and hasn't minded doing it and it's not exactly like it's a problem getting there</u>
<u n="115" who="S0179">try <unclear/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0058">it's cool isn't it? And those are massive handlebars</u>
<u n="117" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0058"><unclear/> Erm yeah I don't think my dad has minded doing it at all I think it's more just that if he's not particularly well himself erm yeah then we might be able to get somebody in to er</u>
<u n="119" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="120" who="S0058">help him out <unclear/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0179">it's the one member of that family family is still working</u>
<u n="122" who="S0058">I think my mam really can't er can't do it</u>
<u n="123" who="S0179">when is she planning on retiring?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0058">well she was planning on retiring the minute she hits sixty and but there's been no talk of it so presumably she's keeping going while things are still kind of</u>
<u n="125" who="S0179">interesting <pause dur="short"/> well it probably makes it as one member of the household working while they've still got a daughter at uni</u>
<u n="126" who="S0058">yeah I think that's maybe the thought erm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0179">oh and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> working and supporting herself pulling her weight <pause dur="short"/> I'm just thinking at Leeds you could probably get away with part-time job</u>
<u n="128" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you probably could</u>
<u n="129" who="S0179">again but that would interfere with you know choir and tea-drinking <pause dur="short"/> as in not like a full part-time job</u>
<u n="130" who="S0058">well exactly</u>
<u n="131" who="S0179">but but you could  you could certainly you know fit in I don't know</u>
<u n="132" who="S0058">A six-hour shift on a Saturday probably</u>
<u n="133" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> or three hours Saturday three hours Sunday</u>
<u n="134" who="S0179">yeah exactly it wouldn't kill you</u>
<u n="135" who="S0058"><unclear/> fit it in</u>
<u n="136" who="S0179">exactly it wouldn't kill you</u>
<u n="137" who="S0058">not a lot of money</u>
<u n="138" who="S0179">but</u>
<u n="139" who="S0058">depending on what you're doing but it would be better than</u>
<u n="140" who="S0179">well no I mean you can probably get something like about eight if you're lucky ten quid an hour</u>
<u n="141" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0179">around ten</u>
<u n="143" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah so is it eight quid now probably?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0179">if you were creative so what like it's eight times six and that's er forty-eight fifty quid a week you know that's</u>
<u n="145" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0179">that would be  that would be  below tax you'd actually get all of it <pause dur="short"/> but actually it would pay for a lot of that it would pay for all of your</u>
<u n="147" who="S0058">food</u>
<u n="148" who="S0179">the vast majority of your your living expenses food</u>
<u n="149" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0179">erm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0058"><unclear/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0179">but</u>
<u n="153" who="S0058">I guess you you know it's that or you can put the kind of the extra hours in to work and sort of go over and above what you need to do</u>
<u n="154" who="S0179">but she won't be doing that</u>
<u n="155" who="S0058">well</u>
<u n="156" who="S0179">as in you know I'm perfectly sure that erm if you go over and above without that</u>
<u n="157" who="S0058">hmm probably</u>
<u n="158" who="S0179">as in yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0058">er I don't know I don't think it's the worst I think</u>
<u n="160" who="S0179">no but it's nothing it would not be comparable to Oxbridge</u>
<u n="161" who="S0058">no no</u>
<u n="162" who="S0179">as <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> herself has told you</u>
<u n="163" who="S0058" trans="overlap">as in you couldn't <pause dur="short"/> yeah well no as in you couldn't even contemplate doing six hours week working</u>
<u n="164" who="S0179">well no any subjects could English could objectively</u>
<u n="165" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah true as in  put more than six hours a week into <unclear/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0179">yeah but you'd need to try and <unclear/> fair enough <pause dur="short"/> but on the other hand if you could do that much work at Cambridge and still be a <unclear/> member of a couple of different societies and still have a social life and you could damn well do all of that and have a job at Leeds</u>
<u n="167" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0179">if you wanted to <pause dur="short"/> er but it's just the fact that er I don't know it's one fact that there's just never been sort of any inclination but actually she should be supporting herself?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0058">I mean I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what conversation that they have on <unclear/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0058">I don't know whether she said this and my dad said</u>
<u n="172" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0058">there's no way you're getting a job</u>
<u n="174" who="S0179">no but it's the household this is your household there will not have been any conversation</u>
<u n="175" who="S0058">hmm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0179">you know that</u>
<u n="177" who="S0058">in all fairness though <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is the one who brings the <unclear/> and is the one who brings up the conversations</u>
<u n="178" who="S0179">not all good conversations</u>
<u n="179" who="S0058">she usually does <pause dur="short"/> she's been pretty</u>
<u n="180" who="S0179">I wouldn't call them conversations</u>
<u n="181" who="S0058">well the fact is she was very kind of open about how she was feeling all the time</u>
<u n="182" who="S0179">well no that wasn't bringing stuff like that up it was being inappropriate with just inappropriate levels of discussion about me that's attention-seeking not really stuff like that <unclear/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0058">but I can imagine her bringing that up though</u>
<u n="184" who="S0179"><unclear/> you know that's something that that's not what I think she likes to think about</u>
<u n="185" who="S0058">no but I can imagine there would be I can imagine her thinking about that and then talking about it</u>
<u n="186" who="S0179">I can't I don't think it's ever really occurred to her</u>
<u n="187" who="S0058">well I I disagree I think she <pause dur="short"/> it <trunc>c</trunc> it could well have been brought up and it's just that I'm not involved in the discussion erm</u>
<u n="188" who="S0179" trans="overlap">well no I mean you were fairly involved in the discussion about what to do at uni it was</u>
<u n="189" who="S0058">well no but I don't there's no reason for me to be involved in the discussion of if if</u>
<u n="190" who="S0179">I know but</u>
<u n="191" who="S0058">it has been brought up</u>
<u n="192" who="S0179">but actually maybe because to some extent it it does affect you because it's a disparity between the support that two daughters have received and you being one of them <pause dur="short"/> and I think that it is appropriate for you to be involved in but what I was actually getting at specifically was you know when she was thinking about moving to Leeds one of her considerations wasn't well actually if I do this then I'm going to take you know another year to get a worthy degree</u>
<u n="193" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0179">and actually financially it makes more sense to stay at Oxford if I can <pause dur="short"/> I don't think that occurred to her <unclear/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0058">what because she'd have started <unclear/> the degree?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0179">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> erm and likewise it didn't occur to her to get a job in the eight months that she wasn't doing anything else which I still can't quite believe <pause dur="short"/> I don't understand</u>
<u n="197" who="S0058">well</u>
<u n="198" who="S0179">what you could do with that time?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0058">I mean I did tell her to sort of make sure she did something</u>
<u n="200" who="S0179">but she wasn't even on Job Seeker's Allowance for fuck's sake</u>
<u n="201" who="S0058">I did tell her to make sure she did something with it and she didn't really and which is such a shame because it was a really good opportunity to get some really good solid even unpaid work just working for that for six months would have been incredible for her CV</u>
<u n="202" who="S0179" trans="overlap">learn a foreign language</u>
<u n="203" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0179">learning to drive</u>
<u n="205" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0179">you know <pause dur="short"/> any number of useful skills you could do in that time</u>
<u n="207" who="S0058" trans="overlap">go travelling</u>
<u n="208" who="S0179">yes that <pause dur="short"/> well no because that would cost money</u>
<u n="209" who="S0058">true yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0179">anything that <unclear/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0058" trans="overlap">you could probably go and work in another country is what a lot of people would do <pause dur="short"/> erm so they get the travelling experience but they pay for it entirely with the wages they earn</u>
<u n="212" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0058">erm</u>
<u n="214" who="S0179">but anything just sitting on your arse and apart from everything else from a CV perspective that's just chronic</u>
<u n="215" who="S0058" trans="overlap">no I know that's the thing <pause dur="short"/> I did say at the beginning of it you've got to do something and that's a great opportunity that most people don't have and you really need to use it for something good and exciting because of the CV saying I spent I took you know I had to take time off uni but I spent it doing this great thing and look how much better it's made me rather than I had to take time off uni and I've got a big gap <pause dur="short"/> I didn't do anything you know <pause dur="short"/> it's not yeah it's such a shame</u>
<u n="216" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0058">I mean I didn't particularly do an awful lot after leaving uni between getting a job but I was</u>
<u n="218" who="S0179">no you were job hunting fairly intensively</u>
<u n="219" who="S0058">so I was very intensively <pause dur="short"/> yeah I was  I was  really I really was spending all day doing job applications and also I did teach myself proof reading which in retrospect was a very good idea</u>
<u n="220" who="S0179">yeah I mean retrospectively you know possibly could have learnt to drive</u>
<u n="221" who="S0058" trans="overlap">I could have <pause dur="short"/> no exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah I don't think I made completely good use of it but I wasn't sitting around</u>
<u n="222" who="S0179" trans="overlap">well no the thing is you were making use of it and to some extent you'd finished your degree and you'd earned a break</u>
<u n="223" who="S0058">yeah yeah I I did have really golden summer I wasn't intensively</u>
<u n="224" who="S0179">right yeah erm that's again you just <pause dur="short"/> oh that's quite dangerous</u>
<u n="225" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0179">I mean I couldn't slow down after I let him in but I mean</u>
<u n="227" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="228" who="S0179">I couldn't move out so he had to stop and he didn't quite twig as in he didn't stop</u>
<u n="229" who="S0058">no no</u>
<u n="230" who="S0179" trans="overlap">because he came in unexpectedly <unclear/> came in too fast</u>
<u n="231" who="S0058">yeah not enough time <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="232" who="S0179">now that is why dual carriageways are so much more dangerous than motorways</u>
<u n="233" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="234" who="S0179">oh yes good <pause dur="short"/> now not having learnt that speed is dangerous</u>
<u n="235" who="S0058">oh there's a sign the guy with a sign for the George Inn</u>
<u n="236" who="S0179">oh</u>
<u n="237" who="S0058">oh</u>
<u n="238" who="S0179">maybe it's the same guy</u>
<u n="239" who="S0058">at least it's a nice day today I suppose</u>
<u n="240" who="S0179" trans="overlap">maybe you know so <unclear/> you know instead of employee of the month they have like a sin-bin</u>
<u n="241" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0179">worst employee of the last month gets</u>
<u n="243" who="S0058">yeah gets the shifts</u>
<u n="244" who="S0179">so you're coming off there so we're literally on the four one junction <pause dur="short"/> who are you?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0058">yeah that makes sense</u>
<u n="246" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0058">four lads <pause dur="short"/> england shirt hanging in the back</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="248" who="S0058">I don't know I mean it's actually quite weird sort of think thinking back to all the interviews and stuff I did and how just how much better qualified I am now to do things <pause dur="short"/> does that make sense? So just comparing yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0179">one of the you've always done very not fortunate but you did very well as in it'll take you further on you know</u>
<u n="250" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="251" who="S0179"><unclear/> you know Liam spent you know over a year</u>
<u n="252" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no entirely</u>
<u n="253" who="S0179">lots of erm graduate improvement days which I can <unclear/> still think are the worst thing on the face of the planet</u>
<u n="254" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0179">yeah but how can you work cooperatively in a team of people you are competing against? It's a situation it's a skill which is not acquired in</u>
<u n="256" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="257" who="S0179"><unclear/> because you're working as a team of people who you are working with and you want to the same goal</u>
<u n="258" who="S0058">yes it's a ridiculous</u>
<u n="259" who="S0179">this is barmy</u>
<u n="260" who="S0058">balance to ask you to strike</u>
<u n="261" who="S0179">in this situation you need to show that you are better than everyone else</u>
<u n="262" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0179">and but you are decisive <unclear/> also but you're wanting to work with people</u>
<u n="264" who="S0058">yeah it's it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0179">you can't achieve that that's almost impossible</u>
<u n="266" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's er <unclear/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0179">A mental dichotomy</u>
<u n="268" who="S0058">I'm very glad that the things I was going for didn't require that because it's a very odd thing to have to do <pause dur="short"/> erm and you find it very hard I think as well</u>
<u n="269" who="S0179">anyway</u>
<u n="270" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but erm it's kind of good because I'm erm thinking about is it you know because we're recruiting somebody well I'm not but we were the team is recruiting somebody for erm for this other job the one-year contract <pause dur="short"/> erm and I'm going to sit in on erm they've asked the final three to prepare a five-minute presentation as like as if they were giving a <trunc>presen</trunc> because the the job is about going in to universities and schools colleges and persuading people to submit their work</u>
<u n="271" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="272" who="S0058">for the academic <anon type="place"/> and they they basically have to prepare a presentation as if they as if we were a group of science undergraduates <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0179">but if you were anything like qualified to do that</u>
<u n="274" who="S0058" trans="overlap">no no it just doesn't matter that's just the the name we've been given as a group <pause dur="short"/> we're not going to ask science questions but they're going to <pause dur="short"/> they have to give us a presentation to explain what the project is and why you know well what we'd have to do <pause dur="short"/> erm so I'm going to sit on those on Friday but it's I mean that's quite a difficult that's quite involved for the two people who don't get it</u>
<u n="275" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="276" who="S0058">erm</u>
<u n="277" who="S0179">I mean that's a year year's contract</u>
<u n="278" who="S0058">exactly and you know it's got quite a lot of erm recruiting time and effort on their part and you sort of feel a bit sorry for the two who just definitely won't get it</u>
<u n="279" who="S0179">I would just pick one of them if I was you</u>
<u n="280" who="S0058">what from the first interview to and then pick one of them to give a presentation?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0179">yeah and then if they don't</u>
<u n="282" who="S0058">if they don't do it then</u>
<u n="283" who="S0179">like it <unclear/> another one</u>
<u n="284" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think it might make more sense because I do feel a bit sorry for the people and and you know you could have put a lot of time into preparing that and these people are mostly all working in one capacity or another <pause dur="short"/> erm so you've got to give up a lot of your free time <pause dur="short"/> but I guess people really want jobs and it is a prestigious organisation <pause dur="short"/> and I feel really bad I get loads of people because I'm looking at a lot of freelancers and so many people going I'll do anything for you for free because I need to have worked for <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> you know they they just want they're throwing themselves at me and volunteering to do things and it's just it's insane</u>
<u n="285" who="S0179">yeah that's a bit weird</u>
<u n="286" who="S0058">I had somebody ring me up yesterday and she was very sweet but she rings me up a lot and asks me things that she knows <pause dur="short"/> and then doesn't like she's oh I'll submit the files today and then just hasn't submitted them like for the last three days <pause dur="short"/> erm but still rings me quite a lot erm and basically says is there going to be any work after the deadline and said well erm I said there is the possibility of further work and I will be contacting people who have been involved in this project if and when that that happens <pause dur="short"/> you know very diplomatically <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0179">but not you</u>
<u n="288" who="S0058">well that's the thing she hasn't actually submitted anything so I don't know what she's going to produce she's erm she sent me the this thing that</u>
<u n="289" who="S0179" trans="overlap">what is she doing sorry she's transcribing?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0058">she's a recorder</u>
<u n="291" who="S0179">oh</u>
<u n="292" who="S0058">so she's just doing this <pause dur="short"/> but erm</u>
<u n="293" who="S0179">oh right</u>
<u n="294" who="S0058">so yeah but she's like taking it quite seriously and she's doing she's at the <anon type="place"/> and</u>
<u n="295" who="S0179"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0058">yeah and</u>
<u n="297" who="S0179">where is <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0058">near <anon type="place"/> I think</u>
<u n="299" who="S0179">I didn't even know that was a place let alone a university</u>
<u n="300" who="S0058">so there's a university there apparently erm and I think it must be quite small</u>
<u n="301" who="S0179">is it just her?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0058">and she sent an advert out in the newsletter asking for people to help with her research which was a little bit dodgy erm I mean</u>
<u n="303" who="S0179">how do you mean?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0058">Cos it's not her research she's being paid to provide recordings <pause dur="short"/> she's not it's not er help out someone with their PhD project</u>
<u n="305" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0058">you tell somebody you earn money which I'm I'm a little bit gutted with but it did explain under the headline the headline was a bit dodgy but the rest of it was just our advert <pause dur="short"/> she explained very clearly what was  what was  happening so <unclear/> I I mean I don't know exactly what we're going to get and if it's dreadfully kind of pre-prepared still I'm going to have to say this isn't good and I don't know how long she's spent sort of doing this <pause dur="short"/> erm so I really do I've said to her can you you know I really need this stuff <unclear/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0179" trans="overlap">versus our approach of just</u>
<u n="308" who="S0058">just conversing</u>
<u n="309" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0058">but I'm going to feel a bit bad if it's not er you know if it's not very good stuff because she's clearly <pause dur="short"/> and you know she said if you know any work I'd be very interested because it's good for my CV to have worked with <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> and I thought yeah I know but we can't just pay people</u>
<u n="311" who="S0179"><unclear/> but what we actually produce is actually want as far as I understand just actual conversations</u>
<u n="312" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's sometimes we we ask for specific things because obviously <unclear/> okay we'd really like some recordings of teenagers talking about IT so we get that <pause dur="short"/> but yeah there's normally it's just erm yeah people talking in two thousand and twelve <unclear/></u>
<u n="313" who="S0179">erm <pause dur="short"/> what was I thinking of doing <unclear/> thinking about erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0058">sorry?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0179">Silver <unclear/> directions</u>
<u n="316" who="S0058" trans="overlap">oh right I thought you said  I thought you said  <unclear/> and I couldn't work out the connection</u>
<u n="317" who="S0179">erm so she <unclear/> sort of ideas what she's going to do close to uni yes?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0058">well I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if erm if she's had anymore thoughts or whether she's still <pause dur="short"/> because I think that's part of the idea of the work experience that</u>
<u n="319" who="S0179">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0058">that she doesn't really know very much about work and so I think</u>
<u n="321" who="S0179" trans="overlap">never having done any obviously</u>
<u n="322" who="S0058">well I think she's still half thinking about the teaching which will be good</u>
<u n="323" who="S0179" trans="overlap">it's strange she's never been in paid employment in any capacity actually thinking about it</u>
<u n="324" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="325" who="S0179">as in sort of even when I was at school and this is me I had a part-time job as in I did it like three or four times and I still actually had that experience</u>
<u n="326" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0179">and this is sort of me</u>
<u n="328" who="S0058">I mean I had</u>
<u n="329" who="S0179">and I was doing nothing but work</u>
<u n="330" who="S0058">I had a little bit of lifeguarding was the only paid employment I'd had</u>
<u n="331" who="S0179">exactly but you still</u>
<u n="332" who="S0058" trans="overlap">but I <trunc>s</trunc> I sorted it out and made the effort and I'm not sure I actually came out in pocket at all because of the MPLQ but I made the effort and I really did try to get more it just wasn't you know wasn't to be <pause dur="short"/> but I worked very hard for those two weeks of however long it <pause dur="short"/> I think it was two weeks <pause dur="short"/> but yeah I was doing you know I did a couple of ten-hour shifts and the rest they were still pretty much full days you know</u>
<u n="333" who="S0179">yeah but my point being again that she's literally never earned any money in her life which I find quite <pause dur="short"/> actually no she did that</u>
<u n="334" who="S0058">she <unclear/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0179">she did that  festival thing</u>
<u n="336" who="S0058">yeah she did the festival and she did erm she got paid for and she's done open days and stuff that she gets paid for</u>
<u n="337" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah but that's not really</u>
<u n="338" who="S0058">no it's certainly different</u>
<u n="339" who="S0179">that's actually volunteering and you happen to be paid <pause dur="short"/> she's never actually been employed by an organisation</u>
<u n="340" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="341" who="S0179">erm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0058">but</u>
<u n="343" who="S0179" trans="overlap">which is sort of again just a little bit interesting</u>
<u n="344" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="345" who="S0179">but it's possible to have <unclear/> is virtually so she's going to <pause dur="short"/> so you started uni and did three years another three years out of that if she's lucky she's going to graduate</u>
<u n="346" who="S0058">er yes</u>
<u n="347" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0179">quite weird</u>
<u n="350" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I mean I was a year ahead and I I was just</u>
<u n="351" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah I know but <unclear/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0058" trans="overlap">which was just natural <pause dur="short"/> but yeah then I know what you mean <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="353" who="S0179">but the fact that the timescale wasn't essentially dealt with</u>
<u n="354" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="355" who="S0179">er right <unclear/> ring from here now as soon as it's clear</u>
<u n="356" who="S0058">okay erm can I borrow your <pause dur="short"/> I don't have his number</u>
<u n="357" who="S0179">er I did used to know it by heart and then put it in the phone and didn't <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="358" who="S0058">oh right right of course <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0179" trans="overlap">so yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0058" trans="overlap">oh one new message</u>
<u n="361" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0058">shall I read it? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oh You still up? Date went well <pause dur="short"/> what was that?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0179">oh shit <pause dur="short"/> last night</u>
<u n="364" who="S0058">last night it must have been last night <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> oh well that's good</u>
<u n="365" who="S0179">I think if you text him back</u>
<u n="366" who="S0058">erm oh hang on I've just closed it <pause dur="short"/> erm I'll bring that back up</u>
<u n="367" who="S0179">no don't bring it back</u>
<u n="368" who="S0058">no let's text him back</u>
<u n="369" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0058">options</u>
<u n="371" who="S0179">you just said bring it back</u>
<u n="372" who="S0058">I'll bring it back</u>
<u n="373" who="S0179">oh</u>
<u n="374" who="S0058"><trunc>o</trunc> on the phone <pause dur="short"/> okay erm right</u>
<u n="375" who="S0179">just say er hi er just picked it up sorry er had a mental piss-up with my dad last night <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="376" who="S0058">yeah you're going to have to give me what I saw on his phone</u>
<u n="377" who="S0179">so am I actually it's not the most intuitive interface and I'll probably get used to it eventually</u>
<u n="378" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0179">I'm not used to my new role at all at work which fills me <pause dur="short"/> it took a while but I got there</u>
<u n="380" who="S0058">Good <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="381" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0058">just picked it up</u>
<u n="383" who="S0179">sorry just picked it up <pause dur="short"/> sorry just picked it up just <pause dur="short"/> just <pause dur="short"/> sorry just picked your message up or something like that</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="384" who="S0179">er had a rather mental night <pause dur="short"/> er say I had a rather mental family piss-up last night or something like that</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="385" who="S0058">piss-up it wasn't in the dictionary</u>
<u n="386" who="S0179">not that <pause dur="short"/> oh the pigs</u>
<u n="387" who="S0058">oh I love the pigs</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="388" who="S0179"><unclear/> in the space of fifty yards <pause dur="short"/> that's impressive</u>
<u n="389" who="S0058">nice <pause dur="short"/> you don't see that many of them</u>
<u n="390" who="S0179">no</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="391" who="S0179">okay I think now we've stopped which is surprising but excellent <pause dur="short"/> oh that's a pothole</u>
<u n="392" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> okay er</u>
<u n="393" who="S0179">is it taking you that long to write that much?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it says <unclear/> and I keep cancelling it and I keep pressing close rather than cancel <pause dur="short"/> erm because my it's got an extra set of buttons of to to mine <pause dur="short"/> Hi sorry just picked your message up had a rather mental family piss-up last night</u>
<u n="395" who="S0179">erm er erm er driving at the moment er er brackets <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> typing</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="396" who="S0058"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> typing</u>
<u n="397" who="S0179">erm er er er and then just details details details exclamation mark</u>
<u n="398" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> I put Hi sorry just picked your message up had a rather mental family piss-up last night driving at the moment <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> typing</u>
<u n="399" who="S0179" trans="overlap">so do you think that should be er <unclear/> you trying to just pick a message up comma</u>
<u n="400" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="401" who="S0179">hyphen et cetera rather than full stop</u>
<u n="402" who="S0058" trans="overlap">full stop</u>
<u n="403" who="S0179">it shouldn't be a full stop it should be a comma or a hyphen</u>
<u n="404" who="S0058">after pick your message up?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0179">yeah because that the had a mental rather family had a rather mental family piss-up is explaining the reason</u>
<u n="406" who="S0058">alright okay</u>
<u n="407" who="S0179">why I've just picked it up <pause dur="short"/> honestly</u>
<u n="408" who="S0058">comma had a rather</u>
<u n="409" who="S0179">you're not very good at this</u>
<u n="410" who="S0058">you paused in a full stop kind of way</u>
<u n="411" who="S0179">no I didn't <pause dur="short"/> I paused so you could write it</u>
<u n="412" who="S0058">hi sorry just picked your message up <pause dur="short"/> had a rather family piss-up last night</u>
<u n="413" who="S0179">that's better</u>
<u n="414" who="S0058">driving at the moment <pause dur="short"/> bracket <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is typing close brackets full stop details details details <trunc>que</trunc> exclamation mark</u>
<u n="415" who="S0179">yeah is that a question mark and exclamation mark?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0058">question mark exclamation mark okay?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0179">have we managed that simple task?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0179">Good</u>
<u n="420" who="S0058">okay send?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0179">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="422" who="S0058">so now I'll ring your grandpa</u>
<u n="423" who="S0179">please yes <pause dur="short"/> we were you know forty minutes out we're now thirty minutes out now after you've sent the text message</u>
<u n="424" who="S0058">okay erm so we'll be there in about half an hour you reckon?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0058">erm hopefully he'll know who I am?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0179">just say it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0058"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0179"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I will be there</u>
<u n="430" who="S0058">with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0179">it's not rocket science <unclear/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0058" trans="overlap">I know okay</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="433" who="S0179">you also forgot to get your iPod out</u>
<u n="434" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh well <pause dur="short"/> we can listen to it on the way back</u>
<u n="435" who="S0179">I know it's not critical <pause dur="short"/> I just was interested to observe the fact</u>
<u n="436" who="S0058">hello it's Sarah and I'm just letting you know erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I will be with you in about half an hour</u>
<u n="437" who="S0179">for lunch</u>
<u n="438" who="S0058">erm</u>
<u n="439" who="S0179">bringing lunch</u>
<u n="440" who="S0058">and we've got some lunch with us as well <pause dur="short"/> so we'll erm <pause dur="short"/> brilliant okay <pause dur="short"/> well we'll see you for some lunch in about half an hour then <pause dur="short"/> okay bye <pause dur="short"/> yeah that just seemed fine they seemed to <unclear/> I'll be here then erm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0179">Good <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> if we turned up <unclear/></u>
<u n="442" who="S0058">and I didn't quite catch it but I think I said you know we'll be there in about half an hour <pause dur="short"/> I think he said Oh for lunch?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0058">but you were talking at the same time so I didn't quite catch but I think he said Oh for lunch? erm which was good so</u>
<u n="445" who="S0179">yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0058">I'll put that down there in case they text back</u>
<u n="447" who="S0179">because it's easier than getting it back into my pocket</u>
<u n="448" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0179">so yes</u>
<u n="450" who="S0058">yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah your mam said again it's best to get there <unclear/> erm you have to get back by half past four if they go out <pause dur="short"/> but I think we were going to anyway</u>
<u n="451" who="S0179">yeah but <unclear/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0058">yeah but I mean I don't think we need to be back any you know very much earlier than that but apparently erm yeah it's just if erm and it might not be at half four it might be five because they haven't got a timetable <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="453" who="S0179">well I have one</u>
<u n="454" who="S0058">if it's yeah if we  if we  get back by four that should be fine <pause dur="short"/> that should be doable</u>
<u n="455" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="456" who="S0058"><unclear/> yeah erm but I just think it's interesting thinking about employment and interviews and</u>
<u n="457" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="458" who="S0058">experience and stuff</u>
<u n="459" who="S0179">like I said we'll see how erm we'll see how she's er coped this week</u>
<u n="460" who="S0058">yeah I mean I think she'll probably really enjoy it and I mean there's always a question after that of whether you want to do it for your job but I think she'll really enjoy</u>
<u n="461" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="462" who="S0058">no I was thinking more just yeah having things to do and being in an office and it is quite exciting and I really enjoyed my work experience <pause dur="short"/> there was boring bits but but and I mean the the one thing that I didn't particularly like about <unclear/> was the team weren't particularly nice</u>
<u n="463" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="464" who="S0058">they weren't particularly friendly or welcoming or <pause dur="short"/> I mean there was one person who was kind of looking after me and she was perfectly pleasant but she wasn't very chatty or open</u>
<u n="465" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> have essentially a permanent member of staff who <unclear/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's kind of weird <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="467" who="S0179">but it is quite a good way to do it because you're not at the <unclear/> somewhere for long enough to feel bad about not paying them <unclear/> someone permanently there</u>
<u n="468" who="S0058">yeah exactly it does make sense erm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0179"><unclear/> random quality element to it</u>
<u n="470" who="S0058">but having said that though I mean I wasn't doing anything very critical I was mainly reading erm slush which is a difficult there's so much of it even in an idiot would know it was bad</u>
<u n="471" who="S0179">yes but the point is you could have missed something that was actually good</u>
<u n="472" who="S0058">yes entirely yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0179">constantly quite a lot</u>
<u n="474" who="S0058">yes I could have done <pause dur="short"/> if they'd taken it to a publisher yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0179">so it was actually quite important</u>
<u n="476" who="S0058">yes I think but I think it I was basically flagging up anything that wasn't dreadful erm and I was being you know very careful because <trunc>every</trunc> everything all of my comments went to somebody else and I wasn't completely rejecting it out of hand and it was never checked <pause dur="short"/> I had to write a report on everything I read and sometimes there really wasn't anything to say it was just this is dreadful don't publish it <pause dur="short"/> erm this is surely this is a joke I think you know erm but yeah I mean I gave quite balanced reviews and said this is quite decent <pause dur="short"/> and there was one which really was very good and I think it had been published else you know in with the country <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="477" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="478" who="S0058">yeah so that's why I thought it was you know quite a good <unclear/> take a look <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="479" who="S0179">is he in another country reading another language?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0058">no no I think it's Australia</u>
<u n="481" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="482" who="S0058">or New Zealand <pause dur="short"/> erm and he'd sent it in which like I said I mean it was good you know it was erm it was quite informative so <unclear/></u>
<u n="483" who="S0179" trans="overlap">oh you're not seriously trying to do that are you or are you? Please don't try to do <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="484" who="S0058">oh my God</u>
<u n="485" who="S0179">you fucktard</u>
<u n="486" who="S0058">wow</u>
<u n="487" who="S0179">so what has that gained you?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0058">just incredible <pause dur="short"/> there should be a law against driving without a brain</u>
<u n="489" who="S0179"><unclear/> all that often <pause dur="short"/> it's just that people like that they get away with it</u>
<u n="490" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="491" who="S0179">and they consider themselves good drivers</u>
<u n="492" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yes because they haven't actually killed anyone <pause dur="short"/> dear-y me <pause dur="short"/> mm but yeah erm I think erm the <trunc>f</trunc> the folk at <anon type="place"/> are a lot more welcoming than working at er <anon type="place"/> or whatever so that'll make it better I think</u>
<u n="493" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> well that's actually because they're not cycling through</u>
<u n="494" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yes exactly</u>
<u n="495" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="496" who="S0058">yeah how was <unclear/> though I think even if <pause dur="short"/> I think it was partly that that they were you know obviously which is <unclear/> the thing and also I think they just weren't naturally very warm open kind of people <pause dur="short"/> erm because I think if <unclear/> every week I'd still make an effort to to sort of talk to them <pause dur="short"/> nobody talked to me</u>
<u n="497" who="S0179">ah okay</u>
<u n="498" who="S0058">you know and it really it wasn't a case of you know they they didn't ask me for <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't that they didn't ask me for lunch it was like they didn't ask me for lunch because they never spoke to me <pause dur="short"/> the person who spoke to me was the person who I was with but I had to go and ask her a lot of the stuff a lot of the time and she wasn't very forthcoming</u>
<u n="499" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="500" who="S0058">everyone else I spoke to when I was introduced to them or when I had to go and get work from them it was no interaction other than that you know <pause dur="short"/> erm it was just very different to how I think it would be even if we had someone someone permanent</u>
<u n="501" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="502" who="S0058">so you know erm so that would make it better I think and erm yeah it'll be good <pause dur="short"/> and everyone's trying to think of tasks that they've got that they <pause dur="short"/> cos Clare sort of said that she sort of keep you know doesn't just give me bad you know all the dreadful tasks to do because we've both got a lot to to get on with erm</u>
<u n="503" who="S0179">and declined to be</u>
<u n="504" who="S0058">no no she she erm she <unclear/> I don't get <unclear/> copying to do or anything like that people generally do their own <pause dur="short"/> erm so but while <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is there it'll be like here is some filing <pause dur="short"/> here is some sorting that needs doing</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="505" who="S0058">I think the only thing is we have er like an office PA erm who is very nice called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm and I suppose in theory we could ask her to do admin tasks <pause dur="short"/> erm but she's not kind of officially ours and the point was that we had enough so that we'd be a self-contained unit which is sort of not really working at the minute</u>
<u n="506" who="S0179">well no because you'd be one member of staff might be down and you have twenty-five per cent of the <unclear/></u>
<u n="507" who="S0058">exactly yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah the idea being that it would be enough people to get all the admin stuff done but also work at yeah full full capacity erm which isn't really the case anymore so I don't know if we could include maybe ask the PAs to do something</u>
<u n="508" who="S0179"><unclear/> anyway <unclear/> talking about</u>
<u n="509" who="S0058">erm jobs <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm <unclear/> people</u>
<u n="510" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0058">Rugby rugby <pause dur="short"/> erm I was watching some cookery show and there was like you know sort of getting them to the public to share recipes and this woman had one <unclear/> soup but she just <unclear/> dodgy</u>
<u n="512" who="S0179">yes short answer <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0058">yeah no I don't know this part of the world <pause dur="short"/> not even this week</u>
<u n="514" who="S0179"><unclear/> so what if you</u>
<u n="515" who="S0058">it is more you know the sort of estate market</u>
<u n="516" who="S0179"><unclear/> seventies half the cars are Volvos ninety per cent of those would be seventies</u>
<u n="517" who="S0058">wow</u>
<u n="518" who="S0179">very popular <unclear/> mix of being out there <pause dur="short"/> cars</u>
<u n="519" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0179">incredible</u>
<u n="521" who="S0058">but then if you were living in Sweden though would you feel the need to buy I don't know like a Golf just to be different?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="523" who="S0058" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Would you be happy with that <unclear/> performance?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0179">well it's not performance it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="525" who="S0058" trans="overlap">buying the best car</u>
<u n="526" who="S0179">because they're good</u>
<u n="527" who="S0058">I guess so yeah</u>
<u n="528" who="S0179" trans="overlap">like the Swedes have clearly realised</u>
<u n="529" who="S0058">the Swedes are right</u>
<u n="530" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="531" who="S0058">oh sorry</u>
<u n="532" who="S0179">but yes they are <pause dur="short"/> it's just sort of factual <pause dur="short"/> I mean <unclear/> have produced Saab but no one has really seemed to buy Saabs</u>
<u n="533" who="S0058">that's interesting yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0179">which is kind of funny</u>
<u n="535" who="S0058">Saab are shutting though aren't they?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="537" who="S0058">Saab are shutting or they have shut?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0179">month ago yeah</u>
<u n="539" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0179">well done for the <unclear/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0058">I don't follow the car market avidly</u>
<u n="542" who="S0179">current affairs <unclear/> it would have been in the news fairly prominently</u>
<u n="543" who="S0058">no I read it in <unclear/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0179"><unclear/> only a few dozen of <unclear/> carmakers</u>
<u n="545" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="546" who="S0179">when one of them shuts it's still fairly big news</u>
<u n="547" who="S0058">well definitely I mean I suppose the problem is if I don't look at the BBC website for a few days because I'm busy at lunchtime I end up missing loads of news</u>
<u n="548" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="549" who="S0058">and as it's fairly large news <pause dur="short"/> I love how <unclear/> was mentioned in our book</u>
<u n="550" who="S0179">that wasn't me</u>
<u n="551" who="S0058">the <unclear/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0179">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="553" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> I'm wondering how you'll find out what films are on?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0179">paper</u>
<u n="555" who="S0058">yeah true actually yeah <pause dur="short"/> because the whole</u>
<u n="556" who="S0179">you won't know what what time they're on</u>
<u n="557" who="S0058">no but it'll give us a better idea and I don't know if there's nothing on anywhere in the country that we fancy seeing is there?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0179">I mean I have the iPad but the 3G contract <unclear/> and of course you can't get data without <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit short-sighted and they should give you</u>
<u n="559" who="S0058">it's very short-sighted</u>
<u n="560" who="S0179">a full capacity to do that</u>
<u n="561" who="S0058">yeah the capacity to get on and say you want it because otherwise it's yeah it's limited in its usefulness I think</u>
<u n="562" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> you might be able to <unclear/></u>
<u n="563" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> because who would kind of <pause dur="short"/> is that the iPad that's sort of at fault there? So I'm not really sure how</u>
<u n="564" who="S0179">no it's not worth the mobile <unclear/></u>
<u n="565" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="566" who="S0179">because the hardware would connect you to the signal and it's just a question of</u>
<u n="567" who="S0058">yeah whether they'll let you connect to it <pause dur="short"/> no I mean they should and it would be make more sense because you're going to get more business if they let you get on to connect that you connect in order to connect</u>
<u n="568" who="S0179">I'd assume</u>
<u n="569" who="S0058">well it's not if you're a trade you can connect to the Wi-Fi in order to log-on</u>
<u n="570" who="S0179">well exactly</u>
<u n="571" who="S0058">and to pay your money like it seems daft to not have the not be able to do that <pause dur="short"/> because it's very keenly <unclear/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0179">I think it encourages you to take them out even if you may not need it</u>
<u n="573" who="S0058">yeah and maybe that's the thinking yeah sort of erm just thinking <unclear/></u>
<u n="574" who="S0179"><unclear/> up for the day actually just sort of <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's also now because it doesn't the credit card details so you have to re-enter them every time</u>
<u n="575" who="S0058">does it always say <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="577" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="578" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="579" who="S0058">God <pause dur="short"/> I I don't really <trunc>under</trunc> I don't know how he was talking about all this fancy gadgetry Wi-Fi and I was like can you imagine to put the iPod on the dock? Oh</u>
<u n="580" who="S0179">no you can't and that's the thing</u>
<u n="581" who="S0058">yeah and the answer was no and I was like oh <pause dur="short"/> you can't just buy a cheap dock that you can put the iPod on</u>
<u n="582" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0058"><unclear/> speakers</u>
<u n="584" who="S0179"><unclear/> a service station <unclear/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0058">popular</u>
<u n="586" who="S0179">oh yeah they're very popular there's a  there's a  waiting list</u>
<u n="587" who="S0058">oh right <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="588" who="S0179">they're not actually that expensive either</u>
<u n="589" who="S0058">oh you're so in love with <unclear/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0179">no I'm not objectively I don't want one myself</u>
<u n="591" who="S0058" trans="overlap">well who would want a massive? That's quite creepy</u>
<u n="592" who="S0179">what's creepy is it's falling over</u>
<u n="593" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh that's really scary</u>
<u n="594" who="S0179" trans="overlap">I mean that's a bit of an issue</u>
<u n="595" who="S0058">I don't like that that's weird</u>
<u n="596" who="S0179">you don't like your <unclear/></u>
<u n="597" who="S0058">that reminds me of the massive marshmallow man in erm Ghostbusters</u>
<u n="598" who="S0179">I've never seen that</u>
<u n="599" who="S0058">I haven't seen it either but I've seen it's kind of an iconic scene where <unclear/> trampling through New York <pause dur="short"/> anyway erm yeah I don't you you don't even need a dock and you can get some speakers that'll plug into the top of your iPod like <unclear/> the solutions</u>
<u n="600" who="S0179">well the iPod has got a speaker in it</u>
<u n="601" who="S0058">has an iPod?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0179">yeah the Touches they've got <unclear/> speakers</u>
<u n="603" who="S0058">have they? So in fact</u>
<u n="604" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="605" who="S0058">I just can't help thinking that the options of spend seventy pounds spend two hundred pounds and I'm like well yes</u>
<u n="606" who="S0179">or just</u>
<u n="607" who="S0058">or</u>
<u n="608" who="S0179">use your existing one and just learn to use it</u>
<u n="609" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just learn to use it if you want to slash buy some speakers</u>
<u n="610" who="S0179">but no if there's an option to <unclear/> by spending money on it</u>
<u n="611" who="S0058">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0179">or just trying harder for about five minutes</u>
<u n="613" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I I didn't want to be too obvious you know but I'll just be like why? Why can I not just why does it need to be wireless surely <pause dur="short"/> never mind <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if I was missing something critical but yeah</u>
<u n="614" who="S0179">no just dad</u>
<u n="615" who="S0058">you really should stop suggesting that he buys a laptop <pause dur="short"/> your mum is going to get so pissed off if he buys a laptop</u>
<u n="616" who="S0179" trans="overlap">I'm I'm kind of teasing him</u>
<u n="617" who="S0058">I know but the thing is he'll get the idea in his head and he'll buy a laptop and your mum will be so annoyed</u>
<u n="618" who="S0179" trans="overlap">I've had the idea in my head for ages but I did I have actually been in touch with him and we did this when we were at the final stage of when we were just buying a kettle I think</u>
<u n="619" who="S0058">right</u>
<u n="620" who="S0179">and you know to buy that specific one which was quite an effort <unclear/> a bit specific one <pause dur="short"/> but I'm very pleased we did because that was by far the nicest one there</u>
<u n="621" who="S0058">it's very nice</u>
<u n="622" who="S0179">but you know the issue was that so we were in this erm as I say he was looking at laptops in Dixons or <unclear/> or whatever <pause dur="short"/> comet sorry Comet <pause dur="short"/> and it was erm dad you don't need a laptop but mum wants it to use Windows on <pause dur="short"/> no she's happy with Windows on the iMac <pause dur="short"/> no but she says <pause dur="short"/> no she didn't you are imagining that you just want it <pause dur="short"/> so but no one else is using the iMac</u>
<u n="623" who="S0058">no exactly</u>
<u n="624" who="S0179">stop it</u>
<u n="625" who="S0058">I don't think he likes the idea of her using it sort of wrongly <pause dur="short"/> and booting it in Windows and I don't think he's massively keen on <pause dur="short"/> she did say she doesn't like sitting in the chair because it's too low for her varifocals in order to see the screen properly or something like that in that weird chair</u>
<u n="626" who="S0179">yeah <unclear/> the chair but <unclear/></u>
<u n="627" who="S0058" trans="overlap">exactly yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah all of that your mum wants one but she really doesn't <pause dur="short"/> she she's not that keen <pause dur="short"/> do you think you'd buy a MacBook?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0179">I think I'm too old to <unclear/> But it is well they're just nice pieces of hardware</u>
<u n="629" who="S0058">oh that's the thing they're lovely</u>
<u n="630" who="S0179">and there's no reason that <unclear/></u>
<u n="631" who="S0058">yeah that's a permanent thing then</u>
<u n="632" who="S0179">oh okay</u>
<u n="633" who="S0058">it's been there the last couple of times we've been down and I think it must just be parked there as an advert</u>
<u n="634" who="S0179">but occasionally move it just so as to <unclear/></u>
<u n="635" who="S0058">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> like erm <unclear/> they occasionally just move it up er Cranmer Road a bit <pause dur="short"/> so bad</u>
<u n="636" who="S0179">even if one of the colleges was trying to get it removed and the ulterior for that is</u>
<u n="637" who="S0058">oh I'm sure they have</u>
<u n="638" who="S0179">just <unclear/> is virtually never open</u>
<u n="639" who="S0058">no well that's the weird thing it's just part of it <pause dur="short"/> it has you know <unclear/> both bought things from there but you know it does open but</u>
<u n="640" who="S0179">no I once bought something for my first year</u>
<u n="641" who="S0058">yeah I bought a kind of Fanta from there and then looked at it and it was erm it had a writing on it I didn't recognise the alphabet and I and it was a brighter colour orange than I'd seen Fanta before and I thought I'm not sure I should be really very sure what to drink this <pause dur="short"/> so I just threw it out <pause dur="short"/> ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> it just looked wrong you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="643" who="S0058">because like it erm it looked a bit like Fanta in Swaziland which language has chemicals in it which are banned in England <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="644" who="S0179">but you drank it there?</u>
<u n="645" who="S0058">I drank it there yeah</u>
<u n="646" who="S0179">and look what it did to you</u>
<u n="647" who="S0058">exactly <pause dur="short"/> but erm yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> what was I going to say?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0179">I don't know <unclear/></u>
<u n="649" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I imagine the college has tried to get something done about it but presumably they can't so long as it's just parking and moving up and down</u>
<u n="650" who="S0179">but I was er <pause dur="short"/> oh thinking of college I was reading the financial policy and you know thanks to rigorous cost control measures we're actually not doing that badly including pay and bonus freezes for staff</u>
<u n="651" who="S0058">shit</u>
<u n="652" who="S0179">and I said hah alright that's why the porters must be pissed off</u>
<u n="653" who="S0058">oh dear-y me <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="654" who="S0179">it's like because we don't think of the college as an employer but of course it is</u>
<u n="655" who="S0058">it is yeah</u>
<u n="656" who="S0179">it's kind of a big employer</u>
<u n="657" who="S0058">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="658" who="S0179">it must employ fifty people and</u>
<u n="659" who="S0058">and yeah you've got <pause dur="short"/> I mean I guess it's a very odd thing to be on the other side of it and see all these students running around and then know that you're not your pay isn't going to go up this year</u>
<u n="660" who="S0179"><unclear/> also now that the students are now paying through the nose <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="661" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I guess that makes it easier</u>
<u n="662" who="S0179">yeah it is interesting and it worked out that the full cost of us educating an average Cambridge student is about eighteen thousand pounds <pause dur="short"/> so in reality it's sort of heavens</u>
<u n="663" who="S0058">yeah <trunc>e</trunc> exactly you're not paying through the nose but er</u>
<u n="664" who="S0179">well you are but</u>
<u n="665" who="S0058">well you are but it's it depends how you look at it really</u>
<u n="666" who="S0179">well <unclear/> university <unclear/> university is hugely wealthy</u>
<u n="667" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="668" who="S0179">in itself</u>
<u n="669" who="S0058">yes <pause dur="short"/> I think yeah I mean I think the idea is that the they need to kind of gather large large amounts of funding just so that they can afford to teach people which is what they want to do you know <pause dur="short"/> people complain about massively wealthy universities but actually you know it's</u>
<u n="670" who="S0179">well it's just <unclear/> generation that needs to</u>
<u n="671" who="S0058">yeah it needs to examine</u>
<u n="672" who="S0179">essentially the entire thing is giving a wage out</u>
<u n="673" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but erm</u>
<u n="674" who="S0179">but <unclear/> there should be a sort of <pause dur="short"/> I mean because there is currently a as it were Robin Hood tax amongst the colleges but it should be much greater</u>
<u n="675" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I agree <pause dur="short"/> I agree</u>
<u n="676" who="S0179">so it's not <pause dur="short"/> because it does this does essentially effect the level of tuition the students get but it's not <pause dur="short"/> there are to go in to different colleges to have massive swings and roundabouts <unclear/> space at all</u>
<u n="677" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> no they're not and it's very much apply to the college you like the look of and it doesn't make a difference but it no really does and <trunc>y</trunc> yeah it's not</u>
<u n="678" who="S0179">so for example if you're an art student and you don't want a long walk you should apply to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="679" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="680" who="S0179">if you want to er if you're going to do astronomy at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> if you're a lesbian applying to <unclear/> you know under no circumstances apply to <anon type="place"/> erm</u>
<u n="681" who="S0058">well I I think yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="682" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/> apply to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="683" who="S0058">if you hate social contact apply <anon type="place"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="684" who="S0179">if you you know if you wanted to go to a big ball every year apply to <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="685" who="S0058"><anon type="place"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> if you want to play rugby with idiots <unclear/> go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="686" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="687" who="S0058">and like it should be made clearer that there's differences and</u>
<u n="688" who="S0179">some colleges <unclear/></u>
<u n="689" who="S0058">in terms of financial support in gyms exactly facilities <pause dur="short"/> in fact you know book grants and there's no <unclear/></u>
<u n="690" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="691" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="692" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0058">yeah you can get book grants at the colleges</u>
<u n="694" who="S0179">wow</u>
<u n="695" who="S0058">which colleges can give their students however much a year towards books? You know it's unheard of at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="696" who="S0179">but we should also make it very clear that if you go into a central college you will spend most of your time living off site</u>
<u n="697" who="S0058">yes exactly</u>
<u n="698" who="S0179">and</u>
<u n="699" who="S0058">there's so many differences</u>
<u n="700" who="S0179">and you won't get accommodation in the fourth year if you're on a four-year course</u>
<u n="701" who="S0058">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="702" who="S0179">in which <unclear/> So it's you know massive swings and roundabouts and and but it is you should be told about this</u>
<u n="703" who="S0058">I entirely agree yeah it's</u>
<u n="704" who="S0179">and access doesn't do that because it would actually then it would seem to apply and the college's decision is important <unclear/></u>
<u n="705" who="S0058">yeah it is evidently it is <pause dur="short"/> but then you need to emphasise you know if it doesn't matter where you apply because if you're good enough you'll get in because of the closed system so that's why they they kind of shy away from that <pause dur="short"/> and they just <unclear/> pick the one that you think is prettiest</u>
<u n="706" who="S0179">reducing stress</u>
<u n="707" who="S0058">and exactly reducing the stress and the amount of <pause dur="short"/> and then of course yeah you can't you obviously can't publish if you're a rugby idiot going to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> they can't say that</u>
<u n="708" who="S0179">but you you know if you're savvy you'll look at the public school ratios</u>
<u n="709" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm and you also get to talk to students I think is what you know the the last point like people who are in the know can do that but if you're just from some random state school and you really don't know how to go about it the visual access policy</u>
<u n="710" who="S0179">it's useless</u>
<u n="711" who="S0058">it's yeah if it's not helpful in terms of getting that inside look erm</u>
<u n="712" who="S0179">but the thing on <anon type="place"/>'s website is useless I mean</u>
<u n="713" who="S0058">it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="714" who="S0179">there's a couple of like a couple of like so which college has a decent gym? But that <unclear/> useful information</u>
<u n="715" who="S0058">yeah that's quite a privilege <unclear/></u>
<u n="716" who="S0179">but but that's not actually helping people <pause dur="short"/> none of it has been what it's targeted at which is helping</u>
<u n="717" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="718" who="S0179">disadvantaged students get even a more even footing <pause dur="short"/> it'd just be</u>
<u n="719" who="S0058">none of it has been erm I'm applying for English I have no English teacher at my school can you tell me a little bit about what the interview is going to be like so I can compare <pause dur="short"/> it's all</u>
<u n="720" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="721" who="S0058">it it's not about that it's being like</u>
<u n="722" who="S0179" trans="overlap">it's just trivia</u>
<u n="723" who="S0058">yes it's trivia it's a lot of it isn't from people in this country</u>
<u n="724" who="S0179">yeah which isn't what it's designed for</u>
<u n="725" who="S0058">it's not what it's <trunc>desi</trunc> exactly it's <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="726" who="S0179">when it's badly written and</u>
<u n="727" who="S0058">and some of it's just for people who think well you don't need to know that</u>
<u n="728" who="S0179">well I think one was what's the best motorway route from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="729" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="730" who="S0179">and I think I'm <unclear/> access work been so literal</u>
<u n="731" who="S0058">yeah nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's just ridiculous that's not</u>
<u n="732" who="S0179">who gives a shit?</u>
<u n="733" who="S0058">it's stupid</u>
<u n="734" who="S0179">you know look on Google apps</u>
<u n="735" who="S0058">yeah well exactly it's it's not TAZ's job to field questions like that <pause dur="short"/> she should be fielding questions like</u>
<u n="736" who="S0179">more to the point</u>
<u n="737" who="S0058">erm what can I do about</u>
<u n="738" who="S0179">she should be making sure she's getting questions like that and she's not</u>
<u n="739" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="740" who="S0179">she's getting questions yeah but not the right sort of questions</u>
<u n="741" who="S0058">well with the whole service is being kind of advertised and sort of made available how who knows about it you know? It's a good service and <trunc>i</trunc> in principle it's a really good idea</u>
<u n="742" who="S0179">but if you Google <anon type="place"/> I'm sure you would find it</u>
<u n="743" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="744" who="S0179">but how many people know to Google <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0058">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="746" who="S0179">you know I'm sure she's doing lots of initiatives but how many of those are actually doing <unclear/></u>
<u n="747" who="S0058">they're targeting the right people I guess because yeah this is just it's stupid it's not <pause dur="short"/> if these are serious concerns that are affecting access</u>
<u n="748" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/> access is nothing to do with university it is to do with schools</u>
<u n="749" who="S0058">schools</u>
<u n="750" who="S0179">and the education a child receives</u>
<u n="751" who="S0058" trans="overlap">and and the <trunc>g</trunc> general attitude of the school is critical and some schools have a very bad approach and you know they should be going to schools and teaching headmasters and headmistresses and head teachers <pause dur="short"/> sorry <pause dur="short"/> and teachers and <anon type="place"/> coordinators and they should be teaching the heads</u>
<u n="752" who="S0179">but that's not what we're doing and that's</u>
<u n="753" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="754" who="S0179"><unclear/> but but not even that it's <unclear/> be doing with schools should just be <unclear/> but it's not just <pause dur="short"/> but so much of it isn't about that it's about so what GCSE choices are you making and what A-level choices are you taking?</u>
<u n="755" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yes yeah <pause dur="short"/> don't take these A-levels that you will not get into <anon type="place"/> with these A-levels they're no good to you</u>
<u n="756" who="S0179" trans="overlap">that's really weird because that sign</u>
<u n="757" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="758" who="S0179">the round circle with a red outline means no vehicular access</u>
<u n="759" who="S0058">which is wrong</u>
<u n="760" who="S0179">which is very very bizarre and they really should get that fixed</u>
<u n="761" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so it is it's a mistake is it? Or either one with the faded?</u>
<u n="762" who="S0179" trans="overlap">no it it was in the thirties but worn off</u>
<u n="763" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="764" who="S0179">but that current technically if you obey that road sign as read you'd stop</u>
<u n="765" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yes you'd stop <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's quite bad</u>
<u n="766" who="S0179">yeah that's what I thought</u>
<u n="767" who="S0058">but no I agree I think erm the the the access is kind of it's so small scale and talking to individual students and I'm not sure</u>
<u n="768" who="S0179">that's just a piss take</u>
<u n="769" who="S0058">of you need to change</u>
<u n="770" who="S0179">yeah it looks good but it's doing fuck all</u>
<u n="771" who="S0058" trans="overlap">I mean I think yes it might make a difference in if one pupil from a disadvantaged school is involved in some kind of access or target scheme and goals and then they go back to their old school and say apply it's for the likes of us</u>
<u n="772" who="S0179">yes but that's different that that's giving them <pause dur="short"/> but if they're on a scheme like that that that's the job done</u>
<u n="773" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="774" who="S0179">they've already thought about it</u>
<u n="775" who="S0058">I guess so yeah</u>
<u n="776" who="S0179">a bit but that's not the people it should be targeting</u>
<u n="777" who="S0058">it's for people who the schools have seen oh you don't want to go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="778" who="S0179">yeah exactly but that again is a very small portion of the problem because fundamentally there isn't a problem and that's why you commented and I think</u>
<u n="779" who="S0058">well yeah I mean that's the thing</u>
<u n="780" who="S0179">but <anon type="place"/> actually has</u>
<u n="781" who="S0058">and I mean the media are really up in arms and it's like well actually</u>
<u n="782" who="S0179">you know <anon type="place"/> has to be the best-est in in the world</u>
<u n="783" who="S0058">it really does it's incredibly <unclear/></u>
<u n="784" who="S0179" trans="overlap">it's far better than the American system and the fact that really annoys me is The Times is writing it so it boosted <unclear/> the article about how sort of an applicant at <anon type="place"/> was saying that you know the system is much better there and they're much more interested in you as an all-round individual rather than just what you can bring to a subject</u>
<u n="785" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="786" who="S0179">and like that's why I've got two problems with that <pause dur="short"/> the first one is you're seriously joking as in you are going to be elite <unclear/> <anon type="place"/> <unclear/> best academic institution in the world and yeah what relevance does that have? You can be a sociopath that's fine</u>
<u n="787" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's an academic institution I agree</u>
<u n="788" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/> you have the ability to interact with your classmates and your supervisors</u>
<u n="789" who="S0058">and and your academic context if you can interact in an academic setting</u>
<u n="790" who="S0179">yeah but it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="791" who="S0058">and that's all that matters surely? Obviously if you can't interact in an academic setting that's different</u>
<u n="792" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="793" who="S0058">if you were a genius but you can't express it that's no good</u>
<u n="794" who="S0179">so but you know</u>
<u n="795" who="S0058"><unclear/></u>
<u n="796" who="S0179">that is  that is  almost relevant</u>
<u n="797" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="798" who="S0179">you know you shouldn't get be a <pause dur="short"/> you know if that's <unclear/> just be to relax you</u>
<u n="799" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="800" who="S0179">there's no other relevance to that <pause dur="short"/> the second problem is <anon type="place"/> yeah but it was the question and it was literally asked erm of what's his name? Erm Oceans? The guy <unclear/></u>
<u n="801" who="S0058">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="802" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="803" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0179"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was asked on an interview so erm so when I was there actually he was telling someone erm</u>
<u n="805" who="S0058">I like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="806" who="S0179">yeah but he was asked at the end of his talk that we had <unclear/> open day</u>
<u n="807" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="808" who="S0179">erm er er a guy out of of <unclear/> said erm if I was to donate a million pounds to a department would it help my daughter's chances of getting an offer? He was literally</u>
<u n="809" who="S0058">wow</u>
<u n="810" who="S0179">asked that question and the answer was no sir <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="811" who="S0058">well yeah my response would have been if you would like to donate a million pounds the department we would be extremely grateful it will not have any relevance at all to your daughter's application but please a million pounds is great thanks very much</u>
<u n="812" who="S0179">but the thing that was that at Harvard that would make a difference</u>
<u n="813" who="S0058">it would yes that's <unclear/> yes</u>
<u n="814" who="S0179">that would make a huge difference</u>
<u n="815" who="S0058">I think that's the problem if you can take</u>
<u n="816" who="S0179">and the fact that there's a sliding scale so if you can pay the interest <unclear/> actually pretty low</u>
<u n="817" who="S0058">yeah if you can pay you're in and if you can't pay you've got to be quite good</u>
<u n="818" who="S0179">yeah and it wouldn't</u>
<u n="819" who="S0058">and that doesn't seem right</u>
<u n="820" who="S0179">and it's actually saying and the BBC was actually saying yeah this is a good system <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="821" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="822" who="S0179">how possibly? And you're judging <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="823" who="S0058"><anon type="place"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="824" who="S0179">of being elitist</u>
<u n="825" who="S0058">yeah I'm sorry</u>
<u n="826" who="S0179">fuck off</u>
<u n="827" who="S0058">you you know yes there's still a kind of a <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean like we're saying there's no point</u>
<u n="828" who="S0179">there'll always be a higher ratio of people from public schools because oddly enough two reasons firstly public schools are selective <pause dur="short"/> secondly intelligent is to some extent inherited</u>
<u n="829" who="S0058">well I was just going to say that if you've been taught well and properly for your entire school career in small classes</u>
<u n="830" who="S0179">of course you're going</u>
<u n="831" who="S0058">you're probably more confident and more and and talk better <pause dur="short"/> whereas if you really haven't ever been taught properly</u>
<u n="832" who="S0179" trans="overlap">well no just leaving that aside assuming the standard of teaching was the same which it is obviously because people pay <unclear/> on average better <pause dur="short"/> they select who they take and that means people who won't get five GCSEs don't go that's half the population out of a job already</u>
<u n="833" who="S0058">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> whereas state schools they have you know they take everyone so people who really yeah aren't going to do very well go to state schools <unclear/></u>
<u n="834" who="S0179" trans="overlap">so if you wanted to you know the only meaningful comparison would be between <unclear/> as a percentage between grammar schools and private schools</u>
<u n="835" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="836" who="S0179">that would be a meaningful thing and anywhere with selective entry</u>
<u n="837" who="S0058" trans="overlap">because <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="838" who="S0179">rather than you know if this is</u>
<u n="839" who="S0058" trans="overlap">I think selective entry free and selective entry appealing is an interesting</u>
<u n="840" who="S0179">A lot of state schools you know are getting what two million and in some cases as low as twenty per cent of people getting five As and A stars and Cs</u>
<u n="841" who="S0058">well yeah <anon type="place"/> was about twenty per cent</u>
<u n="842" who="S0179">yeah so that's an eighty per cent of people who just you know unless</u>
<u n="843" who="S0058">they can't do it</u>
<u n="844" who="S0179"><unclear/> seeing ninety per cent of people who won't do A-levels</u>
<u n="845" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="846" who="S0179">because just to get you <unclear/> get them to A-level <pause dur="short"/> so if ninety per cent of schools are doing A-levels versus at a school where there's no way you would get in unless you were going to get good A-levels <pause dur="short"/> what the fuck do you think is going to happen?</u>
<u n="847" who="S0058">exactly</u>
<u n="848" who="S0179">and you just you'd just be an incredible ignorance of people and the media playing up to people</u>
<u n="849" who="S0058">well I know but most people think that selecting people for academic students on the basis of academic ability is elitist</u>
<u n="850" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="851" who="S0058">an elitism in a negative sense not in a sense of any <trunc>sys</trunc> as in <pause dur="short"/> so yeah it's easier if you're picking the England football team right? And in order to make it not elitist you decide to pick people who aren't very good at football for the England football team</u>
<u n="852" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="853" who="S0058">people don't think about it like this like</u>
<u n="854" who="S0179">but that's because most people are very stupid</u>
<u n="855" who="S0058">I think it's because university hasn't is is stopped to be synonymous with academia <pause dur="short"/> does that make sense?</u>
<u n="856" who="S0179">yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="857" who="S0058">there's a  there's a  yeah there's a disconnection exactly <pause dur="short"/> it's a  it's a  progression so like rather than a an academic <pause dur="short"/> I think we very much think of it as an academic <unclear/></u>
<u n="858" who="S0179">sorry can I just finish off what I was saying back then?</u>
<u n="859" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="860" who="S0179"><unclear/> because the other half of that problem is that people leave aside the genetic intelligence which is an issue as in you know you cannot deny that intelligence is to some extent genetic <pause dur="short"/> it's a combination of both upbringing and what you've inherited</u>
<u n="861" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="862" who="S0179">it's just</u>
<u n="863" who="S0058">I agree with that yeah your ability</u>
<u n="864" who="S0179">as are every other personality character</u>
<u n="865" who="S0058">yeah I was going to say all everything is genetic like your ability in sports</u>
<u n="866" who="S0179"><unclear/> Exactly and that's fine</u>
<u n="867" who="S0058">is partially determined by their genes</u>
<u n="868" who="S0179">but it's unacceptable to say that you know</u>
<u n="869" who="S0058">yeah but you can't say</u>
<u n="870" who="S0179">both parents have got an IQ of point six you're not going to produce a child who is <unclear/> but it's just not going to happen <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="871" who="S0058">but mind you with genetics</u>
<u n="872" who="S0179">no it won't it's almost I'd say that's pretty much an impossibility er and <pause dur="short"/> right he has opened the gate however</u>
<u n="873" who="S0058">excellent <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm going to have to pause this rant</u>
<u n="874" who="S0179">that's fine <pause dur="short"/> but yeah the issue of course is that  is that  erm quite apart from the genetic issue people middle-class parents who have achieved as a result of their own <trunc>ed</trunc> education value education and they want their child to go to school <unclear/> schools are a beneficial exercise</u>
<u n="875" who="S0058">if your parents don't want you to go to school you're probably not going to go to Cambridge are you?</u>
<u n="876" who="S0179">well no if you  if you  don't value education you won't accept it and that's another problem with the whole system is that you can't force an education on someone <pause dur="short"/> you can give them the opportunity but if they don't achieve not in terms of <pause dur="short"/> well <unclear/> a significant proportion of the time it will be down to them not accepting it and you can't do anything about that <pause dur="short"/> well I've seen some fairly non-academic people achieve a lot for them and on the other hand I've seen people who probably are reasonably intelligent not give a shit <pause dur="short"/> and so part is the government's fault <pause dur="short"/> no I'm sorry you do just <pause dur="short"/> people won't <pause dur="short"/> you know if you grow up in a council estate and neither your parents will work you will not achieve in life and that's not the government's fault that's you should have</u>
<u n="877" who="S0058">well I think you can I think the problem is I think you can achieve in life if you're in that situation</u>
<u n="878" who="S0179" trans="overlap">I'll tell  you why</u>
<u n="879" who="S0058">if if you then refused to take part in anything that's a different matter but I don't think it's a case of saying you won't so I'm not going to bother to teach</u>
<u n="880" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah but you can't you <pause dur="short"/> no no exactly and they don't</u>
<u n="881" who="S0058">I think it's it's you said okay both parents are from a council estate and it's pointless spending money on your own education because you're not going to achieve anything and that's obviously</u>
<u n="882" who="S0179">well no but that's not what's done</u>
<u n="883" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="884" who="S0179">by anyone</u>
</body>
</text>
