<text id="SMEG">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:01:26</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-28</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>5</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0018 S0036 S0048 S0066 S0067</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Lakeside Interiors family business, Birmingham</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Shops / small businesses, online commerce, scams, hairdressing, health / illness, work, family, fast food</topics>
		<activity>Members of a family business chatting at the back of the shop.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T20</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0036">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>49 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0048">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Glasgow</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Scotland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Scotland</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Scottish</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>25 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>scotland</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>scotland</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>scotland</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Shop assistant</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>7</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0066">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>48 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Small business owner</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>4</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0067">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>46 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Small business owner</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>4</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0036">has the computer got to pick this up in this?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0018">sorry?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0036">has the computer got to pick pick this up or does somebody sit and listen to it and?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0018">do you know what <pause dur="short"/> I don't actually know <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure cos erm I imagine voice recognition technology nowadays is very advanced</u>
<u n="5" who="S0036" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> you can't imagine somebody actually sort of sitting going through it can you though</u>
<u n="6" who="S0018">I know it must be a a very painstaking job if they have to</u>
<u n="7" who="S0036">mm</u>
<u n="8" who="S0018">but mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah no isn't it a beautiful day?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0036">yeah <pause dur="short"/> lovely yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0018">oh I wish it would last forever <pause dur="short"/> england when it's sunny <pause dur="short"/> it's such a nice place isn't it?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0036">yeah yeah it's lovely</u>
<u n="12" who="S0018" trans="overlap">did you  Did you  have a good weekend? Did you enjoy the sun?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0036" trans="overlap">erm <trunc>y</trunc> well we we er were here Saturday all day so erm that's erm and it was quiet so that's just feels like it's just a waste of time really <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> didn't you get some chairs out the front and sunbathe?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0036" trans="overlap">no no no we thought about it because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got a bench out of the garage and er we thought erm maybe we might find time to put it outside and get an ice cream but didn't happen <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="16" who="S0018">oh no were you busy?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0036">no not really</u>
<u n="18" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0036">that's what's so annoying cos when it's really sunny and it's not that busy and you're not really doing anything you just think oh you know you open all day for nothing but</u>
<u n="20" who="S0018">mm they'll be at home <pause dur="short"/> I guess everybody's enjoying the weather <pause dur="short"/> they're not out buying things and</u>
<u n="21" who="S0036" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> no  no it's been  no it's been like that all week <pause dur="short"/> it was like I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what was it like yesterday? And he said no really quiet <pause dur="short"/> but it's worrying because you you know we're a shop and you know we need people coming in</u>
<u n="22" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0036">Cos you do you know if it's quiet we've still you've still got to pay all the overheads</u>
<u n="24" who="S0018">definitely</u>
<u n="25" who="S0036">so it is worrying <pause dur="short"/> I worry all my time <pause dur="short"/> I wake up in the middle of the night in cold sweat thinking oh God you know</u>
<u n="26" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh no <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0036">it's horrible but what can you do?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0018">yeah no I get that sometimes you waking up and worrying and your brain won't stop and</u>
<u n="29" who="S0036">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0018">gosh <pause dur="short"/> so you want  you want  the the bad weather so that people get <unclear/> get stuff done?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah they don't necessarily come out in bad weather either I don't think <pause dur="short"/> I don't think you can erm that's the thing at the moment <pause dur="short"/> that's what's so worrying about it <pause dur="short"/> is that you can't like <trunc>s</trunc> even begin to start to figure out what's going on because it's you know you can have a really really busy day and then it will just be really dead for a couple of weeks and erm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0036">you know you can't <trunc>p</trunc> you can't erm second guess it <pause dur="short"/> and you don't like now at the moment like it's just gone really really quiet and it probably is the good weather</u>
<u n="34" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0036">but you don't know when that's going to end and when are people going to come out again and?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0036">you know and if that's like going to be if this continues <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's Easter next week and which I hadn't realised that it was Easter next week</u>
<u n="38" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh huh <pause dur="short"/> is it next <trunc>Fri</trunc>?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0036">it's next Friday's Good Friday <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>d</trunc> I hadn't even erm realised</u>
<u n="40" who="S0018">we're still in March aren't we?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0036">mm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0018">okay so it's next <pause dur="short"/> is it a bank holiday weekend?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0036">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0018">the Friday and the Monday</u>
<u n="45" who="S0036">well of course Easter's always quiet anyway so then you think well okay so <trunc>the</trunc> there's gong to be that two weeks which you can probably more or less write off</u>
<u n="46" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mhm</u>
<u n="47" who="S0036">and then if the good weather continues after that I don't know it's just  it's just  I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I think everybody just thinks it's hunky dorey having your own business and that <pause dur="short"/> oh it must be great having your own business and you're loaded <pause dur="short"/> no it's just not like that</u>
<u n="48" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0036">it's not like that <pause dur="short"/> it's hard all the time</u>
<u n="50" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos you are you're at the you're the victim of random events as you say if nobody comes in</u>
<u n="51" who="S0036" trans="overlap">and just you know everybody knows that the people are struggling and you know like small independent retailers they're like struggling and all that</u>
<u n="52" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0036">and then like we had the rates bill and the rates have gone up and</u>
<u n="54" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0036">it's like <trunc>s</trunc> I mean I don't know exactly cos when I phoned them up they even they couldn't tell me the the exact figures for last year and that but I worked it out based on what she told me and it's a six and a half percent increase <pause dur="short"/> six and a half percent <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's huge isn't it <pause dur="short"/> that's a huge hike</u>
<u n="56" who="S0018" trans="overlap">that's so much <pause dur="short"/> all of my friends have been absolutely flabbergasted at how much the the all their bills have gone up just in the past  in the past  month</u>
<u n="57" who="S0036" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know so <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="58" who="S0018">Cos it was a cold winter as well everyone had their heating on all the time and they've been whacked with huge bills and</u>
<u n="59" who="S0036" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I know <unclear/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0018">where are people getting the money to pay for it? It's</u>
<u n="61" who="S0036">I know it's worrying</u>
<u n="62" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> and do you find that there's erm that you've lost a lot of business to the big  the big  commercial shops the shopping centres and?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0036">we we lose it to the erm internet <trunc>bec</trunc></u>
<u n="64" who="S0018" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0036">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos of the er wallpapers and the fabrics <pause dur="short"/> cos there's people that trade online that all they need is codes</u>
<u n="66" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="67" who="S0036">so they don't have to do anything <pause dur="short"/> they don't have any photos <pause dur="short"/> they don't have anything and they they they actually there's one website and it's just got on it on the first page erm go into your local shop and get the information and then come back to us and</u>
<u n="68" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="69" who="S0036">and of course you can't compete with it because they haven't got the overheads that we've got <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="70" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and have you thought of setting up your own online?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0036">yeah well we've just erm we've just got <trunc>s</trunc> Yell er erm we advertise with Yell and they've just started doing this website package thing <pause dur="short"/> this new thing <pause dur="short"/> she came to see us last week and erm and I've just opened up the emails and erm we've started to get the information through</u>
<u n="72" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="73" who="S0036">in fact we've just got the that's that's the first bill</u>
<u n="74" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0036">but it's good <pause dur="short"/> I mean it is a good price but how it's going to work I don't know</u>
<u n="76" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0036">because you need <pause dur="short"/> they say you need to be on the first two pages of Google <pause dur="short"/> well how can you all be on the first two pages of Google? It doesn't <pause dur="short"/> I mean I know they cycle round</u>
<u n="78" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0036">but if there's million of well you know e-commerce websites</u>
<u n="80" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0036">they can't <pause dur="short"/> how <trunc>o</trunc> how often are they all getting on the first two pages? And how long are they on it for if it's? I don't understand how it works really but</u>
<u n="82" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0036">so but we are going to try and do that but I don't know</u>
<u n="84" who="S0018">and how about on eBay?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0036">yeah we thought about eBay but erm there's certain restrictions with certain erm people that we deal with</u>
<u n="86" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0036">and er and also me not <pause dur="short"/> my understanding of eBay is you you have to have the stock <pause dur="short"/> that's an eBay rule that you have to have the stock</u>
<u n="88" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="89" who="S0036">so then what do you buy? And what do you stock? And where do you stock it? And I mean it's always a nightmare in here</u>
<u n="90" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="91" who="S0036">and but we know that people on eBay don't do that <pause dur="short"/> so we know that for a fact</u>
<u n="92" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0036">yeah cos we try we tried to get some fabric once from a supplier and erm they'd sold out but somebody on E-Bay was advertising it so we thought well they must have the stock</u>
<u n="94" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0036">erm because you have to on eBay <pause dur="short"/> you're supposed to have the thing there to sell</u>
<u n="96" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0036">so erm we thought well we're going to have to get it <pause dur="short"/> we need it <pause dur="short"/> we need a couple of metres of this fabric so we contacted the er <pause dur="short"/> we went through eBay to get it and erm they said er they'd come back to us <pause dur="short"/> and then they came back to us and said it was out of stock because they were they haven't got it in stock <pause dur="short"/> they're ordering it from the company</u>
<u n="98" who="S0018">they're ordering it from the same company that you were ordering it from?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0036">yeah and the company <unclear/> I know</u>
<u n="100" who="S0018"><event desc="sound of gasping"/> Cheeky</u>
<u n="101" who="S0036">I know <pause dur="short"/> so then you feel like you want to contact eBay and say <pause dur="short"/> cos obviously they're undercutting everybody by huge amounts</u>
<u n="102" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0036">you feel like you want to contact eBay and say these people aren't operating within your rules</u>
<u n="104" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0036">because they haven't got the stock <pause dur="short"/> but who do you contact? They're faceless</u>
<u n="106" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0036">you you look and try and find a number for eBay</u>
<u n="108" who="S0018">mhm <pause dur="short"/> my dad had the same problem because they'd been receiving letters for erm random strangers <pause dur="short"/> so <trunc>obv</trunc> obviously someone who's trying to scam somebody is using our address</u>
<u n="109" who="S0036">yeah right</u>
<u n="110" who="S0018">to <trunc>u</trunc> to do the scams and they're in debt to eBay <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how many hundreds of pounds</u>
<u n="111" who="S0036">oh really</u>
<u n="112" who="S0018">but they got he got as letter from a debt collecting agency saying that they were going to come round and collect the money for this random that we don't know</u>
<u n="113" who="S0036">yeah yeah right</u>
<u n="114" who="S0018">through E-Bay <pause dur="short"/> and Dad was was trying to contact eBay and trying to get confirmation that you know E-Bay could prove that it wasn't him</u>
<u n="115" who="S0036">yeah right</u>
<u n="116" who="S0018">but no <pause dur="short"/> nobody was answering and as you said they're faceless</u>
<u n="117" who="S0036" trans="overlap">no no <pause dur="short"/> he managed to get a number though <pause dur="short"/> that's good if he managed to get a number because I can't even find any <pause dur="short"/> but I mean I gave <pause dur="short"/> you know I haven't got time to follow it up really</u>
<u n="118" who="S0018">yeah I know</u>
<u n="119" who="S0036">erm my er nephew erm he my sister's just had erm <pause dur="short"/> cos he lives with my sister <pause dur="short"/> erm a bill's through for Travel Lodge for my nephew</u>
<u n="120" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0036">my nephew's never stayed in Travel Lodge <pause dur="short"/> and whoever it was <pause dur="short"/> and I don't know how they do it but they'd obviously got my nephews name and address <pause dur="short"/> whether it was somebody he knows or what I don't know</u>
<u n="122" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="123" who="S0036">but basically they damaged the room <pause dur="short"/> so of course Travel Lodge are are billing my nephew and saying you damaged the room you owe us</u>
<u n="124" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="125" who="S0036">I don't know what it is <pause dur="short"/> a couple of hundred pounds it is they're trying to charge him</u>
<u n="126" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="127" who="S0036">he's never stayed in Travel Lodge <pause dur="short"/> in fact the night that they said that he was there he was actually with my sister <pause dur="short"/> they were out <pause dur="short"/> it was some family thing and they were out and erm but but they're insisting <pause dur="short"/> they're saying no it was him</u>
<u n="128" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0036">and er then they said they'd got erm a driving licence number <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said well okay send me the proof <pause dur="short"/> send me a letter with the driving license number <pause dur="short"/> and the driving license number is the same all bar the last four digits</u>
<u n="130" who="S0018">how weird</u>
<u n="131" who="S0036">I know <pause dur="short"/> and it's like what's going on? And but they're insisting <pause dur="short"/> they're saying no we know it was him and he owes us the money <pause dur="short"/> and er so now my sister's having to try <pause dur="short"/> I told her to go to Citizens' Advice Bureau</u>
<u n="132" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="133" who="S0036">erm but I don't know what has happened <pause dur="short"/> that was like just last week she she because she said obviously she's they having got the correct driving license number <pause dur="short"/> but how did they get that? Unless they ask people to show some ID when they book in or I don't know I mean that's</u>
<u n="134" who="S0018">very bizarre <pause dur="short"/> but driving license does that? Cos it it doesn't have a <trunc>ph</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> or does it have a photo on nowadays?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0036">I I don't think erm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0018">I think some do some don't</u>
<u n="137" who="S0036">yeah like I think they <pause dur="short"/> I think his has got a photo on but the thing is is that erm <pause dur="short"/> I suppose if they just flash it I suppose if it's only a small photo they can you're not necessarily</u>
<u n="138" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> but that that's their lookout <pause dur="short"/> you know if they haven't checked that the person who's paying is the person who is has the account that's their problem surely</u>
<u n="139" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> you'd have thought so wouldn't you but they're absolutely adamant that erm it's him and he's paying the bill <pause dur="short"/> erm but anyway obviously he's he's not going to and nor is my sister but erm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0036">but I said to her you do need to speak to Citizens' Advice or something and just ask them</u>
<u n="142" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0036">and I don't know how it works with driving license like if they've got all the same numbers but I mean there's probably thousands of people that have got all the first numbers are the same <pause dur="short"/> and just the last few digits that are different</u>
<u n="144" who="S0018" trans="overlap">no it's weird it's that all of the digits are the same apart from the last four <pause dur="short"/> maybe they try to estimate or maybe they maybe they've got someone who works in the DVLA and</u>
<u n="145" who="S0036" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> who knows? You just feel like there's always somebody tried to scam you don't you though</u>
<u n="146" who="S0018" trans="overlap">I know isn't it a shame? Such a shame when you think back to you know how communities used to operate and everyone used to know each other and they'd be a lot more <trunc>a</trunc> you know accountability than you know you can't <pause dur="short"/> stuff like that didn't happen <pause dur="short"/> oh it's a shame</u>
<u n="147" who="S0036" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="148" who="S0018">it's such a shame</u>
<u n="149" who="S0036">I think it's just easier for it to happen though isn't it?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no they're all out for scamming <pause dur="short"/> I booked a ticket on er Ryan Air and the there there was this box that came up when I booked the ticket that said do you want a ten pound discount voucher off your next flight? And so I thought they're giving me a free money <pause dur="short"/> yes okay alright then if I ever feel that I have to book a ticket with Ryan Air again I'll get ten pounds off okay alright <pause dur="short"/> so I pressed yes and then about a year later I realised that erm about thirty pounds had been taken out of my bank account every month <pause dur="short"/> no it wasn't thirty pounds it was about I think it was about twenty euros which wouldn't be that much but still over a year it all mounts up <pause dur="short"/> and I was thinking who is this Shopping Discount? Cos it came up as erm debited by Shopping Discounts</u>
<u n="151" who="S0036">mm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0018">and I was thinking well I've never used a company called Shopping Discounts and especially not every month <pause dur="short"/> so I did an internet search on it and found that it was a company that erm you know like Groupon?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0036">no I haven't heard of them but er</u>
<u n="154" who="S0018" trans="overlap">no but they erm they basically they're a a company that offer online discounts</u>
<u n="155" who="S0036">mm</u>
<u n="156" who="S0018">erm so if you as a company want to discount you've got lots of stock that you want to get rid of you contact this company and say put a special offer out to your members that gives them a very reduced price in all their stuff</u>
<u n="157" who="S0036" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="158" who="S0018">erm so their members of of Shoppers Discounts erm pay a certain amount every month in order to get the information about all these discounts <pause dur="short"/> and you can get like a a facial for ten pounds or a hair cut for ten pounds</u>
<u n="159" who="S0036">mm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0018">but obviously you know I'd never signed up to this <pause dur="short"/> and it transpired that me clicking I want a ten pound money off voucher on the Ryan Air I'd agreed to then passing my details on to a third party to then take money out of my account without my permission every month</u>
<u n="161" who="S0036" trans="overlap">you'd agreed for <pause dur="short"/> unbelievable isn't it? That's disgraceful</u>
<u n="162" who="S0018">in the end I got it back but they were  they were  evil about it</u>
<u n="163" who="S0036">mm <pause dur="short"/> terrible</u>
<u n="164" who="S0018" trans="overlap">they were no we didn't you know I was <pause dur="short"/> you know you did this on the basis of deception</u>
<u n="165" who="S0036">mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0018">it was never made er covert or clear what was going on <pause dur="short"/> and it's yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0036" trans="overlap">clear yeah mm <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> terrible <pause dur="short"/> I had one the other day I mean it's not as bad as that but erm I had this email come through and it was for erm free sample for something for <trunc>O</trunc> Olay or something <pause dur="short"/> so I thought oh yeah I'll have I'll try some of that you know if it's a miracle cream on <trunc>fif</trunc> on fifty about four five weeks time so I thought yeah you know</u>
<u n="168" who="S0018">you're going to be fifty?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0036">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="171" who="S0036">like I'm willing to try anything do you know what I mean so I thought I'll have a free sample of that <pause dur="short"/> so I went in to it and erm it was this erm savvy Supersavvyme site which I have heard of</u>
<u n="172" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="173" who="S0036">and I'm not quite sure what they are but I had heard of them <pause dur="short"/> but it was through them this free sample <pause dur="short"/> so I clicked on it and then it went through and it said for your free sample click here <pause dur="short"/> so I followed it through and then I put my details in <pause dur="short"/> my name and my email address and everything <pause dur="short"/> and then it kind of went all the way through and I clicked finish and it went and then there was nothing about the sample so I thought well okay usually it says thank you your free sample is on it's way or you'll receive it in a few days or whatever</u>
<u n="174" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> confirmation</u>
<u n="175" who="S0036">but nothing came up so I thought well that's a bit strange <pause dur="short"/> so I went into it again to find out what this thing was and there was an email address <pause dur="short"/> so I emailed it and it was a bit vague <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc> I didn't really know who I was emailing and then I had this email back from Proctor and Gamble so it was obviously a Proctor and Gamble product which <trunc>prob</trunc> Olay probably is and it said erm sorry we don't know what sample you're talking about we don't actually have any offers at the moment for any samples</u>
<u n="176" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh huh <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mhm</u>
<u n="177" who="S0036">but this was all through this Supersavvyme er website</u>
<u n="178" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0036">but of course now I'm getting emails every single day from Supersavvyme</u>
<u n="180" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0036">so all they've done is <pause dur="short"/> there was no sample</u>
<u n="182" who="S0018">they collected your email</u>
<u n="183" who="S0036">they've got me to go in <pause dur="short"/> got all my information so they can email me and there's nor erm there's no sample <pause dur="short"/> but I've tried to <trunc>re</trunc> all the stuff they send you <pause dur="short"/> it's all this no reply stuff</u>
<u n="184" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0036">so I've tried to email them back to these things to say actually I only registered with you for a sample and you've conned me into registering with you and now you're emailing me every day <pause dur="short"/> please remove me</u>
<u n="186" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0036">and there's nothing <pause dur="short"/> it's no reply</u>
<u n="188" who="S0018">can you not get onto the site? And or is there nothing in the email that says click on this link to</u>
<u n="189" who="S0036" trans="overlap">it might say yeah to stop receiving it</u>
<u n="190" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0036">there might be something on there but I wanted to have my say about the fact that I'd felt like I'd been conned to do it by this free sample offer</u>
<u n="192" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0036">which obviously clearly didn't exist <pause dur="short"/> I mean trading standards would have a field day wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0018">it's so cheeky <pause dur="short"/> it really is</u>
<u n="195" who="S0036">disgusting <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="196" who="S0018">totally</u>
<u n="197" who="S0036">but you just I suppose cos you know coming in here as well and then if you feel like those things happen in your personal life but then when you're at work as well and you've got people coming in</u>
<u n="198" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0036">that are just coming in for information</u>
<u n="200" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0036">and you just feel like you start to feel a bit paranoid <pause dur="short"/> you just start to feel like everybody's out to get you <pause dur="short"/> do you know?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="203" who="S0036">and like I know a lady came in here the other day and I know she's been in here before and never ordered anything from us and then she said she was going to order this wall paper for her <pause dur="short"/> but while I'm writing it down she's writing it down and I'm thinking I'm not going to see her again <pause dur="short"/> and she said she'd phone us with the order <pause dur="short"/> that was three weeks ago <pause dur="short"/> she's just come in <pause dur="short"/> she's borrowed the book <pause dur="short"/> she's found what she's wanted and I I even gave her a twenty percent discount but I looked online <pause dur="short"/> they've got it at twenty-five percent <pause dur="short"/> so she's obviously just gone away and realised she can save a few extra pound <pause dur="short"/> doesn't care about the fact that she's taken up a good two couple hours of our time</u>
<u n="204" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0036">she's borrowed our books <pause dur="short"/> if she actually found it we helped her to find it <pause dur="short"/> just none of that matters and you just start to think</u>
<u n="206" who="S0018">what's the point? It's all futile isn't it <pause dur="short"/> oh God that must be so frustrating</u>
<u n="207" who="S0036">well cos you never really kind of how how often that happens either because people just say oh well yeah I'll come back to you and you don't monitor it and people just don't you know and you don't know whether they're going and buying it on the internet or <pause dur="short"/> I don't mind if they're buying it from Treadwell's <pause dur="short"/> I don't mind if another shops getting it</u>
<u n="208" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0036">but the internet is just sickening cos they're just not doing anything for it at all <pause dur="short"/> they're just feeding off the backs of people like us</u>
<u n="210" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's going to kill small businesses <pause dur="short"/> it's such a shame</u>
<u n="211" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's already people going <pause dur="short"/> there's already <trunc>peo</trunc></u>
<u n="212" who="S0048">that came in yesterday <pause dur="short"/> she came round with it <pause dur="short"/> I don't whether anybody's interested in it cos I won't won't use it</u>
<u n="213" who="S0036" trans="overlap">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> oh okay <pause dur="short"/> oh with this voucher you're entitled to</u>
<u n="214" who="S0018">watch out it might be a scam</u>
<u n="215" who="S0048">no no no she was the girl from the shop so</u>
<u n="216" who="S0036">oh that's good <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh that's nice</u>
<u n="217" who="S0048" trans="overlap">I mean it's quite a good deal</u>
<u n="218" who="S0036">I mean I have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> so you know and I obviously wouldn't go to somebody else <trunc>f</trunc> not have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos I've had <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> two times three times now</u>
<u n="219" who="S0048">only only for a one off yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0036" trans="overlap">but it's <trunc>dif</trunc> somebody else <pause dur="short"/> yeah if somebody else <pause dur="short"/> and that's not  that's not  bad twenty-five pound for it <pause dur="short"/> is that for a cut and blow dry?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0048" trans="overlap"><unclear/> if you want <pause dur="short"/> cut and blow <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> it it just says a hair cut but it's got it's got to include cut and blow <pause dur="short"/> they're not going to cut</u>
<u n="222" who="S0036" trans="overlap">blow dry <pause dur="short"/> they're not going to send you out with it wet</u>
<u n="223" who="S0048">exactly</u>
<u n="224" who="S0036">no that's good for er that kind of salon isn't it</u>
<u n="225" who="S0048" trans="overlap">do you want it cos I won't use it?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0018">I <trunc>us</trunc> I usually pay about five pounds for a a haircut <pause dur="short"/> or I do it myself</u>
<u n="227" who="S0048" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0036">well could you do mine for me? I'll give you a fiver</u>
<u n="229" who="S0048" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0018">I can't I can't afford twenty-five pounds on a haircut at the moment it's just too</u>
<u n="231" who="S0036">I mean I used to go to one by the doctors where I worked which is a bit of a cheaper one but that's just not practical for me now <pause dur="short"/> it's like yesterday I didn't leave the place till twenty past six <unclear/> You know I did nearly ten hours yesterday there</u>
<u n="232" who="S0018">gosh</u>
<u n="233" who="S0036">so erm you know it's I can't <trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> I can't fit it in <pause dur="short"/> so erm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0048" trans="overlap">yeah you can't fit it in <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> cos <unclear/> I like the streaked colours that you've got in your hair</u>
<u n="235" who="S0018">oh thank you <pause dur="short"/> I had that done when I was in Lanzarote actually <pause dur="short"/> I had my hair cut</u>
<u n="236" who="S0048">I was going to ask what colour it was</u>
<u n="237" who="S0018">ah you see I do the hairdressing and dental tourism</u>
<u n="238" who="S0048">right</u>
<u n="239" who="S0018">so I go to the dentist when I'm in Spain</u>
<u n="240" who="S0048">uh huh</u>
<u n="241" who="S0018">and the hairdressers as well because they they just so much less over there</u>
<u n="242" who="S0048">yeah yeah they do <pause dur="short"/> I noticed that like you can go <pause dur="short"/> when I was in Tenerife last week you look round and you think you could treat yourself to your nails erm you know</u>
<u n="243" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0036">and it's all so much cheaper <pause dur="short"/> really</u>
<u n="245" who="S0048" trans="overlap">everything's so much cheaper <unclear/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0018">I think I got my hair cut and the colour put in for about all in all thirty-five pounds which is amazing</u>
<u n="247" who="S0036">that's good isn't it?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0048">but no it's nice cos you're quite dark</u>
<u n="249" who="S0018">mhm yeah you can see my roots now</u>
<u n="250" who="S0048">no no no well my roots are grey but I mean you you're quite dark and I every time I go I keep saying I want to be a dirty blonde</u>
<u n="251" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="252" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0048">I don't mean a dirty blonde <unclear/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0018">do they give you weird stares?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0048">no no no she knows what I mean <pause dur="short"/> but she can never <pause dur="short"/> because I've got so much red in my hair that the sun brings out the red</u>
<u n="256" who="S0018" trans="overlap">dubious</u>
<u n="257" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I have <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've got a lot of red in my hair as well</u>
<u n="258" who="S0048">she tries to put blonde but it always like because I've come back from the sun now it's it's gone really red and really fair <pause dur="short"/> so what she does I mean I've had no streaks put in my hair for about it'll be three years come Christmas</u>
<u n="259" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="260" who="S0048">and she said  she said  I'm the cheapest streaky person she's ever had because all she does is she does the roots to darken it back up again</u>
<u n="261" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh huh <pause dur="short"/> uh huh</u>
<u n="262" who="S0048">and she pulls some of the root colour through</u>
<u n="263" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="264" who="S0048">so all these red streaks are from the original one that I got done sort of two or three years ago</u>
<u n="265" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="266" who="S0048">so it works out well <pause dur="short"/> but I'd like to go that colour <pause dur="short"/> it's like like you've been out in the sun</u>
<u n="267" who="S0018" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="268" who="S0036" trans="overlap">it's erm sort of Jennifer Aniston's kind of erm base colour isn't it?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0018" trans="overlap">California beachy <pause dur="short"/> well these bits are probably because I was out in the sun because I reckon that amount was from when I was living in Spain</u>
<u n="270" who="S0048">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0018">but er no I went in and I said please <trunc>cov</trunc> put put me some highlights in to cover up my grey hairs</u>
<u n="272" who="S0048">oh God you've not got any grey hairs</u>
<u n="273" who="S0018">oh I have I have <pause dur="short"/> it's all coming out here at the temples but</u>
<u n="274" who="S0036">yeah she's got a couple I can see them</u>
<u n="275" who="S0018">so she went and put platinum blonde like that looked grey itself in it <pause dur="short"/> so she put grey <pause dur="short"/> platinum blonde and a kind of erm I think it was er I can't remember what it was called but some kind of golden blonde</u>
<u n="276" who="S0048" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="277" who="S0036" trans="overlap">you need like a yeah you needed more like a honey blonde didn't you really?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so she put those two colours in and I went back home <pause dur="short"/> well where I was staying and I just looked in the mirror and I thought oh my God it looks more like I've got grey hair now than I did when I went to get the grey hairs covered up <pause dur="short"/> so I went back and I said I'm really sorry I don't like it <pause dur="short"/> you've done it really well but it just doesn't suit me I don't think</u>
<u n="279" who="S0048">mm mm</u>
<u n="280" who="S0018">and so she put in dark brown highlights to to mask it</u>
<u n="281" who="S0036" trans="overlap">oh right low light low lights</u>
<u n="282" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0048">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0018">no of course I guess yeah high lights <pause dur="short"/> low lights</u>
<u n="285" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0048">mm mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0018">so I've got a quite quite a hotchpotch of colours in there at the moment</u>
<u n="288" who="S0048" trans="overlap"><unclear/> cos it moves <pause dur="short"/> when it moves you know it's got the</u>
<u n="289" who="S0036">yeah you can <trunc>c</trunc> see the different highlights and the light yeah which is nice</u>
<u n="290" who="S0048" trans="overlap">yeah the different colours</u>
<u n="291" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="292" who="S0048">so you have to keep going whenever you want your <unclear/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0018">well yeah now I'm thinking oh dear you can see that bit on the top of my head <pause dur="short"/> am I going to have to go to Lanzarote? But I'm like I can't afford a holiday</u>
<u n="294" who="S0048">yeah where abouts in Lanzarote were you?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0018">erm Costa Teguise</u>
<u n="296" who="S0048">yeah my sister goes there all the time <pause dur="short"/> I've not been to Costa Teguise <pause dur="short"/> I've only been to Lanzarote once</u>
<u n="297" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0048">and that was erm <pause dur="short"/> where did we go? It was just outside Puerto Del Carmen</u>
<u n="299" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="300" who="S0048">Cos I didn't like Puerto Del Carmen at all <pause dur="short"/> it's too busy just</u>
<u n="301" who="S0036">I've never been</u>
<u n="302" who="S0048">busy for me <pause dur="short"/> but the  But the  bit just outside it was was pleasant enough <pause dur="short"/> it was a nice bit yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh well if she goes to Costa Teguise I can give her the name of the hairdresser <pause dur="short"/> she's great <pause dur="short"/> she's lovely as well <pause dur="short"/> really nice</u>
<u n="304" who="S0036">yeah that's good business</u>
<u n="305" who="S0048">so this is no good to anyone then?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0018">oh thank you though</u>
<u n="307" who="S0036">erm oh I'm sure I could find somebody yeah <pause dur="short"/> I just feel like I'd be going in there and taking advantage when I normally have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's the thing you see that's why</u>
<u n="308" who="S0048" trans="overlap"><unclear/> one off isn't it?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0036">I suppose so yeah <pause dur="short"/> I suppose they wouldn't mind if I said well you know</u>
<u n="310" who="S0048" trans="overlap">yeah it's a one off <unclear/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0036" trans="overlap">well I'll hang on to it because there's bound to be somebody else anyway isn't there you know so yeah <pause dur="short"/> rather than throwing it away</u>
<u n="312" who="S0018" trans="overlap">maybe <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will get her revenge next time you go with her</u>
<u n="313" who="S0036">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I just erm <pause dur="short"/> I mean I because I did go to Aesthetics erm when I first sort of started sort of when they took the shop over and that <pause dur="short"/> and erm they just did this really bad blow dry <pause dur="short"/> it was terrible <pause dur="short"/> because my hairs really curly</u>
<u n="314" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="315" who="S0036">and erm I wanted it straight and smooth and it was terrible <pause dur="short"/> the the guy just couldn't do it you know you have to have a technique to get curly hair to go straight and smooth</u>
<u n="316" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh-huh</u>
<u n="317" who="S0036">by the time I got home it was all over the place so erm and I told erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I phoned him up and I said my hair's terrible <pause dur="short"/> I said I think this is the worst one I've ever had</u>
<u n="318" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="319" who="S0036">and er he said oh that's okay just come back in and like we'll we'll do it again for you you know another time for free and so I did do that <pause dur="short"/> but the trouble is with Aesthetics it's always so busy in there and I can't stand that</u>
<u n="320" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0036">you know you just go in and it's just like really busy and hectic and and but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>  they're they're quieter <pause dur="short"/> and I just think well Aesthetics probably do okay anyway whereas <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> probably need the business and the support don't they</u>
<u n="322" who="S0018" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0036">and he's ever such a nice guy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> himself <pause dur="short"/> he's he's lovely <pause dur="short"/> he he's a really nice guy you know <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh huh <pause dur="short"/> are there three now on the parade? Three hairdressers?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0036">well there's one upstairs here isn't there? There's one above us</u>
<u n="326" who="S0018">oh wow <pause dur="short"/> that's four then</u>
<u n="327" who="S0036">yeah and well I've got a <trunc>f</trunc> there's yeah there's three <pause dur="short"/> there's one and then those two <pause dur="short"/> but is there another one as well? I can't</u>
<u n="328" who="S0018">is there a barbers?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0036">oh the barbers of course yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> so there is there's four yeah <pause dur="short"/> well three three women's and a</u>
<u n="330" who="S0018">that's quite a lot for a small little parade</u>
<u n="331" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="332" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh well better having that than three restaurants</u>
<u n="333" who="S0036">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah or another wallpaper shop</u>
<u n="334" who="S0018">oh gosh</u>
<u n="335" who="S0036">like we did before</u>
<u n="336" who="S0018">oh really? Was there another one?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0036">yeah yeah on the end <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> a guy came on the end</u>
<u n="338" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0036">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0018">was that before the flower shop was there?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0036">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="343" who="S0036">yeah it was immediately before the flower shop <pause dur="short"/> yeah he erm he er came in and er went again quite quickly <pause dur="short"/> erm can't really say anymore than that to be honest with you because</u>
<u n="344" who="S0018">I bet you were glad that he he went <pause dur="short"/> came and went</u>
<u n="345" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> a lot of people were glad he went</u>
<u n="346" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0036">A lot of people are still trying to find him</u>
<u n="348" who="S0018">oh really</u>
<u n="349" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah we get phone calls yeah <pause dur="short"/> we've had phone calls asking <pause dur="short"/> we had one not long ago from er a company asking if we knew where they'd gone to and we said yeah we actually we they didn't we didn't know where they went to straight away but we know where they are now</u>
<u n="350" who="S0018">really</u>
<u n="351" who="S0036">so we told them <pause dur="short"/> and they were <trunc>ve</trunc> thank you very much <pause dur="short"/> we'll be over there to see them</u>
<u n="352" who="S0018">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> so have they set up shop somewhere else?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0036">erm I don't know what he does <pause dur="short"/> he's had all sorts of things all over the place this guy <pause dur="short"/> he's notorious <pause dur="short"/> even our landlord knew him</u>
<u n="354" who="S0018">really</u>
<u n="355" who="S0036">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0018">I guess that was <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> was it? That was renting out the guy from the bakery <unclear/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0036" trans="overlap">erm yeah I suppose it  I suppose it  would have been wouldn't it? Yeah I mean I don't really like know much about who owns these shops and that and who owns what but erm yeah I suppose it would have been <pause dur="short"/> all I know is that they just charge too much cos it's just ridiculous</u>
<u n="358" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that was in your favour I guess <pause dur="short"/> probably brought people to his shop and then they were like oh let's go and visit the shop down the road <pause dur="short"/> see whether it's cheaper</u>
<u n="359" who="S0036">yeah well erm <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I mean most people that like know us and used to come in here and used to say don't worry we won't be stepping foot inside his place <pause dur="short"/> it's absolutely disgusting you know <pause dur="short"/> so and then of course they couldn't get the accounts anyway because we'd got like the accounts and then they moved in there thinking that they could just get the accounts <pause dur="short"/> so of course they were contacting the company saying can we have an account with you? And they were saying well no you can't</u>
<u n="360" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="361" who="S0036">you're two doors away from Lakeside Interiors and they're long standing <trunc>ges</trunc> clients of ours</u>
<u n="362" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="363" who="S0036">and then of course so they were getting more and more cross <pause dur="short"/> and er I had a bit of a run in with her one day</u>
<u n="364" who="S0018">oh deary me</u>
<u n="365" who="S0036">her she was absolutely vile <pause dur="short"/> erm she came in here trying to cause trouble and er</u>
<u n="366" who="S0018">what kind of trouble?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0036">just erm because they couldn't get an account</u>
<u n="368" who="S0018">uh huh</u>
<u n="369" who="S0036">and so they thought it was us that we <pause dur="short"/> they thought that we were telling the company's not to give them an account <pause dur="short"/> and so she came in and I've got customers <pause dur="short"/> and she came in and erm  and erm  she er she said is the manager here? And I went no <pause dur="short"/> he's not actually <pause dur="short"/> I said oh you <trunc>y</trunc> I said I I can help you because I thought oh this is an angry customer about something <pause dur="short"/> you know gosh what's gone on? You know <pause dur="short"/> and erm she said er oh er tell him to erm I want to speak to him when he comes back or something <pause dur="short"/> and er anyway she started to go out the shop and I followed her out and I went excuse me <pause dur="short"/> I went who are you? And she turned around and she went I you know who I am like that <pause dur="short"/> I didn't <pause dur="short"/> but I watched where she walked <pause dur="short"/> and of course she went up and went in there <pause dur="short"/> so I thought okay I know who you are now</u>
<u n="370" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh huh</u>
<u n="371" who="S0036">anyway I waited till the customers had gone <pause dur="short"/> the customers were like God you know who's that? And I I er said oh I don't know what's going on you know <pause dur="short"/> anyway and when I'd finished I thought I didn't want Steve to go around because you know Steve's not very good at with conflict</u>
<u n="372" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0036">at of any sort <pause dur="short"/> of <trunc>des</trunc> any description</u>
<u n="374" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="375" who="S0036">so erm I went round and he was there as well <pause dur="short"/> and I said can I help you? And erm anyway she basically just wanted to have a go and er she was going on about this company that wouldn't give them an account <pause dur="short"/> and they'd got this erm hanger on the er <pause dur="short"/> cos one company that we dealt with you'd give them the account which we weren't very happy about</u>
<u n="376" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mhm</u>
<u n="377" who="S0036">but they'd made a mistake basically</u>
<u n="378" who="S0018">oh right</u>
<u n="379" who="S0036">and er I just picked up this hanger off the desk and I went er I said you're speaking to the wrong people like it was like a company like that <pause dur="short"/> I said  I said  these are the people you need to speak to <pause dur="short"/> I said if they won't give you an account that's their terms and conditions <pause dur="short"/> not ours</u>
<u n="380" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="381" who="S0036">and erm anyway she started <pause dur="short"/> they were obviously just getting more and more frustrated and then she started having a go at me and erm and then she came right up to me like that and erm she was right in my face and she was like really aggressive and I went  I went  you're getting very aggressive and erm she grabbed hold of me</u>
<u n="382" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="383" who="S0036">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and pushed me out of the door</u>
<u n="384" who="S0018"><event desc="sound of gasping"/> Oh my life</u>
<u n="385" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah they <trunc>sa</trunc> people said that I should the police and put it on record because you know</u>
<u n="386" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0036">but er I said no <pause dur="short"/> she's just erm she's a fish wife</u>
<u n="388" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0036">and she's horrible</u>
<u n="390" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0036">and erm so anyway but anyway they went eventually so</u>
<u n="392" who="S0018">Good riddance <pause dur="short"/> hello</u>
<u n="393" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hiya <pause dur="short"/> alright</u>
<u n="394" who="S0036">it might be best if <pause dur="short"/> can we switch it off for a minute? Is that alright?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0018">yeah sure <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="recording skips"/> Okay</u>
<u n="396" who="S0036">erm I did erm ten <trunc>a</trunc> nearly ten hours at the surgery yesterday but it's constant <pause dur="short"/> cos I'm I'm a <trunc>cert</trunc> the NHS has something called recoding and everything is coded</u>
<u n="397" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="398" who="S0036">and it's all to do with <trunc>quaf</trunc> quality outcome frameworks and meeting targets and all that so they get their money basically <pause dur="short"/> that's what it boils down to</u>
<u n="399" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="400" who="S0036">it's all very mercenaries</u>
<u n="401" who="S0018">yes</u>
<u n="402" who="S0036">and er but I I'd liked all of that so I have to go through everything and pick out the important stuff and erm so it's quite intense really <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="403" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> and so what's that everything every type of treatment is coded? Or everything that costs money is?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah everything <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> every treatment <pause dur="short"/> every disorder <pause dur="short"/> every disease <pause dur="short"/> every er every scan that's done <pause dur="short"/> everything really <pause dur="short"/> but obviously some of it doesn't have to go on because it's not important <pause dur="short"/> I have to sort of pick out the stuff that that needs to be summarised</u>
<u n="405" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="406" who="S0036">because I'd you'd I do it for all the information that's coming in for current patients but I do it for erm new patients as well so every time a new patient comes in I put all of that information on <pause dur="short"/> I have to go through it</u>
<u n="407" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="408" who="S0036">and there's previous summaries from other surgeries that I can just scan through and pick out the <pause dur="short"/> cos sometimes there's stuff on there that doesn't need to be on or sometimes there's stuff that's not been put on that needs to be on so</u>
<u n="409" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="410" who="S0036">and of course some of the files they can be <pause dur="short"/> I mean I had them yesterday <pause dur="short"/> they were A4 files and they were that thick</u>
<u n="411" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="412" who="S0036">especially if there's erm drug problems or mental health problems and that they usually a lot of er paperwork for that sort of thing</u>
<u n="413" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh-huh</u>
<u n="414" who="S0036">so of course it's quite intense <pause dur="short"/> but then I didn't know this but there was a course at our surgery yesterday and some people came from other surgeries and erm I didn't have to do it but I asked the practice manager if she wanted me to do it and she said it's up to you <pause dur="short"/> she said it will be a bit of a break for you if you want to and they've got some sandwiches as well</u>
<u n="415" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="416" who="S0036">and I I'd only got some crackers on me so I thought okay <pause dur="short"/> and it was two and a half hours but I said well I'll just go for an hour an hour and a half if I'm asked I'll explain to the lady that I'm going to have to leave because I've just got too much work to do</u>
<u n="417" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="418" who="S0036">because it was mainly for the girls on the desk and I don't do any deskwork</u>
<u n="419" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="420" who="S0036">but there was just this thing in it that was just because it was about managing customers and dealing with situations and all sorts of things and there was just a couple of things that were really relevant to here</u>
<u n="421" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="422" who="S0036">and I just thought that's really interesting I must remember to tell Steve that which I probably won't take any notice but</u>
<u n="423" who="S0018" trans="overlap">ah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="424" who="S0036">it's about how <pause dur="short"/> what customers pick up on from things you say to them</u>
<u n="425" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="426" who="S0036">and there's been research done on it and it's been proven that that's what people do because it's in their nature to do it</u>
<u n="427" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="428" who="S0036">so they'll always pick the bet scenario for them</u>
<u n="429" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="430" who="S0036">so but I won't say it now cos I'll tell Steve in a minute</u>
<u n="431" who="S0018">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> okay yeah <pause dur="short"/> so how how often do you work at the surgery?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0036">all day Tuesday and any extra hours that erm I need to do <pause dur="short"/> like erm in fact I must remember to email the the practice manager erm</u>
<u n="433" who="S0018">write it down</u>
<u n="434" who="S0036">I'm going to go in on <pause dur="short"/> I'm going to go  I'm going to go  in on erm Friday</u>
<u n="435" who="S0018">is that extra to your hours that they pay you or?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's kind of cos they didn't <pause dur="short"/> cos I took the job off a doctor you see <pause dur="short"/> the doctor used to do all the coding and the summarising</u>
<u n="437" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="438" who="S0036">the female doctor <pause dur="short"/> and erm so they'd never had a member of staff doing it before and a lot of surgeries they <trunc>g</trunc> they do get a clinician to do it <pause dur="short"/> but not all surgeries do <pause dur="short"/> some surgeries do use a member of admin staff</u>
<u n="439" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="440" who="S0036">but they have them doing it full time</u>
<u n="441" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="442" who="S0036">so of course they're trying to get me to squeeze it into like eight or nine hours <pause dur="short"/> that's my contracted hours but then I just do the extra</u>
<u n="443" who="S0018" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="444" who="S0036">but of course because it's so mercenary and because it all it is all about the money erm they don't really want to pay over time so I have this constant battle where I'm told well just come in if you need to do it <pause dur="short"/> but then when I say well shall I come in on Friday? It's like well have you got a backlog then?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0018">urgh</u>
<u n="446" who="S0036">you know and it's er</u>
<u n="447" who="S0018">oh gosh <pause dur="short"/> I can imagine that's only going to get worse</u>
<u n="448" who="S0036">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0018">what do you think of all this NHS reform?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0036" trans="overlap">I don't you know I I don't know</u>
<u n="451" who="S0018">mm mm</u>
<u n="452" who="S0036">because I hear the arguments for it and I think well actually yeah they've got good points there and erm that will be good <pause dur="short"/> and then I hear the arguments against it and I think oh it actually yeah they've got points there and that will be bad</u>
<u n="453" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="454" who="S0036">and then I can't weigh it up and I don't know</u>
<u n="455" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="456" who="S0036">but I tell you what I do know <pause dur="short"/> it I don't know if it's okay to say this on tape <pause dur="short"/> erm I suppose it depends on the GPs and the doctors themselves and I just think that it's a with some GPs it is very much about the er money and the earning potential</u>
<u n="457" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> really</u>
<u n="458" who="S0036">and erm that er that might affect what they do for people</u>
<u n="459" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0036">because of the cost <pause dur="short"/> and if they've got more control over the money then is that going to be worse in places where GPs are <event desc="sound of phone ringing"/> more materialistic and?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely <pause dur="short"/> crickey</u>
<u n="462" who="S0036">and I don't know because I don't know what that means in terms of them having control of the money and their incomes</u>
<u n="463" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="464" who="S0036">because obviously they get basics but then they get extras for things they do</u>
<u n="465" who="S0018">mhm <pause dur="short"/> which sounds strange doesn't it <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>su</trunc> surely they should just get a lump sum</u>
<u n="466" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I just think if you've got  if you've got  people where it the money is important even though they're probably earning a hundred grand a year but they don't want to earn a hundred <pause dur="short"/> they want to earn a hundred and fifty</u>
<u n="467" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="468" who="S0036">I you know</u>
<u n="469" who="S0018">crazy isn't it?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0036">so I think er you know at our place it wouldn't necessarily be a good thing</u>
<u n="471" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0036">but the doctors where I go I couldn't imagine them being like that and maybe it would be  would be  would be a good thing for them <pause dur="short"/> I don't  I don't  know <pause dur="short"/> I don't</u>
<u n="473" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm it depends if they have integrity if they really have the vocation of a doctor to heal people or whether they're in it for the money <pause dur="short"/> what a shame?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0036">terrible <pause dur="short"/> I'm really shocked <pause dur="short"/> I'm shocked every time</u>
<u n="475" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0036">it never ceases to amaze me</u>
<u n="477" who="S0018">crickey <pause dur="short"/> what do you get people that aren't getting treated because it costs too much?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0036" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> one of our doctors never cos I I cos I can type really quickly and the secretary went on a cruise cos it was her fiftieth birthday erm last year in Spring and so they said to me would I mind going in and doing these extra hours I'm doing to help so she didn't have to come back to all this work? I said yeah no problem at all <unclear/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> uh-huh</u>
<u n="480" who="S0036"><trunc>C</trunc> if you've got an audio machine just show me how to use it and I'll I can type all the letter out for her no problem <pause dur="short"/> and he never sent anybody anywhere <pause dur="short"/> never referred any <pause dur="short"/> probably out of about a hundred letters that I did referrals and things probably only two were his</u>
<u n="481" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh-huh</u>
<u n="482" who="S0036">this is erm anonymous isn't it?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0018">yes it is don't worry</u>
<u n="484" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">here you are darling</u>
<u n="485" who="S0018">oh thank you <pause dur="short"/> thank you very much</u>
<u n="486" who="S0036">thanks</u>
<u n="487" who="S0067">there you are weirdo</u>
<u n="488" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="490" who="S0067">no sugar no milk</u>
<u n="491" who="S0036">so erm you know it's er but I mean I I think that they do need to get rid of some of that that like kind of erm the different levels of <pause dur="short"/> cos I I've worked for the NHS for years and when I worked at the hospice well I mean I used to have to go to a lot of meetings <pause dur="short"/> and so in fact I used to go to erm strategic health authority meetings because we used to have to you have to justify what you're doing and you have this called this traffic light systems</u>
<u n="492" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mhm <pause dur="short"/> mhm</u>
<u n="493" who="S0036">so if you've got things in place with your trust you're either on a red light or you're on an amber light or you're on a green light</u>
<u n="494" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="495" who="S0036">and part of what I used to used to involve erm cos it was all about service improvement</u>
<u n="496" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="497" who="S0036">so obviously I used to go along to all of those <pause dur="short"/> and you used to literally have to sit in front of a panel of people and then you'd be questioned</u>
<u n="498" who="S0018">oh right you have to justify every single thing</u>
<u n="499" who="S0036" trans="overlap">and they'd be about four or five of us but we'd be from different aspects of the service</u>
<u n="500" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="501" who="S0036">and we'd have to say yeah okay well this is where we are now with this and this is what we're doing <pause dur="short"/> so we've got this amber light at the moment but when we've done this that should take us to this green light <pause dur="short"/> but of course you've so you've got the strategic health authority doing all that at the top <pause dur="short"/> then you've got the PCTs underneath that doing something and there's just</u>
<u n="502" who="S0018" trans="overlap">what are PCTs?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0036">primary Care Trusts</u>
<u n="504" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="505" who="S0036">and that's what they're doing you see <pause dur="short"/> they're trying to er break up the Primary Care Trust <pause dur="short"/> they'd but they've done it before <pause dur="short"/> they've they've grouped them <pause dur="short"/> they've separated them <pause dur="short"/> they've grouped them again and it you know <pause dur="short"/> many</u>
<u n="506" who="S0018" trans="overlap">what are the Primary Care Trusts? Are like er <trunc>lo</trunc>?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0036" trans="overlap">they er they're the ones that control the money at the moment but cos that's what they're trying to get rid of <pause dur="short"/> that's why they</u>
<u n="508" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh right yeah <pause dur="short"/> right they're like the Local Education Authorities?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0036">I suppose so yeah yeah</u>
<u n="510" who="S0018">comparison with education yeah</u>
<u n="511" who="S0036">yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0018">well the same things happening there isn't it <pause dur="short"/> it's all been privatised <pause dur="short"/> they're all going to be thinking about how to spend the least amount of money but then they're still demanding for people to get results with no resources and</u>
<u n="513" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I mean some of that hierarchy does need to go because there's just way too much of it <pause dur="short"/> there's</u>
<u n="514" who="S0018">too much middle management and</u>
<u n="515" who="S0036">yeah cos I mean there's  I mean there's  a couple of other bodies as well that we used to have to deal with and erm it you never quite know <pause dur="short"/> sometimes seems to overlap what they're doing anyway so you think well why do we have them? And why do we have them? And what do these guys do? And there's just it's like it's the same old story isn't it <pause dur="short"/> too many chiefs and not enough Indians</u>
<u n="516" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> true</u>
<u n="517" who="S0036">and er so anyway I but I in terms of where I work I don't thinks it's going to be a good thing <pause dur="short"/> I really don't <pause dur="short"/> because I just think like I said you know <pause dur="short"/> it's all about the  all about the  money</u>
<u n="518" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="519" who="S0036">and I mean just the way that you hear them talk sometimes <pause dur="short"/> cos I'm out the back so when they all <trunc>c</trunc> finish surgery they come out <pause dur="short"/> they're all sitting by me</u>
<u n="520" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="521" who="S0036">and just some of the conversations you hear are just <unclear/> I'd sometimes I think well I hey I'm here <pause dur="short"/> I'm listening to you <pause dur="short"/> you know and <unclear/> that might not be the kind of thing you want to be saying in front of me</u>
<u n="522" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I bet you worry when you go to your doctor's and</u>
<u n="523" who="S0036">my doctor's lovely</u>
<u n="524" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0036">can't imagine my doctor every being like those guys</u>
<u n="526" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0036">I mean my doctor's a human being <pause dur="short"/> I mean a couple of <pause dur="short"/> well one doctor in particular at our place I mean he's just erm you know <pause dur="short"/> don't know what's wrong with him really</u>
<u n="528" who="S0018">well I think it's a a common disease nowadays to be mercenary as you said</u>
<u n="529" who="S0036">it's that old joke about doctors thinking that they're God or something <pause dur="short"/> of the difference between doctors and God or something so I forget now what the joke is <pause dur="short"/> but like they know they're God <pause dur="short"/> or they think like him <pause dur="short"/> I forget what the joke is now and it's</u>
<u n="530" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="531" who="S0036">I can really understand how that joke came about</u>
<u n="532" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't understand why they get paid so much money <pause dur="short"/> I mean yes they've got a difficult job but so have fire fighters <pause dur="short"/> so have nurses <pause dur="short"/> so have teachers</u>
<u n="533" who="S0036" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="534" who="S0018">it's okay they have to do a lot more training to get where they are but</u>
<u n="535" who="S0036">mm <pause dur="short"/> well I mean I  I mean I  know there's some and they you know they can be earning I mean I don't know how much the Prime Minister gets now <pause dur="short"/> I know a few years ago he only got about a hundred and forty grand didn't he which I thought was quite low for a Prime Minister</u>
<u n="536" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="537" who="S0036">what does he get now John?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0067">I think it's one sixty</u>
<u n="539" who="S0036">is it?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0067">I think so</u>
<u n="541" who="S0036">and I mean some of them they're not <pause dur="short"/> so it's like how do you balance that off <pause dur="short"/> do you think they've got more responsibility than the Prime Minister but some of them aren't like seem to be earning about the same sort of money or not far off</u>
<u n="542" who="S0018" trans="overlap">gosh</u>
<u n="543" who="S0036">I mean</u>
<u n="544" who="S0067">I suppose their argument would be they're saving lives aren't they?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0036" trans="overlap">you can only work so many hours a week can't you <pause dur="short"/> I don't know though are they? I mean look at my mum <pause dur="short"/> I mean twice she's been seriously seriously ill and the GPs just completely missed it</u>
<u n="546" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0036">you hear of it all the time don't you?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="549" who="S0036">I know loads of people</u>
<u n="550" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="551" who="S0036">that have been misdiagnosed and</u>
<u n="552" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="553" who="S0036">things have been missed <pause dur="short"/> loads of people <pause dur="short"/> just people in my own family</u>
<u n="554" who="S0018">they're too busy thinking about their money and not about</u>
<u n="555" who="S0036" trans="overlap">my uncle <pause dur="short"/> I I think I mean I don't know whether <pause dur="short"/> I mean it might not be that all the time with them but I think they just get a bit complacent <pause dur="short"/> I think I think what it is you know there's so many time wasters that go to the doctors <pause dur="short"/> people that just go with the slightest little thing rather than thinking do you know what a couple of days this will be gone and I'll be feeling better</u>
<u n="556" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="557" who="S0036">they just want an instant fix for everything <pause dur="short"/> they want anti-biotics now <pause dur="short"/> they want their sore throat now <pause dur="short"/> they want their diarrhoea gone now</u>
<u n="558" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="559" who="S0036">rather than just do you know stop at home <pause dur="short"/> stay warm <pause dur="short"/> drink plenty of fluid <pause dur="short"/> you'll be fine in a couple of days</u>
<u n="560" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="561" who="S0036">three days max <pause dur="short"/> if you've still got it <pause dur="short"/> if you've still got diarrhoea in a weeks time then that's obviously you know <pause dur="short"/> come back <pause dur="short"/> but they don't want that <pause dur="short"/> they wanna be seen now and they want to be fixed now and they want the anti-biotics now</u>
<u n="562" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="563" who="S0036">and that's what's it's like <pause dur="short"/> really really demanding <pause dur="short"/> erm I forgot was I was going to say</u>
<u n="564" who="S0018">yeah so I guess the doctors have a difficult time <trunc>ch</trunc> yeah sorting out those people from the ones who have really got a problem</u>
<u n="565" who="S0036" trans="overlap">and I think that's what it is <pause dur="short"/> I think that these people are taking up the appointments <pause dur="short"/> and this is what this training course was yesterday <pause dur="short"/> they were saying a lot of surgeries now <pause dur="short"/> when you ring up your doctors you say can I have an appointment with Doctor Smith tomorrow or this afternoon or whatever and then they try and get you in and most times they probably can't get you in</u>
<u n="566" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="567" who="S0036">so what they're starting to do now is some surgeries are saying well what's the consultation for? They don't have to answer it</u>
<u n="568" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="569" who="S0036">but apparently a lot of people do <pause dur="short"/> they will say</u>
<u n="570" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="571" who="S0036">so if they say well I've got a sore throat <pause dur="short"/> then they'll go well we've got an appointment on Friday</u>
<u n="572" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="573" who="S0036">erm so</u>
<u n="574" who="S0018">so like use a triage system</u>
<u n="575" who="S0036">and try and just er you know either put them off or say well can you go to your chemist and get something? Or can you? I mean they'll be more training for people obviously but erm yeah just trying to cut down the <trunc>apoin</trunc> the wasted appointments</u>
<u n="576" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="577" who="S0036">with people coming in with sore throats and you know <pause dur="short"/> I mean you'll be just amazed what they come in with <pause dur="short"/> and they book  they book  emergencies <pause dur="short"/> I mean they well they try to <pause dur="short"/> cos we are allowed to ask <pause dur="short"/> if they say it's an emergency and it's it's for an emergency slot cos all the main slots have gone then we we you you do have to ask them what it's for but erm</u>
<u n="578" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mhm <pause dur="short"/> mhm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0036">so there's obviously going to be a big drive to er try and cut it down <pause dur="short"/> the trouble is with doing it and saying well <trunc>c</trunc> can you come day after tomorrow? Is if they've got a sore throat and the sore throat goes which it probably will</u>
<u n="580" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="581" who="S0036">or the diarrhoea goes or they stop vomiting or whatever then then they get a lot of DNAs because then they don't ring up and cancel their appointment</u>
<u n="582" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0036">so then the DNAs go up</u>
<u n="584" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="585" who="S0036">so then it was about how to manage the DNAs</u>
<u n="586" who="S0018">is that did not attend?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0036">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="588" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure they'll get Tesco involved somehow <pause dur="short"/> they'll probably get a doctor in Tesco's and</u>
<u n="589" who="S0036" trans="overlap">they reckon there's a million people a day are DNAing at erm <trunc>ho</trunc> hospital appointments and GPs appointments across the country every single day <pause dur="short"/> and I know a GP appointment they reckon that costs fifty-six pounds per appointment <pause dur="short"/> every time somebody DNAs that's what it costs the equivalent of what it costs the NHS</u>
<u n="590" who="S0018">I'm not surprised if they're paying doctors so much money to be there</u>
<u n="591" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I suppose there's kind of lots of factors they take into consideration isn't there but erm I mean we get erm we probably get about I think it's about sixty a month at our surgery so <pause dur="short"/> about fifteen a week</u>
<u n="592" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0036">which doesn't sound a lot but that's just the doctors <pause dur="short"/> that's not nurses <pause dur="short"/> we get more <trunc>D</trunc></u>
<u n="594" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="595" who="S0036">and when they DNA the nurse appointments they're bigger slots</u>
<u n="596" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="597" who="S0036">Cos if somebody's coming in for a smear and it's a twenty minute slot and they DNA it that's twenty minutes of</u>
<u n="598" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0036">cos it doesn't include nurse appointments</u>
<u n="600" who="S0018">how much? How long are doctors appointments nowadays? Are they supposed to be five minutes?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0036">ten ten well they <pause dur="short"/> a routine appointment is ten minutes</u>
<u n="602" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="603" who="S0036">some surgeries have started to break that down as well now <pause dur="short"/> they're starting to do different types <pause dur="short"/> so you can have a telephone consultation</u>
<u n="604" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="605" who="S0036">you can have a quick five minute with a duty doctor which is one thing only</u>
<u n="606" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="607" who="S0036">Cos what a lot of people do is they come in and it's like well actually yeah I've got this pain in my foot and erm I've got this and then I've got this and then I've had this and I've been feeling a bit low just lately and you you look and there's three or four things on the consultation</u>
<u n="608" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="609" who="S0036">erm which is too much for ten minutes <pause dur="short"/> so they're trying to break it down and saying they'll do these quick five minute slots but it's one thing only</u>
<u n="610" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="611" who="S0036">they're not allowed to come in and start going on about all sorts of other things <pause dur="short"/> so that's what they want to do <pause dur="short"/> they want to come in for a chat some of them <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="612" who="S0018" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> I guess  I guess  back in the olden days that's what people could do with doctors</u>
<u n="613" who="S0036">I suppose so yeah <pause dur="short"/> when there wasn't so many pressures and people weren't so demanding</u>
<u n="614" who="S0018" trans="overlap">I guess <unclear/> changed <pause dur="short"/> I wonder what has changed?</u>
<u n="615" who="S0036">Don't know <pause dur="short"/> they don't know you know <pause dur="short"/> I hear our doctors talking about it and even they say about like how demanding people are <pause dur="short"/> because people will go into them and say well I want this <pause dur="short"/> I want that <pause dur="short"/> I want a scan <pause dur="short"/> I want this <pause dur="short"/> I want <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="616" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mhm</u>
<u n="617" who="S0036">but then you think about people like my mum and my uncle where they needed those things but didn't ask for them and they weren't sent for them and their things got missed until they got</u>
<u n="618" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="619" who="S0036">my uncle's terminally ill <pause dur="short"/> he was going to the doctors for a couple of years</u>
<u n="620" who="S0018">really</u>
<u n="621" who="S0036">because he was bleeding <pause dur="short"/> classic symptom <pause dur="short"/> and they kept telling him it was piles <pause dur="short"/> and he believed them so he never said well you know can I go for a scan?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0036">he never pushed for it <pause dur="short"/> and now he's he's you know he's going to die because it spread to his liver <pause dur="short"/> it's too late</u>
<u n="624" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh gosh</u>
<u n="625" who="S0036">and then my mum <pause dur="short"/> her tumour had spread all around her lower abdomen</u>
<u n="626" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="627" who="S0036">and it started off in her appendix <pause dur="short"/> and that's when she was really really ill so if they had just got it they could have just took that out <pause dur="short"/> she'd have been fine</u>
<u n="628" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="629" who="S0036">but you know <pause dur="short"/> and then you get people who come in are demanding scans and x-rays and referrals and that <pause dur="short"/> and half the time there's nothing wrong with them and I think that's what I was going to say about doctors getting complacent that they see so many that are just a waste of time that they just they think that everybody is and and they don't send them maybe</u>
<u n="630" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="631" who="S0036">I don't know what it is but you just hear so many stories of erm you know <trunc>pe</trunc> people that are seriously ill and it's not getting picked up</u>
<u n="632" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="633" who="S0036">but then my mum's <pause dur="short"/> she did get get sent for the scopes eventually and even the scopes didn't find it</u>
<u n="634" who="S0018">hmm</u>
<u n="635" who="S0036">so until they MRI scanned her <pause dur="short"/> they didn't MRI scan her early enough</u>
<u n="636" who="S0018">what a shame <pause dur="short"/> yeah it seems crazy because I like Dad for example he's got erm he had some fungus under his nail or something</u>
<u n="637" who="S0036">mm</u>
<u n="638" who="S0018">and so he went to the doctors <pause dur="short"/> he had to have an appointment to go and see the doctor about it</u>
<u n="639" who="S0036">mm</u>
<u n="640" who="S0018">then he had to take a toe nail clipping and take it back and that had to be sent off to a lab to see if he actually <trunc>div</trunc></u>
<u n="641" who="S0036" trans="overlap">clippings <pause dur="short"/> mm that's right <pause dur="short"/> they have to grow it <pause dur="short"/> it takes a while as well because they actually have to grow it don't they to find out what it is</u>
<u n="642" who="S0018">oh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> really?</u>
<u n="643" who="S0036">yeah yeah they have to grow it <pause dur="short"/> if it's fungal they have to er culture the organism to find out what it is</u>
<u n="644" who="S0018">er</u>
<u n="645" who="S0036">and yeah</u>
<u n="646" who="S0018">and then</u>
<u n="647" who="S0036">Cos people phone up and say well I bought it in a week ago but it they they take a while those</u>
<u n="648" who="S0018">right <pause dur="short"/> but then he had to go back and have a live test to make sure that his liver was okay to take the drugs for the fungal infection</u>
<u n="649" who="S0036" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah right</u>
<u n="650" who="S0018">I'm just thinking <pause dur="short"/> when you know when doctors have to cope with people who are terminally ill and things like that why don't why can't you just do stuff like that in a pharmacy?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0036">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="652" who="S0018">and do it all over the counter and</u>
<u n="653" who="S0036">I mean I think this it what they'll <pause dur="short"/> cos they're going to try and start cutting down er the next thing big drive will be A and E appointments</u>
<u n="654" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="655" who="S0036">they're going to try because it's just <pause dur="short"/> they were telling us yesterday there was erm <pause dur="short"/> there was a documented case of er somebody who went to A and E <pause dur="short"/> and to get to A and E they'd have to walk past their doctors anyway to this hospital</u>
<u n="656" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="657" who="S0036">they had to actually go past their doctors <pause dur="short"/> and erm it was erm when I woke up this morning and my shoulder felt a bit funny <pause dur="short"/> I mean not even an emergency at the doctors</u>
<u n="658" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="659" who="S0036">you know and they went to A and E and it you know I mean that's what they get all the time isn't it?</u>
<u n="660" who="S0018">gosh</u>
<u n="661" who="S0036">and so they're going to try and er do something about it <pause dur="short"/> they're going to try and with GPs to try and do something about this</u>
<u n="662" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mhm</u>
<u n="663" who="S0036">because the A and E appointments <pause dur="short"/> every time somebody goes to A and E the cost is even greater than the the GPs <trunc>a</trunc> appointments and erm so they're going to try and do something about it</u>
<u n="664" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="665" who="S0036">I'm not quite sure what they're going to do</u>
<u n="666" who="S0018">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="667" who="S0036">Cos people are <pause dur="short"/> they're they're hypochondriacs</u>
<u n="668" who="S0018">yeah it's changing peoples attitudes more than anything else isn't it?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah that's it <pause dur="short"/> it is It is  that's exactly what it</u>
<u n="670" who="S0018">and how can you do that apart from you know trying to put up posters and trying to educate them <pause dur="short"/> make them realise the bigger picture that they're part of</u>
<u n="671" who="S0036">mm</u>
<u n="672" who="S0018">and if that doesn't work well they're <trunc>y</trunc> I mean yeah they have to start taking draconian measures to</u>
<u n="673" who="S0036" trans="overlap">and making them <pause dur="short"/> they've got  They've got  to know that the NHS isn't free</u>
<u n="674" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="675" who="S0036">they just think it's free <pause dur="short"/> it's not free</u>
<u n="676" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="677" who="S0036">none of it's free <pause dur="short"/> it's expensive <pause dur="short"/> really expensive <pause dur="short"/> so instead of like we flash our DNA appointments up <pause dur="short"/> at some surgeries they flash more information up now</u>
<u n="678" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="679" who="S0036">so we flash up you know sixty people didn't attend their appointments with doctors last month <pause dur="short"/> but that's all they flash up <pause dur="short"/> but they should start flashing up please cancel your appointment</u>
<u n="680" who="S0018" trans="overlap">name and shame</u>
<u n="681" who="S0036">this is the number to phone</u>
<u n="682" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="683" who="S0036">this is our email address <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ema</trunc> and they should start flashing up more information</u>
<u n="684" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="685" who="S0036">and they should flash up it costs the NHS whatever it is I forget the figure now <pause dur="short"/> fifty</u>
<u n="686" who="S0018" trans="overlap">or start penalising people who don't <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0036" trans="overlap">mm they can't they're not allowed to charge them <pause dur="short"/> they told us that yesterday</u>
<u n="688" who="S0067">Carolynn <pause dur="short"/> while you're there can you are you recording me as well?</u>
<u n="689" who="S0036">yeah recording you now as well <pause dur="short"/> no it's fine you can carry on <pause dur="short"/> you can talk as well <pause dur="short"/> I've already asked</u>
<u n="690" who="S0018" trans="overlap">Don't worry</u>
<u n="691" who="S0067">can you look up Mrs Knowles?</u>
<u n="692" who="S0036">K?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0067">yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0066">did you hear the one about <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="695" who="S0018">go on tell us <pause dur="short"/> tell us</u>
<u n="696" who="S0036">it looks like we've got a work number for her <pause dur="short"/> is it sixteen Parklands?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0067" trans="overlap">parklands</u>
<u n="698" who="S0036">what do you want her home number?</u>
<u n="699" who="S0067">yeah</u>
<u n="700" who="S0018">can you remember the joke about the doctor and the God?</u>
<u n="701" who="S0036">about doctors thinking they're Gods</u>
<u n="702" who="S0067">no I can't <pause dur="short"/> no I can't no</u>
<u n="703" who="S0036">anyway let me tell you this <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> from yesterday cos it's erm hang on <pause dur="short"/> seven O five <pause dur="short"/> that's her home number</u>
<u n="704" who="S0067">oh ta</u>
<u n="705" who="S0036">we've got her work number as well I think <pause dur="short"/> erm we had this er thing yesterday <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I only stayed for a part of it <pause dur="short"/> but they were talking about all this erm stuff with the NHS they're going to be doing and that</u>
<u n="706" who="S0067">mm</u>
<u n="707" who="S0036">and about managing patients and everything <pause dur="short"/> and they've <trunc>re</trunc> done research on this <pause dur="short"/> and they said to us never ever ever ever be  Never ever <pause dur="short"/> never tell somebody that their er X-ray will be back in four to six days cos they don't hear the six days they hear the four days</u>
<u n="708" who="S0067">yeah four days so I'll bear that in mind will I <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="709" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> do you know? And they've researched it <pause dur="short"/> they've done research on it to find out what is it that makes people pick up? It's because they always want the best scenario for themselves</u>
<u n="710" who="S0067" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="711" who="S0036">so they'll automatically cut out what they don't want to hear and what they do want to hear <pause dur="short"/> never say four to six days <pause dur="short"/> say six days</u>
<u n="712" who="S0067">yeah or two to three weeks <unclear/></u>
<u n="713" who="S0036" trans="overlap">never say up to six days <pause dur="short"/> say six days <pause dur="short"/> don't</u>
<u n="714" who="S0067" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0036">even if you know it's up to six days and it will back in four don't tell them that <pause dur="short"/> tell them six days <pause dur="short"/> never say I'll try <pause dur="short"/> never say I'll try and get that <pause dur="short"/> this is but obviously it relates to here</u>
<u n="716" who="S0067">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="717" who="S0036">I'll try and get that prescription done for you today <pause dur="short"/> cos they don't here try they'll hear I'll get that prescription done for you today <pause dur="short"/> and they're on the phone at the end of the day where's my prescription?</u>
<u n="718" who="S0067" trans="overlap"><unclear/> do you know it's a good thing? <unclear/></u>
<u n="719" who="S0036">never say might <pause dur="short"/> never say it might be tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> it might be the next day <pause dur="short"/> say it'll be next week</u>
<u n="720" who="S0067">yeah</u>
<u n="721" who="S0036">even if you think it might be the because they don't hear it</u>
<u n="722" who="S0067">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="723" who="S0036">and it's been researched apparently</u>
<u n="724" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="725" who="S0036">of what people they they say to people <pause dur="short"/> they do it and then they say well what what what what were you just told? Er I was told it would be four weeks <pause dur="short"/> and they weren't <pause dur="short"/> they were told it would be four to six weeks but they don't hear it</u>
<u n="726" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="727" who="S0036">and it's something to do with erm er biology and our evolution and and what about kind of picking out what's best for us</u>
<u n="728" who="S0067" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Selective memory that's what it is <pause dur="short"/> you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="729" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="730" who="S0067">yeah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0036">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> and so they were saying all these different things that get said at doctor surgeries to people <pause dur="short"/> and that what you shouldn't be saying because of what they're picking up</u>
<u n="732" who="S0018">mm that's interesting</u>
<u n="733" who="S0067" trans="overlap">that's what that Paul Simon said <pause dur="short"/> you pick out what you want to hear and disregard the rest <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="734" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="735" who="S0036" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> so I just thought it was really interesting as I was sitting there thinking this is just so relevant when you tell people oh it could be <pause dur="short"/> it'll be a couple of weeks</u>
<u n="736" who="S0067">yeah</u>
<u n="737" who="S0036">or or or I'll try and call in tonight on my way home and then they <trunc>pho</trunc></u>
<u n="738" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="739" who="S0067">yeah</u>
<u n="740" who="S0036">and then they <trunc>pho</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> cos they phone and I'll say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oh you were supposed to go to <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> last night <pause dur="short"/> she's been on the phone saying you were <pause dur="short"/> and he says no I didn't say that <pause dur="short"/> I told her I would try and go</u>
<u n="741" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="742" who="S0036" trans="overlap">or I you know I might call in on the way home but and it happens all the time <trunc>St</trunc></u>
<u n="743" who="S0067" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I'll call in <pause dur="short"/> you know if it's like they want me to do something and I haven't got time to do it cos I've been booked up <pause dur="short"/> instead of saying I'll come around in three weeks time I say to them <pause dur="short"/> I'll try and pop round one night in the week after work <pause dur="short"/> you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="745" who="S0036" trans="overlap">and some people they they do</u>
<u n="746" who="S0067" trans="overlap">and they they take it as face value if if you told them that on a Tuesday <trunc>the</trunc> on the Wednesday they might think you're going to turn up or whatever you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="747" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="748" who="S0036">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="749" who="S0067">so er <trunc>e</trunc> I'll just have to say to people no</u>
<u n="750" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="751" who="S0036">well that's it yeah</u>
<u n="752" who="S0067">learn to say no</u>
<u n="753" who="S0036">that's what they said yesterday <pause dur="short"/> they had it  They had it  on this <trunc>Power</trunc> Powerpoint display <pause dur="short"/> and they had don't be woolly be precise</u>
<u n="754" who="S0067">yeah</u>
<u n="755" who="S0036">Don't don't say might try er four to six days <pause dur="short"/> don't just stop</u>
<u n="756" who="S0067">mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="757" who="S0036">doing it altogether</u>
<u n="758" who="S0067">yeah</u>
<u n="759" who="S0018">yeah it's like managing people's expectations isn't it and</u>
<u n="760" who="S0067">yeah</u>
<u n="761" who="S0036">so I went down yesterday and when when I got back downstairs after this course yesterday it was so busy <pause dur="short"/> it well there was this poor woman that comes into to help out that used to work there years ago</u>
<u n="762" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="763" who="S0036">and she was the only person on the desk and it was absolute <pause dur="short"/> I could tell she was stressed she was bright red and it was crazy <pause dur="short"/> and the phones were ringing so I was picking up the phones <pause dur="short"/> so this bloke rings up and he says erm cos the doctors don't fill in forms for people <pause dur="short"/> they charge for it but it's not a priority</u>
<u n="764" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="765" who="S0036">they can put them back for weeks you know because obviously the medical stuff takes priority <pause dur="short"/> and erm they do do them eventually because they like to have the money but they don't like doing it <pause dur="short"/> especially the male doctors <pause dur="short"/> they don't like filling in the forms</u>
<u n="766" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="767" who="S0036">and er this guy rang up and said er he dropped this compensation form in and had the doctor done it? And I said well when did you bring it in? And he went last week <pause dur="short"/> I said no <pause dur="short"/> I said it won't be done <pause dur="short"/> and he said well will it be done this week? And I went no</u>
<u n="768" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="769" who="S0036">I went no</u>
<u n="770" who="S0066">you sound <pause dur="short"/> you feel awful don't you</u>
<u n="771" who="S0036">I'd just been on this course <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="772" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="773" who="S0036">so I cos I thought well I know it won't be done</u>
<u n="774" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="775" who="S0036">I thought it's no good me saying it might be because I know it won't be done</u>
<u n="776" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="777" who="S0036">and erm</u>
<u n="778" who="S0066">what did he say <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="779" who="S0036" trans="overlap">anyway I said let me look on your erm screen and of course what it is we're getting more and more and more of this <unclear/> people constantly trying to claim money for things that have happened to them</u>
<u n="780" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="781" who="S0036">there's constantly forms coming in for people trying to get money for accidents and what have you</u>
<u n="782" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="783" who="S0036">so I looked on his screen and it  and it  had said this form had been passed to the doctor <pause dur="short"/> and I said well he has got it <pause dur="short"/> it has been passed to him <pause dur="short"/> so he said well could you ask him when he's going to do it for me? And I went no <pause dur="short"/> I said because there's no mileage in me doing that because he he won't tell me</u>
<u n="784" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="785" who="S0036">so he said well do you think somebody could just tell him to try and get it done for me this week? So I went no <pause dur="short"/> cos it's like I just know the doctor won't do it <pause dur="short"/> they just it the doctor would look at me as if to say who the hell do you think you are? Speaking to me and telling me to do this form</u>
<u n="786" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="787" who="S0036">anyway so I said to him erm <pause dur="short"/> I said I tell you what I said <pause dur="short"/> you speak to the doctor and you ask him to get that form for you this week <pause dur="short"/> I said phone back between twelve thirty and one O'clock when the doctors are out the back <pause dur="short"/> ask to speak to him <pause dur="short"/> and you tell him that you want that form done this week <pause dur="short"/> and I put the phone down <pause dur="short"/> he went oh okay thank you thank you and put the phone down</u>
<u n="788" who="S0018">ah did he phone?</u>
<u n="789" who="S0036" trans="overlap">I just sat there and I went good luck with that one</u>
<u n="790" who="S0018">do you know whether he phoned?</u>
<u n="791" who="S0036" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="792" who="S0018">that would have been interesting to be a fly on a wall in that conversation</u>
<u n="793" who="S0036">I just does he want some money for something that has happened to him?</u>
<u n="794" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="795" who="S0036">well it doesn't make any difference whether that forms done now or whether it's done in there months time <pause dur="short"/> as long as he's put a claim in he'll still get it if he's entitled to it</u>
<u n="796" who="S0018">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="797" who="S0036">but erm oh no no he wants the money and he wants it now</u>
<u n="798" who="S0018">yep <pause dur="short"/> anyone can delay gratification nowadays</u>
<u n="799" who="S0036">mm</u>
<u n="800" who="S0018">it's all about want it yesterday</u>
<u n="801" who="S0036">so er anyway</u>
<u n="802" who="S0018">crazy crazy <pause dur="short"/> so you're going to visit your mum tonight?</u>
<u n="803" who="S0036">yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0018">in <anon type="place"/> what's the deal with house sit then? What's she doing?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0036">they they erm it's er they've worked for them for years <pause dur="short"/> they were just erm a couple of gynaecologists <pause dur="short"/> they used to live in another house on <unclear/> Road and they used to sit for them there <pause dur="short"/> and they've got a</u>
<u n="806" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh you <pause dur="short"/> did your parents sit at my parents' house to look after the cats?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="808" who="S0018">ah ha</u>
<u n="809" who="S0036">and erm so they've got cats</u>
<u n="810" who="S0067" trans="overlap"><unclear/> got back and they were traumatised</u>
<u n="811" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="812" who="S0036">what your parents or the cats?</u>
<u n="813" who="S0018">your parents probably <pause dur="short"/> knowing my own parents' cats</u>
<u n="814" who="S0067" trans="overlap"><unclear/> cultivating drugs in <unclear/> Two or three days</u>
<u n="815" who="S0036" trans="overlap"><unclear/> because because of being er you know she pops round here and she could have a little walk up the parade and you know</u>
<u n="816" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="817" who="S0036">and she doesn't tend to sort of go out much but erm you know it's just a nice little spot isn't it round there <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="818" who="S0018">so that is she looking after animals in <unclear/> Road?</u>
<u n="819" who="S0036">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> well <trunc>sh</trunc> the house <pause dur="short"/> they look after the house and obviously it makes it more secure doesn't it if you've got somebody stopping there</u>
<u n="820" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="821" who="S0036">and erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah they've got erm a couple of dogs and about four cats and a couple of birds haven't they <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="822" who="S0067">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> lovely location <unclear/> to <anon type="place"/> Park</u>
<u n="823" who="S0018">gorgeous isn't it?</u>
<u n="824" who="S0067">absolutely fantastic</u>
<u n="825" who="S0018">I go to yoga class down there and just walking down that road and seeing all those houses and</u>
<u n="826" who="S0067" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="827" who="S0036">I mean some of them are erm some of them are in er broken into flats aren't they</u>
<u n="828" who="S0018" trans="overlap">it's so green as well <pause dur="short"/> yep</u>
<u n="829" who="S0036">but there's a lot of <pause dur="short"/> I think there's quite a few doctors that live down there and erm they've just got those great big houses all to themselves</u>
<u n="830" who="S0067">they're the only ones that can afford to live there now aren't they <unclear/> you know</u>
<u n="831" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> but you just think when the NHS is in <trunc>st</trunc> such a state do people really need to earn one thousand?</u>
<u n="832" who="S0036" trans="overlap">well <trunc>the</trunc> I mean these guys they work for the NHS but they've got private er practice as well</u>
<u n="833" who="S0018" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> they get even more</u>
<u n="834" who="S0036">but I mean she was on erm you know when they did that program on hospitals and they had different aspects of erm <pause dur="short"/> they had one about A and E <pause dur="short"/> they had one about erm teenage pregnancy</u>
<u n="835" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="836" who="S0036">er and erm then another one <pause dur="short"/> I forget what the other one was <pause dur="short"/> and every time time they had it they were our programs and erm they had an expert talking and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the the lady <pause dur="short"/> she was the expert on the program about erm yeah teenage pregnancies and that and about erm er because you know obviously she does caesareans and things like that as well so</u>
<u n="837" who="S0067" trans="overlap">specialist isn't she?</u>
<u n="838" who="S0018" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> mhm</u>
<u n="839" who="S0036">erm she was the er expert and it was she was really good wasn't she John <pause dur="short"/> because they were interviewing her and she was talking <pause dur="short"/> she's a I mean she's a really lovely women anyway</u>
<u n="840" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="841" who="S0036">and she just used to say something and then she'd just give this really wry smile because she couldn't comment on these teenage pregnancies but she just gave this slightly wry smile in between sentences <pause dur="short"/> like just said a thousand words even though she wasn't saying it <pause dur="short"/> she was really really really good</u>
<u n="842" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> one smile</u>
<u n="843" who="S0067" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="844" who="S0036">it was a TV natural <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> tV natural <pause dur="short"/> because she's Irish and she's just lovely <pause dur="short"/> mum and Dad really really like her and er</u>
<u n="845" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> and where have they gone?</u>
<u n="846" who="S0036">er skiing aren't they  skiing aren't they  They sit for them about four times a year</u>
<u n="847" who="S0018">oh lovely</u>
<u n="848" who="S0036">they're skiing this time <pause dur="short"/> erm but they just they're just really really nice people <pause dur="short"/> and cos because she's a gynaecologist and that and she's knows a lot of <pause dur="short"/> when my mum had to go and see the oncologist when we found out it was cancer which takes eight weeks before we knew she actually got cancer</u>
<u n="849" who="S0018" trans="overlap">uh-huh</u>
<u n="850" who="S0036">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm said to my mum let me know when your appointment is and I'll meet you there</u>
<u n="851" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="852" who="S0036">and she took the time out of it <pause dur="short"/> she got her husband to take over her clinic because I think it was the private bit they doing</u>
<u n="853" who="S0018" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> uh-huh</u>
<u n="854" who="S0036">and then she met my mum at the oncologists and then she said to my mum how much do you want to know? And my mum and dad just said well just whatever you know whatever it is the situation is we're going to need to know <pause dur="short"/> because she wanted to know how much to ask in front of my mum and dad and whether they wanted to hear the answers or not</u>
<u n="855" who="S0018">right mhm</u>
<u n="856" who="S0036">but she knew exactly what to ask</u>
<u n="857" who="S0018">okay</u>
<u n="858" who="S0036">questions that you just wouldn't know to ask yourself</u>
<u n="859" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="860" who="S0036">about the treatments and just things like you know are you going for a cure or is it palliative? And all that sort of thing</u>
<u n="861" who="S0018" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="862" who="S0036">so but luckily they were going for a cure</u>
<u n="863" who="S0018">and has she responded well to treatments?</u>
<u n="864" who="S0036">erm we don't know <pause dur="short"/> she's waiting now for a</u>
<u n="865" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="866" who="S0036">she's just had all the tests again</u>
<u n="867" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="868" who="S0036">so she's waiting for the results</u>
<u n="869" who="S0018">gosh so it must be stressful timings</u>
<u n="870" who="S0036">yeah</u>
<u n="871" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="872" who="S0036">yeah so</u>
<u n="873" who="S0018">and how long?</u>
<u n="874" who="S0036">I've told  I've told  her what to I've told her to phone them <pause dur="short"/> I've told her what to ask because I see the reports</u>
<u n="875" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="876" who="S0036">and erm so I've said you need to ask this <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> you need to ask about erm whether it's all been removed and how much of it that whether they've excised it all if it is cancer <pause dur="short"/> what they've snipped out and that <pause dur="short"/> but erm she phoned the doctors and erm they haven't had it yet</u>
<u n="877" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="878" who="S0036">so well they probably have had it and it's probably sitting waiting to be scanned on which is what happens at our surgery</u>
<u n="879" who="S0018">really</u>
<u n="880" who="S0036">so</u>
<u n="881" who="S0018">is she seeing a doctor at your surgery or?</u>
<u n="882" who="S0036">no no no <pause dur="short"/> she erm goes to one in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="883" who="S0018">oh right do they live around there?</u>
<u n="884" who="S0036">they live yeah they live in <anon type="place"/> <trunc>Ko</trunc> <unclear/> off <unclear/> Road</u>
<u n="885" who="S0018">ah not far from my nan</u>
<u n="886" who="S0036">oh right <pause dur="short"/> oh really?</u>
<u n="887" who="S0018">she's in Ardenvale Road</u>
<u n="888" who="S0036">oh right <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure which one that is</u>
<u n="889" who="S0018">just after the roundabout <pause dur="short"/> you know the roundabout when you come off the duel carriageway from <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="891" who="S0018">where the the rugby club is?</u>
<u n="892" who="S0036">I don't know the rugby club but I know roughly where you mean</u>
<u n="893" who="S0018" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="894" who="S0067" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="895" who="S0036">do I? Yeah</u>
<u n="896" who="S0018">erm</u>
<u n="897" who="S0067">you know by the island where that wasteland is where the gypsies were?</u>
<u n="898" who="S0018">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="899" who="S0036">oh right oh okay <pause dur="short"/> oh no I'm thinking of the wrong island then</u>
<u n="900" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="901" who="S0018">it's first on the left after that island</u>
<u n="902" who="S0036">oh right I'm thinking of the wrong island <pause dur="short"/> I'm thinking of that island as you go before you get go into <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="903" who="S0067" trans="overlap"><unclear/> your nan's road at the bottom</u>
<u n="904" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="905" who="S0067">and went up where the gypsies were camped</u>
<u n="906" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="907" who="S0067">cal's mum and dad's house is the other side of the big wall on the right hand side</u>
<u n="908" who="S0018">oh oh okay</u>
<u n="909" who="S0067">so it's literally as the crow flies it's not far at all</u>
<u n="910" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah cool <pause dur="short"/> and where do you guys live?</u>
<u n="911" who="S0036">maypole</u>
<u n="912" who="S0018">where's that? Maypole?</u>
<u n="913" who="S0036">erm you go through erm do you know <anon type="place"/> Lodge?</u>
<u n="914" who="S0018">mhm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="915" who="S0036">erm you go through <anon type="place"/> Lodge and you keep going and then before you get to the big big Maypole island with the Sainsbury's and the Travel Lodge</u>
<u n="916" who="S0018">mhm</u>
<u n="917" who="S0036">before you get to the <trunc>bypa</trunc> do you know the bypass that goes out to <anon type="place"/>? </u>
<u n="918" who="S0018">right yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0036">erm we just live <pause dur="short"/> we just turn off right before you get to that big island and we just live in one of those</u>
<u n="920" who="S0018">oh lovely <pause dur="short"/> so that's quite close to Moseley isn't <pause dur="short"/> it's just up the road</u>
<u n="921" who="S0036">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="922" who="S0067" trans="overlap">yeah well we lived in the road before years ago we lived in the road which will runs parallel to us when on the main <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="923" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="924" who="S0067">and that was <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="925" who="S0018">ah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="926" who="S0067">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="927" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="928" who="S0067">so it's like a</u>
<u n="929" who="S0018">oh I like <anon type="place"/> too <pause dur="short"/> it's a nice nice atmosphere there as well <pause dur="short"/> good pubs</u>
<u n="930" who="S0067" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="931" who="S0036" trans="overlap">that's been so many <pause dur="short"/> we drove through <anon type="place"/> the other day and we were amazed weren't we of what was there and what wasn't there <pause dur="short"/> it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="932" who="S0067" trans="overlap">you know we spent so much time here it has been years</u>
<u n="933" who="S0018">really</u>
<u n="934" who="S0067">probably three years or something like that since we've been down the <anon type="place"/> <unclear/> drive down there it would be like driving into another world you know</u>
<u n="935" who="S0036" trans="overlap">Cos I used to drive down there everyday to get to work</u>
<u n="936" who="S0018" trans="overlap">really? What's changed?</u>
<u n="937" who="S0067">yeah well we we cos I was brought up in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="938" who="S0036" trans="overlap">just shops and that</u>
<u n="939" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="940" who="S0067">do you know what I mean? So we know the area really well</u>
<u n="941" who="S0036">well there's some buildings for a start on the left hand side as you go through it's like hang on a minute there used to be <pause dur="short"/> wasn't there a little car park there? And it's like oh it's those buildings?</u>
<u n="942" who="S0067" trans="overlap">the shops have changed</u>
<u n="943" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="944" who="S0067">and we're like where's McDonald's? Where's McDonald's?</u>
<u n="945" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="946" who="S0067">not that we <trunc>thou</trunc> not that we wanted a burger but do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="947" who="S0066">it's all coming out now</u>
<u n="948" who="S0067">you think how can how can  McDonald's be closed? You know</u>
<u n="949" who="S0036" trans="overlap">that was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> obviously <pause dur="short"/> not me</u>
<u n="950" who="S0067">I think it was just boarded up <pause dur="short"/> was it boarded up? Or was it another shop there?</u>
<u n="951" who="S0036">I can't remember now <pause dur="short"/> it's just really different</u>
<u n="952" who="S0018" trans="overlap">it's probably a kebab shop nowadays</u>
<u n="953" who="S0067">yeah</u>
<u n="954" who="S0036">probably <pause dur="short"/> or a Subway <pause dur="short"/> they seem to be doing alright <pause dur="short"/> actually Subway's taking over a lot of McDonald's <pause dur="short"/> I heard it on the radio the other day</u>
<u n="955" who="S0067">yeah</u>
<u n="956" who="S0036">subway's taking up a lot of the McDonald's that are closing down <pause dur="short"/> cos they're apparently they're doing really well <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how cos they're so expensive</u>
<u n="957" who="S0018">they are <pause dur="short"/> and they taste like cardboard</u>
<u n="958" who="S0036" trans="overlap">yeah I</u>
<u n="959" who="S0067" trans="overlap">yeah but they're the healthy option aren't they <pause dur="short"/> yeah they do taste like cardboard you're right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="960" who="S0018">I don't like them at all</u>
<u n="961" who="S0036">I I'm not keen on there rolls <pause dur="short"/> they just kind of disappear to nothing don't they?</u>
<u n="962" who="S0018">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="963" who="S0036">you you bit them and they just go like they go like that</u>
<u n="964" who="S0018">it's just like eating plastic and cardboard <pause dur="short"/> at least with a McDonald's you know that you're eating crap even though it tastes nice</u>
<u n="965" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="966" who="S0067">be up front about it</u>
<u n="967" who="S0036">whereas with Subway you see them and they look really nice don't they on the pictures and that and then you bite them and</u>
<u n="968" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="969" who="S0036">it's the bread <pause dur="short"/> I don't mind the fillings <pause dur="short"/> it's the bread <pause dur="short"/> just that I don't <pause dur="short"/> the bread's not very good</u>
<u n="970" who="S0018">yuk <pause dur="short"/> yuk yuk <pause dur="short"/> right well I'm going to let you get back to work <pause dur="short"/> have you got a lot on today?</u>
<u n="971" who="S0036">erm well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> goes <unclear/></u>
<u n="972" who="S0067" trans="overlap">there's always something to do isn't there?</u>
<u n="973" who="S0036">yeah</u>
<u n="974" who="S0018" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="975" who="S0036">there's always something</u>
<u n="976" who="S0067" trans="overlap"><unclear/> go and order that pipe later on can't we</u>
<u n="977" who="S0036">yeah okay</u>
<u n="978" who="S0067">so we'll have to look through that book and you know sort what <unclear/></u>
<u n="979" who="S0036" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> I was going to sit and put the er the voices on here actually</u>
</body>
</text>
