<text id="SMGY">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:54:48</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-07-06</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0435 S0436</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Theatre, music, books, technology, radio, education, friends, film and TV, family, pets and household, politics</topics>
		<activity>Sisters chatting</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, inquiring, complaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0435">
				<exactage>15</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Crawley, West Sussex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South Eastern RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Horsham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>15 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0436">
				<exactage>22</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Crawley, West Sussex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Standard Southern British English/RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Horsham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>student (just graduated)</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0436"><vocal desc="yawn"/> right then anyway I don't know whether you did have anything to say well I'm going to use the opportunity of having you cornered to make you tell me all about your erm Oliver performance</u>
<u n="2" who="S0435">if you insist</u>
<u n="3" who="S0436">well yes I want to know go on</u>
<u n="4" who="S0435"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm what about it in particular?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0436">I just want to know how it went</u>
<u n="6" who="S0435">yeah?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0436">cos you never told me anything <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0435">well it generally went quite well nothing very eventful happened or at least not that I could see happening being not on the stage</u>
<u n="9" who="S0436">in the pit</u>
<u n="10" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0435" trans="overlap">pit yes</u>
<u n="12" who="S0436">they exile the orchestra to a hole in the ground</u>
<u n="13" who="S0435">it's a very nice hole in the ground</u>
<u n="14" who="S0436"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0435">we get a much more spacious sort of so the the for the amount of people there are you get a lot more space as an orchestra player than you go as a person being an actor</u>
<u n="16" who="S0436">you mean what they have backstage?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="18" who="S0436">fair enough I suppose they just have a lot of them and they have to squeeze into the dressing rooms or something don't they?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0435">and there were sofas down there</u>
<u n="20" who="S0436">sofas in the pit?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0435">no in the bit behind it</u>
<u n="22" who="S0436">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0435">so it was very nice</u>
<u n="24" who="S0436">I was thinking I have never been in a pit with sofas in it that would be interesting</u>
<u n="25" who="S0435" trans="overlap">well there was there there there was the sort of stand falling over and that that was that was eventful</u>
<u n="26" who="S0436" trans="overlap">oh yes you said it collapsed on to the piano or</u>
<u n="27" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="28" who="S0436">oh yes but does not the piano was okay?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0435">er it was a keyboard so</u>
<u n="30" who="S0436">oh well fair enough who cares then you know it's only well however many hundred pounds</u>
<u n="31" who="S0435">yes it's but it's quite old it's it's the school's one</u>
<u n="32" who="S0436">fair enough but er anyway so but how is the oboe part I you know?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0435">it's it it's reasonably good it's</u>
<u n="34" who="S0436">do you get any tunes</u>
<u n="35" who="S0435">er yeah I did actually</u>
<u n="36" who="S0436">lucky thing</u>
<u n="37" who="S0435">well the first violin part was much better</u>
<u n="38" who="S0436">yeah well that's what you get if you're a first violinist</u>
<u n="39" who="S0435">you get silly you get silly cadenzas and everything</u>
<u n="40" who="S0436"><vocal desc="laugh"/> where do they have silly cadenzas in Oliver?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0435">in the erm Fagin number you know the one where he just wanders around the stage</u>
<u n="42" who="S0436">oh yeah I Think I'd Better Think it Out Again</u>
<u n="43" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="44" who="S0436">I like that one</u>
<u n="45" who="S0435">and yeah <pause dur="long"/> it's when people cos we've stretched them out and shortened them a bit it was all sort of a bit conductor going no no stop and the violinists going to have to get to the end of this cadence</u>
<u n="46" who="S0436">who was the conductor?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0435">erm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0436">one of the music teachers</u>
<u n="49" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="50" who="S0436">do I know them?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0435">probably not</u>
<u n="52" who="S0436">so it wasn't they erm the lady with the loud velvet clothes</u>
<u n="53" who="S0435" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="54" who="S0436">what's she called again?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0435">Miss <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0436">ah yes I keep on forgetting her name it sort of mentally rewrite her as our know that one with the clothes</u>
<u n="57" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0436">obviously they all have clothes but you know what I mean</u>
<u n="59" who="S0435">I think she did it I think she did it last year</u>
<u n="60" who="S0436">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0435">I think this is first year she hasn't done it you know</u>
<u n="62" who="S0436"><trunc>o</trunc><trunc>o</trunc>other teachings just have clothes whereas she as you know clothes</u>
<u n="63" who="S0435">yes no yeah but there was erm I'm not sure what's happening next year because the erm drama teacher who does it erm the music teacher who's who did it this year aren't going to be there so they're leaving</u>
<u n="64" who="S0436">oh they're leaving are they?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="66" who="S0436">heavens</u>
<u n="67" who="S0435">so it's all a bit of a sort of luck to what we're ending up doing I think one of the ones people think is likely to happen is Hairspray which I think it's rubbish</u>
<u n="68" who="S0436">is it? I'll admit I watched it and I now don't remember you know I watched the video thingy of it</u>
<u n="69" who="S0435">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0436">and I don't remember any of the music from it which is not a good sign no I lie I remember one bit of music from it but that's I don't remember it for being in Hairspray</u>
<u n="71" who="S0435">fair enough I don't know</u>
<u n="72" who="S0436">well</u>
<u n="73" who="S0435">I I I think there are quite a lot of things I think they ought to do but they never would cos they'll never do Sunset Boulevard quite apart from the fact it probably not fitting into their appropriate standards although they have down Oliver Miss Saigon and Les Mis so you can't really</u>
<u n="74" who="S0436">well especially Miss Saigon come on</u>
<u n="75" who="S0435" trans="overlap"> gon but erm quite apart from that nobody likes the music</u>
<u n="76" who="S0436">no I don't think that's even the problem I think the problem is it has three main roles</u>
<u n="77" who="S0435">yeah but it's got</u>
<u n="78" who="S0436" trans="overlap">and no one else gets to do anything</u>
<u n="79" who="S0435">but the chorusy bits are proper chorusy bits</u>
<u n="80" who="S0436">oh yeah but I mean there really aren't very many chorusy bits is my point</u>
<u n="81" who="S0435">yeah but I think there are ones that come up a lot worse than that in terms of nothing but solo parts</u>
<u n="82" who="S0436">yeah fair enough I wouldn't know I'm not as educated in the matter of musicals as I probably ought to be considering how much time they spend listening to them</u>
<u n="83" who="S0435">I don't know I think that</u>
<u n="84" who="S0436">your sister's useless</u>
<u n="85" who="S0435">I have an entirely different everyone else is saying even though it's probably not possible for licensing reasons everyone and their dog wants to do Wicked</u>
<u n="86" who="S0436" trans="overlap">oh this is the Wicked thing again</u>
<u n="87" who="S0435">cos I think they're making it into a film at the moment aren't they?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0436">oh yes I heard that</u>
<u n="89" who="S0435">so you won't be able to get licensing I'm sort of ninety-nine percent sure you wouldn't be able to get licensing</u>
<u n="90" who="S0436">I thought you liked it</u>
<u n="91" who="S0435">yeah well I think the best bit about it isn't the music</u>
<u n="92" who="S0436">fair enough the costuming is good</u>
<u n="93" who="S0435">the costuming and sets sort of would definitely put the music to shame</u>
<u n="94" who="S0436">yeah well it's I mean I can't judge it's it's not my style of music and frankly that sort of narrative isn't thrilling me either so yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0435" trans="overlap">and if you're going and I don't know if you're going to do tacky pop music musicals it</u>
<u n="96" who="S0436">you should do Mamma Mia <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0435">no no no you should do Legally Blonde cos that one's just funny that one is just it's it's ridiculously American but it's funny and it's actually got some quite music in it for being a silly pop music musical</u>
<u n="98" who="S0436">I don't understand where you developed your sudden obsession with Legally Blonde</u>
<u n="99" who="S0435">it's really it's ridiculously tacky but it's good</u>
<u n="100" who="S0436">is this your friends on the internet again?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0435">no not really</u>
<u n="102" who="S0436">or is it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> an influence or</u>
<u n="103" who="S0435" trans="overlap">no no I don't think it ever has done</u>
<u n="104" who="S0436">well I really don't understand it then</u>
<u n="105" who="S0435">well ah <pause dur="short"/> well the one everyone likes at the moment is on the er erm internety people I know at the moment is a one a <trunc>ve</trunc>very recent one that's about Shakespeare</u>
<u n="106" who="S0436">erm a musical that's about Shakespeare</u>
<u n="107" who="S0435" trans="overlap"><trunc>sha</trunc> yes</u>
<u n="108" who="S0436">er go on you have to elaborate now</u>
<u n="109" who="S0435">I think it pretty much comes down to it it's not as in they put Shakespeare to music it's a musical about the guy Shakespeare</u>
<u n="110" who="S0436" trans="overlap">about I gathered that cos musicals based on Shakespeare plays already exist that's what you should do you should definitely put on Shakespeare for kids</u>
<u n="111" who="S0435">oh no</u>
<u n="112" who="S0436">yes</u>
<u n="113" who="S0435">I think if you're going that you ought to do</u>
<u n="114" who="S0436" trans="overlap">complete with the sheepskin costume thing</u>
<u n="115" who="S0435">no I I think they ought to do that erm the <trunc>re</trunc> the very weird musical version of Much Ado About Nothing that actually had some quite decent music</u>
<u n="116" who="S0436" trans="overlap">that's just because it has Paul Mcgann in and Paul Mcgann with not come to your school <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0435">no I I just found it hilarious that somebody did that</u>
<u n="118" who="S0436">bless you</u>
<u n="119" who="S0435">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0436">oh dear speaking of Paul Mcgann you were saying weren't you? have you heard anything more about your</u>
<u n="121" who="S0435">oh the rivers of London?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0436">yes and your optimistic</u>
<u n="123" who="S0435">but he no no no no no it's erm there's there's the it's so far there's it it has been it's a project that's being openly done by sort of said to be being done and so that's all fine cos it's erm they're sort of it's they haven't yet cast anyone or officially put down anyone's name sort of for anything in particular yet but well</u>
<u n="124" who="S0436">then personally I wouldn't put any faith in it but</u>
<u n="125" who="S0435">mm well the the fact that they've just been done very well on the erm the the the Jonathan Strange and Mr Norrell television thing</u>
<u n="126" who="S0436">oh it's the same people doing it is it?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="128" who="S0436">oh fair enough oh hang on you said that before didn't you?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0435">yeah and so it's the same people doing it</u>
<u n="130" who="S0436" trans="overlap">I just wasn't listening obviously</u>
<u n="131" who="S0435">and they've had quite a lot of a success there</u>
<u n="132" who="S0436">mm</u>
<u n="133" who="S0435">but it's sort of still hopeful that they might it's not that they've er and it's not just that they've said oh we will do this it's a sort of they've officially put it on their website as one of the projects we're working towards so</u>
<u n="134" who="S0436" trans="overlap">mm that's <unclear>seems okay</unclear> yeah by the way when I finish that Jonathan Strange and Mr Norrell ha ha she says being you know two hundred pages through it or something it's quite a dense book really I mean</u>
<u n="135" who="S0435">for something which is really not erm for kind of</u>
<u n="136" who="S0436" trans="overlap">it's kind of embarrassing to admit that but I don't know I think I've just lost the knack of reading things sort of for pleasure so many academic articles er but anyhow but anyway when I finish it would you be keen to join me in watching the television thing you know I'm no good at watching television by myself</u>
<u n="137" who="S0435">I've already watched it but I'll watch it again</u>
<u n="138" who="S0436">well that was sort of what I was asking</u>
<u n="139" who="S0435">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0436">hang on has the final one come out already?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0435">oh yes last week or the week before or something</u>
<u n="142" who="S0436">oh fair enough I'm just behind the times aren't I? then again what else should I expect but er but anyway it was good was it?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0435">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0436">well yeah promising</u>
<u n="145" who="S0435">you've probably come <trunc>go</trunc> across what's his name John Segundus and you have to admit he's he's he's lovely</u>
<u n="146" who="S0436">he's only been in the book a bit so far basically at the beginning</u>
<u n="147" who="S0435" trans="overlap">he never gets much further he's never a main main character but</u>
<u n="148" who="S0436">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0435">he's he's recurring none main character</u>
<u n="150" who="S0436">he seems like one of the more decent people in it so far</u>
<u n="151" who="S0435">and what the his er hit his friend erm <unclear>Mr Honeyford</unclear></u>
<u n="152" who="S0436">oh yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0435">you know they're nice</u>
<u n="154" who="S0436">well I don't know kind of <unclear>Mr Honeyford</unclear> was a bit of a I don't know a pompous caricature kind of character but</u>
<u n="155" who="S0435" trans="overlap">yes but I think he's nice they're nicer than</u>
<u n="156" who="S0436">I suppose fundamentally I tend to go for sort of you know well meaning characters at least but there you are that's why I don't do literature course I ran off and studied medieval literature where everyone is a psychopathic murderer</u>
<u n="157" who="S0435" trans="overlap">anyone else it's only because that's what they thought was interesting</u>
<u n="158" who="S0436">erm perhaps I don't know you know in the case of Icelandic sagas you do wonder whether it's just <unclear/> I don't know you know modern Icelandic literature seems to be pretty much the same they just like reading stories about psychopathic murderers obviously</u>
<u n="159" who="S0435" trans="overlap">I think it comes from living in a country with with no sun probably I think it's a general whole different outlook on life and then it is a it's less let's look for happy things in our book and let's look for actually things happening lots of things happening cos if you if you don't actually have any sun for ninety per cent of the time you might want to spend your time being interested rather than just</u>
<u n="160" who="S0436">yeah I don't know I I like to think it's not how I'd react but then again I'm sure there are lots of lovely happy books written in Iceland and I just haven't read them but</u>
<u n="161" who="S0435">yeah but that probably comes the fact that if you if you look at the English books that are famous in other countries probably have not very many of them are sort of nice lovely happy ones</u>
<u n="162" who="S0436" trans="overlap"><unclear/> happy reads you might be right yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0435">I think you'd probably get a ridiculous</u>
<u n="164" who="S0436" trans="overlap">I've graduated I don't need to read literature</u>
<u n="165" who="S0435">you'd probably get an <trunc>un</trunc> disproportionately high amount of sort of murder mystery things and crime stuff from sort of</u>
<u n="166" who="S0436">you know I think they tended to kind of</u>
<u n="167" who="S0435">I think there's</u>
<u n="168" who="S0436">I suppose old school crime we is a thing but</u>
<u n="169" who="S0435">yes but they I think it's all sort of</u>
<u n="170" who="S0436" trans="overlap">sort of the more modern stuff</u>
<u n="171" who="S0435">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0436">it's all Harry Potter isn't it?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0435">I think it's probably the main one everyone's heard of</u>
<u n="174" who="S0436">I don't know lots of things sadly the rest of the world English books and we don't read theirs cos the English are too snobby to do a decent translation of foreign literature is there any particular reason why you're trying to take my hat apart?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0435">no</u>
<u n="176" who="S0436">well please don't then it's a nice hat I like it just cos you think it looks daft</u>
<u n="177" who="S0435">it does</u>
<u n="178" who="S0436">of course it looks daft it's a straw boater what did you expect?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0435">well <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I I think you can just I don't think you have learnt anything from Dirk Gently it's not trying to persuade people not to wear hats it doesn't work</u>
<u n="180" who="S0436" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's the only thing you learnt from Dirk Gently?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0435">I think the only real applicable life thing</u>
<u n="182" who="S0436">not even about the inventor of the cat flap?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0435">yeah possibly</u>
<u n="184" who="S0436">the difficulty of discovering gravity</u>
<u n="185" who="S0435">it had never occurred to me and I don't think I have much use for it now I know it but I would say that <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0436">dearie me <pause dur="short"/> they are funny book though aren't they?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0435">I'm still embarrassed about how long it took me to realise that erm erm in the radio adaptation what the the the guy in the second the Long Dark Tea-Time of the Soul erm</u>
<u n="188" who="S0436">mm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0435">the guy the <trunc>wh</trunc> the married couple I can't remember their surname now</u>
<u n="190" who="S0436">oh oh</u>
<u n="191" who="S0435">Cynthia and Simon Bracock?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0436" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> something like that</u>
<u n="193" who="S0435">that that that the guy was played by Peter Davies and it honestly didn't click</u>
<u n="194" who="S0436">oh I remember you came running up to me and squeak <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> he's Peter Davies in the <trunc>mi</trunc></u>
<u n="195" who="S0435">I never noticed</u>
<u n="196" who="S0436">erm I I suppose if I was feeling a little less charitable I'd point out he's an actor it's kind of his job to sound like different people but erm yes</u>
<u n="197" who="S0435" trans="overlap">yes but but but but I can recognise quite a lot of people in anything by their voice cos I mean you know the guy who played Vimes in erm the erm Night Watch</u>
<u n="198" who="S0436">oh yes and you heard him on the radio</u>
<u n="199" who="S0435">you can I can always tell him</u>
<u n="200" who="S0436">but he has a really distinctive voice</u>
<u n="201" who="S0435">yes but I suppose Peter Davidson doesn't have a highly highly distinctive voice but it's still not exactly generic</u>
<u n="202" who="S0436" trans="overlap">well I don't know I thought it was fairly generic whereas the the chappy you were talking about he's very distinctive cos he's one of those people like Roger Allam he's completely incapable of saying a word that doesn't sound deeply sarcastic which is I suppose why he makes such a good Vimes in the first place</u>
<u n="203" who="S0435">mm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0436">speaking of Roger Allam</u>
<u n="205" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="206" who="S0436">did you ever erm listen to the er the the the the</u>
<u n="207" who="S0435">I listened to a bit of it it was on the radio recently</u>
<u n="208" who="S0436">I didn't even say what it was</u>
<u n="209" who="S0435">yes the Les Mis</u>
<u n="210" who="S0436">yes</u>
<u n="211" who="S0435">I listened to a bit of it cos it was on the radio</u>
<u n="212" who="S0436">and?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0435">I think it was done quite well it's it's a really weird though because it's it sits somewhere between the book and the musical which I'm really not used to in terms of it goes into far more detail in quite a lot of bits that the the musical doesn't even notice <trunc>i</trunc> happened in the first place and then them then then then you have then you have the then it skips over massive bits in the book that I wouldn't have well maybe not massive bits but then then it sort of it goes into loads of detail about him stealing the coin from the small child and things and angsting about it for ages</u>
<u n="214" who="S0436" trans="overlap">come on that's dramatically important</u>
<u n="215" who="S0435">yes but it's dramatically important and entirely not at all present in the musical</u>
<u n="216" who="S0436">yes</u>
<u n="217" who="S0435">if you get what I mean</u>
<u n="218" who="S0436">I don't know I just</u>
<u n="219" who="S0435">but so but it's not vital to the plot but is a sort of atmosphere builder in a sense</u>
<u n="220" who="S0436">well I don't know I I'd at least rank it as characterisation</u>
<u n="221" who="S0435">okay but</u>
<u n="222" who="S0436">but go on what's what's the bit they left out?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0435">I can't remember but I seem to they they just sort of <trunc>i</trunc></u>
<u n="224" who="S0436">it's a very long novel I suppose different adaptations can make different choices</u>
<u n="225" who="S0435" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="226" who="S0436">you probably didn't get far enough into the radio adaptation to notice that it was rather sweet they basically telescoped all of the spare students into one person</u>
<u n="227" who="S0435"><vocal desc="laugh"/> which one did they name it after?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0436">er hang on it was</u>
<u n="229" who="S0435">I think it's Combeferre in the end</u>
<u n="230" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0436">yes which was kind of odd</u>
<u n="232" who="S0435">one of the distinctive ones to begin with wasn't he?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0436">well no that's the thing he doesn't really do much in plot term doesn't do an awful lot of plot terms but er you know sort of in the book Courfeyrac is the one who you know goes around doing stuff and rescuing lost puppy <unclear>Marios</unclear> and laughing at his terrible fashion choices and things so did they still have?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0435">So did they still have Courfeyrac?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0436" trans="overlap">no they just kind of</u>
<u n="236" who="S0435">oh</u>
<u n="237" who="S0436">so they</u>
<u n="238" who="S0435">had <trunc>Gran</trunc>Grantaire marries <unclear/> Enjolras and then they just condense the rest?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0436">yep</u>
<u n="240" who="S0435">so there were four of them</u>
<u n="241" who="S0436" trans="overlap">hang on come here your hair is doing awful things</u>
<u n="242" who="S0435">no it's fine</u>
<u n="243" who="S0436">well no you're</u>
<u n="244" who="S0435">no it's fine</u>
<u n="245" who="S0436" trans="overlap">actually your hand is stuck in your hair</u>
<u n="246" who="S0435">no it isn't it's fine no</u>
<u n="247" who="S0436">okay</u>
<u n="248" who="S0435">so there were four of them?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0436">er pretty much</u>
<u n="250" who="S0435">trying to lead a revolution</u>
<u n="251" who="S0436">well it was implied that there were lots of people in the background</u>
<u n="252" who="S0435">okay</u>
<u n="253" who="S0436">I mean you know there's what there's</u>
<u n="254" who="S0435">just the rest of them were mute</u>
<u n="255" who="S0436">there's what was nine of them in the novel or something</u>
<u n="256" who="S0435">but it's all <unclear/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0436" trans="overlap">and there's nine of them trying to lead a revolution</u>
<u n="258" who="S0435" trans="overlap">that's a double not but I think four people being the only people who talk during a revolution is a bit</u>
<u n="259" who="S0436">perhaps but come on it's a radio play how many</u>
<u n="260" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="261" who="S0436">you know distinct voices can you really get? but you know? there you are I suppose also you know they added in the oddest bits though from what I remember</u>
<u n="262" who="S0435">I presume they didn't add in pot plants and things</u>
<u n="263" who="S0436">no they they did dedicate several lines to erm sort of miscellaneous composite student rambling about tomatoes and I presume</u>
<u n="264" who="S0435">and I presume they didn't wasn't</u>
<u n="265" who="S0436" trans="overlap">which wasn't in the original</u>
<u n="266" who="S0435" trans="overlap">I presume they didn't do the erm mystic sultana or whatever</u>
<u n="267" who="S0436">but that was just the <trunc>narra</trunc> come on the that was perfectly unexceptionable in the original it was just you know</u>
<u n="268" who="S0435">the translation?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0436">yeah translators with cloth ears I don't know it was just mystic sultana</u>
<u n="270" who="S0435">wonder which erm which translation they mainly based the radio thing on?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0436">oh doesn't make much odds does it?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0435">probably not but i presume they lifted quite a lot of the erm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0436">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0435">text straight out quite a lot of the erm speech straight out of the book</u>
<u n="275" who="S0436">not that I particularly remember but <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I suppose of course if you erm based it on the Penguin Classics translation you might fall into problems</u>
<u n="276" who="S0435">what did they do?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0436">er basically the Penguin Classic translator hates the book</u>
<u n="278" who="S0435">oh</u>
<u n="279" who="S0436">it's rather funny he writes a long sort of translators note at the beginning explaining how he felt it was his moral duty <vocal desc="laugh"/> to make up for all of the terrible things in this book which does make you wonder why he chose to translate it in the first place but there you are</u>
<u n="280" who="S0435">presumably they told him you're going to translate this cos you're our you are our French translator</u>
<u n="281" who="S0436">mm perhaps but it would seem a little what do I know about translation</u>
<u n="282" who="S0435">I presume they don't get very much choice in it really cos if I presume they don't have sort of hundreds of each language translators</u>
<u n="283" who="S0436">I'm sure there are gazillions people who can translate French</u>
<u n="284" who="S0435">but I mean you have to be not only competent at reading French and reading in English you have to be competent at reading and working out what on earth he means and then writing it out in something which is close enough to the original that it can count as a translation but not so awful as sort of let's get out my dictionary and translate every word</u>
<u n="285" who="S0436">yes well I think some people would argue how much er the er a Penguin Classics translator actually succeeds on that front but again you know I think trying to translate all those puns in French would drive anyone mad</u>
<u n="286" who="S0435" trans="overlap">and like the usual</u>
<u n="287" who="S0436" trans="overlap">I'm pretty sure most of them sailed right over my head because you know look at me do I speak fluent French? ha ha no do I speak fluent nineteenth century posh French by someone who's disturbingly addicted to bad puns er what do you think? but</u>
<u n="288" who="S0435">I don't know I I like in the version I've read the the the fact you've occasionally got footnotes on seemingly sort of entirely unneeded footnote sections just sort of saying this means this this this okay good to know but I don't know what you're talking about</u>
<u n="289" who="S0436">yes yeah dear</u>
<u n="290" who="S0435">mm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0436">did you bother finish reading the book?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0435">I don't know I took it off my Kindle when I was doing a whole sort of <pause dur="short"/> spring</u>
<u n="293" who="S0436" trans="overlap">spring cleaning</u>
<u n="294" who="S0435">yes because I ended up changing the battery but first I took everything off to see whether that helped cos whether it was a sort of er what do you call it? er a sort of what I sort of</u>
<u n="295" who="S0436">you're going to have to give me some more information to go on</u>
<u n="296" who="S0435">erm it's a sort of er you you they when it goes through and sort of er so you can use a search function and search through books I've forgotten what the word is called and it it sort of it has to go analyse the books first and if it hasn't done it yet it slows down the battery life horrifically it's a</u>
<u n="297" who="S0436">oh you mean it lets you search inside the text of the books you have stored on it?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0435" trans="overlap">yes <trunc>in</trunc></u>
<u n="299" who="S0436">it I don't know that mine even</u>
<u n="300" who="S0435" trans="overlap">indexing yes it does</u>
<u n="301" who="S0436">lets you do that</u>
<u n="302" who="S0435">erm it's an index</u>
<u n="303" who="S0436" trans="overlap">cos mine isn't a Kindle</u>
<u n="304" who="S0435">erm the it it indexes books and if it's halfway through it or sort of got stuck indexing a book or something it will it slows down the battery life to or sort of <trunc>i</trunc>it makes it sort of</u>
<u n="305" who="S0436" trans="overlap">eats up the battery life</u>
<u n="306" who="S0435" trans="overlap">eats battery life ridiculously quickly</u>
<u n="307" who="S0436">mm fair enough</u>
<u n="308" who="S0435">and so I just took everything off and then that was one of the things which I didn't end up putting back on because I wasn't reading at that point</u>
<u n="309" who="S0436" trans="overlap">mm fair enough I need to do that with my silly phone though</u>
<u n="310" who="S0435">what's the matter with it? is it just slowing down?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0436">although you know it did it before but apparently it's just what Android phones do sometimes I looked it up on the internet and pretty much everyone says this happens and just after a while it decides that there's erm there's no space left for sort of downloading apps and things even though you do have storage space left it just refuses to acknowledge that</u>
<u n="312" who="S0435">ah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0436">and there's apparently no way to fix it other than putting it back to the factory settings</u>
<u n="314" who="S0435">oh</u>
<u n="315" who="S0436">so mine's got to that point again this is the second time it's happened and furthermore I've finally got my new er SIM card</u>
<u n="316" who="S0435">ah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0436">in the post and low and behold it's not recognising that either so sort of you know last bright glimmer of optimism is that if I put it back to factory settings it might finally twig what's going on with that as will which would be nice cos I rang up the man this morning and he said oh yes yes yes that's perfectly fine you just need to leave the SIM card in your phone for an hour before you restart it so I walked it into town this afternoon and funnily enough it did nothing thank you man on the phone really helpful</u>
<u n="318" who="S0435">I don't know I just keep everything on an SD card on my phone</u>
<u n="319" who="S0436">I keep everything on an SD card but it doesn't recognise the space on the SD card</u>
<u n="320" who="S0435">oh</u>
<u n="321" who="S0436">I think it's just one of those</u>
<u n="322" who="S0435">can yours use an SD card?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0436">yes that's why it has an SD card in it</u>
<u n="324" who="S0435">yeah but but the tablet you've got upstairs is an Android one and it updated and it didn't it it refused to use it unless you sort of did sort of jail breaking it</u>
<u n="325" who="S0436">really?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0435">yes the newest versions of Android don't let you use them even if you've got slots in your device</u>
<u n="327" who="S0436">oh heavens well perhaps I don't want to put it back to factory settings then or it'll have a fit at me</u>
<u n="328" who="S0435">maybe it's</u>
<u n="329" who="S0436">rr technology</u>
<u n="330" who="S0435" trans="overlap">maybe it's maybe it's <trunc>o</trunc> maybe it's only for the tablets rather than the phones but I'd check it first just cos seems like a bit of a rubbish thing to</u>
<u n="331" who="S0436" trans="overlap">mm oh I don't know if that is the case I'm sort of stuck either way aren't I?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0435">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0436">I mean I suppose at least in the current situation I can I can access the things that are already stored on the SD card I just can't put any new stuff on there whereas theoretically if it just revoked my SD card I</u>
<u n="334" who="S0435" trans="overlap">what version are you on?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0436">heavens I don't know</u>
<u n="336" who="S0435">is it a sort of is it Jelly Bean or Kitkat at the moment is the new one? I can't remember</u>
<u n="337" who="S0436">do I really look like I pay attention?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0435">no</u>
<u n="339" who="S0436">well you would be right I don't pay attention but no I'm at least one update behind cos I keep on ignoring it cos cos life is difficult and I have too many things to do and making I don't know consoling noises at my phone while it has identity crisis is really not top of my priority list right now</u>
<u n="340" who="S0435">mm</u>
<u n="341" who="S0436">that's the problem with smartphones they just have a much greater capacity to be really really stupid</u>
<u n="342" who="S0435" trans="overlap">that's why everyone that's why that's why everyone buys Iphones because they've got no capacity to anything except exactly what they think you ought to do on them they are sort of they are there's lots of support and there's a generally by having reduced amount of stuff you can do on it you are more sort of not in terms of apps but just in terms of it sort of locking everything away in closed files and not letting you access anything or change anything it means that a lot less is likely to get broken</u>
<u n="343" who="S0436">mm fair enough I wouldn't know everyone keeps on saying how the hardware conks out in no time at all so</u>
<u n="344" who="S0435">in Iphones?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0436">yeah well they've always complained about that</u>
<u n="346" who="S0435" trans="overlap">everyone's complained everyone complains about the screens but I'm I'm not sure whether that one's and actually because they have I think it is partly because they have the exposed screen at the corner cos the glass goes all the way and it doesn't have a bevelled edge</u>
<u n="347" who="S0436">mm</u>
<u n="348" who="S0435">on a lot on the sort of five's and thing so it means if you</u>
<u n="349" who="S0436" trans="overlap">but <unclear/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0435">drop it on its side it's the glass bit is sort of exposed to being</u>
<u n="351" who="S0436">yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0435">taking a lot of the pressure well <unclear/> pressure the energy and sort of</u>
<u n="353" who="S0436">yeah I take your point</u>
<u n="354" who="S0435">yeah whatever you call it</u>
<u n="355" who="S0436">yeah well come on your the one doing physics <pause dur="short"/> I haven't studied physics since I was your age pretty much</u>
<u n="356" who="S0435">that doesn't mean I can remember which of the right words which mean almost exactly the same</u>
<u n="357" who="S0436">I'm pretty sure</u>
<u n="358" who="S0435" trans="overlap">but each different</u>
<u n="359" who="S0436">well they never really bothered teaching you that at GCSE did you did they blah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0435">no not really</u>
<u n="361" who="S0436">no</u>
<u n="362" who="S0435">they're much more keen about teaching about household wiring</u>
<u n="363" who="S0436">really?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="365" who="S0436">you still do that? how quaint</u>
<u n="366" who="S0435">and stopping distances of cars and how stopping distance is affected by whether you are on drugs whether you are have been drinking how sleepy you are the visibility the road surface the weather conditions</u>
<u n="367" who="S0436" trans="overlap">I hate the</u>
<u n="368" who="S0435">the what else is there</u>
<u n="369" who="S0436">and you do stop and wonder what this has to do with physics don't you? It I do hate those socially relevant bits of the curriculum because it's just it's not science it's just</u>
<u n="370" who="S0435" trans="overlap">in on the science no in in one of the in one of the erm chemistry papers I've done recently</u>
<u n="371" who="S0436">mm</u>
<u n="372" who="S0435">one of the questions was honestly it said Humphry Davy discovered erm how to use electrolysis to get erm potassium I think it was</u>
<u n="373" who="S0436">er I'll take your word for it</u>
<u n="374" who="S0435">sort of something like that</u>
<u n="375" who="S0436">it sounds plausible I can't remember which element Humphry Davy discovered</u>
<u n="376" who="S0435" trans="overlap">I think it's potassium I think it was potassium and one of the question</u>
<u n="377" who="S0436" trans="overlap">ask your mother she'll know</u>
<u n="378" who="S0435">was actually why was the scientific community quick to accept this experiment?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0436">well that's good</u>
<u n="380" who="S0435">no the answer is because he was well known as a as a scientist</u>
<u n="381" who="S0436">well I don't know I I see what your objecting to but at the same time I don't know I personally think it's quite interesting and potentially useful to sort of sort of work out how how the science sort of got scienced rather than just you know appearing one day on a stone tablets as it were</u>
<u n="382" who="S0435">mm</u>
<u n="383" who="S0436">it's not as silly as one of the questions we got was it in a practice GCSE paper or was it a practice year nine SATs? I don't remember now but we genuinely got a question oh what was it? it was something to do with you know Mrs X says she doesn't want to take these tablets from her doctor because they're made of chemicals what would you say to her?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0435">oh dear the world is made of chemicals</u>
<u n="385" who="S0436">well that was pretty much what I wrote and of course that was the right answer but that's one step away from the biology question about what the plants need water sunlight ice cream <vocal desc="laugh"/> come on I've told you that story before it was in the multiple choice section and one of the choices it had was ice cream <vocal desc="laugh"/> ah I don't know</u>
<u n="386" who="S0435">but I think I mean</u>
<u n="387" who="S0436" trans="overlap">ice cream</u>
<u n="388" who="S0435">what is it in in what is it in physics again they really struggle to <trunc>fi</trunc>fill the physics lessons with actual physics cos they had a a how mobile phones affect your health and how sort of we erm and and why some people think that mobile phones are evil and you should never have them and kill you because they have microwaves</u>
<u n="389" who="S0436">mm so do microwaves</u>
<u n="390" who="S0435">they weren't putting those arguments against microwaves they were just saying</u>
<u n="391" who="S0436">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0435">there there there there there's microwaves and and and microwaves heat up water and there's water in people</u>
<u n="393" who="S0436"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh Miss <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm of all the possible arguments you can bounce against mobile phones imagine that stupid br-engine thing they made us do at <unclear/> remember that?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0435">yes the the drink lots of water because you're you you're brain needs water to function because it's it it it</u>
<u n="395" who="S0436">your brain runs on electricity</u>
<u n="396" who="S0435" trans="overlap">electricity</u>
<u n="397" who="S0436">and water conducts electricity <vocal desc="laugh"/> where do you even start with that</u>
<u n="398" who="S0435" trans="overlap">and I think it's the same people who said that the water is absorbed through your mouth into your brain</u>
<u n="399" who="S0436">through the roof of your mouth or something yes</u>
<u n="400" who="S0435" trans="overlap">your mouth in</u>
<u n="401" who="S0436">they didn't actually say that to our faces to be fair that was just on their silly website or something my goodness it was embarrassing we used to have you know actual activity week and we got to do activities and then <unclear/> giving us that nonsense was some kind of replacement I'm sorry mm and I never even got to do any of the real activities weeks because I was always at <anon type="place"/> and I mean I liked <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0435">no but we had a basically we had a study skills workshop</u>
<u n="403" who="S0436" trans="overlap">but well to be fair if that's good it's useful but</u>
<u n="404" who="S0435" trans="overlap">and it okay we all say oh look here how how to remember a list of <trunc>we</trunc> they honestly gave us seven random words or something and said how will you remember these? one of their things how to do</u>
<u n="405" who="S0436" trans="overlap">oh this is your stupid pneumonic thing that you hate</u>
<u n="406" who="S0435">okay one of them was come up with an action for each of the words</u>
<u n="407" who="S0436"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you'd look pretty daft in the exam wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0435">well that gets you probably disqualified from the exam</u>
<u n="409" who="S0436">I don't know how much waving you have to do before they throw you out of an exam one of my friends from erm last</u>
<u n="410" who="S0435" trans="overlap">no and the other one</u>
<u n="411" who="S0436" trans="overlap">year was an invigilator I could ask him I suppose</u>
<u n="412" who="S0435">and and one of one of the other ones was okay so now we've got your word</u>
<u n="413" who="S0436">uh</u>
<u n="414" who="S0435">now think of something which sounds like that word okay? then put it in a scenario with a word that rhymes with a number in in a sequence</u>
<u n="415" who="S0436" trans="overlap">oh yes you said that</u>
<u n="416" who="S0435">I'm learning three times as much stuff here how is that helpful?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0436">mm well you know sort of I have to give them the benefit of the doubt and assume that for certain things it works because you know those people who can memorise entire card decks</u>
<u n="418" who="S0435">but they do it in actual</u>
<u n="419" who="S0436" trans="overlap">do you use these kinds of things</u>
<u n="420" who="S0435">but they <trunc>j</trunc>use much they then the the card decks the thing about the difference between those is that instead of <trunc>ac</trunc> having actual meaning it what the each of the things have they are just sequences aren't they?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0436">I've never you you mean the card deck is a meaningless sequence</u>
<u n="422" who="S0435" trans="overlap">yes the card is just is just a meaningless sequence and maybe people can see patterns in it but as it is it's just a <trunc>meaning</trunc> <trunc>le</trunc> <trunc>se</trunc></u>
<u n="423" who="S0436">whereas the problem the problem with trying to teach you that you should be doing your revision by learning things as meaningless sequences is most of it isn't a meaningless sequence yes</u>
<u n="424" who="S0435" trans="overlap">a meaningless sequence</u>
<u n="425" who="S0436">yes it's just like erm</u>
<u n="426" who="S0435" trans="overlap">and if if if you reduce things to meaningless sequences you find it harder to then apply it when you need it cos there are very few exam questions which just say name the thing this arrow is pointing at</u>
<u n="427" who="S0436">yeah it's just like mummy always used to complain about with the er <vocal desc="misc"/> CGP maths text books</u>
<u n="428" who="S0435">oh oh</u>
<u n="429" who="S0436">cos they did an awful lot of that thing where they say would say you know memorise five formulae or</u>
<u n="430" who="S0435">yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0436">you know proofs for geometry or something</u>
<u n="432" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="433" who="S0436">whereas actually you could condense it down to one or two</u>
<u n="434" who="S0435">mm</u>
<u n="435" who="S0436">if you actually understood how they worked but</u>
<u n="436" who="S0435">yes but honestly I somebody was looking through a maths text book whoever writes these text books I don't understand what happens in their brains they had a picture of a triangle and for no apparent reason there was a photo of a goat in the middle of it</u>
<u n="437" who="S0436">that's just CGP trying to be quirky</u>
<u n="438" who="S0435">yeah but it wasn't even CGP</u>
<u n="439" who="S0436">really?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0435">no</u>
<u n="441" who="S0436">oh no the blight is spreading obviously</u>
<u n="442" who="S0435" trans="overlap">it was something it was something that was trying to be more sensible than it obviously was because it it I don't know you can tell it was trying to be a upmarket one</u>
<u n="443" who="S0436">mm yes</u>
<u n="444" who="S0435">honestly the CGP ones the little comments they put on are so patronising they're just okay so now you've read this page over once so now what I want you to do is close the book go on a nice brisk five minute wake come back read it again and repeat so then you will now automatically remember this for the rest of your life and this will automatically be the best way of you learning this information</u>
<u n="445" who="S0436">you're just objecting to being told to go on a five minute walk don't you?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0435">mm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0436">lazy little so and so</u>
<u n="448" who="S0435">no not exactly but it's just this idea that they say how much time are you meant to spend if you're meant to be doing this for every single page they ask you to</u>
<u n="449" who="S0436">no I I accept that it's rather patronising but honestly for for all my final exams I did memorise almost all of it by writing down the things I needed to have memorised on bit of paper and then just walking round and round and round in circles in the garden just you know declaiming them to the trees</u>
<u n="450" who="S0435">I find doing actual</u>
<u n="451" who="S0436" trans="overlap">I got some rather funny looks I will admit but you know it worked</u>
<u n="452" who="S0435">I find doing <trunc>ac</trunc> sort of doing actual sort of questions and things on them cos that means when you get one wrong or you can't answer it you look back find out the answer and that answer always is the one that you can remember</u>
<u n="453" who="S0436">cos you just remember the crippling embarrassment that can fail to remember something so obvious the first time</u>
<u n="454" who="S0435">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0436">at least that's how it works for me but yeah no obviously some things you do need to just memorise by rote and to be honest I do kind of favour the you know recite ad infinitum thing you remember when I did er GCSE was it GCSE or was it A level? A level the one where we er had to do all memorise all those English Lit set texty things so we could cos it was closed book you had to be able to do quotes well I don't know they wanted us to just take relevant quotes out of these poems and memorise the quotes but they were poems you can just memorise the poems so I</u>
<u n="456" who="S0435" trans="overlap">I think the whole getting it a I think the whole idea about getting you to</u>
<u n="457" who="S0436" trans="overlap">I remember I spent a lot of time in the garden that summer reciting you know Dylan Thomas and stuff</u>
<u n="458" who="S0435">to mm mm sort of all of the things that have the closed book English things is that you're not actually</u>
<u n="459" who="S0436">it's not really testing your literary analysis in a way yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0435" trans="overlap"> ly testing your English cos if they wanted to just stop you from having the answers written on the book you're taking in just give just give people the passage you want them to use or the poem they want you to use as a fresh piece of paper it's not like you're</u>
<u n="461" who="S0436"><trunc>A</trunc>level we had erm open book exams and they just said you have to have a clean copy of this text to take into the exam</u>
<u n="462" who="S0435">yes but that that that's a fair enough thing but doing that because actually you're not really English is I don't know the one thing in its favour is that actually it's not something where mindless memorisation is a sort of</u>
<u n="463" who="S0436">it doesn't seem like a terribly relevant skill in many ways yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0435">cos I mean for science you can you can't really get away from the fact that it's pretty much mindless memorisation</u>
<u n="465" who="S0436">on a certain level the whole the whole stick they're selling with the English literature is you know engaging your creativity creativity and stuff so yeah you do kind of wonder</u>
<u n="466" who="S0435">well I I I personally don't think maths is mindless sort of memorisation but I think a lot of people do</u>
<u n="467" who="S0436">mm maths nerd</u>
<u n="468" who="S0435">mm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0436">oh well I tease but it's good are you still thinking of doing maths at university then?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0435">I'm not I'm certainly doing it at A level I think</u>
<u n="471" who="S0436">yeah but you know you've got plenty of time to decide from there</u>
<u n="472" who="S0435">I'm still probably thinking either computer or computers or maths</u>
<u n="473" who="S0436">well they're both sensible choices I mean except in the sense that you're then going to have to support your <trunc>im</trunc>impecunious older sister when you grow up</u>
<u n="474" who="S0435">well I don't think I will need to I think you're probably going to get along fine</u>
<u n="475" who="S0436">erm</u>
<u n="476" who="S0435"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're going to do better than somebody who hasn't got a degree at all</u>
<u n="477" who="S0436">perhaps it's possible to be over qualified for stuff but</u>
<u n="478" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0435">I think you're probably not aiming to get the jobs that you are going to be over qualified for</u>
<u n="480" who="S0436">I don't know at some point I might end up settle for settling for you know give me money please before I have to live in a cardboard box will conjugate verbs for food</u>
<u n="481" who="S0435">er yeah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0436">yeah I don't think many people make it with a where the big money is as linguists but there you are</u>
<u n="483" who="S0435">you could go and do speech therapy and things</u>
<u n="484" who="S0436">erm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0435">yes that is your response to that and it was about the most obvious response ever</u>
<u n="486" who="S0436">well you know it needs doing but</u>
<u n="487" who="S0435">you're not</u>
<u n="488" who="S0436">I'm not sure why anyone would think I would help but er there you are also you know I'd probably just lose concentration and start teaching them how to speak old English by a mistake which would be kind of funny but probably not very socially responsible</u>
<u n="489" who="S0435" trans="overlap">you'd teach them how to how to learn the names of small furry animals in old English or was that old Norse but?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0436">no it was old English Dr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> used to give us small furry animal of the week <unclear>hatterfaggle</unclear> it's a hedgehog</u>
<u n="491" who="S0435">I was about to say hedgehog <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0436">I can't remember what we cos we ended up buying a little cuddly hedgehog as a mascot but er we sent him travelling I can't remember where he went in the end I expect he'll come back at some point we might have sent him to Australia with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's I mean she was very attached to the yes <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is an odd fish</u>
<u n="493" who="S0435" trans="overlap">so does it just get sent around the world and people take pictures of it next to various recognisable things and send it back or is it just a</u>
<u n="494" who="S0436">erm I think that was sort of theoretically the idea but erm mainly it was just sort of you know in the way that a bunch of students do a hedgehog turned up so there was a hedgehog and we all thought it was funny</u>
<u n="495" who="S0435">and did it get a name?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0436">erm sometimes it was just called <unclear>hatterfaggle</unclear> erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> named him something incredibly long that had lots of Irish in it</u>
<u n="497" who="S0435">oh</u>
<u n="498" who="S0436"><vocal desc="nonsense"/> at one point I think I didn't dare ask I leave the Irish to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="499" who="S0435">is that like nineteen hamsters?</u>
<u n="500" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="501" who="S0436">er no</u>
<u n="502" who="S0435">so it wasn't a weird as knighting hamsters</u>
<u n="503" who="S0436">well it wasn't in that the whole thing was deliberately silly from the first place whereas</u>
<u n="504" who="S0435"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0436"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I giving you know inappropriately formal names to hamsters was just us getting rather over enthusiastic in first pet naming no ASNaCs are just strange there was the time where we walked into the common room and found someone had covered the entire whiteboard with dragon <unclear>poems</unclear> it's just the kind of thing that happens</u>
<u n="506" who="S0435">my computer thing the computer thing I go to on Saturdays we walked into one of the other rooms and there was a whiteboard in there and they had entirely filled it up with <unclear/> meme things as in</u>
<u n="507" who="S0436">oh dear</u>
<u n="508" who="S0435">you had Pepe the frog and</u>
<u n="509" who="S0436">what?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0435">oh it's just a thing</u>
<u n="511" who="S0436">no go on you have to explain what is this? do I want to know?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0435" trans="overlap">it it it's one of the it's an internet meme and it's a particular drawing of a frog I think originally from a children's colouring book</u>
<u n="513" who="S0436" trans="overlap">hang on is this that horrifying thing you had on a balloon?</u>
<u n="514" who="S0435">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="515" who="S0436">and I asked mummy why on earth you had a balloon with a cartoon frog on it and she said you wouldn't tell her</u>
<u n="516" who="S0435">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="517" who="S0436">why did you have a balloon with a cartoon frog on it?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0435">cos everyone was drawing things on balloons</u>
<u n="519" who="S0436">did you draw that on the balloon?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="521" who="S0436">well it was very well drawn if you were trying to draw a distorted cartoon frog</u>
<u n="522" who="S0435">they were also drawing Pokmon on them as well</u>
<u n="523" who="S0436">er well actually you know drawing Pokmon on them is slightly more understandable I mean except in the fundamental sense which I don't understand Pokmon personally yeah</u>
<u n="524" who="S0435">yeah you you were never I think it's a sort of next stage horsy person thing in a way</u>
<u n="525" who="S0436">mm really?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0435">yes it's the sort of get to collect a lots of cutesy things</u>
<u n="527" who="S0436">oh fair enough</u>
<u n="528" who="S0435">or maybe it's a pre-horsey stage</u>
<u n="529" who="S0436">I don't know my experience was they were done by rather different sort of cliques as it were</u>
<u n="530" who="S0435">okay maybe I think it's in the same vein though</u>
<u n="531" who="S0436" trans="overlap">well in weird obsessive things to do as a child yes but</u>
<u n="532" who="S0435">but I mean even weird obsessive things you do as a child</u>
<u n="533" who="S0436">mm I don't know</u>
<u n="534" who="S0435">and I think the people who actually play the computer games are a different set of people from who played the trading card things</u>
<u n="535" who="S0436">yes I think it was people I knew mainly played the cards again I wouldn't have known if they'd played it one the Nintendo doodlies because you know what attention did I pay? er but there you are but no mainly what I got out of</u>
<u n="536" who="S0435">but the but the thing about the trading cards was it it was a sort of mainly boys doing it it when I was around anyway it was mainly boys doing and it was very much a status it didn't actually matter what the cards were sometimes</u>
<u n="537" who="S0436" trans="overlap">just as long as you had a super rare one yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0435">so sometimes it was football sometimes it was Pokmon there was there were those little plastic erm</u>
<u n="539" who="S0436">the Crazy Bones things you mean?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0435">the little plastic figurines the ones <trunc>so</trunc> which were sort of</u>
<u n="541" who="S0436" trans="overlap">they were</u>
<u n="542" who="S0435">sparkly and some of which were plain colours</u>
<u n="543" who="S0436">yeah I think they were I think they were the Crazy Bones ones</u>
<u n="544" who="S0435" trans="overlap">or well I I think they might be</u>
<u n="545" who="S0436" trans="overlap">they were <trunc>sor</trunc> they were sort of an inch tall and</u>
<u n="546" who="S0435" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="547" who="S0436">various kinds of coloured plastic and they were sort of shaped like little cartoony monster alien things</u>
<u n="548" who="S0435">yeah <trunc>ma</trunc> I'm not sure if that's what they were called or that they were a forerunner or whatever to them I can't really remember exactly but those were another thing and it was a</u>
<u n="549" who="S0436">well</u>
<u n="550" who="S0435">it was a very much a status thing have as many and as sort of exciting a one as possible and so it didn't actually matter whether you were interested so lots of people doing the Pokmon cards had no interest in Pokmon but they did it as a <pause dur="short"/> I'm a <trunc>be</trunc> I'm better than you I have better Pokmon cards than you</u>
<u n="551" who="S0436">you're a purist aren't you dear?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0435">no</u>
<u n="553" who="S0436">just a little bit</u>
<u n="554" who="S0435">I think I I just don't get the trading cards</u>
<u n="555" who="S0436">well you know me</u>
<u n="556" who="S0435">you might as well</u>
<u n="557" who="S0436" trans="overlap">I have no collecting instincts so</u>
<u n="558" who="S0435" trans="overlap">you might as you might as well just have a set of trading cards which are numbers and the higher the number you have the better so you swap a a a hundred and twenty-four for a for two seventies or whatever and er</u>
<u n="559" who="S0436">well I think that would be a little bit too transparent they they need to have sort of you need to have more than one I don't know more than one axis on which you can measure the value of an individual thing</u>
<u n="560" who="S0435" trans="overlap">you can count the next</u>
<u n="561" who="S0436" trans="overlap">so that both people think they're getting a good deal</u>
<u n="562" who="S0435">you can have an X and a Y axis and the further away from the point of origin the better the card</u>
<u n="563" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="564" who="S0436">yeah you really are a mathematician at heart okay now all I'm thinking of is er that bit in Cabin Pressure <unclear/> and I started three months ago with a cheese sandwich</u>
<u n="565" who="S0435" trans="overlap">cheese sandwich <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0436">oh dear</u>
<u n="567" who="S0435"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is the sort of person who wouldn't end up buying them at all but would still end up with the largest collection</u>
<u n="568" who="S0436"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I do like Cabin Pressure</u>
<u n="569" who="S0435">of course you would be heartless not to</u>
<u n="570" who="S0436">that was erm Helsinki wasn't it?</u>
<u n="571" who="S0435">yes cos it was the</u>
<u n="572" who="S0436" trans="overlap">cos he was er taking the orchids to his friends Milo</u>
<u n="573" who="S0435">and there was the not chocolate cake I I I <unclear/> make it more cakey but it didn't it just made it bigger</u>
<u n="574" who="S0436" trans="overlap">made it bigger</u>
<u n="575" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="576" who="S0436">oh dear have you had those Scandinavian mostly chocolate the import tax</u>
<u n="577" who="S0435" trans="overlap">the import</u>
<u n="578" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="579" who="S0435">poor Caroline in that one you felt so sorry for her</u>
<u n="580" who="S0436">well you felt sorry for a lot of them poor Arthur</u>
<u n="581" who="S0435" trans="overlap"><unclear/> give me some cake</u>
<u n="582" who="S0436" trans="overlap">some cake</u>
<u n="583" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="584" who="S0435">I think I feel particularly sorry for Carolyn in that one just because none of it was her fault at all</u>
<u n="585" who="S0436" trans="overlap">yes well come on the whole point of Carolyn as a character is it is very rarely her fault I mean it's often more her fault that she'll admit but generally speaking she's always sort of</u>
<u n="586" who="S0435">yeah but I think this was so much not her fault that</u>
<u n="587" who="S0436">yes</u>
<u n="588" who="S0435">it was all far too much to do with her but entirely not her fault</u>
<u n="589" who="S0436">yes it turns out that's how many cigarettes you can fit in a fishcake</u>
<u n="590" who="S0435" trans="overlap">in a fishcake</u>
<u n="591" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0436">oh dear that reminds me actually erm I need to bother you to er <vocal desc="misc"/> give me er your Zurich so I can finally put it on my MP3 player</u>
<u n="593" who="S0435">oh haven't you listened to it?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0436">of course I've listened to it</u>
<u n="595" who="S0435">oh you just haven't</u>
<u n="596" who="S0436">I just don't</u>
<u n="597" who="S0435">own it at the moment</u>
<u n="598" who="S0436">I just don't have a copy whereas we do own a copy it's just you know not on my</u>
<u n="599" who="S0435" trans="overlap">I'm talking about sort of talking about audio you know last year for my birthday</u>
<u n="600" who="S0436" trans="overlap">I do know last year</u>
<u n="601" who="S0435">you got my <unclear>Dark Ice</unclear></u>
<u n="602" who="S0436" trans="overlap">oh yes you still want me to log into to the diddly-squat yes</u>
<u n="603" who="S0435">yes so I can just download it because actually ripping CDs is just honestly the the system to which they name the erm for the tracks is</u>
<u n="604" who="S0436">well it's not designed for it</u>
<u n="605" who="S0435">I know it isn't but honestly I have done audio stuff and I have got German rock music track names and pictures and I'm just sitting here going isn't there a way to just do clear all and it just labels it one two three four five six</u>
<u n="606" who="S0436" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="607" who="S0435">it doesn't do that it thinks it's clever enough that it knows that this is German rock music</u>
<u n="608" who="S0436" trans="overlap">yeah well I suppose it's the you know it doesn't really want you to be doing it because</u>
<u n="609" who="S0435">I know it doesn't but it's entire it's entirely fine to do it with the CDs you've bought though for quite a lot of quite a lot of circumstances because then once you buy a CD it comes with a sort of a you you're allowed to rip this and put it on your MP3 player slash phone</u>
<u n="610" who="S0436" trans="overlap">I don't know it's mm so long as you keep it for private use</u>
<u n="611" who="S0435">so long as you keep it for you self</u>
<u n="612" who="S0436" trans="overlap">blah blah blah</u>
<u n="613" who="S0435">and although they they don't have a very good way of enforcing it if they're giving that you that function</u>
<u n="614" who="S0436">it would be nice to have it functioning</u>
<u n="615" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="616" who="S0436">functioning functions wow</u>
<u n="617" who="S0435">oh and the fact it has a silly thing where it doesn't always organise them by track it sometimes it has a an inherent erm sort of ordering system that it it doesn't show you in the track name or number or sort of date or anything</u>
<u n="618" who="S0436">mm</u>
<u n="619" who="S0435">and so then when you transfer it to other things it doesn't keep that inherent ordering</u>
<u n="620" who="S0436">it just does its own weird mixture?</u>
<u n="621" who="S0435">yes it would be much better if you want to order it like that just put an 0 one 0 two 0 three</u>
<u n="622" who="S0436">it just really needs to come with its own you know sort of numbering wizard thingy doesn't it?</u>
<u n="623" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="624" who="S0436">yeah well go on you're the computer whiz you write a programme</u>
<u n="625" who="S0435">honestly it really wouldn't take much</u>
<u n="626" who="S0436">I'm a medievalist I don't believe in computers that's a lie most medievalists know all about computers oh well but anyway yes I could do that this evening if you remind me to be honest</u>
<u n="627" who="S0435">yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0436">yeah</u>
<u n="629" who="S0435">you liked Dark Ice didn't you?</u>
<u n="630" who="S0436">oh yes definitely I mean I won't pretend to <unclear>understand</unclear> but I'm</u>
<u n="631" who="S0435">it's very good it's got evil glowing clouds of orange gas</u>
<u n="632" who="S0436">fair enough that's really not selling it to me but</u>
<u n="633" who="S0435" trans="overlap">that want to take over the universe</u>
<u n="634" who="S0436">I thought the all hail the glow cloud thing was something else</u>
<u n="635" who="S0435" trans="overlap">no no no no no this is this is the erm the join the eminence and infinite warriors</u>
<u n="636" who="S0436">you say that as if you expect me to understand</u>
<u n="637" who="S0435" trans="overlap">no I don't</u>
<u n="638" who="S0436">okay I just won't ask</u>
<u n="639" who="S0435">but it it it doesn't I don't think it I'm not sure how much it glows but it's definitely orange and it's made up of the consciousness of a weird megalomaniac scientist and a weird megalomaniac Dalek</u>
<u n="640" who="S0436">and it's a cloud?</u>
<u n="641" who="S0435">it's a gas</u>
<u n="642" who="S0436">okay</u>
<u n="643" who="S0435">that the weird megalomaniac scientist created to upload his consciousness into then everything all sort of went a bit wrong and</u>
<u n="644" who="S0436">ah this really is more fi than sci isn't it?</u>
<u n="645" who="S0435">er yes</u>
<u n="646" who="S0436"><vocal desc="laugh"/> to say the least</u>
<u n="647" who="S0435">but then you look at Star Trek</u>
<u n="648" who="S0436">erm well</u>
<u n="649" who="S0435">you've probably never watched enough Star Trek to</u>
<u n="650" who="S0436">oh I've only watched the episodes that you have so I I saw that odd one where they were there was some kind of salt monster thing</u>
<u n="651" who="S0435">oh the one</u>
<u n="652" who="S0436">that turned people spotty</u>
<u n="653" who="S0435">oh that one</u>
<u n="654" who="S0436">I was a bit confused</u>
<u n="655" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="656" who="S0436">I don't know and apart from that I sort of know by reputation the Tribbles</u>
<u n="657" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="658" who="S0436">thing but</u>
<u n="659" who="S0435">and the fact that everyone wearing red dies</u>
<u n="660" who="S0436">yes I think I mainly learnt about that from Galaxy Quest</u>
<u n="661" who="S0435">I have never watched Star Trek when I watched <unclear/></u>
<u n="662" who="S0436" trans="overlap">well neither had I but it is just funny</u>
<u n="663" who="S0435" trans="overlap">it's just so funny even so and <trunc>ju</trunc> I can't imagine how much funnier it would be if you'd actually watched a decent amount of Star Trek</u>
<u n="664" who="S0436">it was just a very very funny film that</u>
<u n="665" who="S0435">I think Alan Rickman really did it well</u>
<u n="666" who="S0436">well</u>
<u n="667" who="S0435">I think he really was the stand out one there really</u>
<u n="668" who="S0436">erm</u>
<u n="669" who="S0435">for it the woman</u>
<u n="670" who="S0436" trans="overlap">whoever it was playing the token lady who was fed up with being the token lady</u>
<u n="671" who="S0435" trans="overlap">she token lady she was quite good</u>
<u n="672" who="S0436" trans="overlap">she was very good as well they were all pretty good though</u>
<u n="673" who="S0435">but I think you if you were going to give prizes out I think Alan Rickman would win the prize for that film</u>
<u n="674" who="S0436">well he just he just very much has a line in that particular kind of supercilious fed up with the world</u>
<u n="675" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="676" who="S0436">doesn't he? at least from the very few things I've seen him in</u>
<u n="677" who="S0435">but I mean as far as I I've been led to believe people who really like Star Trek are entirely on board with the fact they they don't differentiate and say this isn't a Star Wars film</u>
<u n="678" who="S0436">hang on</u>
<u n="679" who="S0435" trans="overlap">they count it as being the the Galaxy Quest</u>
<u n="680" who="S0436">you mean Star Trek?</u>
<u n="681" who="S0435">Star Trek</u>
<u n="682" who="S0436">yes</u>
<u n="683" who="S0435">I do I still get them <trunc>wro</trunc> but the people</u>
<u n="684" who="S0436">well they sound similar</u>
<u n="685" who="S0435" trans="overlap">the the Star Trek thing is erm that they basically do just go oh well it's a Star Trek film if we say it is</u>
<u n="686" who="S0436">and you'd have to be pretty heartless not to recognise that I haven't even watched Star Trek</u>
<u n="687" who="S0435" trans="overlap">apparently apparently and apparently</u>
<u n="688" who="S0436">and I could tell that the people making it obviously genuinely really like Star Trek and it was entirely affectionate</u>
<u n="689" who="S0435" trans="overlap">no mm no but I mean er to the extent where apparently sort of multiple proper sort of no official in terms of internet official done by at sort of when when you have you know on the internet you have the official favourite sort of favourite Star Trek films lists and things you know when people do them</u>
<u n="690" who="S0436">erm</u>
<u n="691" who="S0435">instead of just being one person sitting there on their computer and doing it sort of you have big websites publishing these</u>
<u n="692" who="S0436">which I expect are also one person sitting on their computer to be honest</u>
<u n="693" who="S0435" trans="overlap"> puter yeah but quite probably but and you sort of quite often <trunc>y</trunc> er it gets put sort of as one of the top Star Trek films</u>
<u n="694" who="S0436">well good for them</u>
<u n="695" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="696" who="S0436">good for them yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="697" who="S0435">why do we have a little spinney thing stuck in the garden</u>
<u n="698" who="S0436">oh the er?</u>
<u n="699" who="S0435">is that an <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="700" who="S0436">windmilly thing?</u>
<u n="701" who="S0435">yeah</u>
<u n="702" who="S0436">it might be I sort of presumed it was a futile attempt to keep the pigeons away from the beans</u>
<u n="703" who="S0435">possibly that makes more sense</u>
<u n="704" who="S0436">cos you know sparkly spinney things are meant to scare birds like people hang up erm <vocal desc="misc"/> old CDs</u>
<u n="705" who="S0435">yeah I think</u>
<u n="706" who="S0436">I cannot operate my tongue today</u>
<u n="707" who="S0435">I think pigeons are pretty unphased these days</u>
<u n="708" who="S0436">yes well certainly these pigeons are</u>
<u n="709" who="S0435">honestly you you run up to them and they just sit there looking at you</u>
<u n="710" who="S0436">you're all so proud of how tame the degu's are they've got nothing on the pigeons</u>
<u n="711" who="S0435"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't think I really want to stroke a pigeon though</u>
<u n="712" who="S0436">probably not a wild one no yes I don't really want to think about where it's been then again if you thought to hard about where a degu's been you probably wouldn't want to stroke it either</u>
<u n="713" who="S0435">oh don't be mean to them</u>
<u n="714" who="S0436">they are filthy little vermin <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="715" who="S0435">they're no more than</u>
<u n="716" who="S0436">yes they are</u>
<u n="717" who="S0435">no more than any other pet rodent</u>
<u n="718" who="S0436">they really are other pet animals can be litter trained</u>
<u n="719" who="S0435">I think degu's can technically ours were just</u>
<u n="720" who="S0436">well you didn't did you?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0435">ours were just not very good at it</u>
<u n="722" who="S0436">what are they very good at apart from making a mess?</u>
<u n="723" who="S0435">eating</u>
<u n="724" who="S0436">oh wow</u>
<u n="725" who="S0435">actually no they're not</u>
<u n="726" who="S0436">no they can't even do that because they drop their food on the floor and can't find it again yeah sorry <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they're pretty dim</u>
<u n="727" who="S0435">I know they're just innocent gerbils though</u>
<u n="728" who="S0436">mm I don't know it's a debatable point I reckon they're definitely not as dim as <unclear/></u>
<u n="729" who="S0435">that would take some doing</u>
<u n="730" who="S0436">it was just so sad when she kept pulling her bedding out of her nest and taking it round and putting it back in poor little thing</u>
<u n="731" who="S0435">I think <pause dur="short"/> she wasn't exactly the brightest</u>
<u n="732" who="S0436">no she was a very good little hamster</u>
<u n="733" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="734" who="S0436">she just was a bit thick</u>
<u n="735" who="S0435">and didn't like running or anything</u>
<u n="736" who="S0436">she did she used her wheel</u>
<u n="737" who="S0435">she <trunc>wa</trunc> she does the she did the hamster walk in the wheel but if you out her sort of and see whether she'd actually do anything faster than walking speed she very much refused</u>
<u n="738" who="S0436">oh no she did she just did it at night well she's a hamster they're nocturnal come on give her some credit</u>
<u n="739" who="S0435">mm</u>
<u n="740" who="S0436">oh honestly</u>
<u n="741" who="S0435">I don't think I'm not going to you can try and persuade me but I don't think she actually would ever be an athletic hamster</u>
<u n="742" who="S0436">probably not but she wasn't as useless as you're trying to make out she was very nice she was fluffy</u>
<u n="743" who="S0435">she bit you</u>
<u n="744" who="S0436">no she didn't</u>
<u n="745" who="S0435">she bit me</u>
<u n="746" who="S0436">she got a lot better anyway</u>
<u n="747" who="S0435"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="748" who="S0436">she was just a bit scared that's all</u>
<u n="749" who="S0435">yes I know</u>
<u n="750" who="S0436">poor <unclear/></u>
<u n="751" who="S0435">but you have to admit that's one place where she was very much more horrible vermin than degus</u>
<u n="752" who="S0436">yes I really don't want to be bitten by a degu though that could do serious damage I think</u>
<u n="753" who="S0435">they could I think hamster's pretty hamsters can if they really try</u>
<u n="754" who="S0436">oh I did get a hole in my thumbnail once</u>
<u n="755" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="756" who="S0436">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you know on the whole we'll just have to treat them nicely</u>
<u n="757" who="S0435">lots of green</u>
<u n="758" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="759" who="S0436">well I don't know in the case of the degus it's probably likely to lead to your fingers being chewed entirely accidentally but</u>
<u n="760" who="S0435">well you don't mean that</u>
<u n="761" who="S0436">yes they've just vicious little teeth</u>
<u n="762" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="763" who="S0435">I</u>
<u n="764" who="S0436">or vicious big teeth</u>
<u n="765" who="S0435">very much bigger than hamster teeth</u>
<u n="766" who="S0436">mm and with a lot more power behind them</u>
<u n="767" who="S0435">I think a lot more power in practice but theoretically I think hamsters could probably do</u>
<u n="768" who="S0436">I'm not engaging in a who would win in a fight conversation about small rodents this is silly</u>
<u n="769" who="S0435">Cookie</u>
<u n="770" who="S0436">I have some dignity</u>
<u n="771" who="S0435">not Cookie would win in a fight if there were and if there were any food at stake</u>
<u n="772" who="S0436">I have my dignity</u>
<u n="773" who="S0435"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="774" who="S0436">not much but I'm attempting to cling to it okay? plus it's silly anyway I didn't say when I went out to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> today she asked after the degus</u>
<u n="775" who="S0435">they're definitely still around boinging</u>
<u n="776" who="S0436">that's pretty much what I said she she's decided she wants a pet</u>
<u n="777" who="S0435">what does she want does she still go for ducks?</u>
<u n="778" who="S0436">of course she still has pet ducks this is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we're talking about</u>
<u n="779" who="S0435" trans="overlap">but is there anything she's <trunc>ac</trunc> but it's not a serious consideration wanting pet ducks</u>
<u n="780" who="S0436">well long term it is but</u>
<u n="781" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="782" who="S0436">all of this wanting a pet is fairly long term</u>
<u n="783" who="S0435">mm but I mean it's not the the the wanting a duck isn't something she's taking into full consideration right now is it?</u>
<u n="784" who="S0436">er</u>
<u n="785" who="S0435">or is she thinking so is she thinking small furry animal fish stick insect or dog? or cat?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0436">well I think she was more just thinking in the abstract that she's lacking small furry animals in her life cos you know when she was at university she er did the her volunteering thing at this bird shelter</u>
<u n="787" who="S0435" trans="overlap">yes she likes birds</u>
<u n="788" who="S0436">yes she really does we went and sat by the pond in the park</u>
<u n="789" who="S0435">and fed the ducks or</u>
<u n="790" who="S0436">well we didn't have any bird seed but we talked to them</u>
<u n="791" who="S0435" trans="overlap">probably not allowed allowed to anymore are you?</u>
<u n="792" who="S0436">I don't know really to be honest certainly not allowed to feed them bread so cute though the duckling there was a tiny baby duckling</u>
<u n="793" who="S0435">ah</u>
<u n="794" who="S0436">and you know you know the erm sort of gravel thing that sloped down to it keeps on falling on it it just keeled over sideways and it waved its little feet in the air and then it's mother had to come and sort of prod it up right again <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="795" who="S0435">they are idiot little creatures aren't they?</u>
<u n="796" who="S0436">well it was very baby it was trying its best</u>
<u n="797" who="S0435">ducklings are unreasonably cute aren't they?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0436">they really are</u>
<u n="799" who="S0435">I mean quite a lot of baby birds aren't very cute are they?</u>
<u n="800" who="S0436">well certainly before they have feathers they're just kind of icky</u>
<u n="801" who="S0435">and even afterwards quite a lot of them are still a bit sort of small and not quite right shaped</u>
<u n="802" who="S0436">oh bother</u>
<u n="803" who="S0435">what?</u>
<u n="804" who="S0436">oh just speaking of me speaking of my going into town thingummy</u>
<u n="805" who="S0435">forgot to buy something?</u>
<u n="806" who="S0436">no I forgot to post a letter</u>
<u n="807" who="S0435">oh</u>
<u n="808" who="S0436">I mean it doesn't really matter and I could walk down to the end of the road and post a letter I was just you know having a nice little glow of pretending I was a competent adult who remembered to do things but I have been revealed mm</u>
<u n="809" who="S0435">oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="810" who="S0436">are you okay?</u>
<u n="811" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="812" who="S0436">you're just looking kind of zoned out</u>
<u n="813" who="S0435">I'm tired</u>
<u n="814" who="S0436">yeah are you still feeling poorly?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0435">nobody's really taught me how to sleep properly</u>
<u n="816" who="S0436">most people don't need to be taught</u>
<u n="817" who="S0435">I know</u>
<u n="818" who="S0436">usually it just sort of happens</u>
<u n="819" who="S0435">I still can't get to sleep in the summer I'm definitely not somebody who's good in warm weather</u>
<u n="820" who="S0436">little squeekity</u>
<u n="821" who="S0435">yeah I've never worked out how people actually enjoy summer I mean I enjoy not being at school and being able to not</u>
<u n="822" who="S0436">I like the sunshine</u>
<u n="823" who="S0435">having some sunshine is nice but I don't like the fact that it makes everything far far too hot and everything's all humid and sticky and</u>
<u n="824" who="S0436">no it was it was horrible the other day but it's really rather nice now</u>
<u n="825" who="S0435">yes but most people think this is too cold for summer</u>
<u n="826" who="S0436">mm don't move to America and you'll be okay</u>
<u n="827" who="S0435">I know I wasn't planning to</u>
<u n="828" who="S0436" trans="overlap">well to be fair stay in England</u>
<u n="829" who="S0435">there are lots of reasons why I don't really want to move to America but</u>
<u n="830" who="S0436">yes</u>
<u n="831" who="S0435">and the weather is probably one of the least ones the least important ones</u>
<u n="832" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">hello hello still talking?</u>
<u n="833" who="S0435">yes we are</u>
<u n="834" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">officially?</u>
<u n="835" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="836" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh it's a long conversation</u>
<u n="837" who="S0435">erm well sorry erm yes but I think the weather is probably one of the reasons why one of the least important reasons why I don't want to go to America</u>
<u n="838" who="S0436">er that's probably fairly reasonable on the whole I mean there are lots of nice things about America I'm sure but yeah</u>
<u n="839" who="S0435">I'm still worried they have places in America where it's sort of thought of as normal to just walk to the shops with a gun</u>
<u n="840" who="S0436">I know</u>
<u n="841" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="842" who="S0436">it's cos you're just a crazy liberal eh?</u>
<u n="843" who="S0435">yes I know but</u>
<u n="844" who="S0436">don't you know it's a human right to be able to shoot people whenever you feel like it</u>
<u n="845" who="S0435">yep</u>
<u n="846" who="S0436">enjoy <pause dur="short"/> well that's</u>
<u n="847" who="S0435">somebody who I don't like the like the look of looked at me I think I feel threatened I shall shoot at them</u>
<u n="848" who="S0436">yes</u>
<u n="849" who="S0435">that is does seem how seem to be how it goes down quite a lot</u>
<u n="850" who="S0436">yes and I mean I'd like to give them the benefit of the doubt doubt and assume that almost all of the time it is nowhere near that bad but it doesn't take very many times for it to be not alright certainly what you get in the newspapers is a bit scary</u>
<u n="851" who="S0435">but I mean I I did I was in sort of I can't remember it was one of these sort of English or FPT lessons where we were told</u>
<u n="852" who="S0436">FPT</u>
<u n="853" who="S0435">faith philosophy and thinking it's your</u>
<u n="854" who="S0436">oh</u>
<u n="855" who="S0435">whatever you as you called it</u>
<u n="856" who="S0436">we have PSHE was it?</u>
<u n="857" who="S0435">no no no it's the RE</u>
<u n="858" who="S0436">oh no RE why were you doing gun control in RE?</u>
<u n="859" who="S0435">cos we <trunc>d</trunc> general do ethicy stuff</u>
<u n="860" who="S0436">oh fair enough whereas we did our ethicy stuff is PSHE</u>
<u n="861" who="S0435">ah and it was either an Englishy thing or whatever and it was it was a sort of a sort of we did stuff on a you know when you do things on arguing whether capital punishment is right and things and whether gun control is lots of things about gun control and I looked it up and I was you <trunc>do</trunc> <trunc>e</trunc> I think the amount of people <trunc>sh</trunc> sort of who are <trunc>mu</trunc>murdered sort of firearm murders in America is more than sort of most of Europe put together or something</u>
<u n="862" who="S0436">oh well I mean that's what you would expect</u>
<u n="863" who="S0435">yeah</u>
<u n="864" who="S0436">I mean you have to take into account the facts because</u>
<u n="865" who="S0435">no but I mean I <trunc>ne</trunc></u>
<u n="866" who="S0436">it's a bigger place with more people</u>
<u n="867" who="S0435" trans="overlap">place people</u>
<u n="868" who="S0436">but also honestly you would expect no less when it's so much easier to get hold of firearms but</u>
<u n="869" who="S0435">and it's a sort of the mass shooting rate is I think in a year is higher than sort of in the last year was higher than sort of <trunc>Ameri</trunc> erm higher than England and Australia put together or something</u>
<u n="870" who="S0436">mm I've no idea what gun control is like in Australia</u>
<u n="871" who="S0435">er less strict than in England but still reasonably so I think</u>
<u n="872" who="S0436">fair enough I suppose</u>
<u n="873" who="S0435">and did you know in erm one of the Arcticy Circle places I think it's in Canada it's Svalbard or somewhere it's a country where</u>
<u n="874" who="S0436">Svalbard isn't in Canada</u>
<u n="875" who="S0435">okay maybe it isn't wherever wherever it is</u>
<u n="876" who="S0436">it's really not</u>
<u n="877" who="S0435">where is it then?</u>
<u n="878" who="S0436">isn't Svalbard Norway?</u>
<u n="879" who="S0435">possibly it's one of the very Arcticy Circle bits where there are lots of polar bears</u>
<u n="880" who="S0436">uh</u>
<u n="881" who="S0435">apparently if you erm if you go out of one of the main cities you have to legally have carry a rifle with you and a <trunc>s</trunc> and somebody who's trained to use it cos there are so many polar bears around</u>
<u n="882" who="S0436">mm well then</u>
<u n="883" who="S0435">and apparently it's the only place in the world where there's any legal requirement to carry apparently there's a place in actually apparently there's a place in America where for political reasons although it's not an enforced law you have to erm your it was a sort of it was a a political statement thing they made it the law that everyone has to own a gun or something</u>
<u n="884" who="S0436">oh but surely that's just something daft like all of those old rules they say are on the books about</u>
<u n="885" who="S0435" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="886" who="S0436">I can't remember being allowed to shoot Welshman with a bow and arrow</u>
<u n="887" who="S0435">and the not being allowed to shoot cans within fifty foot of housing or whatever or <trunc>car</trunc>carry a plank of wood down a street</u>
<u n="888" who="S0436">I don't believe that one was ever real</u>
<u n="889" who="S0435">apparently so</u>
<u n="890" who="S0436">nah</u>
<u n="891" who="S0435">I think it was only a crowded street or something not a street full stop but</u>
<u n="892" who="S0436">well then</u>
<u n="893" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="894" who="S0436">deary me but no I'd always I'd always find think I find those er you know sort of hilarious laws things well a lot more hilarious if not for the fact that you know they are entirely artificial in sort of in the same way that the world longest word or whatever is</u>
<u n="895" who="S0435">the erm is the element not element the erm compound</u>
<u n="896" who="S0436">well well</u>
<u n="897" who="S0435">the the erm <unclear>typing</unclear> thing</u>
<u n="898" who="S0436">well in <trunc>En</trunc> well in English obviously you can make a a word that's pretty much as long as you like by just naming a really complicated molecule</u>
<u n="899" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="900" who="S0436">and obviously that's one way of cheating so most people don't count that you but know even when you have supposedly real words</u>
<u n="901" who="S0435">long they're a</u>
<u n="902" who="S0436">mostly made up to be</u>
<u n="903" who="S0435" trans="overlap">the longest word</u>
<u n="904" who="S0436" trans="overlap">long words you know it's like no one ever got pneumona-ultra-microscopic-silica-volcana-choliosis or whatever it was did they? and if they did they certainly never called it that</u>
<u n="905" who="S0435">and erm it's like the building the tallest building in the world you have no use for</u>
<u n="906" who="S0436">oh no that's a lot more aggravating</u>
<u n="907" who="S0435" trans="overlap">a building a building that tall but you do it anyway but you do it anyway to prove that your better than whoever's got the tallest one in the world</u>
<u n="908" who="S0436" trans="overlap">I wish they'd stop doing that</u>
<u n="909" who="S0435">at that point</u>
<u n="910" who="S0436"><vocal desc="sigh"/> I mean it's just a sure fire sign that you have too much money and not enough hobbies as a country well at least some people live in the country but you know</u>
<u n="911" who="S0435">if the whole country had that much too much money then you could spend it on useful things</u>
<u n="912" who="S0436">yes but I was going to say it would be a little bit less <unclear>grievous</unclear> than if you know you'd spent the equivalent equivalent amount of money building a giant skyscraper when you know half the people in the country were living below the poverty line that's when it really do have to start looking at people a bit funny but there you are I mean we can't talk London's going to get a stupid garden bridge isn't it?</u>
<u n="913" who="S0435">I'm not sure why I think it's a silly idea</u>
<u n="914" who="S0436">it's daft it's it's a complete vanity project I'm sure</u>
<u n="915" who="S0435">yes I know but</u>
<u n="916" who="S0436">I mean you know sort of</u>
<u n="917" who="S0435">they could do worse</u>
<u n="918" who="S0436">yes</u>
<u n="919" who="S0435">but you <trunc>no</trunc> <trunc>o</trunc>one one</u>
<u n="920" who="S0436" trans="overlap">you can always do worse but</u>
<u n="921" who="S0435">fact about silly erm London architecture</u>
<u n="922" who="S0436">uhu</u>
<u n="923" who="S0435">you know the skyscraper the one that's the cheese grater shaped one</u>
<u n="924" who="S0436">the cheese grater yes</u>
<u n="925" who="S0435" trans="overlap">yes the reason it's like that is because you have sight lines that are set up so that they are on that if things don't cover the erm that so they're not in the way of the view of St Paul's from certain areas</u>
<u n="926" who="S0436">oh</u>
<u n="927" who="S0435">and apparently the reason they have to build it like that</u>
<u n="928" who="S0436">really?</u>
<u n="929" who="S0435">was because to to get it just outside the sightline</u>
<u n="930" who="S0436">really?</u>
<u n="931" who="S0435">apparently so</u>
<u n="932" who="S0436">where did you learn that?</u>
<u n="933" who="S0435">erm it was the internet but it wasn't just a random person</u>
<u n="934" who="S0436">mm I'll have to look that one up before I believe it but fair enough yeah already done <unclear/> on the skyline</u>
<u n="935" who="S0435">but apparently they're sort of ridiculously old laws that sort of</u>
<u n="936" who="S0436">mm mm</u>
<u n="937" who="S0435">it it it was a it was a when you started to get building erm taller er</u>
<u n="938" who="S0436">yes yes</u>
<u n="939" who="S0435">sort of just slightly taller than the erm St Paul's they started saying ah but what will happen you won't be able to see St Paul's</u>
<u n="940" who="S0436">well it's an entirely silly sentimental thing but</u>
<u n="941" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="942" who="S0436">I think it's nice being able to see St Paul's and that is admittedly sort of an embarrassing large amount of that is in my case due to having watched Mary Poppins at an impressionable age which is really stupid because that's such a kitschy commercialised idea of what London is and I genuinely believed Dick Van Dyke had a cockney accent I didn't know any better</u>
<u n="943" who="S0435">oh dear</u>
<u n="944" who="S0436">it was the first rendition of a cockney accent I'd ever heard I had nothing to compare it against <vocal desc="laugh"/> also I was never very good at accents <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="945" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="946" who="S0436">but no you never spent as much watching Mary Poppins as I did</u>
<u n="947" who="S0435">I really didn't</u>
<u n="948" who="S0436">no cos you were too busy watching the Shiny Show</u>
<u n="949" who="S0435">oh shut up I think I was at a younger age at that point</u>
<u n="950" who="S0436">ah I don't know</u>
<u n="951" who="S0435">I watched the Clangers and</u>
<u n="952" who="S0436">well good</u>
<u n="953" who="S0435">I watched a lot of the Clangers</u>
<u n="954" who="S0436">everyone should watch the Clangers have you seen the new Clangers yet?</u>
<u n="955" who="S0435">no</u>
<u n="956" who="S0436">it's really disconcerting</u>
<u n="957" who="S0435">do they do the wrong whistle noises?</u>
<u n="958" who="S0436">no why it's disconcerting is because it it's very close</u>
<u n="959" who="S0435">but not quite there?</u>
<u n="960" who="S0436" trans="overlap">to the yes it's sort of it's sort of the faithfulness equivalent of Uncanny Valley or something</u>
<u n="961" who="S0435">okay</u>
<u n="962" who="S0436">it's made weirder by being almost but not quite but er yeah they've it's still a bit too jazzed up and computerified for my taste and they seem to have done some sort of recolouring of things presumably so they can better sell merchandise to people which is vaguely annoying but I don't</u>
<u n="963" who="S0435" trans="overlap">you see I'm but I I don't know</u>
<u n="964" who="S0436">it was it was rather good and you know on the whole I'm going to say well done them</u>
<u n="965" who="S0435" trans="overlap">I'm generally</u>
<u n="966" who="S0436">but they took away the original music</u>
<u n="967" who="S0435">and how can you remember it? I'm really awful at remembering music</u>
<u n="968" who="S0436">oh I just think I just think the music really makes all of those <unclear/></u>
<u n="969" who="S0435">but generally I'm not very good at computer animation for films and things generally I like computer animation but I really don't like the way they do computer animated films</u>
<u n="970" who="S0436">mm in what way?</u>
<u n="971" who="S0435">the style they've chosen to do it in?</u>
<u n="972" who="S0436">oh you're just talking about the current trend for children's films sort of the</u>
<u n="973" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="974" who="S0436">bubble head doll thing</u>
<u n="975" who="S0435">and it's really become a thing that all of them do that to a certain extent</u>
<u n="976" who="S0436">mm yeah just I don't know that's not a that's not a thing about the animation per se</u>
<u n="977" who="S0435" trans="overlap">I mean the and the really disconcerting thing is that that that that you have these really sort of tiny necks tiny nose tiny mouth massive eyed people but with with</u>
<u n="978" who="S0436">so it's like all those manga people you used to draw</u>
<u n="979" who="S0435">yeah with with perfect sort of unruffleable hair and sort of blocky unruffleable hair and then then then then you have these background which are pretty passable as being filmed</u>
<u n="980" who="S0436">that is the problem I have with em your <vocal desc="misc"/> Studio Ghibli thing</u>
<u n="981" who="S0435">Studio Ghibli</u>
<u n="982" who="S0436">the background are so beautiful and detailed and it looks really weird see this you know</u>
<u n="983" who="S0435">well I think they do it well I I think it's very much I think that the erm</u>
<u n="984" who="S0436" trans="overlap">no I I appreciate it's a matter of taste but</u>
<u n="985" who="S0435">the contrast between the background and erm the people I think I don't know I think there's <trunc>cer</trunc>certain levels but the thing about the people I have a problem with the background is the backgrounds are perfectly sort of rendered but look almost photographic then you have the people they are really out of proportion stylised but then there's fine details and there's sort of the the textured skin the textured lips</u>
<u n="986" who="S0436" trans="overlap">yes that's the mm that's the problem I have</u>
<u n="987" who="S0435" trans="overlap">and the and the really detailed irises and things and it just looks wrong</u>
<u n="988" who="S0436" trans="overlap">yes they have you know they have a whole team of people doing the their hair physics</u>
<u n="989" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="990" who="S0436">so it moves right and so it looks like a I don't know like a nonperson made out of person material and it's a little bit disconcerting isn't it?</u>
<u n="991" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="992" who="S0436">yeah but there you are that's why I think you ought to come with me to see the erm was it is the er</u>
<u n="993" who="S0435">the thingy one the</u>
<u n="994" who="S0436">the thing they're advertising by the people who did Secret of Kells</u>
<u n="995" who="S0435">the one that looks very very twee</u>
<u n="996" who="S0436">yes but remember Secret of Kells looked really really twee but it was just I don't know I'm</u>
<u n="997" who="S0435" trans="overlap">I think this one looks more this is one looks</u>
<u n="998" who="S0436" trans="overlap">I'm not sure I would watch the film as a film</u>
<u n="999" who="S0435">this one looks more twee than the Secret of Kells being a person and their dog go on an adventure kind of thing</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0436" trans="overlap">but it's yeah well that was what Secret of Kells ended up being really</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0435">oh</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0436">and I didn't see so many adverts for that so possibly that's what the adverts looked like for this but anyway I mean I really wasn't watching the Secret of Kells for the story was I?</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0435">no</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0436">I watched it because it's just it does my heart good to see people sort of doing doing animation that sort of takes advantage of the fact that it's animation and sort of explores that</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0435">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0436">you know</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0435">but I think that's why I so really like the Studio Ghibli things because I think they are they they do take into account the erm they are a bit twee in the general sense but I think it's a it's probably a sort of I think it's a probably more of a culture difference thing why it feels less sort of sickeningly twee and more sort of happily twee</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0436">I think you're making distinctions I never even knew existed but fair enough I you should probably make me watch some more of it you know give your sister some cultural education</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0435">Howl's Moving Castle was good though</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0436">Howl's Moving Castle was weird I I honestly thought that the book was sort of odd and hard to follow but it had nothing on that film</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0435">that film was nothing compared with some of her other books though</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0436">no the the book was nothing compared to some of her other books but simply why did the black blob things where did they come from and why did they wear straw hats?</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0435">that was that was Spirited Away</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0436">no no they were in the thing wasn't it? I could swear Howl's Moving Castle</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0435" trans="overlap">the little black spider things?</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0436">no</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0435">oh</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0436">there sort of er blobby monsters and they oozed after them and they wore straw hats and I never understood why they were there</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0435" trans="overlap">oh those I think they were just meant to be the witchy person's servanty people</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0436">yes</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0435">and if they</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0436">that doesn't explain why they were black ooze blobs wearing straw hats come on</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0435">I think they were lack ooze blobs because they were meant to be being a shown as being evil</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0436">and they wore straw hats because?</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0435">to blend in with the crowds</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0436">naturally</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0435">because or they were meant to be being shown to be evil but they were not meant to be looking like they were they were meant to be being they were being used as passably human servant things</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0436">hello Eldritch abomination oh but you're wearing a hat so that's okay are you okay?</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0435">mm fine</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0436">no I don't really buy that sorry</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0435">I didn't really question it but obviously I should have done</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0436">well obviously you shouldn't have done in sort of how the film worked it was just at that point I was still naively trying to understand what was going on and it was obviously a bad idea</u>
<u n="1033" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1034" who="S0435">yeah but they chose the right one to turn into a a sort of film that was going to make even less sense than the book because if they'd done it to pretty much any of her other ones</u>
<u n="1035" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1036" who="S0436">although you do have to wonder how much weirder it would be possible to make <unclear/></u>
<u n="1037" who="S0435" trans="overlap">to make well with the Tale of Time City the Tale of Time City was more easy to understand what was happening but why it was happening was an entirely different matter</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0436">yes and er what was the other one? Fire and Hemlock</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0435">I never read that one</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0436">didn't you? I could swear we got it up no I don't see why I would have read it if you didn't because I don't spontaneously read these things so I assume I pilfered it off you</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0435">oh I don't I don't remember reading it</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0436">it was the erm Tam Lin one</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0435">oh I think I might have done actually I can't remember what it's about</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0436">erm oh don't ask me it made no sense there was something odd to do with stone gateposts at one point</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0435">oh yes</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0436">and erm she did her slightly disconcerting narrative fetish for age gappy relationships again</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0435">I think so</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0436">and I honestly can't remember what else happened cos yeah I was rather lost</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0435">don't know I think her her what's his name <unclear/> ones were good I liked them</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0436">yeah they were good fun</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0435">but I think after that they just got weirder and weirder</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0436">and Howl's Moving Castle is genuinely funny but it's not really my cup of tea I suppose I I do remember when I I was remember when I was reading you Howl's moving Castle and the Lord of the Rings at the same time</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0435">oh vaguely</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0436">and it was astounding how much easier the Lord of the Rings was to read out loud</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0435">that's what didn't mummy find that when she was trying to read you Crest of <unclear/></u>
<u n="1056" who="S0436">oh that was she refused cos she hated reading it out loud yes</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0435" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0436">I think it's it's not bad to read one it you don't notice it when you read it to yourself I don't think at least you have to sort of be paying half an ear to it as it were</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0435">no but I I don't know it's very easy to you know the Rivers of London books I have a similar problem I've had a similar problem reading them and it's nothing to do with a problem with the writing as such because he's a screenwriter you can if if if you look for it you can really tell cos quite a lot of other writers do have a maybe not to a very great extent but it's not just a he said they said she said sort of thing they sort of add stuff in to to put the text into put the speech into context</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0436">yes</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0435">whereas as a screenwriter you notice that what he does is he has text full stop thing happening and he does it very well it works very well but once you notice that consciously while reading a passage it's really difficult to get past it</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0436">fair enough yeah I suppose I don't know I enjoyed Rivers of London well enough but I don't think I'd ever bother to read the rest</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0435">I think it is just cos I do like his things I think I think it's I think it's because I do like a Dr Who level of weirdness in my books</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0436" trans="overlap">no it wasn't the weirdness putting me off it was genuinely just too gory for me</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0435">well I think it gets less or it doesn't it's not as bad in the later books</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0436">people got their faces ripped off okay? it was traumatising</u>
<u n="1067" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1068" who="S0435">okay I <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1069" who="S0436">I'm a delicate flower</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0435">I don't know but I did like it though I really do like those books</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0436">yeah yeah fair enough I I think they're one of those things where I'm sort of going to be happy that they exist on other people's behalf but I'm not really going to bother getting into it myself</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0435">mm yeah fair enough I</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0436">seeing as we appear to be talking about books again</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0435">mm</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0436">we're not very good at having conversations about other things are we? anyway I was going to ask you have you started er reading the <unclear>Gutnicks</unclear>?</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0435">no not yet</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0436">fair enough</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0435">it's kind of depressing sometimes I forget that there are some people that don't like Douglas Adams you have to be a real really different person not to <trunc>ac</trunc> it's like</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0436">I can see how you could not like like certain aspects of it but it's hard to see how you could not find the jokes funny and and the thing is you always notice they're in people who read book I entirely could never manage they have different tastes</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0435">I know but you know those sort of pseudo erm life like sort of people go on an adventure with their dog kind of books</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0436">no I really don't</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0435">no no you know Michael Morpurgo is a sort of is an Uncanny <trunc>va</trunc>Valley sort of real-life thing</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0436">you just don't like Michael Morpurgo</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0435">I don't but you know that kind of style of book and those sort of those soppy feel-good books and the sort of the sort of erm that the oh I'm spending my time talking about my life nothing very much happens and this sort of books</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0436" trans="overlap">you mean I don't know I suppose I tend to think of those as two separate things really</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0435">I think they are but I think they're very linked</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0436">Michael Morpurgo is just a children's writer writes children's books</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0435" trans="overlap">I just can't stand it</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0436">whereas when you say soppy books about my life I think of those you know sort of awful ten-a-penny library books pastel covers and pictures of blonde ladies on the front</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0435">no I don't mean those ones I mean the ones with the erm the sort of the the those light blue sort of photographs with the swirly white writing on kind of one's</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0436"><vocal desc="laugh"/> just thinking</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0435">but you know the ones I mean</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0436">don't judge a book by its cover ah</u>
<u n="1094" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1095" who="S0435">but I mean I think it's same sort of people who go on from things like Michael Morpurgo to those sorts of books and the sort of the sort of people who really no</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0436" trans="overlap">is this The Fault in Our Stars or something you're thinking</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0435">no not particularly</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0436" trans="overlap">but you liked that didn't you?</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0435">not particularly but that kind of style of thing and the erm and the er sort of the whole sort of people who really like first person stuff</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0436"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1101" who="S0435">I mean there's nothing in practice wrong with first person there are</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0436">some of my best friends are in first person</u>
<u n="1103" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1104" who="S0435">I mean there are lots of really good books in first person but first person does quite often bring the worst out in books for me</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0436">yeah well I guess fair enough <pause dur="short"/> I've forgotten what you were reading oh people who don't like Douglas Adams</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0435">yes I just there are people who like very peopley books rather than ploty books yes</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0436">well Douglas Adams does not have any plot either</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0435">no but he's working on the assumption that the lack of plot is erm I think the lack of plot is a is due to a sort of the fact that he's packed it too full of other stuff</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0436">I think he just</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0435" trans="overlap">to put in a plot</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0436">didn't really have the attention span to write plots sadly</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0435">no</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0436">the jokes are just so funny I don't know how you cannot find them funny</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0435">I have no I sort of have an understanding why</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0436">lord you're turning into a penguin stop it</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0435" trans="overlap">but I I can sort of understand why some people may not like Hitchhiker's Guide because of the sort of weird non sequitur</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0436">yeah it is very whacky and very disjointed</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0435">it is but how you cannot like Dirk Gently or Hitchhiker's Guide</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0436">well by most people's standards Dirk Gently is also very whacky and disjointed it only doesn't look whacky and disjointed when you come to it after reading the Hitchhiker's Guide which doesn't even pretend to have a plot</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0435">well in the later ones it sort of tries to</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0436">and frankly goes massively downhill with it but there you are</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0435">I still can't get over the fact that the erm Eoin Colfer sequel is just so <unclear/> cos it was it was just a oh it was all a dream</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0436">really? oh</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0435">it really was and it was that was the worst thing you could ever apply and it was all a dream to</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0436">er I don't know I'd say that it's as valid a plot move as most things that happen</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0435">yes but it was just a no no no no</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0436" trans="overlap">in the series and</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0435">but but it was nowhere near as funny because he obviously wasn't Douglas Adams</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0436">yes but that was sort of inevitable</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0435" trans="overlap">and so so he went down the plot route and took what little plot there was and tried to make it into a big plot and then just said oh well it was all a dream they all actually died</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0436">really?</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0436">okay now I'm glad I didn't read it I mean I never really liked Eoin Colfer anyway</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0435"><unclear/> I almost could manage but it was just slightly off</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0436">well I tried to read Artemis Fowl and it was just it smacked far too much of the target audience being hyperactive teenage boys for me to sort of really have the patience for what it was sort of it was very he jumped up and down shouting in your face</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0435" trans="overlap">I think I managed my way though I managed about three quarters of the way through first book I think or something</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0436">I think I turned all the pages in the book but mainly because I was transliterating the silly cipher they had at the bottom of the pages which it turned out it repeated so that was pointless <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1138" who="S0435">I think I think if you do that you should at least write something interesting that you wouldn't already find in the book</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0436">oh you you you didn't it was it was genuinely something new I think but anyway so I had fun with that but anyway I don't know who who would there's no one who could really write Douglas Adams except Douglas Adams I mean the closest you could get is Terry Pratchett</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0435" trans="overlap">you could get is Terry Pratchett if they'd given it to Terry Pratchett you would have maybe you wouldn't have got a Douglas Adams look-alike out of it but you would have got a good book out of it</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0436">yes <pause dur="short"/> I'm still sad about Terry Pratchett</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0435">yes the new book's coming out though</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0436">yeah I don't even know whether I want to read it or whether it would feel a bit you know weird and morbid</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0435">I am because it's another Tiffany Aching one and I sort of</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0436">I'm not so keen on them you see</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0435">no I I do like them but I think the thing is that they're they're one of the few actual proper coherent sort of series within the</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0436">oh yes I just</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0435">and I feel that it would be a bit of a shame to</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0436">to sort of let that go you mean</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0436">fair enough and I'll probably end up reading it at some point anyway I don't know I think I'll probably just you know steal Going Postal from you again and curl up in a little nest of Going Postal <pause dur="short"/> so funny</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0435">I I still can't I still think Night Watch is just so utterly brilliant</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0436">the Night Watch is utterly brilliant</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0435">and I think that's not just cos it's funny though</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0436">yes Night Watch is one of the very thinky ones Going Postal has some very good thinky stuff in it as well it's just also I think in many ways sort of overtly funny</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0435">oh yes I think Night <trunc>Wa</trunc> <trunc>Wat</trunc> Night Watch is one of the least overtly funny ones</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0436">yeah I mean it has some fairly good gags in but</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0435">the boiled eggs</u>
<u n="1159" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1160" who="S0436">poor <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and his hardboiled egg but er yes <pause dur="short"/> I just really like Going Postal</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0435">okay</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0436">yes <pause dur="long"/> but yeah you have to read it now you see you've only for the <unclear/> thing</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0435">mm</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0436">mm ah anyway we should probably wrap up now considering that we've been wittering on at each other for nearly two hours</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0436">you were telling me you couldn't think of anything to say for that long</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0435">no</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0436">and you didn't even have to resort to summarising entire big finishes and things which is</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0435">you still have time ten minutes</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0436">no no no no</u>
<u n="1171" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1172" who="S0435">are you sure you don't want the communist Daleks on drugs?</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0436">I think I have never been surer of anything in my life</u>
<u n="1174" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1175" who="S0435">actually no you wouldn't get that one anyway cos I still don't understand it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="1176" who="S0436">and I think that proves my point</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0435">ahem just because there are far too many layers of non-reality in it <pause dur="short"/> and then they start singing</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0436">do they start singing Gilbert and Sullivan is the question</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0435">no but they start</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0436">good</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0435">singing patriotic songs I think</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0436">real patriotic songs or?</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0435">yes like?</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0436">I can't remember what it is it it was cos all I can imagine now is sort of a fleet of Daleks all bursting into I don't know Jerusalem or something</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0435">no it's a I think it's a communist thing or thing you songy thing</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0436">yeah well that would make more sense I don't know any communist songs the closest I know to a communist song is the song about the history of communism set to the Tetris theme tune</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0435">oh</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0436">have you never heard that?</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0435">I've heard of it</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0436">it's it's quite something put it that way</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0435">yeah</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0436">no I came across that at er one of those</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0435">ASNaCs</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0436">er not actually ASNaCs but one of those sort of student gatherings of those kinds of people yes this was also one of er Youtube watching at midnight events that led to me finding that erm that those clips from a Playstation game with Tom Baker's narrating a story about magical dolphins stop and saving the universe</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0435">I sort of want to play that computer game</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0436">you've have to wonder what was going through their head</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0435">if it wasn't narrated by Tom Baker it would have been great</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0436">if by great you mean terrible</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0436">how did that get pitched?</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0435">I don't know I think they said well we know you like Douglas Adams so let's have dolphins cos cos Douglas Adams had dolphins</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0436">see the link?</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0435">okay and okay get this saving the universe see universe galaxy Douglas Adams and and then okay who can we think of that had a erm mm sci-fi Dr Who</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0436">I think all of that implies a level of logical thought that</u>
<u n="1205" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1206" who="S0435">wasn't it Splash the Dolphin or something</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0436">something equally awful yes</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0435">and didn't he get dolphins in spaceships and things?</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0436">I wouldn't be at all surprise but all the weird Youtube videos have been introduced to they do sort of blend into one</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0435">has there been more than one time time where you have dolphins saving the universe</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0436">er no but then there was also the video about erm the mass murdering llama that wears a hat</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0435" trans="overlap">oh very everyone's heard of that though</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0436" trans="overlap">well I hadn't</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0435">the erm the Stephen Carl one</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0436">oh yes it was called Carl</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0435">I think the other one was called Steve</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0436">fair enough I I wasn't paying attention I was too busy being traumatised er there was also the <unclear>Hayleg Thulu</unclear> song</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0435">no not heard that one</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0436">you probably don't want to I mean you've actually read Love Prophet so you might like it</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0435">and then there's the Nargle Song did you never see that <trunc>ne</trunc></u>
<u n="1221" who="S0436">no I don't want to do I?</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0435">probably not it's not that bad it's an animated song about nargles</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0436">naturally cos what else would it be? well this is the internet</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0435">it's less disturbing than the llamas in hats</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0436">good although that's not really saying very much</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0435">it is significantly less so</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0436">good although that's still not saying an awful lot</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0435">and it's less traumatising then the Charlie the Unicorn</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0436">did you ever have to watch that?</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0435">no nobody ever showed that one to me</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0436">you just need to be surgically removed from the internet</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0435">oh no no no no if <trunc>s</trunc> people my age I can say that</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0436">youth these days</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0435">a large proportion of them will have heard of the Nargle Song erm Charlie the Unicorn and what was the other one I was saying that you haven't heard of? was there another one? no and probably Llamas in Hats as well</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0436">fair enough then again I learnt fairly recently that what people of my age are supposed to remember on the internet is something about badger badger badger badger mushroom snake</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0435" trans="overlap">well everyone knows that yes</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0436">no I'd I'd never come across that</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0435">okay</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0436">I didn't spend very much time on the internet when I was little I spent a lot of time doing equally pointless things but you know other pointless things reading things of questionable literary value but you know maybe I can't claim to have grown out of that</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0435">you've read Blank and Fire</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0436">come on that was at least impressive</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0435">yes</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0436">you can't really claim it was bad just because that implies you have some coherent standards by which to judge its literary merit</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0435">I think I think that one has won discussions when people have been discussing who has read the weirdest book</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0436">no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> still has be beat on that one</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0435">what one has?</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0436">she swears blind she can't remember much about it anymore but she swears blind she once read a book called the Voodoo Handbag</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0435">okay but it is weirder than a dragon that's dead and alive and a bridge all at the same time and trapped in a railway tunnel and somebody gets their arm burnt off by a dragon bone?</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0436">er I don't know I think we really do need to wrap this up now</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0435">yeah okay</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0436">bye bye Mr recording device</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0435">bye bye</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
