<text id="SMK7">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:37:08</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-20</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0631 S0632</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Kitchen in a shared House in Finchley London; all speakers’ home.</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Slimming World Healthy Extra options, free food and ‘syns’ in various foods, tea, the cooking, 0 calorie syrup, artificial flavour, making plans for ‘treat day’ Saturday, Siri, calendars, cauliflower cheese with a roast, weight loss, unreliable scales, exercise, Supermarkets feeling best Quorn range, veg box deliveries, saving money, tax, work, targets, spice mix, double peas in the freezer, frylight, mint.</topics>
		<activity>Best friends and Housemates talking while cooking dinner no.1. </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T04</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0631">
				<exactage>27</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hereford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>England</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Neutral</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years 6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Pharmacy Dispenser</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0632">
				<exactage>26</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kings Lynn, Norfolk, UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>England</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Neutral</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Carer/ Freelance Illustrator and writer</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0631">I'll have a little bit of erm a little bit of soft cheese sometimes</u>
<u n="2" who="S0632">yeah I've never really thought about it as an option because I always drink so much milk in my tea and coffee like</u>
<u n="3" who="S0631" trans="overlap">mm I only I drink tea but I kind of like I drink tea in the morning</u>
<u n="4" who="S0632" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="5" who="S0631">and sometimes that's the only tea I drink because if I go to work I won't drink tea in a day like no</u>
<u n="6" who="S0632">so that's a smidgen of milk isn't it?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0631" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="8" who="S0632">in one like one cup of tea <unclear/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0631" trans="overlap">exactly and then I'll come back home and I won't have a tea in the evening most of the time because and if I want to I'll have green tea</u>
<u n="10" who="S0632">erm yeah no that's a good option I need to drink more green tea and herbal teas really because</u>
<u n="11" who="S0631">there's still caffeine in green tea and that's all you really <unclear/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's true I've got my sweet rhubarb I like that but it's a different thing it's just a different <unclear/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0631" trans="overlap"><unclear/> though</u>
<u n="14" who="S0632">mm?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0631">would that count though? well did it count <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0632">you know I never really thought about it cos it's it's a tea do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm but yeah I think I did take a look at the box and it was like you know it's a teabag and how much can there be in a teabag?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0631">mm</u>
<u n="20" who="S0632">one has got like no calorific content whatsoever what does?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0631">yeah if it's zero calories then you're alright so it'll be a sin because you'll have to count the calories and if it's zero it's nothing</u>
<u n="22" who="S0632">yeah yeah hibiscus rosehip natural flavourings apple sweet blackberry leaves there's like no nutritional information</u>
<u n="23" who="S0631">it's gonna be leaves isn't it? so</u>
<u n="24" who="S0632">a flavour of leaves is it can't be much can it?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0631">no</u>
<u n="26" who="S0632">I wouldn't have thought so it's good to have one type of rice today because it was a bit of a faff to do the two types of rice</u>
<u n="27" who="S0631">like what what do you mean?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0632">because I did this red rice as well as the brown rice</u>
<u n="29" who="S0631">okay</u>
<u n="30" who="S0632">it's really tasty</u>
<u n="31" who="S0631">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0632">oh well it takes ages it takes like half an hour to boil</u>
<u n="33" who="S0631">yeah it's like wild rice <unclear>it tastes so good</unclear></u>
<u n="34" who="S0632">yeah <unclear/> really nice but</u>
<u n="35" who="S0631">have you had <unclear/> my syrup?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0632">did I?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0631">no no I'm not <unclear/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0631" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="39" who="S0631">but this is my syrup</u>
<u n="40" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="41" who="S0631"><unclear/>?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0632">no I haven't</u>
<u n="43" who="S0631">you can help yourself to it</u>
<u n="44" who="S0632">is it a zero?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0631" trans="overlap">American <unclear>chemically</unclear></u>
<u n="46" who="S0632" trans="overlap">so like fake</u>
<u n="47" who="S0631">and you need only a tiny bit</u>
<u n="48" who="S0632">fake flavour it says here zero <trunc>cara</trunc> zero caramel? zero calorie caramel syrup there we are</u>
<u n="49" who="S0631" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0632">I said it</u>
<u n="51" who="S0631">if you ever want something sweet</u>
<u n="52" who="S0632" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="53" who="S0631">or like syrup and on on porridge</u>
<u n="54" who="S0632">it does smell like caramel in a really weird way</u>
<u n="55" who="S0631">in like American</u>
<u n="56" who="S0632" trans="overlap">like like</u>
<u n="57" who="S0631">way like Americans like</u>
<u n="58" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0631">if you have something grape flavoured the Americans</u>
<u n="60" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it doesn't taste anything like a grape</u>
<u n="61" who="S0631">and it just tastes artificial in a kind of nice way</u>
<u n="62" who="S0632">yes</u>
<u n="63" who="S0631">it's a little bit like that</u>
<u n="64" who="S0632">slightly trashy</u>
<u n="65" who="S0631">it's trashy sauce yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0632">yeah trash sauce</u>
<u n="67" who="S0631" trans="overlap">if you ever wanna put it on like porridge or anything or like if you make magic pancakes you can just make them with an egg apparently you just whip up the egg whites and mix it in with the egg or something weird like that</u>
<u n="68" who="S0632">oh</u>
<u n="69" who="S0631">sin-free not really a pancake just a flat thing put you can put stuff on it though</u>
<u n="70" who="S0632">like a little well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> looked up these erm sin-free erm Slimming World burritos like the in burrito things and I was like how are they sin-free? like do you obviously you'd have to use the tortilla as your like healthy choice B and he was like no it's made out of egg so that's just <unclear/> omelette</u>
<u n="71" who="S0631">yeah they do though they do all sorts of stuff like that but you can make <trunc>ca</trunc>cauliflower <unclear/> can't you?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0632">oh the one</u>
<u n="73" who="S0631" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0632">I had cauliflower pizza once and it was absolutely horrible really really disgusting</u>
<u n="75" who="S0631" trans="overlap">I've had cauliflower pizza and I was disappointed cos it smells of just no it <trunc>ta</trunc> can you even taste the smell?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0632">yeah cos like boiled cauliflower or cooked cauliflower it does have that smell that it has and</u>
<u n="77" who="S0631">so</u>
<u n="78" who="S0632">you know that you're just eating a big flat flat thing of cauliflower</u>
<u n="79" who="S0631">but you could kind of like pimp it up a little bit and make it a bit garlicky or I suppose couldn't you? you could</u>
<u n="80" who="S0632" trans="overlap">you could pimp that up yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0631" trans="overlap"><unclear/> a cauliflower garlic</u>
<u n="82" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's true I still haven't had your cauliflower cheese</u>
<u n="83" who="S0631">no</u>
<u n="84" who="S0632">not this treat day <trunc>ne</trunc><trunc>ne</trunc></u>
<u n="85" who="S0631" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0632">next treat day <pause dur="short"/> cos I've got erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s baby shower on the Saturday but that's not all day</u>
<u n="87" who="S0631" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0632">so we could like exercise in the morning and could come home and eat cauliflower cheese</u>
<u n="89" who="S0631">yeah no actually what weekend is that? I'm going to <unclear/> weekend on the <trunc>thir</trunc> to the fourteenth thirteenth and I'll be home on the fourteenth so that's the Sunday</u>
<u n="90" who="S0632">oh is that in erm that's February this is still January it's the</u>
<u n="91" who="S0631" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah okay</u>
<u n="92" who="S0632">thirteenth yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0631">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0632">so it's all</u>
<u n="95" who="S0631" trans="overlap">oh yes okay cool</u>
<u n="96" who="S0632">it's all good not this weekend but the weekend after</u>
<u n="97" who="S0631">I can't visualise dates very well I can't see them in my head</u>
<u n="98" who="S0632">I I have a calendar on my desk and it really helps me cos I'm such a forgetful person you know how I I tell <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> everything and I'll sort of write it in the diary and on the calendar?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0631" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0632">I haven't written in my lunch date for tomorrow I'm going to have lunch with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> tomorrow as well</u>
<u n="101" who="S0631" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0632">so but I've told <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> to remind me so it should be fine</u>
<u n="103" who="S0631">mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0632">that sometimes goes wrong and I get the reminder at completely the wrong time and I'm like</u>
<u n="105" who="S0631" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0632">oh I don't know how it went wrong but that's definitely wrong</u>
<u n="107" who="S0631">erm mm <unclear/> or something <unclear/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0631"><unclear/> for the rice I know you're not like</u>
<u n="110" who="S0632" trans="overlap">cos I've never had</u>
<u n="111" who="S0631">all about the rice but I love <trunc>ri</trunc>rice</u>
<u n="112" who="S0632" trans="overlap">well I like an interesting rice so I've never had a rice with cauliflower cheese before which and I don't know if that's weird to you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0631">mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0632">is it is it something that you</u>
<u n="115" who="S0631" trans="overlap">some people just haven't I'm all over it love it</u>
<u n="116" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it's just it's not tradition in my house</u>
<u n="117" who="S0631">I loves it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0632">I think it's meant to be like a handful per person but I put in</u>
<u n="119" who="S0631">I dunno</u>
<u n="120" who="S0632">two handfuls per person cos me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> eat a lot</u>
<u n="121" who="S0631"><unclear/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0632">rice brown rice no less</u>
<u n="123" who="S0631">I don't know how much erm is in erm ketchup because I had a lot of ketchup yesterday <unclear/> because I bought some pop chips and a sushi</u>
<u n="124" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0631">and I had a dollop of ketchup and normally in place of that dollop of ketchup I'd have had a little slimming chocolate bar</u>
<u n="126" who="S0632">ah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0631">I don't know whether <unclear/> be more</u>
<u n="128" who="S0632" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="129" who="S0631">it won't be be more than a little chocolate bar</u>
<u n="130" who="S0632">no</u>
<u n="131" who="S0631"><unclear/> the same calories <unclear>that I</unclear> shouldn't be eating</u>
<u n="132" who="S0632">yeah maybe</u>
<u n="133" who="S0631"><unclear/> to be honest <unclear/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0632" trans="overlap">well you said you said this morning that you'd lost eight pounds this year</u>
<u n="135" who="S0631">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0632">so did you weigh yourself this morning and that's how much you've lost in total? that's amazing</u>
<u n="137" who="S0631">well I got got on the scales and it said erm ten stone eight and I'm no and I was that the other day and I was like okay that's fine</u>
<u n="138" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0631">but then I got back on it this morning and it said it again so I was like but exactly the same for the same quarter</u>
<u n="140" who="S0632">so the same quarter wow</u>
<u n="141" who="S0631" trans="overlap">and I was like</u>
<u n="142" who="S0632">that's a good system</u>
<u n="143" who="S0631">I was like okay so I get off it so I gave it a kick like to see if maybe the floor or maybe it was just kind of stuck on the same weight as I got on and I got on again and it went ten stone six so I was like right better but it could be the floor</u>
<u n="144" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0631">so I got I moved it around a lot and I got on</u>
<u n="146" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0631">it again and I got on it again and it kept saying the same thing</u>
<u n="148" who="S0632">I've done that for I I had three different readings the other morning</u>
<u n="149" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0632">and one was lower and one was higher</u>
<u n="151" who="S0631" trans="overlap">obviously <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0632">and then the one in the middle</u>
<u n="153" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0632">kept coming up over and over again when I moved it to a different point and I was like</u>
<u n="155" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0632">and again and again and again</u>
<u n="157" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah getting on it</u>
<u n="158" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0631">and I was like it it would be very strange for it to be precisely the same weight as the other day</u>
<u n="160" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0631">when erm like to the same quarter of a pound</u>
<u n="162" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0631">and erm so I thought I'll move it cos I expected it <unclear/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0631">and then well hopefully you know</u>
<u n="166" who="S0632">yeah fingers crossed</u>
<u n="167" who="S0631">I kept moving in that direction <unclear/> so you think it would be</u>
<u n="168" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0631">so I moved it on the floor to a floor that because you know the floors are obviously the floorboards get creaky <unclear/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="171" who="S0631">so maybe it was just sitting differently so I moved it a lot and I kept getting on it and moved it around and it just kept coming up with ten six</u>
<u n="172" who="S0632">that's really good</u>
<u n="173" who="S0631">my lowest last year was 10 five <unclear/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0632"><unclear>probably how</unclear> like you are it's like why <unclear>are you lighter</unclear> than my goal? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0631">oh do you know what? erm <unclear/> and that's why it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah I mean I know but it actually does make a big difference and I have to</u>
<u n="177" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0632">remind myself that</u>
<u n="179" who="S0631">you are I am shorter</u>
<u n="180" who="S0632">because yeah I just can't even imagine weighing that though</u>
<u n="181" who="S0631" trans="overlap">I just don't want to have the wobbly bits <unclear/> do you know what? if I got to nine something</u>
<u n="182" who="S0632" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0631">I'd feel like when I was like I was the size I was at <unclear/> school</u>
<u n="184" who="S0632">oh</u>
<u n="185" who="S0631">and that's kind of like what it's all about</u>
<u n="186" who="S0632">I think I was about twelve and a half at school</u>
<u n="187" who="S0631">okay</u>
<u n="188" who="S0632">and that's like when I look at people obviously at the time I thought I was huge a huge heffalump</u>
<u n="189" who="S0631" trans="overlap">I thought I was huge though</u>
<u n="190" who="S0632">but isn't that ridiculous?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0631" trans="overlap">it is ridiculous</u>
<u n="192" who="S0632">and then you look back and you're like</u>
<u n="193" who="S0631">do you know what though? at school I wouldn't have walked around in a bikini I wouldn't though</u>
<u n="194" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="195" who="S0631">so</u>
<u n="196" who="S0632" trans="overlap">no chance you'd have been mortified</u>
<u n="197" who="S0631">I wouldn't have ever got in a bikini and walked around no I didn't at school</u>
<u n="198" who="S0632">no I know I know <vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="199" who="S0631" trans="overlap">but I would</u>
<u n="200" who="S0632">I did have that vision initially of just like <unclear/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0631" trans="overlap">it would have been but it would have been inappropriate wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0631">but I wouldn't have I wouldn't have just come to and got in a bikini but because now I'm bigger than that obviously I'm a bit like oh no <trunc>w</trunc>why wouldn't I have done that then? and I wouldn't do it now</u>
<u n="204" who="S0632">it's the curse of a teenager to be like the slimmest that you're <trunc>e</trunc> like probably ever gonna be and then also hate your body more than you'll ever hate it because</u>
<u n="205" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0632">you're a teenager</u>
<u n="207" who="S0631">but then it's the legs thing so really I just need to get my legs moving it's cardio rather than strength and stuff I need to do</u>
<u n="208" who="S0632">do you think so? yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0631">I read it online if you <trunc>cardi</trunc>cardio just like burns it away where it like like it doesn't build up muscle as fast as the cardio</u>
<u n="210" who="S0632" trans="overlap">no and it does build up yeah but like less</u>
<u n="211" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah it it does</u>
<u n="212" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0631">but it's not like I'm just gonna put on like I'm doing the bike thing again now</u>
<u n="214" who="S0632">you should do your special <trunc>s</trunc>sofa cycling</u>
<u n="215" who="S0631" trans="overlap">oh god</u>
<u n="216" who="S0632">that you were doing the other night</u>
<u n="217" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0631">oh</u>
<u n="220" who="S0632">where <unclear/> else though to be honest</u>
<u n="221" who="S0631">it I don't I was just like ah ah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0631">sofa cycling was good though I liked that erm but yeah do you know what part of it probably is though?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="225" who="S0631">it's probably because of my sister because she is significantly tinier</u>
<u n="226" who="S0632" trans="overlap">so that</u>
<u n="227" who="S0631">and I'm not trying to be like that cos I don't</u>
<u n="228" who="S0632" trans="overlap">no no but</u>
<u n="229" who="S0631">want to be</u>
<u n="230" who="S0632">I think when you have a sister who is like significantly small that</u>
<u n="231" who="S0631">her legs are too thin <pause dur="short"/> have you have you?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0632">I think I have like I think I I did see her when you</u>
<u n="233" who="S0631">if you see her in skinny jeans her legs are like</u>
<u n="234" who="S0632">I've always thought that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was really really slim</u>
<u n="235" who="S0631">she yeah she is</u>
<u n="236" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0631">erm <pause dur="short"/> but if you see her in jeans like I took her out for her birthday like last year and erm only to like out for dinner</u>
<u n="238" who="S0632" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0631"><unclear/> come on let's go for dinner erm and she wore jeans and I was walking behind her and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was with us as well and I <unclear/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0632" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0631">her legs are too skinny and she has admitted that she's been a bit obsessive generally <pause dur="short"/> not like she has been previously obsessive <pause dur="short"/> but then I suppose if you're trying to maintain being <unclear/> it doesn't mean you actually are ill it just means <unclear/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0631">and then she is naturally thin she's slim she's a slim person</u>
<u n="244" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah I mean people people are</u>
<u n="245" who="S0631" trans="overlap">but you see you see her legs are really tiny <pause dur="short"/> but I just I don't wanna walk around like on holiday with my legs going woohoo</u>
<u n="246" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0631">and it's like and hers are just like that <pause dur="short"/> I don't I'm not like I don't want to be that size</u>
<u n="248" who="S0632" trans="overlap">but you</u>
<u n="249" who="S0631">I really don't</u>
<u n="250" who="S0632">well if you're just happy you know if you've like accepted that you're not going to look like your sister</u>
<u n="251" who="S0631" trans="overlap">but I don't want to</u>
<u n="252" who="S0632">cos you're different people you just want to be happy</u>
<u n="253" who="S0631" trans="overlap">cos that's stupid</u>
<u n="254" who="S0632">with yourself</u>
<u n="255" who="S0631">yeah so <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> there's that there's that <unclear/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0631">it's that it's all there that's where it is now and it needs to come off there <unclear/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I think yeah if you do that sofa cycling that'll be it</u>
<u n="259" who="S0631" trans="overlap"><unclear>it's not gonna do anything though</unclear></u>
<u n="260" who="S0632" trans="overlap">you know what I just need some amazing results from workouts in just a few months like not just not not</u>
<u n="261" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0632">even not even when I'm jogging jogging on the spot because</u>
<u n="263" who="S0631">why do we not just do this anyway?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0632">yeah just like cook and jog <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0631">we could one day one one treat day we could get a really nice picnic but then</u>
<u n="266" who="S0632" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="267" who="S0631">we could go on a Boris bike around Hyde Park</u>
<u n="268" who="S0632">let's do that that's a nice idea</u>
<u n="269" who="S0631">why are we not doing that?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0632">I think maybe treat day could also be like exercise day cos then you're like you know what?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0631">and it's a day off</u>
<u n="272" who="S0632">yeah exactly it's always a day off and you know how food always tastes better if you work for it like if you're really hungry</u>
<u n="273" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0632">you're gonna appreciate that burger a lot more then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0631" trans="overlap">and we might not feel so shit after we've eaten it either</u>
<u n="276" who="S0632">no because it'll be like necessary</u>
<u n="277" who="S0631" trans="overlap">and my appetite does get smaller but I always feel like just saying no put it all on all on</u>
<u n="278" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it's the greed of like oh I really want all the <unclear/> and I've only got twenty-four hours to eat everything I want</u>
<u n="279" who="S0631">oh we can oh we can</u>
<u n="280" who="S0632" trans="overlap">we can</u>
<u n="281" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0632">I don't know if I'm meant to be doing anything else all I'm doing is boiling rice erm that takes ages</u>
<u n="283" who="S0631">I'm done now</u>
<u n="284" who="S0632">okay</u>
<u n="285" who="S0631">I need to vomit</u>
<u n="286" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0631">oh I'm gonna retch in the sink</u>
<u n="288" who="S0632">it's full <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0631">oh dear let's go in the bin then</u>
<u n="290" who="S0632">go in the mop bucket and like which I still haven't taken outside</u>
<u n="291" who="S0631">it's alright <unclear/> like every time somebody <unclear/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0632">yeah it's like kind of handy though to have because I've been doing that too and go eh just get it</u>
<u n="293" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah maybe we should get you know one of the flat ones the cheap flat you know</u>
<u n="294" who="S0632" trans="overlap">that's the Swiffering type ones</u>
<u n="295" who="S0631">and then just spray the floor a little bit and just go this and just of course spray it done</u>
<u n="296" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0631">so it's not wet then</u>
<u n="298" who="S0632">so true</u>
<u n="299" who="S0631">so so true</u>
<u n="300" who="S0632">a nice little <unclear/> and then you don't need to do the big mop as often</u>
<u n="301" who="S0631">no</u>
<u n="302" who="S0632">oh good there's lots of eggs</u>
<u n="303" who="S0631">of course</u>
<u n="304" who="S0632">of course</u>
<u n="305" who="S0631">that's I I said though didn't I?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0632" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0631">you'd go on this diet and <unclear/> I'm gonna go for eggs like there's no tomorrow</u>
<u n="308" who="S0632">that's true you did say that and I love an egg</u>
<u n="309" who="S0631">I love an egg and those ones are free as well <unclear/> box</u>
<u n="310" who="S0632">they're like added extra bickies</u>
<u n="311" who="S0631">are they nice? are they nice?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0632">they look nice yeah they look</u>
<u n="313" who="S0631"><unclear/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0632" trans="overlap"><unclear/> eggs</u>
<u n="315" who="S0631">oh they're big</u>
<u n="316" who="S0632">they are big</u>
<u n="317" who="S0631"><unclear/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0632">I was gonna do some fish with this dinner <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0631">I'm gonna start buying frozen food you know but not frozen everything but</u>
<u n="320" who="S0632">some things frozen are really handy</u>
<u n="321" who="S0631">yeah I'm gonna just start buying Quorn and put it because <trunc>O</trunc>Ocado sell more Quorn products than Tesco they just have a better range and so I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> if I get a fresh box every week do you wanna just once a month <unclear/> Quorn shop?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0631">but I'm thinking I might cancel all that fresh box already because it's just <unclear/> and to be honest there might be a broccoli in there that looks really nice but it's still costing me two quid and it costs me forty-nine P at Tesco</u>
<u n="324" who="S0632">yeah I did think that's a particularly big healthy looking broccoli but two pounds?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah just <unclear/> is nice</u>
<u n="326" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0631">but it's like <unclear/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0632">no</u>
<u n="329" who="S0631">I might as well because it's organic and it's not <unclear/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0632">yeah that's so true</u>
<u n="331" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0632">and it's like oh no now it's gone off instantly</u>
<u n="333" who="S0631">yeah and like as good as good as it is to eat organic and stuff at the same time I'm a little bit like well if you throw enough of it out which I hope not to and that's why I've got <unclear/> might cost me twenty quid a week but <unclear/> throw some of it out but actually</u>
<u n="334" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0631">I like the novelty it's the novelty that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0632" trans="overlap">I know I ordered some one of these eat fresh boxes and and I did it for like a week or two but I was like actually it's not worth the money <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like maybe it will be but then like actually having it and seeing the money go out of your account was a bit like no it's not really worth it</u>
<u n="337" who="S0631">yeah I might keep <unclear/> box if my <trunc>mo</trunc>money's gonna go down I might <unclear/> box because I like that <unclear>place</unclear></u>
<u n="338" who="S0632">mm that is one of the things though like I I used to when we were talking about though where does your money go when you've got plenty of money? because like I was on more money at <anon type="place"/> I was on more like one thousand five hundred a month</u>
<u n="339" who="S0631" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0632">one thousand seven hundred I think I was on <unclear/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0632">and erm but obviously you know saving for the wedding and everything and then I would I spent fifty pounds a month on gym membership and there were all sorts of</u>
<u n="343" who="S0631" trans="overlap">you just do don't you? you kind of</u>
<u n="344" who="S0632" trans="overlap">like hair appointments</u>
<u n="345" who="S0631">is it within your means? yeah oh I'll do it then</u>
<u n="346" who="S0632">yeah going for like waxes and things before my honeymoon and it all just added up to the point where I just didn't feel any better off than I do now on on less money</u>
<u n="347" who="S0631" trans="overlap">is it is erm the thing though isn't it like there's only a certain amount you can earn where you just start living differently <unclear/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0631">so like say you could be on like fifty grand a year right but you're not gonna live any better than somebody on thirty grand a year because you'll just have a better car you'll have a more expensive car</u>
<u n="350" who="S0632" trans="overlap">it's true and then there's tax</u>
<u n="351" who="S0631" trans="overlap">and you'll have a more expensive rent</u>
<u n="352" who="S0632">it's true it's true you'll just you'll get a nicer car and a nicer house</u>
<u n="353" who="S0631">but you'll live the same</u>
<u n="354" who="S0632">but you <trunc>re</trunc>realistically your lifestyle will be the same and er you get up to a certain amount and and most</u>
<u n="355" who="S0631" trans="overlap">it won't make you happier</u>
<u n="356" who="S0632">most of it goes in erm goes in taxes and I like I was paying a lot more tax and paying back my student loan a lot more at <anon type="place"/> as well so a lot of that money would go out of my account before I'd seen it whereas now I'm on I'm on such a small amount that I don't pay back my student loan</u>
<u n="357" who="S0631" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="358" who="S0632">at all and I'm paying tax but they taxed me a stupid amount when I arrived and now they can't charge me any more because I've basically I've paid all the tax that I should in a whole year in one go</u>
<u n="359" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah yeah put on emergency tax so you would get a rebate until it balanced out</u>
<u n="360" who="S0632">yeah and now it's like my wages just go in and I just get it</u>
<u n="361" who="S0631">mm</u>
<u n="362" who="S0632">apart from when it doesn't work and</u>
<u n="363" who="S0631">I pay a little bit national insurance <unclear/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0631"><unclear/> but I spoke to that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who I work with cos basically the reason that I've been told to <unclear/> by <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is because the one pharmacist <unclear/> and he was like basically <unclear/> manager bitching about how like he's not happy <unclear/> and he doesn't wanna have no dispenser in <unclear/> like so into the evening even though like you have training but whatever</u>
<u n="366" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0631"><unclear/> so obviously she's based in the <unclear/> him that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that I worked with that I work with she does every day she works every day but she works seven thirty until fourish but they wanna move her hours so she starts later slightly later so she's doing eight until half past four but she's got childcare arrangements in that it's her sister's child that she looks after that enables her to sister to go to work</u>
<u n="368" who="S0632">okay yeah and then swap</u>
<u n="369" who="S0631" trans="overlap">so she so yeah there is a childcare issue for her and so so actually though the reason that I'm not allowed to work there is literally it would take her three hours every evening oh no on the Thursday evening they won't have a dispenser because in three hours I <unclear/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0631">they're so stupid</u>
<u n="371" who="S0632">so I'm I texted her saying do you reckon <unclear/>? and she rang me back and she chatted to me and that's how I know about <unclear/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0632">uhu</u>
<u n="373" who="S0631">because then moving her hours it would make it so it's literally three hours</u>
<u n="374" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0631">erm</u>
<u n="376" who="S0632">that's that's like nothing and you're saying you could get your work done way ahead of time so</u>
<u n="377" who="S0631" trans="overlap">I could get it done by five and then I'll be out the door earlier but if I just happened to stay later</u>
<u n="378" who="S0632">if they're willing to be flexible it would save them money</u>
<u n="379" who="S0631">mm exactly and then so like it's like either they have me like apparently my the two pharmacists there's <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> who's erm who's a snake right? I get on with the him to his face apart from when we do argue and I tell him when we're getting on and we argue</u>
<u n="380" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0631">you pick arguments with me and anyway but he's a snake right? but then there's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who is completely fair and completely nice which maybe a little bit too he he says he's too nice and I told him there's no such thing as too nice but like if there was such a thing as too nice <unclear/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0632">he would be it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0631" trans="overlap">right erm but he even picked up <unclear/> and do you know what you've done though right? you've stuck your oar in about <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> having to go to uni has meant that now we don't have a dispenser you're gonna have to work on your own now anyway because we don't we won't have a dispenser because you said</u>
<u n="384" who="S0632" trans="overlap">but for way more time yeah the three hours</u>
<u n="385" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah you've just made it worse</u>
<u n="386" who="S0632">did she say that to him?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0631">no he said that to no he <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said that to <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="389" who="S0631">and so <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is very much just he doesn't care <unclear/> just do whatever</u>
<u n="390" who="S0632" trans="overlap">ah okay phew</u>
<u n="391" who="S0631">so she's just responded to what <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> said to her about how <unclear/> erm <unclear>you should stay</unclear> for three hours so anyway I <unclear/> genuinely really good dispenser from now</u>
<u n="392" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0631">I'm an old school now <unclear/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0632">yeah you look better in dispenser now</u>
<u n="395" who="S0631">yeah because I was I was taught the old school way</u>
<u n="396" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="397" who="S0631">and then they changed it so that now people are learning stuff on the computer but then they're never actually doing the practice so no one's any good like <unclear/> not <unclear/> jobs but they're not thrown in up at the deep end okay?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="399" who="S0631">and so she's saying <unclear/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I wish I did</u>
<u n="401" who="S0631">it's just ridiculous I wish I could get <unclear/> cos part of me says that I are you recording me?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0632">I am <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0631">well part of me says that I don't even want that job now</u>
<u n="404" who="S0632">yeah yeah I know because like you'd have to work for her and</u>
<u n="405" who="S0631" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="406" who="S0632">and</u>
<u n="407" who="S0631">if it wasn't that <unclear/> down the line but what</u>
<u n="408" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah yeah you can look at it that way as well and just think well I was a little bit like that at <anon type="place"/> as well and I was a bit like I kind of I didn't really feel like I was gonna get pushed out any time soon but I could see it happening to people around me</u>
<u n="409" who="S0631">mm</u>
<u n="410" who="S0632">so I was like I'd rather jump before I was pushed</u>
<u n="411" who="S0631">yeah that's like how I feel yeah and so if someone knows that so that <trunc>M</trunc> er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at <anon type="place"/> she will genuinely always be lovely</u>
<u n="412" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0631">and so part of me just thinks do you know what? she'd looked after <unclear/> and then they got really funny because I left <unclear/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0632" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="415" who="S0631">and now she's helping me again just <unclear/></u>
<u n="416" who="S0632">such a nice person</u>
<u n="417" who="S0631">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0632">yeah well it's good but like the <unclear/> nice people</u>
<u n="419" who="S0631">mm it's corporate companies though and my friend that I was talking to when I go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0631">she said when I described it to her she said that's how it was at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0632">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0631">cos cos she used to work in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="424" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0631">in the game part <unclear/> but erm she said yeah you're just all numbers and all the good people leave</u>
<u n="426" who="S0632" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="427" who="S0631">because they're not willing to just pander to it and then you're just left with people that <unclear/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I think that's the big company structures erm they don't seem to work well for people like keeping good people</u>
<u n="429" who="S0631">no</u>
<u n="430" who="S0632">like it's not it it's not structured that way</u>
<u n="431" who="S0631" trans="overlap">because they're not they don't run morally they run regarding numbers and I was saying though to my friend that like I I don't believe that you can have it both ways if you've got targets I don't believe that you have to be a strict manager and to achieve those targets <unclear/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0632" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="433" who="S0631">and you're kind of diplomatic and you respect your staff and help them out where you can they will help you out and cos then you're just putting <unclear/> won't you?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0631">as long as you make everyone happy in their work <unclear/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah absolutely it's</u>
<u n="437" who="S0631">and you wouldn't have to be one of these managers that goes around threatening you shouldn't manage by threatening</u>
<u n="438" who="S0632" trans="overlap">threatening people does not work no</u>
<u n="439" who="S0631">to achieve what they should be achieving you should</u>
<u n="440" who="S0632">I work rather well with the <unclear/> system myself</u>
<u n="441" who="S0631">I yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0631">I work well if I've got someone I'm actually like who is actually gonna say thank you</u>
<u n="444" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="445" who="S0631">because the thing is I was also saying to erm her though as in my friend</u>
<u n="446" who="S0632" trans="overlap">aha</u>
<u n="447" who="S0631">erm that if so we have stupid targets <unclear/> services blagging people up that need reviews right? so she'll come in and she'll look and she'll see she'll say she'll see say if I did ten sign-ups that day she sees that as a good result someone could come into work and they could be feeling unwell and I could be spotting that as signs of a heart attack call them an ambulance and send them away</u>
<u n="448" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0631"><unclear>with a fatal</unclear> heart attack</u>
<u n="450" who="S0632" trans="overlap">but that wouldn't be</u>
<u n="451" who="S0631">and there would be no recognition</u>
<u n="452" who="S0632">nothing for that yeah that's stupid</u>
<u n="453" who="S0631">and mine mine is a job where and <unclear/> I'm doing this job because I wanna do this job well and <unclear/> to do the job well I'll probably just need <unclear/> targets hand-in-hand</u>
<u n="454" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0631">don't come in and just take all that away from me about being a nice you know being a good person and doing the actual caring</u>
<u n="456" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="457" who="S0631">side of the job well</u>
<u n="458" who="S0632">like actually focusing on completely the wrong aspect</u>
<u n="459" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0632">of like what should essentially be a caring profession really</u>
<u n="461" who="S0631" trans="overlap">everything everything is removed from like the focus is should be on caring and stuff and that's completely removed by having erm me doing a tally chart of the things I've done that day</u>
<u n="462" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0631">and it's all hit and miss because they don't have many customers so erm is that Cajun?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0631"><unclear/> cine</u>
<u n="466" who="S0632">oh cine is it?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0631">cine <unclear>bound together with oil</unclear> I used to cook with that one</u>
<u n="468" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh thanks for the heads up I might just <unclear/></u>
<u n="469" who="S0631" trans="overlap">give it a bit of erm have you just got a bit of cayenne pepper?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0632">yeah cayenne pepper paprika chilli powder</u>
<u n="471" who="S0631">yeah I saw something online <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> you know those tasty videos?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0631">and they said put Cajun spice in it and then they quickly just made the Cajun spices like yeah why am I not doing that?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0631" trans="overlap">it's good for erm</u>
<u n="476" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah it's just like when you you're like having a shortcut aren't you?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0631">yeah you'd assume it would be the same wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0632">you would assume it <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="479" who="S0631">that's why I bought it I assumed it was that</u>
<u n="480" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah and you're just like oh it's a spice mix they've just mixed the spices together and I'm just being lazy and and it won't like cost me anything yes it will</u>
<u n="481" who="S0631" trans="overlap">it's got like yeah I think <unclear/> what it is really erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah but there's no explaining that to that lady I can tell but I'm gonna <pause dur="short"/> er explain that to the area manager though and I'll say like I know it's about targets and things but I do believe that you can do the two and you can be a</u>
<u n="482" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0631">nice manager <pause dur="short"/> and have everybody respect you for being a nice manager and I might say that's why this like that's why <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who took me on was brilliant because you wanted to do well for her</u>
<u n="484" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0631">because you also <pause dur="short"/> you didn't feel like there was any threat but you also <pause dur="short"/> it's always good to just know that you can get on with the person that's actually managing you</u>
<u n="486" who="S0632">yeah that's really important it's really important</u>
<u n="487" who="S0631">cos I know it's a business and I know it's <anon type="place"/> and I know it's on <anon type="place"/> street and I know that there's a massive pressure and we're thirty-ninth in the country last week</u>
<u n="488" who="S0632" trans="overlap">that's good</u>
<u n="489" who="S0631">that's a pretty high target what's their issue?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0632" trans="overlap">that's really good</u>
<u n="491" who="S0631">you ain't gonna be you're not gonna be number one you're not so <unclear/> erm the big we're not we're not the big one are we?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0632" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="493" who="S0631">we're not the flagship we're not gonna be number one I know you should always do your best and everything but don't look at thirty-ninth and go that's bad</u>
<u n="494" who="S0632">no <pause dur="short"/> it's unreasonable</u>
<u n="495" who="S0631">yeah when you've got people who are in stores not doing quite as well but they're all happy and their</u>
<u n="496" who="S0632" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="497" who="S0631">staff are happy and no one ever leaves it's all uncomplicated and they all help each other out</u>
<u n="498" who="S0632">and like what's what's important to you as a person as well like?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0632">like as a human being? <vocal desc="laugh"/> like isn't it nice to be nice?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0631">I think to be nice is just standard and you should be and it's nice when you when you've been nice</u>
<u n="502" who="S0632">are these your peas or our peas?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0631">erm I have peas but have them are mine not near the top?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0632">yeah there are two sets of peas cos I was sure we had peas and me</u>
<u n="505" who="S0631" trans="overlap">I don't think we actually have opened ours but either way just use whatever</u>
<u n="506" who="S0632">okay so</u>
<u n="507" who="S0631">if it turns into communal peas <unclear>next time</unclear> it's buy separate peas</u>
<u n="508" who="S0632">okay cos I was sure that we had peas</u>
<u n="509" who="S0631">yeah you do have peas there's two bags of peas</u>
<u n="510" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="511" who="S0631">we had one and you had one</u>
<u n="512" who="S0632">do you have soya beans?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0631">no</u>
<u n="514" who="S0632">yeah I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has been putting things in the wrong drawer that's okay so I was just like there's peas and soya beans in this drawer and I'm sure we had peas and soya beans and like obviously you have peas too but there's two bags of peas so</u>
<u n="515" who="S0631">so I don't have one of those little clips</u>
<u n="516" who="S0632">aha oh there's some down here if you do want them</u>
<u n="517" who="S0631" trans="overlap">and I don't think I opened the peas so</u>
<u n="518" who="S0632">yeah there's an unopened peas and an opened peas and I was like I'm sure I've got an open peas and we didn't eat</u>
<u n="519" who="S0631" trans="overlap">those are peas and I think you should have them</u>
<u n="520" who="S0632">I'm gonna have some peas</u>
<u n="521" who="S0631">I'm even telling you those are your peas but regardless don't worry they're just peas</u>
<u n="522" who="S0632">even if they weren't my peas thank you</u>
<u n="523" who="S0631">they're your peas</u>
<u n="524" who="S0632">they're they're totally my peas aren't they?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0631">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0632"><shift new="singing"/> mm mm mm <shift new="normal"/> okay oh I don't want that <unclear>black to get too far</unclear> I've done that before <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="527" who="S0631">oh you know when you've put it in and it just sort of sticks straightaway even though <unclear/> in it</u>
<u n="528" who="S0632">yeah I'm gonna blacken it <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="529" who="S0631">I'm watching you cos I don't eat meat</u>
<u n="530" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0631">and life could be a bit easier sometimes I think if I did</u>
<u n="532" who="S0632"><unclear/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0631" trans="overlap">more choice I think</u>
<u n="534" who="S0632">yeah there's more choice sorry if it makes you cough <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0632">frying spices now</u>
<u n="536" who="S0631">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="537" who="S0632"><unclear>put that on the side</unclear> slightly and deal with that in a minute <pause dur="short"/> I'm so wet <pause dur="short"/> that's actually what <unclear>fire light</unclear> is good for actually cos when things are wet it kind of like everything gets dried pretty quickly cos there's not much</u>
<u n="538" who="S0631" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="539" who="S0632">moisture to it is there?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0631">no but sometimes though I start things up with <unclear>fire light</unclear> and then add a little bit of water you know when you're frying something</u>
<u n="541" who="S0632" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="542" who="S0631">and it keeps drying out?</u>
<u n="543" who="S0632">yeah you know Quorn chicken pieces are really bad for that sometimes no it's not that</u>
<u n="544" who="S0631" trans="overlap">I find mushrooms are bad for that</u>
<u n="545" who="S0632">mushrooms?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0631">sometimes</u>
<u n="547" who="S0632"><unclear>I was gonna say</unclear></u>
<u n="548" who="S0631">to be honest though it's because I've been using a metal pan and not a non-stick pan</u>
<u n="549" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="550" who="S0631"><unclear/></u>
<u n="551" who="S0632">non-stick is the boss I love this pan so much</u>
<u n="552" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="553" who="S0632">and it really</u>
<u n="554" who="S0631" trans="overlap">I bought mine because I needed new pans and I didn't like the way that my existing non-stick had been scratched erm but then I realised actually because somebody who I won't name right?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="556" who="S0631">erm who are not actually stays with me anymore</u>
<u n="557" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="558" who="S0631">came around and offered to do my washing up and I was like no no no put I'll put it in the dishwasher and scrubbed it with a with a metal thing</u>
<u n="559" who="S0632">with a Brillo pad?</u>
<u n="560" who="S0631">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="561" who="S0632">no that's so annoying oh</u>
<u n="562" who="S0631" trans="overlap">and so then they all just I just didn't <unclear/></u>
<u n="563" who="S0632">well once they're already like a bit ruined you don't do you?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0631">no <pause dur="short"/> but honestly I said just shove them in the dishwasher it's fine <unclear/></u>
<u n="565" who="S0632" trans="overlap">why did you do it by hand? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0631">oh my god you've ruined my pans</u>
<u n="567" who="S0632">thanks for nothing <pause dur="short"/> huh</u>
<u n="568" who="S0631">oh that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0632">that's very minimal you could add more food</u>
<u n="570" who="S0631">I could do but I'm a bit mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0631">I'll have a banana actually as well <unclear/> something I haven't had</u>
<u n="573" who="S0632">oh no <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="574" who="S0631"><unclear/> lemon squash <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> leaves the squash out all the time <unclear/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0632">I saw there's lemon squash in the door normally</u>
<u n="576" who="S0631">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> leaves the squash out <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0632">I might need your garlicky cubes <unclear/> and I'm gonna egg fry the rice</u>
<u n="578" who="S0631">yeah I think you should <pause dur="long"/> that'll be nice</u>
<u n="579" who="S0632">yeah a bit of an epic one <unclear>actually</unclear> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0631"><unclear/> as well</u>
<u n="581" who="S0632"><unclear/> cos we didn't really eat many proper meals yesterday we were we were very picky</u>
<u n="582" who="S0631">yeah <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> do you know what? <unclear/> yesterday but also <unclear/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="584" who="S0631">one bit</u>
<u n="585" who="S0632">just one</u>
<u n="586" who="S0631">and it was only the it was <unclear/> and it was this I heard her answerphone message and I did speak to her on the phone and I did ask are you so-and-so? I was like I'm sure that's so-and-so</u>
<u n="587" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="588" who="S0631">and then then I got an an answerphone message saying no they've got nothing <unclear/></u>
<u n="589" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0631">they had nobody there so I said that erm so I messaged her and I was like is this <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she was like eh?</u>
<u n="591" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0631">who's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like like who's this? like oh</u>
<u n="593" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="594" who="S0631"><unclear/> yeah and I thought that was quite funny</u>
<u n="595" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="596" who="S0631">I'm sure this is someone I know</u>
<u n="597" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="598" who="S0631"><unclear/></u>
<u n="599" who="S0632" trans="overlap">yeah oh</u>
<u n="600" who="S0631"><unclear/> it's so <unclear/></u>
<u n="601" who="S0632">that would be so <unclear/></u>
<u n="602" who="S0631">and <unclear/> are quite interesting <unclear/></u>
<u n="603" who="S0632">yeah you must get all sorts of people <unclear/></u>
<u n="604" who="S0631">it's either really busy or really intense because everyone's in a hurry</u>
<u n="605" who="S0632" trans="overlap">aha</u>
<u n="606" who="S0631">or <unclear/> Kit Kats and journeys</u>
<u n="607" who="S0632">yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0631" trans="overlap"><unclear/> in <anon type="place"/> station <unclear/> Kit Kats and <unclear>Mini Cheddars</unclear></u>
<u n="609" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="610" who="S0631"><unclear>pretty much</unclear></u>
<u n="611" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="612" who="S0631"><unclear/> afternoon</u>
<u n="613" who="S0632">wow</u>
<u n="614" who="S0631"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> get rid of it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0632">okay <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="616" who="S0631"><unclear/></u>
<u n="617" who="S0632">no</u>
<u n="618" who="S0631"><unclear/> oh <unclear/> it'll be alright</u>
<u n="619" who="S0632"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said he'd eat it <unclear/></u>
<u n="620" who="S0631">well blame <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="621" who="S0632">yeah blame <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he said he'd eat it totally eat it</u>
<u n="622" who="S0631">mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="623" who="S0632">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="624" who="S0631">it's more like the five-a-day today <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> I think for dinner</u>
<u n="625" who="S0632">mm</u>
<u n="626" who="S0631">I might have erm I've got broccoli I've got a big broccoli</u>
<u n="627" who="S0632">you've got lots of broccoli</u>
<u n="628" who="S0631">I've got some carrots and then I might roast some potatoes with that rosemary <unclear/> and I might have it with some Quorn <unclear>item</unclear> that I might get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to bring home</u>
<u n="629" who="S0632" trans="overlap">oh lovely</u>
<u n="630" who="S0631">yeah</u>
<u n="631" who="S0632">fancy some rosemary we do have a rosemary bush <unclear/> you like rosemary</u>
<u n="632" who="S0631">mm</u>
<u n="633" who="S0632">yeah I've got a big bush there rosemary <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> rosemary <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="634" who="S0631">have you got any mint to go with <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="635" who="S0632">no we don't have mint</u>
<u n="636" who="S0631">you should grow mint it grows like wildfire though</u>
<u n="637" who="S0632">it does yeah I it's funny that we don't have mint we've got sage and rosemary and that's gone mental over those things</u>
<u n="638" who="S0631">mm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> we had did I tell you we had like mint coming from next door?</u>
<u n="639" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="640" who="S0631">you can't kill the stuff you can't get rid of it</u>
<u n="641" who="S0632">no it's really</u>
<u n="642" who="S0631" trans="overlap">so we just ended up utilising it but we had to really cut it back all the time</u>
<u n="643" who="S0632">we yeah yeah and some some herbs are really hardy <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="644" who="S0631">and also though it was very growing from behind the next door's shed</u>
<u n="645" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="646" who="S0631">so we didn't even know it was there</u>
<u n="647" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="648" who="S0631">so like there wasn't even any way of saying can can we like get <unclear>around our fence</unclear>? he was elderly as well and we never told him but</u>
<u n="649" who="S0632" trans="overlap">ah yeah</u>
<u n="650" who="S0631">it was like you know when you're just trying to even out your garden and just make it so it was just lawn?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0632">yeah</u>
<u n="652" who="S0631">we were nearly there just apart from this one mint <unclear>tree</unclear></u>
<u n="653" who="S0632"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> okay <pause dur="long"/> I'm gonna need to run and get a tissue</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
