<text id="SMKK">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:50:04</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-01-04</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0148 S0149 S0167</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A coffee shop in London</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>English language, friends, presents, work, relationships, holidays, car problems, pets, family</topics>
		<activity>Friends catching up</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T06</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0148">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bristol</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Bristolian</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Reading</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Primary School Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2>German</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0149">
				<exactage>25</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Guildford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Reading</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>9_unknown</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0167">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Ashford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South East/Kent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Romney Marsh, Kent</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Copywriter</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0167">yeah it reminds me of doing my dissertation <event desc="sound of restaurant"/> oh it's a small</u>
<u n="2" who="S0149" trans="overlap">shame even where it says it will all be anonymous I kinda feel like I'd like my name on there</u>
<u n="3" who="S0167">anonymised brackets</u>
<u n="4" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0149">you're a funny one <pause dur="long"/> so if it's aimed at language learners</u>
<u n="6" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0149">as in people coming to England? as in foreign people learning the English language based on examples of those speaking the English language?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0149">right okay</u>
<u n="10" who="S0167">yeah they just want loads and loads of examples</u>
<u n="11" who="S0149">that would be hilarious if you had a load of west country people and you had French and German so coming over and they were all speaking like that</u>
<u n="12" who="S0167" trans="overlap">yeah hello my lovely hello there</u>
<u n="13" who="S0149">dictionary of pronunciation</u>
<u n="14" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">there you are</u>
<u n="15" who="S0149">oh thank you so much oh tea</u>
<u n="16" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">ladies who's having peppermint?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0167">oh peppermint <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> very sophisticated</u>
<u n="18" who="S0149">thank you</u>
<u n="19" who="S0167">might put that there as that might be better</u>
<u n="20" who="S0149">yes thank you interesting yes you could get a snack afterwards</u>
<u n="21" who="S0167">I'm quite hungry</u>
<u n="22" who="S0148">have you heard anything from?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0167">I got a text from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> actually</u>
<u n="24" who="S0148">did you?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0149">yeah I got a text from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she never replied again</u>
<u n="26" who="S0167">that's weird no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is having a <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0149">was it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had a row over their flat?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0167"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0149">still a bit funny with it yeah I don't think</u>
<u n="30" who="S0167"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does this thing just all the time when it's like let's Skype let's Skype but it's always like well you're not actually going to do it so why say it? and that occurred a few months ago in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0149">this was before</u>
<u n="32" who="S0167">she broke up with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0149">oh I didn't know that</u>
<u n="34" who="S0148">that doesn't surprise me they met too young</u>
<u n="35" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0149">cosmopolitan</u>
<u n="37" who="S0167">yeah all that jazz and I do feel quite sorry for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and</u>
<u n="38" who="S0149">we met up with her quite recently we went to Pizza Express</u>
<u n="39" who="S0167">where?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0149">Pizza Express near <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0167">oh</u>
<u n="42" who="S0149">at that stage she was still in contact with him and they still met up and it's a bit like</u>
<u n="43" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0149">people still have</u>
<u n="45" who="S0167">yeah exactly maybe out of pity</u>
<u n="46" who="S0149">yeah maybe</u>
<u n="47" who="S0167">if she's free of him she's been going on about that for ages she should move on</u>
<u n="48" who="S0149">yeah find a London boy</u>
<u n="49" who="S0148">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0149">you said I don't have an accent</u>
<u n="51" who="S0167">you do everyone has an accent</u>
<u n="52" who="S0148">it's standard boring boring accent <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0167">yeah boring</u>
<u n="54" who="S0149">sorry</u>
<u n="55" who="S0148">where do you currently live?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0149">England</u>
<u n="57" who="S0167">I suppose that's I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> met up for New Year's together didn't they?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0149">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0167">yeah gets a bit complicated in the end some people were doing things and I was like nah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0149">I know I thought it was a bit weird cos she posted on Facebook I didn't see it until way after she'd posted it but erm she posted oh what are you doing for New Year? I'll go near or far and I was like I've already like told you what I'm doing so why?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0148">near or far aka London</u>
<u n="62" who="S0149">she basically won't go outside London cos otherwise so I didn't bother replying to that either it's like I've told you my plans yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0148">either come or don't come</u>
<u n="64" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0148">topic or subject oh right you said don't worry about that</u>
<u n="66" who="S0149"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about her home</u>
<u n="67" who="S0167">yes have they actually?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0149">I don't know</u>
<u n="69" who="S0167">all I got was the email that you guys got as well that's just like oh like we've broken up and I'm really sad it's the best thing I they broken up</u>
<u n="70" who="S0149">I knew that wasn't going to last either</u>
<u n="71" who="S0148">I don't</u>
<u n="72" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0149">huh why?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0167">cos he posted something recently on Facebook oh like look at me right across the table but still missing loads</u>
<u n="75" who="S0148">what am I doing? writing first to the</u>
<u n="76" who="S0167">and then he may of realised that he'd made a bit of a mistake</u>
<u n="77" who="S0149">yeah does he live in Spain now?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0167">that's the thing cos he works for his dad or something they've got a lot of money apparently doing quite a lot</u>
<u n="79" who="S0149">what's he actually doing is he actually doing reporting with him then?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0148">I can't even write the date down</u>
<u n="81" who="S0167">oh yeah it's twenty fifteen did you write twenty fifteen? let's see let's see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> interesting you did</u>
<u n="82" who="S0149">ah I'm so with it</u>
<u n="83" who="S0167">so how's your teaching job going?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0149">yesgood it is good it's tiring</u>
<u n="85" who="S0167">thanks <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0149">as expected</u>
<u n="87" who="S0149">you all said NQT year's the worst year but I touch wood am not finding it as stressful as people made out</u>
<u n="88" who="S0167">yes</u>
<u n="89" who="S0149">I feel like I should find it more stressful but I am tired it's tiring but you don't have uni to go to as well you don't have dissertations to do I saw someone one a train writing a dissertation and I was like I'll never have to do that again</u>
<u n="90" who="S0167">like having Christmas without having homework</u>
<u n="91" who="S0149">yes that's been nice did you have a good New Year in the end?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0167">I did I went to <anon type="place"/> with my friends <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who I kept calling <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know sometimes I call you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0148">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0167">she's blonde they're both blonde basically the same person and yeah we went to this pub it was only a fiver and I thought it was going to be sedate but it was a really modern pub and there were loads of people there and it had this huge dance floor so it was basically like being in a club but I only paid a fiver</u>
<u n="95" who="S0149">that's cool</u>
<u n="96" who="S0148">good</u>
<u n="97" who="S0149">better than last year you didn't enjoy it last year</u>
<u n="98" who="S0167">well I don't remember it</u>
<u n="99" who="S0148">last year I made a puzzle globe last year that's tragic</u>
<u n="100" who="S0149">oh no</u>
<u n="101" who="S0167">were you ill or something?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0148">my plans fell through I gave dad a puzzle globe for Christmas and I had nothing else to do so I made the globe and sat there</u>
<u n="103" who="S0149">oh sounds better than my New Year last year I paid fifty quid for this really cool evening in London</u>
<u n="104" who="S0167">I remember</u>
<u n="105" who="S0149">an then we got completely wasted before we even left the flat I don't remember anything during the night and I apparently made a fool of myself apparently I insulted <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so which wasn't great</u>
<u n="106" who="S0167">oh dear</u>
<u n="107" who="S0149">anyway tell me about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0167"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is a German boy who's twenty-eight years old</u>
<u n="109" who="S0149">and did you meet him did how where were you?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0167">basically I got this part time job when I was a language student I got this part time job</u>
<u n="111" who="S0149">in a school did you enjoy doing that by the way?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0167">yes I enjoyed it I enjoyed it I think and it was only twelve hours a week and I was getting eight hundred euros a month so that's nice not too bad but I don't think I'd do teaching I think I've done my year</u>
<u n="113" who="S0149">and that's enough</u>
<u n="114" who="S0167">because I did quite enjoy planning lessons and stuff but the kids just wouldn't cooperate they were like</u>
<u n="115" who="S0149">they were older weren't they?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0167">they were so unimaginative so I planned this lesson where they had to create a TV show</u>
<u n="117" who="S0149">how old were they?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0167">they were sixteen and I thought oh that would be an interesting way for them to get active</u>
<u n="119" who="S0149">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0167">so I put them into groups and I said plan a TV show you've got half an hour and they're so unimaginative in Germany they sit there they just sat there at the table and they were all writing and there was silence and I was like guys you don't have to write you can talk to each other but they just couldn't grasp this fact that they didn't write stuff down and that they couldn't be creative and that showed they were really boring they were really dull I said</u>
<u n="121" who="S0149">did they have to speak in English to you?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0167">they had to speak in English yeah they had to do like a cookery show and like a chat show and something else and I thought that would be really fun but they didn't get it they didn't understand the whole concept of it</u>
<u n="123" who="S0149">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0167">so anyway that was a bit of a disaster hey ho but I had this part time job as a waitress in this restaurant and it's owned by <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> parents and he was a chef there and he after about a couple weeks he came up to me cos I'd never fancied him or anything</u>
<u n="125" who="S0149">did he have a girlfriend at work though?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0167">he had a girlfriend at works he but he broke up with her like two weeks before</u>
<u n="127" who="S0149">said two week ago</u>
<u n="128" who="S0167">yeah she was Hungarian and yeah he followed me out one night he followed me out one day when I was leaving and he said by the way <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I was wondering I you wanted to go out for a drink or something or a staff outing and I was like oh what's happening? and he was like oh no just you and me and I thought like I really kind be bothered with this but I didn't want to hurt his feelings so I was like yeah sounds good I'll text you so I text him and I was like yeah let's go out and this was on Sunday and he was like let's go out Tuesday and I was like oh god that's serious so I to put him off me I scraped my hair up didn't wear any makeup and wore my glasses cos I was like I really can't be bothered to start a relationship like so close to the end of my time here it was only like a month before I left</u>
<u n="129" who="S0149">that's funny</u>
<u n="130" who="S0167">I went to pub and actually really enjoyed myself and we went out for dinner again a few days later</u>
<u n="131" who="S0149">you didn't put makeup on?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0167">that time I did and make myself look nice and yeah we saw each other every single day always doing stuff together</u>
<u n="133" who="S0149">did you speak German with him?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0167">yeah we always speak German with each other and then he took me out for a weekend away in Poland</u>
<u n="135" who="S0149">that's so nice</u>
<u n="136" who="S0167">in a five star hotel with a bar and everything</u>
<u n="137" who="S0149">nice find <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0167">and I was still going into it thinking it'll be fun for a month and then at the end we were like oh we don't want to break up so he booked a flight to come and see me cos I was between Germany and Peru and that was really cool and we were like okay still want to be with you and we carried on the relationship while we were in Peru and we Skype all the time and he came to visit me yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0149">yeah I saw the photos</u>
<u n="140" who="S0148">does he speak English at all?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0167">he does speak English he speaks English French and German</u>
<u n="142" who="S0149">oh my god</u>
<u n="143" who="S0167">cos he trained as a chef in France yeah he trained as a chef in France so he speaks French as well</u>
<u n="144" who="S0149">is his English good?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0149">his English is good I mean he makes a few mistakes but nothing major</u>
<u n="146" who="S0167">do you speak to him in German?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0167">yeah unless we're like when we're with my parents we speak English we</u>
<u n="148" who="S0149">that's amazing that you can do that</u>
<u n="149" who="S0167">he's sending me love letters and they're really cute things like origami hearts and stuff like that</u>
<u n="150" who="S0149">oh god</u>
<u n="151" who="S0167">one of the letters was in German and then in English and the last page was in French and I said to him I can't read the last page and he was like oh you have to work out yourself so I had to do on google translate which took ages had to type it all up but yeah that was quite romantic</u>
<u n="152" who="S0149">romantic</u>
<u n="153" who="S0167">yeah but then for my birthday he did this really cute thing he left like a week two weeks before my birthday and we were going to do presents in February when I was going to go out there and so anyway I went down and the doorman said oh I've got something here for you and he gave me freeze dried rose which was given to me and a card saying happy birthday I came and he'd given a present to the maid cos we had a maid in our room and put on my bed like and so there was a present and a card and I was like oh that's cute but it wasn't just that I opened that and then the card said right go into your computer and open this password protected document but you've got to find the password which was referring to our last love letter so I had to go and get the last love letter out and find this password which spelt out I love you</u>
<u n="154" who="S0149">oh my god</u>
<u n="155" who="S0167">and then the word document right now you've got to find</u>
<u n="156" who="S0148">was he in the country?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0167">no he'd left already</u>
<u n="158" who="S0149">oh</u>
<u n="159" who="S0148">darling PS I love you</u>
<u n="160" who="S0167">look where your last present was but deeper so I looked under the bed and it was there and I thought oh it's another present is this the last one? and there was a card</u>
<u n="161" who="S0149">pass the parcel</u>
<u n="162" who="S0167">yeah and I was like when's this going to end and I opened the card and it said right now you've been searching for a long time I think you need a drink go to this pub and buy this particular drink so I was like oh what's there what's waiting there for me? so my friend and I went to this particular pub but unfortunately it had closed down the day before</u>
<u n="163" who="S0148">oh no</u>
<u n="164" who="S0167">cos it was open the night before cos I saw it and there was just a big sign on the door saying we have closed down for the foreseeable future so I was like oh great so I'm never going to get what was left so anyway a few days later I left a note on the door that said if you see this can you give me a ring cos I really I think my boyfriend left a present with you and anyway he rang me and said yeah come and collect it so it didn't quite work out the way <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wanted but I did get my present in the end</u>
<u n="165" who="S0149">what was it?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0167">and that was the end of the treasure hunt erm it was it's like so it sounds really weird it's like a block of plastic in a kind of a cube shape and at the back of the plastic is a picture of us</u>
<u n="167" who="S0148">oh okay I know the kind of you can slot it in</u>
<u n="168" who="S0167">no it's inside</u>
<u n="169" who="S0149">oh</u>
<u n="170" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0149">oh wow</u>
<u n="172" who="S0148">aw that's cute so romantic</u>
<u n="173" who="S0149">how old is he?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0167">twenty-eight</u>
<u n="175" who="S0149">oh my god I hear wedding bells <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I have to say all the shitty relationships that you've been through I'm so glad that you've finally got a gooden</u>
<u n="176" who="S0148">did he propose on Machu Picchu?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0167">no</u>
<u n="178" who="S0149">did you really think he would?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0167">I don't think I would of said yes anyway as it's a bit early but</u>
<u n="180" who="S0149">how long have you been together?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0167">since the beginning of May</u>
<u n="182" who="S0149">that's amazing</u>
<u n="183" who="S0167">the first day he arrived cos we'd never said I love you before</u>
<u n="184" who="S0149">but in letters you had</u>
<u n="185" who="S0167">no I hadn't ever said it and I thought I don't want to do it over Skype I want to do it when we see each other oh I said it first and he was like oh I really hate you and I was like why? and said cos I planned to say it on Machu Picchu and I was like sorry you can still say it on Machu Picchu yeah but it's not going to be sweet now is it?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0149">oh that's so romantic well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you always get flowers and teddies</u>
<u n="187" who="S0148">yeah he's always been good like that not like planned like a now I feel like a bad girlfriend cos he does all these things and I just</u>
<u n="188" who="S0149">that's what they're meant to do that's their role</u>
<u n="189" who="S0148">yeah I know</u>
<u n="190" who="S0167">when he came it was his birthday in October when he came in November I bought him a cake with a candle and put some music on and bought myself some new underwear</u>
<u n="191" who="S0149">did you?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0167">and I made him go have a shower when he arrived so that I could that I could plan it all <unclear/> well it was actually on my bed the cake in the middle of my bed on one side and a romantic evening I had wine so I bought wine and I put two glasses of wine and I had two glasses of wine and standing there in my underwear and then he came in I was like happy birthday but it was no way near as romantic as what he did for me</u>
<u n="193" who="S0149">that's nice though</u>
<u n="194" who="S0167">he loved that</u>
<u n="195" who="S0149">so what's the plan is he going to come here what's the plan?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0167">well I don't want to move to Germany and I want him to move to London with me</u>
<u n="197" who="S0148">he could start a restaurant</u>
<u n="198" who="S0167">he could do that thing is he works in the restaurant with his parents and they're really quite pushy that he stays in the restaurant cos it's like a family business and I said what would happen if he left <anon type="place"/>? and was like oh they'll probably never talk to me again which I'm sure is an exaggeration they would talk to him again but he was like they'll be really upset it I just walked away from the business and my mum was like that's was professional at all it's his life but I think cos it's his parents he feels like it's an obligation</u>
<u n="199" who="S0149">wow</u>
<u n="200" who="S0167">so I don't know what's going to happen</u>
<u n="201" who="S0149">mind you imagine they're not there what do you want?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0167">I should have that conversation</u>
<u n="203" who="S0148">dream</u>
<u n="204" who="S0167">when he next came up imagine I'm going out to Germany for the twentieth of January for two weeks and then</u>
<u n="205" who="S0148">so you're freelancing so to be honest I don't think you can really have a job <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> unless it's online</u>
<u n="206" who="S0167">no I've got an interview on the twelfth here in London not here here but in London and so hopefully if I get that job which I hope but I might not get it they won't want me until February anyway but I can always say sorry I've got a holiday booked can I start in February?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0148">yeah what's the job?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0167">it's in it's called <anon type="place"/> and it's a film TV and literary agency</u>
<u n="209" who="S0148">wow</u>
<u n="210" who="S0167">it's only a six month job</u>
<u n="211" who="S0148">how did you get that then?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0167">well when before I went to uni I wrote letters to loads and loads of publishing companies and most of them emailed me back with loads of rejections and there were a few really positive ones where I did work experience so what I did was the other month I emailed them all again cos I still had all their emails and I emailed them all again and I said I did my work experience with them and here's my CV and I've since been to uni and done all this and blah blah if there's any opportunities please let me know and this girl emailed me back saying yes we're looking to fill an internship from kind of the new year if you're available and we'll have a look at your CV and say if you're suitable and a few days later she emailed me back and said yes we'd like to see you</u>
<u n="213" who="S0148">that's good</u>
<u n="214" who="S0149">wow</u>
<u n="215" who="S0167">but I don't know how many people</u>
<u n="216" who="S0148">what job would it be in the company do you have any idea?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0167">I think it's like agency for the literary department so I'm not sure exactly what I'll be doing</u>
<u n="218" who="S0148">the dreams</u>
<u n="219" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0149">get a job and then move to London</u>
<u n="221" who="S0148">and then you're like you can't move to Germany you're going to have to move here</u>
<u n="222" who="S0167">yeah well he knows I'm looking for jobs in London anyway so I'm hoping he'll just break and just come and he did say to me the other day and just come and he did say to me the other day on Skype if only I could give everything up to come to London with you and I was like mm that's a promising sign and I was like yeah that would be lovely</u>
<u n="223" who="S0148">can he make the family business go bust?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0167">oh nightmare</u>
<u n="225" who="S0148">he could extend it it could be international it could be the same company but in London I mean how long is it to get there from here what's the flight?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0167">it's like an hour and a half</u>
<u n="227" who="S0149">that's good and once you've done all your travelling in between what does that equate to like how far is he from the airport?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0167">well if I fly to Berlin it's two hours from the airport if I fly to Leipzig if I flew to Dresden it's like half an hour like I would never consider flying to Dresden erm Leipzig is about two hours the opposite direction and he's picking me up form Leipzig when I go in January and we're going to go to his sister who lives in Switzerland and stay there for a few days well two days</u>
<u n="229" who="S0149">you're like living the dream</u>
<u n="230" who="S0148">did you go skiing?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0167">I did in Germany in February yeah in Bavaria it was really fun but I kept falling off it was quite hard actually yeah did I tell you? right you really need to watch and I was doing it really slowly each time and I was like I've just got to let myself go and I was like just help me here and got to the top and I just let go and I was like the first I did it I got right to the end and I still haven't got anything to slow myself so I just used to sit on my bum and that used to stop myself so I'd just sit down before I bumped into the queue of people at the bottom so anyway I thought that was cool I'll do that again to I did it again and there was like a man who was doing a skiing lesson with kids and he could see and they started to skate across as I was coming down</u>
<u n="232" who="S0148">yeah they do that they start skating across</u>
<u n="233" who="S0167">and I was like oh my god I can't stop and I moved a tiny bit and fortunately I hit the teacher and not any of the kids and I bashed my head and I had a headache for the whole day and I bashed my head on the snow but fortunately I didn't take out any four year olds</u>
<u n="234" who="S0148">bad</u>
<u n="235" who="S0167">not as bad as it could of been</u>
<u n="236" who="S0149">ho was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0167">no he was fine cos he's like an experienced skier</u>
<u n="238" who="S0149">did you speak to him in French of German?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0167">no he was American actually he was like oh you got to be more careful I was like sorry</u>
<u n="240" who="S0148">I'm a novice</u>
<u n="241" who="S0167">they just stand on the slope having a chat they don't get out the way</u>
<u n="242" who="S0149">so funny <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> family have a chalet in France and they were skiing a few days ago</u>
<u n="243" who="S0167">whereabouts in France?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0149"><anon type="place"/> they were all experienced skiers but it hilarious <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> his aunt reminds me a bit of Dawn French a bit big quite jolly and the visibility the other day was really bad and they know the slopes quite well because they always go to the same place but for some reason she was going really fast <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as like it was the funniest thing she was going really fast and she just disappeared over the front and just landed it's actually quite dangerous but they were laughing cos she was fine and landed like in snow landed like an angel in snow up to here and she spent ages looking for her skis but stuff like that makes me laugh but apparently she just literally just went dum dum dum</u>
<u n="245" who="S0148">I guess she's quite fat</u>
<u n="246" who="S0149">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="247" who="S0167">I could never get I always had to take my skis off cos I could never get myself up I do have poor body strength to do that to do it from your tummy yeah so I couldn't do that</u>
<u n="248" who="S0149">did it go on the you know when you sit down?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0167">yeah I did that nightmare if you fall off it's like damn it</u>
<u n="250" who="S0148">so you're here you going to do your freelancing you're going to try and get that job</u>
<u n="251" who="S0167">yes but I've only got one interview lined up so if that fails I'm back to square one cos I've been applying for so many jobs</u>
<u n="252" who="S0148">I think you've got a good chance I think they'll really the fact that you've applied and that you applied again shows commitment</u>
<u n="253" who="S0167">keen yeah she sent me a load of authors that they agent for which I've got to research and stuff so I suppose I better do that I better find some nice shoes</u>
<u n="254" who="S0148">just don't go in in those trainers</u>
<u n="255" who="S0149">what happened to your other shoes?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0167">I don't have any more I used to have some black shoes that I used to wear to work every day in Peru but I wore them every single day and they just got holes in the end</u>
<u n="257" who="S0167">well it's the sales</u>
<u n="258" who="S0148">shoes are important</u>
<u n="259" who="S0167">yeah it's just that this month cos I don't get cos I've been doing races as well you know I did races I did <anon type="place"/> so whenever I can do casual work I can and I did one at <anon type="place"/> on Boxing day cos it was double pay</u>
<u n="260" who="S0148">is that when you're on the tills?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0148">is that when you take the next bets out</u>
<u n="263" who="S0167">yeah so I did one I did one at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0167">get any good tips?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0167">no rubbish and yesterday I did one at <anon type="place"/> I got offered one at <anon type="place"/>  Festival but if I get this job <anon type="place"/> Festival is not until March so if I accept <anon type="place"/>  Festival and get this job</u>
<u n="266" who="S0148">no definitely get this job <anon type="place"/> Festival will come and go</u>
<u n="267" who="S0167">get a job</u>
<u n="268" who="S0167">if I don't accept it and don't get the job then I haven't got</u>
<u n="269" who="S0149">can you accept it and then if you get the job?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0167">I could yeah I could but I don't want to get a reputation for bad and then they might not offer me any more work cos it is quite good to do it on Saturdays and stuff when you're free</u>
<u n="271" who="S0149">but if you got a job then you won't need any more work</u>
<u n="272" who="S0167">yeah true I won't enjoy it though I might want to carry on doing it I might want to do <anon type="place"/> if I can well obviously if I have a job it might be difficult but I really enjoy doing <anon type="place"/> but yeah you're right I probably won't need it as much if I get this job but I didn't think I'll accept <anon type="place"/> festival until I've got this interview until I've had this interview yeah I did <anon type="place"/> yesterday so I've been trying to earn money in bits and pieces where I can but I want something permanent but all this money I don't get realised until the end of the month anyway so this month I've had to be</u>
<u n="273" who="S0149">mine's been shit cos they've paid on the twenty-third December did they do that with you?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0149">it's really annoying</u>
<u n="276" who="S0167">I hate it when that happens</u>
<u n="277" who="S0149">that dent I made in the car</u>
<u n="278" who="S0148">where did you make that?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0149">I made it in October I was so good at keeping it a secret from my parents</u>
<u n="280" who="S0167">why is it your car or theirs?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0149">it's theirs and all the times I kept it quiet and I was like I kept it quiet all the time I made them park it somewhere and then walk round to my house everything literally and then at Christmas oh I'm going to wash the cars and I was like oh no I'll do mine</u>
<u n="282" who="S0167">very stressful for you having that</u>
<u n="283" who="S0149">and I was like I know it was and I said I was like no seriously I was like you know give me that car you know I'm paying it off</u>
<u n="284" who="S0148">I'll wash it</u>
<u n="285" who="S0149">I must do it and then dad the next morning before I woke up was like how did you do the dent? why don't I know about it? and I learn from my mistakes I very much do and I was like in my head hide the dent but dad was like that was so stupid because you can't claim for it on the insurance now because you have to claim in two weeks</u>
<u n="286" who="S0148">not that you'd want to either you wouldn't want to claim against that</u>
<u n="287" who="S0167">it's probably cheaper to get it</u>
<u n="288" who="S0149">nightmare the mechanics and I've now I've paid dad off and the insurance is a nightmare with my points</u>
<u n="289" who="S0167">you've got points</u>
<u n="290" who="S0148">why have you got points?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0149">speeding I'm sure I told you that ages ago and then we sent it to the mechanic and we're still waiting for them to do work on it cos the excess and the insurance is five hundred pounds and I don't want anyone else the insurers to know if it's under five hundred fine just going to sort it out myself even if it's six hundred I will pay and the man was initially no it's fine we'll bash it out and then he looked at it again and actually the alignment's really not great and he was like turn on your headlights and so I turned them on and cos it was slightly bashed one of them on the brick wall was like here the other one was here it's like it's definitely not right so I haven't told dad that yet</u>
<u n="292" who="S0167">oh no</u>
<u n="293" who="S0149">so I haven't told dad that yet oh it's a nightmare and I couldn't go on the driver awareness course because I was too much over the limit which I think is really wrong because</u>
<u n="294" who="S0148">course</u>
<u n="295" who="S0149">you should have to go on the course and get points but no no</u>
<u n="296" who="S0148">you're the one that needs it</u>
<u n="297" who="S0149">so you just have to have the points</u>
<u n="298" who="S0167">there's always something with cars</u>
<u n="299" who="S0149">dad said to me there's no point buying a new car cos a new driver driving out of the forecourt losing value something crazy like it loses two and a half grand just by driving out of the car park so that was a bit of a nightmare before Christmas</u>
<u n="300" who="S0148">my engine light came on again did I tell you about the engine light?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0167">you're not in the Clio any more?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0149">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0167">you are?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0149">Clio</u>
<u n="305" who="S0148">Cleopatra</u>
<u n="306" who="S0148">the engine light came on we were driving down to Dorset me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and then just like what does that mean? amber light that looks like an engine</u>
<u n="307" who="S0149">I know that one overheating</u>
<u n="308" who="S0148">pulled over and it could be absolutely anything and if it's not red it should be fine</u>
<u n="309" who="S0149">did you find somewhere when you got to Dorset?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0148">of course we couldn't find anywhere in Dorset and ended up going all the way back to Reading and it was something really stupid like and when I went back to Bristol for Christmas and when I got onto the motorway engine light went on</u>
<u n="311" who="S0148">oh my</u>
<u n="312" who="S0167">it's really frightening on the motorway no it was orange if it was red I would of stopped my dad picked my tyres and they were a bit flat and said what shall I do? and he was like oh they'll be alright</u>
<u n="313" who="S0148">put air in them</u>
<u n="314" who="S0149">that was costing a lot more petrol</u>
<u n="315" who="S0148">yeah I get scared of doing that cos I never know if I'm doing it right I'm paranoid I don't know the amount I get a stranger to do it I act like oh I don't know</u>
<u n="316" who="S0167">I'm like every now and then my dad checks my car cos he knows I don't check it cos I never check anything once I'm out of the car I forget about the car once I shut the door off you go</u>
<u n="317" who="S0148">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0167">I never checked my oil and I've had my car for about five years</u>
<u n="319" who="S0148">but it flashes up oil on my dashboard okay when I stop the engine so I'm like great anyway the other day I was going to come home and go to my sister's for dinner and then drive back from my sister's to Reading driving to my sister's it was like der der der anti lock kn the breaks and that grinding sound</u>
<u n="320" who="S0167">sound quite scary</u>
<u n="321" who="S0148">I was thinking what was this I said to my dad and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> dad I'm sitting in the car I don't want to go back to Reading the breaks are going to fail and so I got them in the car and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> dad would slam on the breaks and said they were quite good but yeah it was like the RAC man and he drove and there were a few things the tracking is out the <unclear/> but it is just your anti lock breaking that's what it is</u>
<u n="322" who="S0167">my anti locking comes in really quickly and that really scares me</u>
<u n="323" who="S0149">what is it?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0148">it's like if you're breaking quite hard anti locking is there to slow you down in my head this is the road rather than slowly slowing down it's trying to work hardest it's going der der der breaking harder on each bit it's fucking terrifying that was when I went into the rails with that dent der der der</u>
<u n="325" who="S0149">seriously</u>
<u n="326" who="S0148">yeah it's fine drove back to Reading my dad <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> drove it out into the lanes and they're like it's fine but I drive my sister's car slightly different model put on the breaks and was literally like woah but mine it am I going to stop? am I going to stop? yeah that's good that's what I thought with that railing coming towards me just stop</u>
<u n="327" who="S0149">railings yeah do</u>
<u n="328" who="S0148">so I drove it back to Reading and when I got onto the motorway it was really raining and there were vans and then my ABS light comes on my dashboard and there's a problem with my anti lock breaking system and it's in the garage and it's all the time it's service coming up</u>
<u n="329" who="S0148">shit done to it again</u>
<u n="330" who="S0149">what my dad said can't always be paying for your car</u>
<u n="331" who="S0167">I just pay the car really so they had to pay the tax and the other day I was driving back from somewhere I don't know where I was driving back from oh yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> through <anon type="place"/> and I was daydreaming and I realised I was going at forty just where the speed camera is over those lines so I slowed down but I don't know if I did fast enough unfortunately I also found out that my tax had run out the day before so if I do catch me so I'm hoping the speed camera hasn't caught</u>
<u n="332" who="S0149">a lot of them don't have film in</u>
<u n="333" who="S0167">yeah I'm hoping that hasn't happened it's bad enough them catching me speeding but it's also bad if it's the day I got tax the next day but that was the day that I was speeding</u>
<u n="334" who="S0149">oh so annoying</u>
<u n="335" who="S0167">I'm always so careful with it cos I know where the speed cameras so I always go down to thirty</u>
<u n="336" who="S0148">and I'm pretty sure I've been in the car with you when you're driving slowly anyway</u>
<u n="337" who="S0167">yeah and I'm not a speeder I'm just driving yeah I'm always so careful I always find when it's something when I'm singing along thinking yeah so when I was coming back from <anon type="place"/> I was doing like seventy on the motorway I was like I can't be caught just going really slowly</u>
<u n="338" who="S0149">what is the speed limit on the motorway?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0167">seventy but it's</u>
<u n="340" who="S0148">overtaking you always go beyond I'm always about seventy-five</u>
<u n="341" who="S0167">no I was doing seventy nobody gets tickets on the motorway they're fine but there was a variable sixty so I went right down to sixty and I think other cars were going faster but erm but cos it was dark at this time there was a huge flash and I thought oh my god I hope it isn't me they're flashing I was like I am doing sixty and I was like oh my god maybe it was fifty and I read it wrong</u>
<u n="342" who="S0149">if there were cars going along faster than you</u>
<u n="343" who="S0167">yeah so it was flashing another car maybe cos I was like oh my god if I got caught twice for speeding in two days then that's not good news I'm so careful I've never had any points in my life or anything</u>
<u n="344" who="S0149">who doesn't?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0167">I can't afford to pay fines right now</u>
<u n="346" who="S0149">neither can I</u>
<u n="347" who="S0167">I got paid we got paid a day less we got paid on twenty-first twenty-third we had to close our accounts down so we got paid three hundred and fifty dollars so I had that to bring home for me and it was only like a hundred and fifty pounds or something and so I've had to last me this month which is mostly like gone and</u>
<u n="348" who="S0167">yeah oh wow doing well then</u>
<u n="349" who="S0149">well I suppose you're back with your parents you're not paying rent</u>
<u n="350" who="S0167">well I didn't have to pay rent in Peru because it was provided with our internship and when we worked it out we were working ten hours a day five days a week so we were working fifty hours a week and I was getting two hundred pounds the equivalent of getting paid in dollars but they couldn't so it worked out I was being paid a pound an hour but then we have got we have our flat provided and we got health insurance with that that we did actually end up using</u>
<u n="351" who="S0149">why what was wrong?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0167">erm I think must have used I woke up one day and I was being sick and I couldn't go into work and then I erm I thought I got a bug and then the next day I had diarrhoea and it had blood in it</u>
<u n="353" who="S0149">oh</u>
<u n="354" who="S0167">and I thought maybe and anyway this happened for a whole day and I got to the point where there was nothing to come out either end but it was still trying to come out and really painful so I rang my mum and she was like maybe go to the hospital so I went to the hospital and I went into the doctor's and it sounds like you've got cos here we have bacteria in food that we sometimes get and it sounds like you've got a bacterial infection so I'll give you antibiotics and if it gets worse just comes back the next week so I took the antibiotics and it cleared up so it must have been an infection erm but yeah so I used that but they paid not for the doctor so I had to pay to go to the doctor and to have to pay fifty soles which was only about ten pounds and then I had to pay for my antibiotics which were like twenty soles which is only like four pounds which I guess isn't that much but seventy soles is in Peru it goes a lot further than it does in England cos everything's a lot cheaper so it was like oh god</u>
<u n="355" who="S0149">it's like that all over America and obviously you pay you can't afford it you just want to be done with it</u>
<u n="356" who="S0167">it would have been so much more expensive cos that was only ten percent with my health insurance that was only ten percent of what the actual cost was so I was like oh my god I wouldn't of been able to pay that if I didn't have my insurance always worth getting insurance if your dog has insurance</u>
<u n="357" who="S0148">oh but they cost a fortune too</u>
<u n="358" who="S0167">yeah and my parents did that they had eight hundred pounds for my cat's paw to have like a skin graft</u>
<u n="359" who="S0148">how much?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0167">eight hundred pounds my dog was really ill bless him I woke up on Monday my parents were at work and I was home and I thought where is he? and he was on my mum and dad's bed being sick all over their bed</u>
<u n="361" who="S0148">oh no</u>
<u n="362" who="S0167">I thought maybe he's just eaten something anyway he carried on being sick the rest of the day and he wouldn't eat anything and he was sick all of the next day so we took him to the vet's and it turned out he had <unclear/> got something so they kept him in the vet and he was in there like ten minutes and drank that much from the consultation having his blood scanned</u>
<u n="363" who="S0148">oh my god</u>
<u n="364" who="S0167">and then he was in the vet's for the next two days and then he was in the hospital and he was in the hospital now it must be easily over now</u>
<u n="365" who="S0148">my god</u>
<u n="366" who="S0167">bless him he's not very well his liver's gone now he's jaundiced thinking about having him put down</u>
<u n="367" who="S0149">how old is he?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0167">nine I don't know how long they for</u>
<u n="369" who="S0149">a dog that's not old</u>
<u n="370" who="S0167">is it? I think with his breed his average age is about ten</u>
<u n="371" who="S0149">okay so if his liver's gone</u>
<u n="372" who="S0167">no</u>
<u n="373" who="S0148">we only had pedigrees and they've been off</u>
<u n="374" who="S0149">I've heard it about cats but not about dogs</u>
<u n="375" who="S0167">we always get moggie cats so they live longer I want him buried</u>
<u n="376" who="S0149">my dog my parents will have puppies soon and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I are getting one</u>
<u n="377" who="S0148">will you live with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> parents?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0149">no we get our own house</u>
<u n="379" who="S0167">oh that's good so you can move straight in</u>
<u n="380" who="S0149">yup yup</u>
<u n="381" who="S0167">one or two teething problems moving into together</u>
<u n="382" who="S0149">no we're quite lucky cos when uni finished we had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got a room in his house maybe no but it's I was like can some of my furniture do you mind if I store it before I get a flat share? cos I don't want to and he was like yeah yeah yeah and then it just sort of happened we never sort of discussed this it just kind of like do you need to find a flat with some others?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0167">yeah it's very grown up</u>
<u n="384" who="S0149">I can't wait</u>
<u n="385" who="S0167">I want to get a flat share in London</u>
<u n="386" who="S0149">can't afford to do that does he own it or rent it?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0148">he owns it</u>
<u n="388" who="S0167">what does he do for a job?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0149">he's a landscape gardener and he has his own business erm I think it also makes a big difference cos he never went to uni and he's been working since he was eighteen so he's not in debt never had all of that he's been working but I mean he comes from a very wealthy family and I'm guessing he helped him buy</u>
<u n="390" who="S0167">maybe</u>
<u n="391" who="S0149">I'm not really sure big mortgage though very big mortgage</u>
<u n="392" who="S0148">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0167">I've been looking at houses cos I have a lot of time at work cos it was like ten hours a day and we had to before and afterwards so I spent most of those on the internet</u>
<u n="394" who="S0149"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what do you call him?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0167"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="396" who="S0149">oh he's called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0167">it's like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but it's like the German pronunciation is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0148">how do you spell?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0149"><unclear/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0148">I thought it would be T I</u>
<u n="401" who="S0167">it's like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but with a different pronunciation but I don't call it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos I think that's stupid but I can't call him <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0148">you can't say that that's what I'm calling my first son</u>
<u n="403" who="S0167">I don't know I think it's alright on a kid until about four and then it sounds really childish</u>
<u n="404" who="S0148">oh no</u>
<u n="405" who="S0149">it's like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0148">I'm having <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0149"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is quite grown up but I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is like a little child's name well yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0167">well yeah you could call him <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> my uncle's called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I just think that's a really boring name though <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="409" who="S0148"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is a really boring name</u>
<u n="410" who="S0149"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I talk about names all the time cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is his middle name</u>
<u n="411" who="S0149">I wanted <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but</u>
<u n="412" who="S0148">you can't call her <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0149">I was going to call her <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and</u>
<u n="414" who="S0167">oh no did you have a fight?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0149">she's three months pregnant</u>
<u n="416" who="S0167">had a girl</u>
<u n="417" who="S0149">and then like two months later she said I'm going to call it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I was like praying it was a boy</u>
<u n="418" who="S0167">that's annoying</u>
<u n="419" who="S0149">and she's also stolen my middle name</u>
<u n="420" who="S0167">yeah no I would of just said something like oi you can't call her <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and my mum is like</u>
<u n="421" who="S0149">we have this blanket that my nan knitted and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> my sister when she had her baby and then I had <unclear/> and then no she's got it for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what is her children then maybe we'll let you borrow it</u>
<u n="422" who="S0167">why does she want another grandchild?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0148">have another one from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> maybe I want the one I had as well</u>
<u n="424" who="S0149">you've still got the coil right?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0149">I've researched it I've got an appointment with them on Tuesday painful periods really painful periods</u>
<u n="426" who="S0149">have you got the proper ones?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0167">yeah I've got the proper ones</u>
<u n="428" who="S0149">research painful periods</u>
<u n="429" who="S0148">shorter longer heavier</u>
<u n="430" who="S0167">same but at least they're regular not every week you had weird</u>
<u n="431" who="S0149">well I googled that and pregnancy as in when you take it out how long does it well it's so varied take it out July second pregnant July second and then other people were like no it takes ages</u>
<u n="432" who="S0167">I guess hormonal ones maybe it takes</u>
<u n="433" who="S0149">but it's not is it?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0167">no the proper one is not hormonal</u>
<u n="435" who="S0149">oh yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0167">is it a five year or ten year one?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0149">I think it was quite small</u>
<u n="438" who="S0167">but I'm just having it out cos that's the bit where people</u>
<u n="439" who="S0148">it was painful putting it in how are they going to get it out?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0149">forceps thing they use</u>
<u n="441" who="S0167">it was like they took it out</u>
<u n="442" who="S0149">do that again and then they're gonna the silly thing is you lose your dignity they give you a curtain to take your clothes off and then it's like it would be painful once you put it in</u>
<u n="443" who="S0148">yeah I've got an appointment on the doctor's on Tuesday yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0149">cocktails called absolute vodka</u>
<u n="445" who="S0167">I would never drink at breakfast time unless I'm an alcoholic which I hope I never am <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0149">how much was the breakfast tea?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0167">it was</u>
<u n="448" who="S0149">you're so silly it was like one ninety-five</u>
<u n="449" who="S0167">they've put like three cups of tea there</u>
<u n="450" who="S0149">mm what shall I have? I might have a sausage baguette</u>
<u n="451" who="S0167">yeah I was debating that maybe gonna have that</u>
<u n="452" who="S0149">I love my mum</u>
<u n="453" who="S0167">good I glad you love my mum is that washing?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0149">hand washing only</u>
<u n="455" who="S0167">oh is it?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0149">yeah it's like the</u>
<u n="457" who="S0148">oh I thought you'd done that yourself did you?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0149">I'm sorry <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hand paint</u>
<u n="459" who="S0167">you should I like it it's fun</u>
<u n="460" who="S0149">and I'm going to write it to use this to write down my thoughts day one thought of the day</u>
<u n="461" who="S0148">er a thought of the day</u>
<u n="462" who="S0149">talking of thoughts of the day makes me think of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think she's going to go places with her writing</u>
<u n="463" who="S0148">what's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> up to?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0149">mum and dad</u>
<u n="465" who="S0167">she's living</u>
<u n="466" who="S0148">she works part time in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0149">does she? which is ironic cos she doesn't like children</u>
<u n="468" who="S0148">which is the funny thing I remember her laughing about it in our third year it's funny isn't it cos I don't actually like children</u>
<u n="469" who="S0149">that's the strangest thing I've ever heard she's not doing teaching now is she?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0167">do you ever see her often?</u>
<u n="471" who="S0149">I don't because I don't like her house it's cold</u>
<u n="472" who="S0167">does she live by herself?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0148">no other people</u>
<u n="474" who="S0149">she like wants to be the eternal student so okay what does she blog about?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0148">the life according to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is</u>
<u n="476" who="S0167">I haven't finished my blog actually I forgot to finish it when I was in Peru so my mum has been like finish your blog oh really she finds it quite funny</u>
<u n="477" who="S0167">I haven't read it</u>
<u n="478" who="S0148">that's why</u>
<u n="479" who="S0167">what does she say?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0149">poems that she's written or something she wrote one recently</u>
<u n="481" who="S0148">we wrote for that competition that we never sent off about the owl it's on my pinboard</u>
<u n="482" who="S0149">I wrote a competition for that competition sent the same poem twice I was convinced it was I literally just gone in there and been like give me the money I was so upset it was funny</u>
<u n="483" who="S0149">I think I'm going to look for another poetry competition online and send it in and see what I win</u>
<u n="484" who="S0148">I think it's a good poem actually it's a limerick it's like there once was an owl named heather and she once lost her feather there once was an owl called heather also I thought it had to be seven five seven is that I've answered my own question but that must have been a limerick and that that's wrong</u>
<u n="485" who="S0149">right I'm going to go for a pain au chocolate</u>
<u n="486" who="S0167">oh I might have a fruit salad</u>
<u n="487" who="S0149">I'm freezing are you not freezing my this door?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0167">I just don't know any more what does one have? <unclear/> fruit salad something healthy so</u>
<u n="489" who="S0149">yeah that's what I'm going to have</u>
<u n="490" who="S0148">or do you have French toast and maple syrup? at least we've got fruit on it</u>
<u n="491" who="S0149">yeah</u>
<u n="492" who="S0167">shame about the maple syrup on the French toast</u>
<u n="493" who="S0149">maybe I'll get eggs Benedict</u>
<u n="494" who="S0167">oh</u>
<u n="495" who="S0148">that sounds nice</u>
<u n="496" who="S0149">I'm gonna get eggs Benedict</u>
<u n="497" who="S0167">I'm gonna copy you</u>
<u n="498" who="S0148">I'm really cold can we move?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0149">shall we if I move the person then order</u>
<u n="500" who="S0148">I'm literally so cold</u>
<u n="501" who="S0148">this would be the time to ask</u>
<u n="502" who="S0149">excuse me were about to order to breakfast is it possible to move further in as we're quite cold here? we just wondered if we could move to a table further back cos it's a bit cold here and then move further back okay we want to order too oh yeah yeah thank you yes and then we'll order</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
