<text id="SMM7">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:40:27</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-06-28</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0421 S0423</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A house</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Internet companies, food/ water, holidays, computers/ updates, internet, accommodation, neighbours, slippers, bungalow, dvds, </topics>
		<activity>Father and daughter converse at home before dinner while looking for accommodation for holiday</activity>
		<conv_type>Dicsussing, explaining, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0421">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lytham St Annes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2>Hungarian</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0423">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bolton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Manchester, England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mossley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Customer Services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0421">erm how long do you think it's gonna be?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0423">well <pause dur="short"/> half an hour maybe</u>
<u n="3" who="S0421">oh right</u>
<u n="4" who="S0423">is that too long?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0421">no I'm just wondering I'm quite hungry</u>
<u n="6" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="7" who="S0421">we've got Talktalk internet now as well</u>
<u n="8" who="S0423">have you?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0421">yeah they came and put it in for us like the day after we moved in</u>
<u n="10" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well then how come you've gone with Talktalk then?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0421">it's cheap the cheapest</u>
<u n="12" who="S0423">so who did you have before?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0421">BT</u>
<u n="14" who="S0423">got you a starter</u>
<u n="15" who="S0421">oh <pause dur="short"/> it was an absolute rip off BT</u>
<u n="16" who="S0423">well I'm not on I've not gone with them now and I haven't done in years</u>
<u n="17" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos we used to always had them because like we just never changed</u>
<u n="18" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah look that looks alright</u>
<u n="19" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0423">well that's what they rely on a lot of people don't</u>
<u n="21" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and so they don't look around and that's</u>
<u n="23" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and then but we were paying so much so we've got Talktalk and then he came this person and like sorted it</u>
<u n="24" who="S0423">well yeah I told your mammy years ago that it's really cheap</u>
<u n="25" who="S0421">yeah it's good</u>
<u n="26" who="S0423">and er</u>
<u n="27" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and it works <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0423">of course it does I can watch films on the internet with it</u>
<u n="29" who="S0421">but like he came this engineer</u>
<u n="30" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0421">and then cos we got our box in the post like the the router</u>
<u n="32" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0421">and erm he came to install the phone line and usually they install like the router for you as well and he didn't so I have to</u>
<u n="34" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="35" who="S0421" trans="overlap">follow the instructions in the box and I was like oh it's alright I mean they are cheaper and everything and mammy was like why did they not install it? and I'm like I've managed to do it it only took me five minutes</u>
<u n="36" who="S0423">I just got mine in the post</u>
<u n="37" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0423">and I just did it cos there's not much to install really you just I mean</u>
<u n="39" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos on on BT they're always like don't attempt to install it yourself</u>
<u n="40" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0421">like we will come and do it for you</u>
<u n="42" who="S0423">oh well that's why cos they wanna charge you so much you see</u>
<u n="43" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah probably</u>
<u n="44" who="S0423">and make out that it's something special to do but you know you don't have to do much to put the router get the router sorted do you?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well we don't have erm a phone because we never used a phone so</u>
<u n="46" who="S0423">what so you're just getting the internet yeah?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0421">yeah like we have to have the phone line to get the internet through</u>
<u n="48" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0421">but we're not like plugging in our phone</u>
<u n="50" who="S0423">well it's only another fiver for a phone line isn't it? to have a phone plugged in you know if you want a a line you what are you just paying for the phone line?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0421">yeah so that we can have the internet through it but like we don't want the phone because whenever we've used the landline to make calls it's always worked out like more expensive</u>
<u n="52" who="S0423">well no you you you pay</u>
<u n="53" who="S0421" trans="overlap">than the mobile because of our mobile package is really good and we can make</u>
<u n="54" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you only pay five pound and you call anything for free</u>
<u n="55" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no I mean but it's just the paying for just like no I mean like company numbers and stuff cos that's all we ring and company numbers</u>
<u n="56" who="S0423" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="57" who="S0421">charge and it's the same as like</u>
<u n="58" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos on the mobile they charge more don't they?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0421">no they don't they er it's it's worse on well cos when we used the landline it was just as much because of the mobile package that we've got it's some of them they charge more</u>
<u n="60" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well I thought your mammy was saying she's been paying thirty pound to ring the gas</u>
<u n="61" who="S0421">yeah because we were on the phone to them for like three three hours</u>
<u n="62" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah but if if you rang the landline</u>
<u n="63" who="S0421">no it's just as bad because we rang</u>
<u n="64" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0421">no in <anon type="place"/> we rang all these companies like sorting out gas and internet and everything and our phone bill was like fifty odd pounds or something</u>
<u n="66" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well that's probably cos of the package you have with BT</u>
<u n="67" who="S0421">no because we were supposed to have free calls but all these numbers that we had to ring these companies were all exempt</u>
<u n="68" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh why they were 0845 or something?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah they were all exempt so it just</u>
<u n="70" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="71" who="S0421" trans="overlap">works out just as well for us to just ring on the mobile</u>
<u n="72" who="S0423">can you read that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? temperature and time</u>
<u n="73" who="S0421">er cook for eighteen to twenty minutes</u>
<u n="74" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0421">er what's do you want temperature?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0423">yeah gas mark six</u>
<u n="77" who="S0421" trans="overlap">two er two hundred degrees</u>
<u n="78" who="S0423">gas mark</u>
<u n="79" who="S0421" trans="overlap">gas mark</u>
<u n="80" who="S0423">so even you</u>
<u n="81" who="S0421" trans="overlap">six</u>
<u n="82" who="S0423">struggle to read these things</u>
<u n="83" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos it's crumpled</u>
<u n="84" who="S0423" trans="overlap">why do they do that?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0421">it's crumpled <pause dur="short"/> and it's shiny and the light's shining on it</u>
<u n="86" who="S0423">do you want erm <pause dur="short"/> do you want some smoothie?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0421">yeah what flavour is it?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0423">oh oh</u>
<u n="89" who="S0421">mangoes and passion</u>
<u n="90" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="91" who="S0423">do you want a few crisps to go with it?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0423">is that glass alright?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna have to taste your water later though</u>
<u n="95" who="S0423">why?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because <vocal desc="laugh"/> well cos</u>
<u n="97" who="S0423" trans="overlap">do you not like it where you are?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0421">yeah we've been drinking and we've been like it tastes weird like</u>
<u n="99" who="S0423">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0423">cos this water was supposed to be really pure around here</u>
<u n="102" who="S0421">yeah I don't know I think but it feels different as well like when I wash my hands <pause dur="short"/> it feels different on my skin</u>
<u n="103" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0421">yeah it's like when I put soap on my hands and I'm like washing my hands</u>
<u n="105" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0421">it's like I'm not washing the soap off but I have</u>
<u n="107" who="S0423">strange</u>
<u n="108" who="S0421">yeah I don't know</u>
<u n="109" who="S0423">well the water in this area is meant to be it's meant to be really good</u>
<u n="110" who="S0421">yeah it it's good</u>
<u n="111" who="S0423" trans="overlap">is what I've heard yeah maybe it's just cos it's not what you're used to</u>
<u n="112" who="S0421">yeah it's probably just different</u>
<u n="113" who="S0423">so I mean <anon type="place"/> it's the same as you had in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0421">yeah I just it's just changed so I'd say <pause dur="short"/> it seems different</u>
<u n="115" who="S0423">there you are <pause dur="short"/> mm but but are you going inside or are you staying here? I'm coming in now anyway cos there's nothing to do</u>
<u n="116" who="S0421">oh right okay</u>
<u n="117" who="S0423">coming in in a minute <pause dur="long"/> well you don't have to go to bed early tonight or anything do you?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0421">no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0423">shall I show you what what I've been looking at a couple of</u>
<u n="120" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0423">a couple of options? I mean you can browse and see if you can find anything else if you're not keen on them</u>
<u n="122" who="S0421">well we're lucky that there's still places to book <pause dur="short"/> cos we're leaving it quite late aren't we?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0423">yeah fortunately I don't think the kids will be yet like the kids will <trunc>ha</trunc> in in school holidays at that time then I mean it probably is coming up to it not far off it but <unclear/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like mid July I think isn't it?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="short"/> so you've got from the sixth to the tenth booked</u>
<u n="126" who="S0421">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0423">they said I can upgrade to a better caravan and make it a week where we're staying</u>
<u n="128" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0423">and I'll look <trunc>f</trunc> we could look for somewhere else for a few odd days but <pause dur="short"/> I got <vocal desc="cough"/> I thought well you might prefer a a lodge or something like that for for the weekly stay</u>
<u n="130" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/> don't know the caravan might be a bit cramped</u>
<u n="131" who="S0423">no it wasn't when we were in Scotland was it?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0421">yeah it wasn't bad actually that caravan <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="133" who="S0423">it depends what bungalow type thing you get</u>
<u n="134" who="S0421">yeah cos that could be cramped</u>
<u n="135" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you know some of them are not er great we were lucky in Scotland with that as well we had</u>
<u n="136" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0423" trans="overlap">a nice one</u>
<u n="138" who="S0421" trans="overlap">wow that was cool that was for like six people wasn't it?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0423">mm we won't be getting one like I don't think</u>
<u n="140" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well because when you said when we went to Italy and you were like oh I've got a little like house or whatever it was and it was like a room <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0423">I know that's it you see <trunc>y</trunc>you don't want a you may we may as well have a caravan <unclear>between</unclear> something like that</u>
<u n="142" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0423">some of the caravans are they're great they're massive</u>
<u n="144" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0423">erm <pause dur="short"/> so you could look at that as an option there's the bigger caravans possibly they might be a good price</u>
<event desc="sound of phone"/> <pause dur="long"/>
<u n="146" who="S0423"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0421">have you fixed whatever was wrong with your internet with that re-stall?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0423">well I've I've done it a few times and the problem is it keeps</u>
<u n="149" who="S0421">doing it</u>
<u n="150" who="S0423" trans="overlap">even when I I changed the it's when I get an update so it kept updating and and then I kept changing it and eventually I was fed up so I thought right I'm gonna go into the control panel and say ask me before you install any upgrades</u>
<u n="151" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so I did that and then it just does the bloody update when I shut down again</u>
<u n="153" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0423">so then I've I've shut it off and it said it's not recommended that you don't have updates but for temporarily until I you know get this sorted I've I've shut off</u>
<u n="155" who="S0421" trans="overlap">what is it doing?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0423">so I don't get any updates any more</u>
<u n="157" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0423">and I've checked the updates it's putting down cos I was gonna look if it was something obvious and just delete that update</u>
<u n="159" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's probably a bug in it or something I'm surprised no one's reported it</u>
<u n="160" who="S0423">well no there's various things it could be cos it it's the it it's coming up DEP er the data execution prevention</u>
<u n="161" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0423">there's a programme in there that stops and they said you you may have when you when you say what could be the problem they say it could be when you when you run <trunc>up</trunc>updates a company has <trunc>up</trunc> sent you an update and it's not compatible with this DEP</u>
<u n="163" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="164" who="S0423">and you should install uninstall it but all the updates are from Windows from Microsoft</u>
<u n="165" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0423">so I don't I don't get it</u>
<u n="167" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so I'll have to look a bit more in-depth so this is the only solution I could figure out er temporarily for now erm I mean I've got there's like free erm AVG security er thing and what have you on it so you would think if there <trunc>w</trunc> is a it it the computer's under attack or anything it should pick something up so there's no signs of anything like that going on but I think it's just a glitch in one of these programmes that are downloading maybe if I changed my browser from Internet Explorer to</u>
<u n="169" who="S0421" trans="overlap">is it internet</u>
<u n="170" who="S0423" trans="overlap">something else</u>
<u n="171" who="S0421">internet</u>
<u n="172" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0421" trans="overlap">Explorer is a rubbish browser</u>
<u n="174" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0421">get Google Chrome</u>
<u n="176" who="S0423">yeah I was just</u>
<u n="177" who="S0421" trans="overlap">that's better</u>
<u n="178" who="S0423" trans="overlap">just thinking that today that might be a more better long term solution so I thought Google Chrome or Firefox or</u>
<u n="179" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like if you can help it like no <trunc>o</trunc> no one uses Internet Explorer any more</u>
<u n="180" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0421">I mean people do but it's quite slow and there's like stuff wrong with it and</u>
<u n="182" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0421">I don't have Internet Explorer</u>
<u n="184" who="S0423">well I've not had problems with it before but I think that might be a a way of solving it</u>
<u n="185" who="S0421"><trunc>ye</trunc> have you heard that like you know like Windows ten or something that's coming out? <pause dur="short"/> I think it's gonna be like a free update if you've got an old Windows</u>
<u n="186" who="S0423">oh really?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="188" who="S0423">mm I've not heard of that <pause dur="short"/> this Vista is is not very much rated either is it? it's not supposed to be that great</u>
<u n="189" who="S0421">yeah but the new like</u>
<u n="190" who="S0423"><unclear>seems like quite like</unclear></u>
<u n="191" who="S0421" trans="overlap">the new like Windows eight they've got has got so many problems with it</u>
<u n="192" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and erm like most people have that one and they said they're like oh yeah Windows ten you can have it for free because it was</u>
<u n="194" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right I wonder if they'll give it me or if it's just if you've eight</u>
<u n="195" who="S0421">yeah I dunno I think you might get it</u>
<u n="196" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0421">I don't know if you want it though it looks really different like I don't</u>
<u n="198" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0421">I don't know how to work it</u>
<u n="200" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="201" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's like you know on like your smartphone where you have like apps?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="203" who="S0421">and it's like you click them but on Windows eight they didn't have a start menu but in Windows ten they've brought the start menu back so it's a bit easier to navigate</u>
<u n="204" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="205" who="S0421">but yeah in Windows eight there was no start menu and people were like what am I doing?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0423">yeah you'd think before doing updates like that they'd consult people <pause dur="short"/> I don't like the <trunc>s</trunc> look of that what's come down there</u>
<u n="207" who="S0421">file task</u>
<u n="208" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and I'm gonna get those chips in cos they take half an hour</u>
<u n="209" who="S0421">uhu</u>
<event desc="sound of phone"/> <pause dur="long"/>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="210" who="S0423">got multiple problems with your computer</u>
<u n="211" who="S0421">yeah and it says <vocal desc="laugh"/> you've got loads of security problems</u>
<u n="212" who="S0423">that doesn't sound good does it?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0421">it's probably you er erm disabling all those updates or something <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0423">maybe it's coming from them because it's thinking well why can't we send these updates? he's got a problem</u>
<u n="215" who="S0421">I'm gonna eat all these crisps <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="216" who="S0423">do you want more?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0421">what?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0423"><trunc>may</trunc>maybe maybe you'd better not have more more cos you might not eat your pizza</u>
<u n="219" who="S0421">do you know I was just thinking the other day how long it has been since I had some Doritos and I was like I really want some Doritos and here we are</u>
<u n="220" who="S0423">oh that's good isn't it?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0421">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I don't get them often but they they are tasty and they</u>
<u n="223" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I had one of those</u>
<u n="224" who="S0423" trans="overlap">they're quite addictive aren't they?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0421">I had one of those USB like mobile stick things</u>
<u n="226" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="227" who="S0421">and the internet went quite fast</u>
<u n="228" who="S0423">yeah that's what I was thinking and it might <unclear/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's not like it wasn't a good value for money</u>
<u n="230" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="231" who="S0421">but I dunno you could try it <pause dur="short"/> like it's not too bad if you just browse occasionally</u>
<u n="232" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="233" who="S0421">but it does kind of work out more expensive like if you ever want to use</u>
<u n="234" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="235" who="S0421" trans="overlap">Skype or anything</u>
<u n="236" who="S0423">oh right yeah I'm better sticking to <unclear/></u>
<u n="237" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like there would be like no way you could use Skype</u>
<u n="238" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="239" who="S0423">install the <trunc>la</trunc> I don't want to do this cos it's gonna start installing all that stuff again isn't it?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0421">probably <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0423">now let's see security centre <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0421">yeah who knows what it's doing? just get Chrome you've got Chrome</u>
<u n="243" who="S0423">yeah I've not I've not installed it though</u>
<u n="244" who="S0421">how's it there then? is it just like do you have to?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well it's probably an option if I</u>
<u n="246" who="S0421">do you think?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0423" trans="overlap">right click I think so yeah it doesn't I've took it off anyway</u>
<u n="248" who="S0421">did you ever click it?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0423">probably er I may not have tried it no</u>
<u n="250" who="S0421">what to? it'll be installed</u>
<u n="251" who="S0423">oh right <pause dur="long"/> it's not it's going slow cos it's still probably loading stuff up and from the internet</u>
<u n="252" who="S0421" trans="overlap">nothing's happening yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0423">just leave it to</u>
<u n="254" who="S0421">why is your laptop this like how old is your laptop?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0423">well I don't know it's er</u>
<u n="256" who="S0421" trans="overlap">that wallpaper I put that on for you when your laptop was like brand new within like the first I don't know when you got it and you've still got it</u>
<u n="257" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="258" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0423">it must be six seven years I think this</u>
<u n="260" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mustn't it? so it's done alright hasn't it that?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> really</u>
<u n="264" who="S0421">it is quite slow</u>
<u n="265" who="S0423">well it's not it's been working since I've stopped those updates</u>
<u n="266" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0423">it's been really great</u>
<u n="268" who="S0421">well it's slow now</u>
<u n="269" who="S0423">well yeah it's taking a while to</u>
<u n="270" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="271" who="S0423">yeah that's what it's saying cos I've turned it off and that's what it wants to bring to my</u>
<u n="272" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah look</u>
<u n="273" who="S0423" trans="overlap">attention and it thinks</u>
<u n="274" who="S0421" trans="overlap">you've got Chrome</u>
<u n="275" who="S0423">oh right so shall I just start using that?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0421">well yeah what is it just Internet Explorer that keeps messing up?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0423">well I don't know it's not it well well I'll find out cos <trunc>we</trunc> if I start using Chrome</u>
<u n="278" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0423">to go</u>
<u n="280" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="281" who="S0423" trans="overlap">on the internet and let them do the updates again</u>
<u n="282" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="283" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and it doesn't bring it up then I <unclear/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos I think Internet Explorer is sometimes quite out of date so maybe it's just not compatible with the new software</u>
<u n="285" who="S0423">possibly yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh right so <trunc>m</trunc> I might do that I might</u>
<u n="286" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0423">might er put the er updates on again and then when I try to get on the internet try Chrome and see if that makes a difference</u>
<u n="288" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="289" who="S0423">right what time have I put those things in? <pause dur="long"/> time goes quick doesn't it?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0421">does it?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's twenty-five to eight do you need to?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0421">mm?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0423">shall I put these somewhere for you? if you want your bag beside you it's alright I'll give it you back</u>
<u n="294" who="S0421">got my phone in it</u>
<u n="295" who="S0423">oh right okay</u>
<u n="296" who="S0421">and all my valuables and like treasures oh no wrong one</u>
<u n="297" who="S0423">have you got treasures?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0423">do you want another drink and crisps? it's gonna be half an hour</u>
<u n="300" who="S0421" trans="overlap">er I don't know maybe</u>
<u n="301" who="S0423" trans="overlap">how many phones have you got?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0421">one of them's my Iphone</u>
<u n="303" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="304" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I was just looking at something on it <pause dur="short"/> and I've got I've got three phones I've got my like fan mail phone I've my personal phone</u>
<u n="305" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well some people do</u>
<u n="306" who="S0421">and I've got my business phone and then I've got a fourth phone that's just my private phone for like playing games on <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0423">some people I never understand when people</u>
<u n="308" who="S0421">I can understand when people have a personal and a business phone</u>
<u n="309" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="310" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh <pause dur="long"/> because you wouldn't you wouldn't want like business calls all the time would you?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0423">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> well yeah that that would make sense wouldn't it? yeah it running quite slow it's been it's been on most of the day it's been running okay <pause dur="long"/> so upload <unclear/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0421" trans="overlap">where's this? Cornwall?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0423">yeah don't you know? that's where we're going <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="314" who="S0421">yeah I know I just I wasn't sure</u>
<u n="315" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0421">if you it was like if we were going somewhere nearby</u>
<u n="317" who="S0423">oh right <pause dur="short"/> well the one here is like north Cornwall</u>
<u n="318" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="319" who="S0423">so where we're staying in the first bit we might kind of explore the south part and then</u>
<u n="320" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="321" who="S0423" trans="overlap">use that to go up to the north and we might pop into kind of the bottom end of Devon as well</u>
<u n="322" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="323" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos it's kind of the top end this that's if we get we're going to this one <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="324" who="S0421">pets go free would you have to</u>
<u n="325" who="S0423" trans="overlap">depends</u>
<u n="326" who="S0421" trans="overlap">pay for <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="327" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yes did you? yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0421" trans="overlap">pets?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos a lot of them say twenty thirty pound to add a pet onto them</u>
<u n="330" who="S0421">what?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0423">why is it small?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0421">yeah someone was saying to me at erm <pause dur="short"/> college that cos they work in a shop and sometimes like their customers chat to them and erm this <trunc>per</trunc> man was saying oh he's going on holiday with his family and everything and like you know he's got a dog oh but one of them's just died er so she won't be coming with us this year cos they go every year and then my friend was like oh but and then the man was like <pause dur="short"/> but only she will kind of be coming with us because</u>
<u n="333" who="S0423" trans="overlap">the ashes</u>
<u n="334" who="S0421">we're taking the ashes with us <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0423">fuck <pause dur="short"/> some people are strange aren't they?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0421">and she was just like that's really weird <vocal desc="laugh"/> and like</u>
<u n="337" who="S0423" trans="overlap">she said that to him?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0421">no she was thinking it</u>
<u n="339" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0421" trans="overlap">she was just like oh</u>
<u n="341" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so what did she say?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0421">she just kind of was like oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0423">well fancy saying that anyway</u>
<u n="344" who="S0421">I know to the person in the shop like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0423">well hang on</u>
<u n="346" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0423">oh <pause dur="long"/> enabling and enable</u>
<u n="348" who="S0421">extension</u>
<u n="349" who="S0423">where's that?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0421">I thought you just</u>
<u n="351" who="S0423" trans="overlap">in the pop-up message where's the pop up message that appears when you open the browser? if Google Chrome is currently running you may first need to restart it for more information</u>
<u n="352" who="S0421">that's a I've never had anything like that happen</u>
<u n="353" who="S0423">no this is <pause dur="short"/> this Rapport it</u>
<u n="354" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0423">checks websites if they're safe or not</u>
<u n="356" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="357" who="S0423">and it's installed on the internet browser it's it's it comes with the bank it <trunc>d</trunc> I downloaded it for the bank and it's to make sure you're</u>
<u n="358" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0423" trans="overlap">safe online and it says there's also the additional thing if you want to make a ensure a website's safe you can click on it erm <pause dur="short"/> so shall I start shall I load it again and then click it?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0423" trans="overlap">did you see a pop-up thing?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="363" who="S0423">enable extension in the pop-up message</u>
<u n="364" who="S0421">what so it won't come up? <pause dur="short"/> er I don't think anything came up <pause dur="short"/> what what? <pause dur="short"/> oh maybe it will now</u>
<u n="365" who="S0423">right</u>
<u n="366" who="S0421">oh cos it wants to</u>
<u n="367" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>cos maybe you double click</unclear></u>
<u n="368" who="S0421" trans="overlap">run this</u>
<u n="369" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0421" trans="overlap">safe programme <trunc>li</trunc> using Chrome because it's on Explorer probably</u>
<u n="371" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0421">yeah what are your new neighbours like? <pause dur="short"/> where do they live?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0423">er one's a a man who's upstairs and he his children</u>
<u n="374" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0423">come and stay</u>
<u n="376" who="S0421">is there any?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and it's a different man upstairs yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="379" who="S0423">and I've not really seen them much I don't know but I think it's a woman <pause dur="short"/> and er there's another man I think he might be upstairs but they're all kind of a bit more</u>
<u n="380" who="S0421">normal</u>
<u n="381" who="S0423" trans="overlap">normal I've spoken to him a few times upstairs</u>
<u n="382" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> cos you had some strange people <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0423">well yeah there was</u>
<u n="384" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0423">all around here really</u>
<u n="386" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and the people who've moved in since seem to be like people who not all of them but some people they they have jobs and things well I think</u>
<u n="388" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="389" who="S0423">the majority of people here they don't work</u>
<u n="390" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0423">how did you get this up? did you double click it?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0421">yeah must have done</u>
<u n="393" who="S0423">oh leave it then for now cos <pause dur="short"/> well it's just going slow</u>
<u n="394" who="S0421">well nothing it's not even loading though like it oh</u>
<u n="395" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0421">wow</u>
<u n="397" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah you see</u>
<u n="398" who="S0421">that's slow</u>
<u n="399" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="400" who="S0421">there's no pop-up</u>
<u n="401" who="S0423">oh there's a a</u>
<u n="402" who="S0421">where?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0423">let me close one of these <pause dur="short"/> what's this here?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0421">that's bookmarks</u>
<u n="405" who="S0423">what's this? it's got apps?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0421" trans="overlap">apps <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0423">there was something when it first come on wasn't there?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0421">yeah but it's I didn't remember</u>
<u n="409" who="S0423">there there</u>
<u n="410" who="S0421" trans="overlap">there</u>
<u n="411" who="S0423">enable extension</u>
<u n="412" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0423">yeah? <pause dur="long"/> there it is see?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0421">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0423">are your feet not cold on this floor?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0421">no <pause dur="short"/> why do your feet get cold on this floor?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="418" who="S0421">do you have slippers?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0421">do you wear them?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="423" who="S0423">why do you want some slippers?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0421">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="425" who="S0423">I might have</u>
<u n="426" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because because I I always walk round at home with bare feet and then</u>
<u n="427" who="S0423" trans="overlap">do you?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0421">grandma's always like the <trunc>c</trunc> the floor's cold <trunc>a</trunc> put some slippers on cos I never wear my slippers</u>
<u n="429" who="S0423">I think when you're young I you know well it's probably like and that's while you <trunc>th</trunc> you don't feel the cold</u>
<u n="430" who="S0421">because</u>
<u n="431" who="S0423" trans="overlap">as much</u>
<u n="432" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because she's she's always like you're gonna catch a cold well like when you're older you'll be you'll regret doing this because</u>
<u n="433" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0421">your bones will be aching</u>
<u n="435" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0421">and I'm just like right cos she's like you can catch such a bad cold and then you won't be able to walk because it's like some kind of a foot cold or something</u>
<u n="437" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm yeah well if you don't feel cold then it's fine isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> you don't need to I don't think you need to worry</u>
<u n="438" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="439" who="S0423">what's that? oh just okay then that can</u>
<u n="440" who="S0421">I don't know maybe she's making it up <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0423">well your grandma seems to have an <trunc>a</trunc> a lot of knowledge about all these kind of diseases and things</u>
<u n="442" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0423">she's made you all go round frightened right so looking at this one</u>
<u n="444" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="445" who="S0423"><anon type="place"/> park bungalow in <anon type="place"/> manor</u>
<u n="446" who="S0421">oh a manor</u>
<u n="447" who="S0423">yeah it sounds impressive doesn't it? but</u>
<u n="448" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="449" who="S0423">comfortable bungalow</u>
<u n="450" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="451" who="S0423" trans="overlap">one double with one twin bath and overhead shower double glazed for year round breaks no pets now the thing is this starts on the eleventh and we're out of the other place at the tenth so we'd have to do what we did in Scotland you know and find a bed and breakfast for</u>
<u n="452" who="S0421"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0423">but it it extends the stay as well cos we'll be going on the Monday the sixth</u>
<u n="454" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0423">and this I think the last day is probably the sixteenth then so it's like a twelve day break or something</u>
<u n="456" who="S0421" trans="overlap">that was like such a are we gonna find one? where are we gonna stay?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no we found it alright it was okay that wasn't it?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah I know but</u>
<u n="459" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I mean we won't have a problem finding somewhere I'll even stay in the caravan can we stay another night? and they probably don't do that cos it might be fully booked and they probably don't rent out for one night but I can always ask them if we paid them a bit more so erm <pause dur="long"/> let's go to view yeah it's running very slow <pause dur="long"/> so this is probably what the bungalows are like <pause dur="short"/> that <pause dur="short"/> but I'm guessing</u>
<u n="460" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="461" who="S0423">because it</u>
<u n="462" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's quite nice</u>
<u n="463" who="S0423">oh it is <anon type="place"/> park bungalow</u>
<u n="464" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="465" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so it's like on a holiday park with lots of</u>
<u n="466" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="467" who="S0423"><unclear/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's strange that isn't it them holiday parks with all these just bungalows like next to each other it just looks weird</u>
<u n="469" who="S0423">yeah I mean they have they have all different stuff lodges</u>
<u n="470" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="471" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and all kinds of things but if it's like that</u>
<u n="472" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="473" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that looks alright doesn't it?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0423">it looks spacious it looks like it's probably quite a small TV but what I might do cos I don't know if there's a DV or it says TV DVD</u>
<u n="476" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="477" who="S0423">but just in case I might bring this laptop and I know it's a small screen but if we wanna watch a film</u>
<u n="478" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="479" who="S0423" trans="overlap">and there's no DVD we can always at least we have something rather than you know at night</u>
<u n="480" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0423">there's not always something on telly so if it's like this that</u>
<u n="482" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0423" trans="overlap">looks okay doesn't it? <pause dur="short"/> and a</u>
<u n="484" who="S0421">I think we</u>
<u n="485" who="S0423" trans="overlap">choice of lodges villas apartments bungalows or cabins but we're going for the bungalow</u>
<u n="486" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos that's all that's come up really so the rest must be book er out I mean there is more further down but they're all dearer</u>
<u n="488" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="489" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so that's kind of the price range <pause dur="short"/> erm I'm looking at especially as we're probably gonna have to spend an extra night somewhere I mean we could look at this it's a similar price three forty <anon type="place"/> what is that?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0421">caravan</u>
<u n="491" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it seems it's that's a caravan</u>
<u n="492" who="S0421">oh wide caravan</u>
<u n="493" who="S0423">so that's probably <unclear/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0421" trans="overlap">one double and two twin that's still quite big isn't it?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0423">a twelve foot one</u>
<u n="496" who="S0421" trans="overlap">although er oh that's what we had in <trunc>S</trunc></u>
<u n="497" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no it's not one of those and that</u>
<u n="498" who="S0421" trans="overlap">in Scotland</u>
<u n="499" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that yeah it'll be similar to that though</u>
<u n="500" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos I had an extra bed in mine didn't I?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0423">yeah yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0421">it's got a shower <pause dur="short"/> got a microwave TV DVD</u>
<u n="503" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that's what it said on the other though isn't it?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0421" trans="overlap">is that</u>
<u n="505" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>written on the thing</unclear></u>
<u n="506" who="S0421" trans="overlap">is that the caravan? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="507" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's nice</u>
<u n="509" who="S0423">that is nice that isn't it? why is it showing a picture of that one?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0421" trans="overlap">er is that a lodge?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0423">well it says caravan though doesn't it?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0421">yeah it says caravan but it's showing a picture of a</u>
<u n="513" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well it probably just</u>
<u n="514" who="S0421" trans="overlap">very nice looking lodge</u>
<u n="515" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well yeah probably is doesn't show you the caravan probably thinks well you know what</u>
<u n="516" who="S0421" trans="overlap">that's got a balcony and everything that lodge</u>
<u n="517" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="518" who="S0421" trans="overlap">or is that a cottage? a villa or an <trunc>apartm</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> lots of different things</u>
<u n="519" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh I see oh have I clicked on a right thing? cos</u>
<u n="520" who="S0421">caravan yeah it's just not showing you the caravan</u>
<u n="521" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah I clicked on view accommodation didn't I? accommodation</u>
<u n="522" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0423" trans="overlap">information yeah <pause dur="short"/> but yeah they they look nice these type of lodges</u>
<u n="524" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="525" who="S0423">it's probably a lodge those type of ones aren't they? oh look archery</u>
<u n="526" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="527" who="S0423">golf <pause dur="short"/> we could bring back our love of golf <unclear/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0421" trans="overlap">do you know on that hill across from my house?</u>
<u n="529" who="S0423">see I I think these pictures are quite standard <trunc>wha</trunc> so whatever our</u>
<u n="530" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear>caravan will look like</unclear></u>
<u n="532" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0423"><unclear>it is</unclear> but although this is different to the bungalow though isn't it?</u>
<u n="534" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="535" who="S0423"><unclear>that's a nice one</unclear></u>
<u n="536" who="S0421" trans="overlap">you know on that hill across from my house</u>
<u n="537" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0421" trans="overlap">there's a golf course</u>
<u n="539" who="S0423">yeah? yeah you thinking of joining?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0421">no I was I was like I saw someone pulling something behind them and I'm like what are they doing? and they were playing golf on the hill</u>
<u n="541" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh a golf buggy yeah so the these are it probably is those big they are probably a a lodge or a bungalow although</u>
<u n="542" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="543" who="S0423" trans="overlap">we're in a bungalow they're probably a lodge or a villa aren't they?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="545" who="S0423">cos it look at the the rooms look much nicer don't they? <pause dur="short"/> there's is that a caravan do you think?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0421">no that's a a villa or something</u>
<u n="547" who="S0423">that's a lodge that but well how come it looks square there?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cabin it's a cabin</u>
<u n="549" who="S0423">oh is it?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0421">yeah that's not a caravan</u>
<u n="551" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="552" who="S0421">it's got a porch</u>
<u n="553" who="S0423">well some caravans have those attached to them</u>
<u n="554" who="S0421">do they?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="long"/> so you rather the bungalow than a caravan?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0421">well I've not seen the caravan so yeah probably <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="557" who="S0423">well <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="558" who="S0421">that bungalow looks nice doesn't it?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0423">well I don't know it looks quite basic</u>
<u n="560" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="561" who="S0423">it looks alright but we er we just want somewhere that's reasonable cos <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="562" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="563" who="S0423">we're not gonna be in we're gonna be there the morning and and the evening</u>
<u n="564" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="565" who="S0423">and all day we're gonna be out so it's not something we're gonna be spending ages in</u>
<u n="566" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="567" who="S0423">yeah I don't why is it not showing you a picture of the caravan? <pause dur="short"/> I think that's a bungalow <pause dur="short"/> right caravan <pause dur="long"/> what if I click on that? <pause dur="long"/> right I'm just gonna get that pizza in</u>
<u n="568" who="S0421">oh is it not in yet?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0423">well I er those chips had to be on a bit longer than the pizza so <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0421">mammy just said that she's been to buy Polyfilla</u>
<u n="571" who="S0423">oh right <pause dur="long"/> mm so <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's still not showing the caravan is it on this one? <pause dur="short"/> unless that's inside the caravan <pause dur="short"/> I doubt it though</u>
<u n="572" who="S0421">yeah it looks a bit nice well not that a caravan is not nice but</u>
<u n="573" who="S0423">no we're not gonna see a picture of it are we really?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> is there a reason they don't want to show us the caravan? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0423">I mean it's odd isn't it? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="576" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="577" who="S0423">okay so there's this one</u>
<u n="578" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0423">how do you do a new tab in this Chrome is it this?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0421" trans="overlap">that yeah <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> why are you typing Google in? Google's down there</u>
<u n="581" who="S0423">oh it's already <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="582" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0423">oh it is Google</u>
<u n="584" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like Google please show me Google</u>
<u n="585" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="586" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no I want to see Google</u>
<u n="587" who="S0423" trans="overlap">wonder if</u>
<u n="588" who="S0421">and google Google</u>
<u n="589" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I wonder what would have happened it <trunc>wou</trunc> might have</u>
<u n="590" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it</u>
<u n="591" who="S0423" trans="overlap">have got confused</u>
<u n="592" who="S0421">no it would come up with searches lots of Google I've done it before <pause dur="short"/> and then you just click on it and it comes up with Google <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="593" who="S0423">oh right</u>
<u n="594" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> because it's Chrome</u>
<u n="595" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="596" who="S0421">it Google Chrome like just typing in uses Google cos it's Google's search engine</u>
<u n="597" who="S0423">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="598" who="S0421">browser <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="599" who="S0423">so this one it looks like a nice location <anon type="place"/> is a lovely little town as well</u>
<u n="600" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="601" who="S0423">erm <pause dur="short"/> and it's right at the beach it looks like so</u>
<u n="602" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="603" who="S0423" trans="overlap">let me just put in <pause dur="short"/> some details <pause dur="long"/> arrive</u>
<u n="604" who="S0421">I like the way it says pet friendly what other pets are gonna bring other than a dog?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0423">a cat?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="607" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0421" trans="overlap">well I suppose if you've got a cat that walks on a lead but <pause dur="short"/> I don't usually you wouldn't wanna traumatise the cat like that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="609" who="S0423">okay so these are chalets</u>
<u n="610" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="611" who="S0423">right what's come up now?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0421">none of your properties matched our <trunc>sear</trunc> none</u>
<u n="613" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="614" who="S0421" trans="overlap">of our properties match your search please try again</u>
<u n="615" who="S0423">it had them earlier</u>
<u n="616" who="S0421">maybe they've gone <pause dur="short"/> someone's booked them check your search <pause dur="short"/> is that what you want?</u>
<u n="617" who="S0423">none of our properties match your search</u>
<u n="618" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="619" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well all I did was put in the date</u>
<u n="620" who="S0421">no you've put number of nights</u>
<u n="621" who="S0423" trans="overlap">no hang on what's that? it's the fifteenth of the sixth</u>
<u n="622" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="623" who="S0423">oh <pause dur="short"/> no I thought I put tenth of July yeah tenth try again number of nights seven two people <pause dur="long"/> oh there you are something's come up</u>
<u n="624" who="S0421">refine your search</u>
<u n="625" who="S0423">where is that?</u>
<u n="626" who="S0421" trans="overlap">what do you want?</u>
<u n="627" who="S0423">oh you put on these?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="629" who="S0423">well it doesn't really matter does it?</u>
<u n="630" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="631" who="S0423">just put I want a oh there we go</u>
<u n="632" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh there we go</u>
<u n="633" who="S0423">so erm <pause dur="short"/> put them in is there like a price order there can you see? cos there were some cheaper than that before</u>
<u n="634" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="635" who="S0423">can't see it can you?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no you can't do it</u>
<u n="637" who="S0423">must be cheapest first maybe the cheaper ones have gone <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit more than I like to pay oh no there's some for four there so</u>
<u n="638" who="S0421">electricity included</u>
<u n="639" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="640" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I'd be worried if it wasn't</u>
<u n="641" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well some of them have meters don't they?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0421">oh</u>
<u n="643" who="S0423">I mean people like</u>
<u n="644" who="S0421" trans="overlap">most of them say <vocal desc="laugh"/> electricity included</u>
<u n="645" who="S0423">and they're a bit dearer than I saw earlier and they oh here we are here's one three five six <pause dur="short"/> sleeps up to two <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="646" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="647" who="S0423">looks like a shed doesn't it? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="648" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="649" who="S0423">these other ones look alright but up to two is a bit worrying isn't it?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's weird yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> up to two? <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="651" who="S0423">oh these dates are not right are they?</u>
<u n="652" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like what that almost suggests that well it sleeps one but we can put another</u>
<u n="653" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that you could squeeze a second one in</u>
<u n="654" who="S0421" trans="overlap">bed in <vocal desc="laugh"/> it if you want <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="655" who="S0423">oh this is I think I was looking at this one basic two-bedroom chalet with sea sea glimpses <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="656" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's probably gonna be like <anon type="place"/>'s sand dunes and then it's gonna be like oh I can see the sea today oh can you? where? just over that hill a little bit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="657" who="S0423">so there that's that one it looks like it would be</u>
<u n="658" who="S0421">looks a bit grim like</u>
<u n="659" who="S0423">like <trunc>basi</trunc></u>
<u n="660" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like mm</u>
<u n="661" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it it's probably <trunc>n</trunc>near the beach so it's probably in a nice place</u>
<u n="662" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="663" who="S0423" trans="overlap">look inside it looks clean and</u>
<u n="664" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it looks like it's just been built out of a slab of <trunc>con</trunc>concrete though it's like just sat there on the landscape like mm</u>
<u n="665" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="short"/> some photos were taken were wide-angle angled lens that's to make it look bigger <vocal desc="laugh"/> probably</u>
<u n="666" who="S0421">no but it gets the whole room in as well though</u>
<u n="667" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well yeah it says</u>
<u n="668" who="S0421" trans="overlap">doesn't it?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0423" trans="overlap">to provide the best visual <pause dur="short"/> so that's like the lounge so it's</u>
<u n="670" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="671" who="S0423" trans="overlap">a tiny TV <pause dur="short"/> kitchen <pause dur="short"/> that'll be your room</u>
<u n="672" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="673" who="S0423">that'll be my room</u>
<u n="674" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="675" who="S0423">one double bedroom two single lounge with sofa</u>
<u n="676" who="S0421" trans="overlap">shower room with separate toilet</u>
<u n="677" who="S0423">shower room and separate toilet</u>
<u n="678" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="679" who="S0423">does that impress you does it?</u>
<u n="680" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no it's just strange cos we our shower's got a separate toilet now</u>
<u n="681" who="S0423">oh right so erm what do you think out of those two?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="683" who="S0423">do you <trunc>wa</trunc> you want to browse at all?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0421">I think that would be alright</u>
<u n="685" who="S0423">which one?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0421">I'm not <vocal desc="laugh"/> any of them I suppose <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0423">yeah I think once you start browsing I've been browsing for hours and hours and</u>
<u n="688" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="689" who="S0423" trans="overlap">this is what I've come up with cos you you can't especially I'm limited on what I'm spending</u>
<u n="690" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know but cos like if you don't look at the price you'll just be like oh look at that and it's like mm</u>
<u n="691" who="S0423" trans="overlap">oh yeah you can get some that are great they're like</u>
<u n="692" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="693" who="S0423">seven hundred pounds</u>
<u n="694" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="695" who="S0423" trans="overlap">a thousand pounds</u>
<u n="696" who="S0421">I suppose it's alright if there's lots of people going but</u>
<u n="697" who="S0423">mm well yeah you don't need it for a couple of us something big like that those kind of places</u>
<u n="698" who="S0421">email to a friend <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="699" who="S0423">so there's the beach and that this is the park <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="700" who="S0421">views over the</u>
<u n="701" who="S0423" trans="overlap">what? where?</u>
<u n="702" who="S0421" trans="overlap">estuary <pause dur="long"/> a bus stop fish and chips</u>
<u n="703" who="S0423">it doesn't tell you which is ours though</u>
<u n="704" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cricket pitch</u>
<u n="705" who="S0423" trans="overlap">or where it is does it on the map?</u>
<u n="706" who="S0421">no well does it give you a number when you look at it?</u>
<u n="707" who="S0423"><anon type="address"/></u>
<u n="708" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="709" who="S0423">alright hang on <pause dur="short"/> there's <anon type="address"/></u>
<u n="710" who="S0421">just a bit randomly put in aren't they?</u>
<u n="711" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="short"/> see if it was right close to the beach it wouldn't be too bad would it?</u>
<u n="712" who="S0421">I mean are we even gonna go on the beach though?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0423" trans="overlap">that's not so B is the red</u>
<u n="714" who="S0421">can't even see it <pause dur="long"/> it's not on there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="715" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="716" who="S0421">you'd think it would be on like near the edge cos er the sea views er well I dunno it says some <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="717" who="S0423" trans="overlap">sea glimpse</u>
<u n="718" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> sea glimpse</u>
<u n="719" who="S0423"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="720" who="S0421">like right on the other side no it's not there is it?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0423">hang on I'm zoomed in so there might be</u>
<u n="722" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> is that it there? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="723" who="S0423">oh there it is</u>
<u n="724" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="725" who="S0423">oh it's not the best <trunc>o</trunc> cos you're right opposite where they collect their keys and things like that</u>
<u n="726" who="S0421">where is it?</u>
<u n="727" who="S0423">there this one the orange one B no that's F</u>
<u n="728" who="S0421" trans="overlap">that's F</u>
<u n="729" who="S0423"><anon type="address"/> it's are you sure it's B? yeah</u>
<u n="730" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="731" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="732" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> caf <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="733" who="S0423">right <pause dur="short"/> so B should be all the red shouldn't it?</u>
<u n="734" who="S0421" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="735" who="S0423"><anon type="address"/></u>
<u n="736" who="S0421">maybe it's a new one so they've not got it on</u>
<u n="737" who="S0423">oh right maybe</u>
<u n="738" who="S0421">or they've just missed it off <pause dur="long"/> it's not there</u>
<u n="739" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="740" who="S0421">it's weird <pause dur="short"/> unless they've done it in a different colour but I don't know why they would</u>
<u n="741" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="742" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> of all the ones we're looking at they've not got it on</u>
<u n="743" who="S0423">so it doesn't really tell you much about the place does it though? <pause dur="long"/> so that's a little but you'd think there'd be pictures of it wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="745" who="S0423">I should have a look at Trip Advisor you'll probably get people's pictures there and</u>
<u n="746" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="747" who="S0423">what they think of it and</u>
<u n="748" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh it says recommended on Trip Advisor</u>
<u n="749" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="short"/> do you wanna have a look on there? and also look up that other one er there it is <anon type="place"/> park? er it might be worth looking at that one on Trip Advisor wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0421">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="751" who="S0423">not sure what time I put that pizza in now</u>
<u n="752" who="S0421">hopefully it doesn't burn</u>
<u n="753" who="S0423"><unclear>it won't be yet</unclear></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
