<text id="SMMK">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:27:03</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-10</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0058 S0179</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's car</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Making arrangements, football, cars, tennis, the Angel of the North, flats, parking</topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T03</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0058">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Corpus Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0179">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Harpenden, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years, 7 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Consultant engineer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0058">yep <pause dur="short"/> mm erm <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I mean we'll have a think about tonight <pause dur="short"/> I could text <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and see if she fancies meeting up for a quick drink</u>
<u n="2" who="S0179">well I was just thinking in terms of I think that you should also do what's gonna make you feel better <pause dur="short"/> rather than just your parents</u>
<u n="3" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0179">I don't want to</u>
<u n="5" who="S0058">I don't know in some ways I'm not sure I fancy making a colossal effort though <pause dur="short"/> cos especially if we're not gonna be finished the hospital till eight by the time we've you know we could go up to Northumberland <pause dur="short"/> by the time we got there it would be nine <pause dur="short"/> like you wouldn't be eating till ten at the earliest <pause dur="short"/> it's it's kind of a long time I think <pause dur="short"/> and I think I'd rather maybe just be simpler</u>
<u n="6" who="S0179">okay <pause dur="short"/> I mean we don't have to go somewhere that far <pause dur="short"/> we could go somewhere like you know <anon type="place"/> say <pause dur="short"/> half an hour</u>
<u n="7" who="S0058">could do <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't to be honest I don't really know <anon type="place"/> restaurants very well <pause dur="short"/> there isn't anywhere that jumps out in my head <pause dur="short"/> so anywhere to go</u>
<u n="8" who="S0179" trans="overlap">except Chiquitos</u>
<u n="9" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="10" who="S0179">we have been to Chiquitos in <anon type="place"/> haven't we?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0058">I don't think we have</u>
<u n="12" who="S0179">oh <pause dur="short"/> we've eaten there <trunc>one</trunc> oh no we haven't</u>
<u n="13" who="S0058">we've been to it <pause dur="short"/> as in we've been outside it <pause dur="short"/> but I think it was when we were out with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0179">but I thought we ate out there</u>
<u n="15" who="S0058">one time you had a kebab in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0179">yeah I remember that</u>
<u n="17" who="S0058">I don't remember eating at Chiquitos in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0179">okay never mind <pause dur="short"/> I'm making shit up again</u>
<u n="19" who="S0058">hmm mm <pause dur="short"/> which you should stop doing</u>
<u n="20" who="S0179">yes</u>
<u n="21" who="S0058">ha ha</u>
<u n="22" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> stay there</u>
<event desc="sound of car going over bump"/>
<u n="23" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I didn't know there was a match on today <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> The only time I know when there's a match on is if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at work at work mentions it</u>
<u n="24" who="S0179">so is er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> another <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0058">no no he's not <pause dur="short"/> he's an Arsenal supporter <pause dur="short"/> so erm yeah saw them when they played Arsenal recently and we beat them <pause dur="short"/> and apparently sort of innocently <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sent him an email on the Monday saying you had a nice weekend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? He said no I haven't <vocal desc="laugh"/> Oh sorry <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0179"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well tough luck <pause dur="short"/> stop confessing your happiness will be determined by your football results</u>
<u n="27" who="S0058">no you've heard that quote though erm some people say football is a matter of life and death <pause dur="short"/> that's just stupid <pause dur="short"/> it's far more important than that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Can't remember who said that <pause dur="short"/> it was some manager I think</u>
<u n="28" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> strange</u>
<u n="29" who="S0058">hmm mm <pause dur="short"/> strange but true</u>
<u n="30" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="31" who="S0058">no it's true as in someone said it</u>
<u n="32" who="S0179">oh right <pause dur="short"/> erm and I'm <unclear/> traffic  This is progress</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="33" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0179"><unclear/> these guys <pause dur="short"/> yeah obviously this way <pause dur="short"/> thank you for that</u>
<u n="35" who="S0058">ha ha</u>
<u n="36" who="S0179">mister signpost</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="37" who="S0058">yeah I said to me mam like she was like do you want me to chop up the chicken for you in advance? And I was like no no no we'll we'll sort it all out <pause dur="short"/> don't worry <pause dur="short"/> you know we that was the point we'll you know we'll do it <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> do you think I should just text <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and just see if she's cos she'll be here I think <pause dur="short"/> it's not like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> where it's very unlikely she'd actually be here</u>
<u n="38" who="S0179">yeah I mean just if you'd like to see her then it's an idea</u>
<u n="39" who="S0058">it might be nice</u>
<u n="40" who="S0179" trans="overlap">we could still eat with your parents and then go out</u>
<u n="41" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was thinking we could eat with my parents and then go out and see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>kind of nine or ten <pause dur="short"/> um we could see them in the town or <trunc>a</trunc></u>
<u n="42" who="S0179">well it's going to take us at least an hour to cook and eat</u>
<u n="43" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so yeah er so maybe ten we could see them just if she's not doing anything</u>
<u n="44" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0058">okay I'll I'll just give her a text her then <pause dur="short"/> cos that might be nice <pause dur="short"/> it'll be something different maybe</u>
<u n="46" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0058">and I haven't seen her for ages far too long <pause dur="short"/> I really should keep in better touch with her <pause dur="short"/> I've got better with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well that'll be nice</u>
<u n="48" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0058">ha and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know</u>
<u n="50" who="S0179" trans="overlap">oh yeah of course he'll be here won't he?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> probably unless he's gone up to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="52" who="S0179">what does that number plate say do you reckon?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0058">it's probably initials</u>
<u n="54" who="S0179">oh that's er</u>
<u n="55" who="S0058">impressive</u>
<u n="56" who="S0179">Bling</u>
<u n="57" who="S0058">very bling</u>
<u n="58" who="S0179">it looks quite good</u>
<u n="59" who="S0058">what was it?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0179">Aston Martin</u>
<u n="61" who="S0058">was it? I didn't see it <unclear/> I saw a big yellow sports car <pause dur="short"/> a very low yellow sports car</u>
<u n="62" who="S0179">can't quite believe you didn't recognise that</u>
<u n="63" who="S0058">I wasn't particularly looking</u>
<u n="64" who="S0179">so when I said look at that what were you doing?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0058">I just looked up and saw a yellow car go past <pause dur="short"/> didn't really have time to look at its badges and stuff</u>
<u n="66" who="S0179">the shape of it would have given you a clue</u>
<u n="67" who="S0058">it that's that's not obvious to me <pause dur="short"/> I don't know anything about cars</u>
<u n="68" who="S0179">what's in front of us?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0058">jaguar <pause dur="short"/> I've seen the badge <pause dur="short"/> ha <pause dur="long"/> Fancy bus stop <pause dur="short"/> it had an electronic display thing <pause dur="short"/> like a</u>
<u n="70" who="S0179">had a mini me inside it</u>
<u n="71" who="S0058">ha ha</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="72" who="S0058">yeah it might be nice actually cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s very cheery <pause dur="short"/> we can have a gossip</u>
<u n="73" who="S0179">oh dear</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="74" who="S0179">huh <pause dur="short"/> so is this  itself?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0058">er yes it is <pause dur="short"/> not nothing particularly exciting but erm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0179">I was going to say something it's sort of like being stuck in the middle of nowhere</u>
<u n="77" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> there's an interesting little row of erm miner's cottages <pause dur="short"/> in fact all these are miner's cottages but there's a little sort of quite preserved sort of row of them I think</u>
<u n="78" who="S0179" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0058">oh maybe no it's not here <pause dur="short"/> erm but yeah because the pit was <unclear/> country park</u>
<u n="80" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> when did that shut?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0058">awf <pause dur="short"/> not not recently <pause dur="short"/> erm I think</u>
<u n="82" who="S0179">can I have the ball park? Was it sort of last century? Obviously last century but</u>
<u n="83" who="S0058">erm I'm not positive and I don't  I don't  know if that was already shut by the eighties or whether it shut in the eighties</u>
<u n="84" who="S0179">oh with Thatcher right <pause dur="short"/> I see what you mean</u>
<u n="85" who="S0058">yeah I don't know if it was one of the pit closures or whether it had already gone by then <pause dur="short"/> erm interesting to find out actually</u>
<u n="86" who="S0179">yes that was good <pause dur="long"/> It's got cloudy</u>
<u n="87" who="S0058">yeah it has <pause dur="short"/> it's not quite as nice as it was before <pause dur="short"/> still we're gonna be indoors so it's not so big a deal but <pause dur="short"/> still it was a lovely morning</u>
<u n="88" who="S0179">yes it was rather</u>
<u n="89" who="S0058">weather wise and activity wise</u>
<u n="90" who="S0179">if by activity you mean lying in yes</u>
<u n="91" who="S0058">ha ha <pause dur="long"/> Cool yep that's sent <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0179">yes indeed</u>
<u n="93" who="S0058">hmm <pause dur="short"/> I never noticed the name of this before <pause dur="short"/> wapping bridge <pause dur="short"/> ha <pause dur="short"/> wapping as in the place in London not as in whopping great big</u>
<u n="94" who="S0179">ah <pause dur="short"/> what's the spelling difference? I wasn't aware there was one</u>
<u n="95" who="S0058">yeah Wapping as in the place is W A P P I N G</u>
<u n="96" who="S0179" trans="overlap">look at all this art</u>
<u n="97" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0179">shall we go and have a look there later</u>
<u n="99" who="S0058">ha ha</u>
<u n="100" who="S0179">shits and giggles</u>
<u n="101" who="S0058">could do <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0179">I was being serious</u>
<u n="103" who="S0058">what <unclear/> today?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0058">well it'll be shut when we get back</u>
<u n="106" who="S0179">oh okay fine</u>
<u n="107" who="S0058">I imagine <pause dur="short"/> these places normally shut at five <pause dur="short"/> and if we go there now we will not get</u>
<u n="108" who="S0179">yeah sure</u>
<u n="109" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> though sometime yeah we definitely should</u>
<u n="110" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah but whopping as in big is W H O P P</u>
<u n="112" who="S0179">and how was that spelt?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0058">W A P P <pause dur="short"/> wapping</u>
<u n="114" who="S0179">oh so Wapping not whopping</u>
<u n="115" who="S0058">but but Wapping in London is pronounced whopping</u>
<u n="116" who="S0179">mm <unclear/> Londoners</u>
<u n="117" who="S0058">ha ha</u>
<u n="118" who="S0179">lawn tennis and football club</u>
<u n="119" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0179">cricket <pause dur="short"/> lawn tennis and football <pause dur="short"/> wow</u>
<u n="121" who="S0058">hmm mm <pause dur="short"/> sport's club basically</u>
<u n="122" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> specifically English sports</u>
<u n="123" who="S0058">hmm mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0179">what's the difference between lawn tennis and tennis?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0058">I imagine lawn tennis you play on the grass <pause dur="short"/> whereas tennis is presumably varying surfaces <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it's different to <unclear/> have different surfaces don't they?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0058">so there's like asphalt type</u>
<u n="128" who="S0179">asphalt</u>
<u n="129" who="S0058">and then sort of is Wimbledon on grass or not?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0179">think about that</u>
<u n="131" who="S0058">I am I <pause dur="short"/> no it's not is it?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0179">course it is</u>
<u n="133" who="S0058">is it? That's the thing I genuinely don't know</u>
<u n="134" who="S0179">can you not bring back to bring back from when you've seen it on television it's on green shit</u>
<u n="135" who="S0058">yeah but it could have been any kind of green shit</u>
<u n="136" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="137" who="S0058" trans="overlap">it's so well tended <pause dur="short"/> ha it hasn't got the sort of gnarly bits that normally lawns have</u>
<u n="138" who="S0179" trans="overlap">it has by the end</u>
<u n="139" who="S0058">oh <pause dur="short"/> true yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay fair enough</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="140" who="S0058">and yeah cos that's why some tennis players don't do so well in is it the big American competition where it's on a hard surface?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0179">the American Open</u>
<u n="142" who="S0058">yeah and they don't do so well in that because of the surface</u>
<u n="143" who="S0179">no I don't know <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> no one really knows or cares how Andy Murray is doing</u>
<u n="144" who="S0058">no</u>
<u n="145" who="S0179"><unclear/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0058">it's interesting isn't it? Well I think people are interested but they don't actually want him particularly to win</u>
<u n="147" who="S0179">no it's not that <pause dur="short"/> I mean they probably wouldn't wanna be pleased if he did <pause dur="short"/> they don't care particularly</u>
<u n="148" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yeah but <pause dur="short"/> but there'd be more a kind of oh England's won rather than oh that nice chap</u>
<u n="149" who="S0179">well he's too good</u>
<u n="150" who="S0058">well yeah he is</u>
<u n="151" who="S0179">and he's not particularly nice</u>
<u n="152" who="S0058">he's not very nice <pause dur="short"/> I think if he was slightly less good and slightly nicer everyone would be obsessed with him again like Kevin but <pause dur="short"/> no I agree it's because he's just that little bit miserable and a little bit serious about it all and just <trunc>given</trunc> doesn't give the impression that he'd be any er nice then he you know be any good to talk to or you know <pause dur="short"/> and yeah and he's a little bit too good <pause dur="short"/> he actually has a reasonable um</u>
<u n="153" who="S0179">Chance</u>
<u n="154" who="S0058">chance <pause dur="short"/> he's not really an underdog character</u>
<u n="155" who="S0179">yeah it was him or was it <unclear/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0058">exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah River was obsessed with him but ha</u>
<u n="157" who="S0179">he got to the semi finals once or twice and the quarter finals quite a lot</u>
<u n="158" who="S0058">yeah he was sort of <trunc>qui</trunc> quite a regular quarter finals person I think <pause dur="short"/> which is you know it's not bad <pause dur="short"/> it's not <pause dur="short"/> but he was just not quite so if he would it would have been a really big thing <pause dur="short"/> and I think why all the people were rooting for him <pause dur="short"/> you know a guy comes slightly from beneath to win ha <pause dur="short"/> you feel like he's worked for it ha <pause dur="short"/> you don't like anyone to get anything for you know anything too easily</u>
<u n="159" who="S0179">ah <pause dur="short"/> so I did like Sampras</u>
<u n="160" who="S0058">I don't remember ever really I didn't really watch much tennis <pause dur="short"/> I knew of Henman but I didn't really sort of notice Peter Sampras</u>
<u n="161" who="S0179">well Peter Sampras was sort of <pause dur="short"/> when I started to watch tennis he was sort of a <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? I think he still the record for the number of Wimbledon titles</u>
<u n="162" who="S0058">oh right <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0179">erm he's sort of yeah probably one of the best of world players the world's ever seen</u>
<u n="164" who="S0058">what nationality?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0179">american</u>
<u n="166" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0179">erm but it was just and he was a nice guy</u>
<u n="168" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0179">and the interesting thing was that he and like his <pause dur="short"/> what are they called? Federer and <pause dur="short"/> what's the other one called?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0058">Nadal</u>
<u n="171" who="S0179">yeah just I mean Federer seems quite nice but Nadal doesn't</u>
<u n="172" who="S0058">Nadal is the grumpy one?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0179">and Federer seems fine</u>
<u n="176" who="S0058">ha ha as sportsmen go</u>
<u n="177" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0058">that sign is wobbling really <pause dur="short"/> or is it wobbled funnily there <pause dur="short"/> stay away from that</u>
<u n="179" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> but erm yeah but the interesting thing with Sampras is that he and him were in fact er were quite good friends <pause dur="short"/> and they used to train together a lot</u>
<u n="180" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> ah interesting <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if that's a good thing or a bad thing in terms of kind of you get to know your opponent and how they work</u>
<u n="181" who="S0179">well he had actually I think he'd put Henman out of the semi-finals on one occasion</u>
<u n="182" who="S0058">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0179">er which was a bit sort of oh <pause dur="short"/> but he had a pretty good game against him</u>
<u n="184" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> was it yeah I don't know about whether professionally it's a really good idea to sort of find out where the weak spots are <pause dur="short"/> whether professionally it's a bad idea</u>
<u n="185" who="S0179" trans="overlap">yeah but the point is they were both nice people</u>
<u n="186" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0179">that's kind of what I was going for</u>
<u n="188" who="S0058">yeah they're doing it to bond and make friends and ha</u>
<u n="189" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0058">play tennis with people they like <pause dur="short"/> ha <pause dur="short"/> rather than in it purely to win Wimbledon which I think is what Andy Murray's in <pause dur="short"/> well he he's in it to win <pause dur="short"/> and I'm just not <pause dur="short"/> I I don't really get the impression that he'd be interested in bonding ha</u>
<u n="191" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0058">maybe he's fine <pause dur="short"/> maybe he just comes across badly every single time he's televised</u>
<u n="193" who="S0179">well I don't know if you you can tell a certain amount from the amount of times people argue something with the umpire</u>
<u n="194" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0179">as in he does it quite a bit</u>
<u n="196" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0179">and Henman virtually never did it</u>
<u n="198" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no yeah exactly it shows a certain kind of arrogance I think</u>
<u n="199" who="S0179">I think well yeah but even not <unclear/> it's like well you can just accept oh well that's really <unclear/> It's it might not be fair but I'm just gonna live with it</u>
<u n="200" who="S0058">yeah I'm just gonna get it on with it <pause dur="short"/> exactly <pause dur="short"/> well it's like in football you know you'll often get one guy from the you know from the team going to the ref and saying ref it was a stupid decision <pause dur="short"/> and the captain goes just just leave it <pause dur="short"/> don't worry about it you know <pause dur="short"/> if it's not that big a deal they'll say look just get on with it <pause dur="short"/> don't argue <pause dur="short"/> you know you'll cause yourself more problems</u>
<u n="201" who="S0179">indeed <pause dur="long"/> I can see you've got all these to please me</u>
<u n="202" who="S0058">what Henman?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0179">henman and Sampras <unclear/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's nice <pause dur="short"/> ha ha <pause dur="short"/> I like a nice sports person <pause dur="short"/> that's why I've always loved Lineker and he wasn't an outstanding player <pause dur="short"/> but he was nice and he never got booked</u>
<u n="205" who="S0179" trans="overlap">I think he was just a very good solid player</u>
<u n="206" who="S0058">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> he was</u>
<u n="207" who="S0179">A bit like Beckham really</u>
<u n="208" who="S0058">ah but Beckham was outstanding though <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if he is</u>
<u n="209" who="S0179">was?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0058">I don't know if he is really now <pause dur="short"/> erm but er I think he was special in a way Lineker never really was</u>
<u n="211" who="S0179">hang on <pause dur="short"/> but what was he actually good at?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0058">beckham?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0058">striker</u>
<u n="215" who="S0179">oh I thought he was a midfield</u>
<u n="216" who="S0058">no striker <pause dur="short"/> captain I think</u>
<u n="217" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0058">but erm he scored a lot did Beckham <pause dur="short"/> and I think he was just yeah a a bit of a special player and entertaining to watch and stuff <pause dur="short"/> erm whereas I think Lineker was just yeah very solid <trunc>very</trunc> played by the rules kind of footballer</u>
<u n="219" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0058">and I think sometimes in football there's a very fine line between something being a really really good move and something just being a foul <pause dur="short"/> so a lot of players you know you'd go for it <pause dur="short"/> you know? And if you get it wrong you're booked <pause dur="short"/> and if you get it right it's an extremely good move you know and you have a go at it</u>
<u n="221" who="S0179">yeah indeed</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="222" who="S0179">forty <pause dur="short"/> oh Jesus</u>
<u n="223" who="S0058">is that what it was last time? I can't remember</u>
<u n="224" who="S0179">no</u>
<u n="225" who="S0058">oh</u>
<u n="226" who="S0179">I vaguely understand it being fifty but forty is pushing it</u>
<event desc="sound of car going over bump"/>
<u n="227" who="S0179">just drop down</u>
<u n="228" who="S0058">well you'd think the Angel of the North would make people drive a little slower anyway <pause dur="short"/> like Stonehenge <pause dur="short"/> it is quite a big landmark <pause dur="short"/> I never really thought about it just cos it's just there but</u>
<u n="229" who="S0179">why are we in a forty? For the love of God</u>
<u n="230" who="S0058">Cos there's some cones by the side of the road look <pause dur="short"/> impeding progress there</u>
<u n="231" who="S0179">oh</u>
<u n="232" who="S0058">ha ha</u>
<u n="233" who="S0179">I'm sorry I am just gonna treat that as optional <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0058">what because it's so stupid?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0179">well because the traffic's flowing</u>
<u n="236" who="S0058">yeah at this speed</u>
<u n="237" who="S0179" trans="overlap">we would actually be impeding traffic flow if we were doing forty</u>
<u n="238" who="S0058">no I know</u>
<u n="239" who="S0179">there's no reason not to <pause dur="short"/> there's no significant hazards <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> that was interesting</u>
<u n="240" who="S0058">what is?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0179">well there's <trunc>like</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> it's not that big</u>
<u n="242" who="S0058">no it's not <pause dur="short"/> well you see the people at the bottom <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty big</u>
<u n="243" who="S0179">mm <pause dur="short"/> remind me why it was built again</u>
<u n="244" who="S0058">just art</u>
<u n="245" who="S0179">no was it like a millennium thing?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0058">erm I think it was about the millennium <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it was specifically for that</u>
<u n="247" who="S0179">you didn't see it before that?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0058">no <pause dur="short"/> I think it was just er <trunc>ju</trunc> you know they wanted a bit of art so they got Antony Gormley on the case</u>
<u n="249" who="S0179">fair enough</u>
<u n="250" who="S0058">it it's quite good <pause dur="short"/> I I quite like it <pause dur="short"/> I think a lot of people at the time were like God you know ugly ridiculous bit of metal <pause dur="short"/> rusty and horrible <pause dur="short"/> you know looks like a plane has crashed in the side you know <pause dur="short"/> and people didn't really like it but I think people have grown to to like it a bit more <pause dur="short"/> it was very different I think and really unusual <pause dur="short"/> there's nothing else looks like that anywhere <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="251" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="252" who="S0058">but I like it <pause dur="short"/> I liked it at the time <pause dur="short"/> I thought it was very statuesque and you know proud looking</u>
<u n="253" who="S0179">yes okay</u>
<u n="254" who="S0058">and it's become so iconic that I I don't think people really think about it anymore <pause dur="short"/> whereas at the time cos it was so new it was like whoa ha <pause dur="short"/> I remember one time they were trying to decide what colour to paint the bridge in Sunderland <pause dur="short"/> you know it was green?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0058">I think it still is green <pause dur="short"/> but they had a little sort of poll on the front of the Echo <pause dur="short"/> so like four different colours <pause dur="short"/> so they had like a black one a green one er whatever you know something else <pause dur="short"/> and then this bright red one <pause dur="short"/> ha and everyone was like the bright red one <pause dur="short"/> next to the <unclear/> it was brilliant <pause dur="short"/> er no</u>
<u n="257" who="S0179">can you not stripe it?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0058">yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> that's what everyone wanted ha <pause dur="short"/> I say everyone <pause dur="short"/> that's what the Echo readers wanted</u>
<u n="259" who="S0179">oh good <pause dur="short"/> we're actually now back into an official fifty <pause dur="short"/> what that just <trunc>was</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> they'd just put signs up the side of the road</u>
<u n="260" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0179">the only noticeable difference <pause dur="short"/> that and a few cones</u>
<u n="262" who="S0058">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ha the cones that weren't on the road or even near the road</u>
<u n="263" who="S0179">indeed</u>
<u n="264" who="S0058">never mind <pause dur="short"/> it's all finished now <pause dur="short"/> ha ha until the way back</u>
<u n="265" who="S0179">so it should be sixty</u>
<u n="266" who="S0058">huh?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0179">it's slightly deceiving</u>
<u n="268" who="S0058">I've seen quite a few of those today?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0179">now it's sixty <pause dur="short"/> there's one ahead</u>
<u n="270" who="S0058">is there?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0179">that car but one</u>
<u n="272" who="S0058">oh okay</u>
<u n="273" who="S0179">it's a it's either I think it says eighty <pause dur="short"/> it could possibly be marked to a sixty but adapted</u>
<u n="274" who="S0058">uh-huh</u>
<u n="275" who="S0179">it's like Top Gear's drivers of different cars last time</u>
<u n="276" who="S0058">ha ha yeah <pause dur="short"/> ha ha <pause dur="short"/> what was the guy who faced backwards? <vocal desc="laugh"/> Peugeot was it? Ha ha <pause dur="short"/> what or was it the woman driving? Um I can't remember</u>
<u n="277" who="S0179">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0058">ha he drives a bike ha</u>
<u n="279" who="S0179">why <unclear/> in sixty <pause dur="short"/> not sure it's marked to a sixty <pause dur="short"/> just can you check this when we get closer?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0058">ha okay</u>
<u n="281" who="S0179">we're going a little bit faster then</u>
<u n="282" who="S0058">it looks like it says eighty</u>
<u n="283" who="S0179">oh it is an says eighty <pause dur="short"/> so you can see all the part?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0058">yeah it's eighty</u>
<u n="285" who="S0179">okay</u>
<u n="286" who="S0058">there you are</u>
<u n="287" who="S0179">I'm sorry</u>
<u n="288" who="S0058">two point five T <pause dur="short"/> what does the T stand for?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0179">turbo</u>
<u n="290" who="S0058">ah <pause dur="short"/> you know that Turbo aftershave <pause dur="short"/> what was the other thing? Turbo sunglasses <pause dur="short"/> ha</u>
<u n="291" who="S0179">kind of Ebox going the other way <pause dur="short"/> it's pretty smart you know</u>
<u n="292" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna have to do a little more to convince me</u>
<u n="293" who="S0179">it's not that big <pause dur="short"/> see my injunction to Range Rover's is that they're huge</u>
<u n="294" who="S0058">it's quite ugly but it's</u>
<u n="295" who="S0179">I think it's ugly in a charming way</u>
<u n="296" who="S0058">ha ha <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0179">yeah is it? It's not the next left is it? It's after that</u>
<u n="298" who="S0058">um yeah it is after that yeah <pause dur="short"/> handy little sign there <pause dur="short"/> metrocentre straight on</u>
<u n="299" who="S0179">is that a new building they're putting up?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0058">looks like it doesn't it? Flats presumably</u>
<u n="301" who="S0179">it's like when you want to put them up a lot of them are pulling down</u>
<u n="302" who="S0058">yes</u>
<u n="303" who="S0179">which around here I'd have thought it was more likely to be the latter but</u>
<u n="304" who="S0058">it could <pause dur="short"/> it's hard to know actually</u>
<u n="305" who="S0179">well you think they'd demolish them with explosives <pause dur="short"/> that's what they'd normally do</u>
<u n="306" who="S0058">unless there's too much stuff around it too close to it</u>
<u n="307" who="S0179">mm you'd be surprised what you can do</u>
<u n="308" who="S0058">mm <pause dur="short"/> it does seem odd <trunc>dimans</trunc> dismantling it brick by brick <pause dur="short"/> I mean it seems a bit of a waste of time</u>
<u n="309" who="S0179">mm maybe</u>
<u n="310" who="S0058"><trunc>J</trunc> which looks cos cos they're sort of very yeah <pause dur="short"/> it looks like they're doing it <trunc>s</trunc> slowly <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? Do you think they're putting it up? They might be building flats <pause dur="short"/> it just seems like a bit old fashioned block of flats <pause dur="short"/> they don't really build like that now</u>
<u n="311" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="312" who="S0058">do you know what I mean? They build sort of slightly lower wider</u>
<u n="313" who="S0179">well the structure  should still be the same regards of the time</u>
<u n="314" who="S0058">no it it just seems like an a kind of an unusual thing to be building <pause dur="short"/> I haven't seen many blocks of flats like that being built</u>
<u n="315" who="S0179">excuse me</u>
<u n="316" who="S0058">Excused</u>
<u n="317" who="S0179">excuse me</u>
<u n="318" who="S0058">Excused</u>
<u n="319" who="S0179">excuse me</u>
<u n="320" who="S0058">ha ha <pause dur="short"/> how long can I keep excusing you? As long as it takes</u>
<u n="321" who="S0179">er</u>
<u n="322" who="S0058">so where do you wanna try parking?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0179">has that hit you yet?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0058">yes it has <pause dur="short"/> thank you <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Look at the joy <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0179">I didn't think it had</u>
<u n="326" who="S0058">I thought it had <pause dur="short"/> oof</u>
<u n="327" who="S0179"><vocal desc="laugh"/> This is going to go down very well on the tape</u>
<u n="328" who="S0058">ha <pause dur="short"/> anyway where do you wanna try parking?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0179">erm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0058">shall we just?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0179">it's okay <pause dur="short"/> I've got that figured</u>
<u n="332" who="S0058">cool</u>
<u n="333" who="S0179">actually have I? I might not have <pause dur="short"/> actually I've just changed my mind</u>
<u n="334" who="S0058">okay <pause dur="short"/> do you have it figured now?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0179">yeah cos before I was gonna park as close to M and S as possible but if we're gonna walk along the entire length anyway it doesn't make a difference <pause dur="short"/> unless we just park closer to the motorway junction</u>
<u n="336" who="S0058" trans="overlap">if you're gonna go to M and S and the Apple Store then it doesn't make much difference</u>
<u n="337" who="S0179">right</u>
<u n="338" who="S0058">so if we erm <pause dur="short"/> we could see what time Marks' is is open till in the evening</u>
<u n="339" who="S0179" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> use both lanes <pause dur="short"/> he's going left and that does seems to be in</u>
<u n="340" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0179">because I want to go immediately left <pause dur="short"/> I'll just get over</u>
<u n="342" who="S0058"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I remember once <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dad drove us here and we ended up sitting in the hashed bit <pause dur="short"/> it was like oh my God <pause dur="short"/> ha</u>
<u n="343" who="S0179">oh dear</u>
<u n="344" who="S0058">yeah it's really bad <pause dur="short"/> I was panicking</u>
<u n="345" who="S0179">who was?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0058">I was panicking quietly in the back</u>
<u n="347" who="S0179">why?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0058">sitting in the middle of the Hash <pause dur="short"/> it was embarrassing</u>
<u n="349" who="S0179">but you were in a Range Rover or something weren't you?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0058">no we were in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s little MG</u>
<u n="351" who="S0179">oh yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0058">I say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it was her mam's little MG <pause dur="short"/> I was just sweating <vocal desc="laugh"/> in embarrassment and fear <pause dur="long"/> Not the most illustrious place to build a Mariott Hotel here</u>
<u n="353" who="S0179">where?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0058">to the left</u>
<u n="355" who="S0179">ah <pause dur="short"/> no not really</u>
<u n="356" who="S0058">ha <pause dur="short"/> retail park <pause dur="short"/> still I guess if you want a really good shopping experience and you live in the sticks <pause dur="short"/> then you come out here and you book your Mariott <pause dur="short"/> you go to the Metrocentre <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> bob's your uncle <pause dur="short"/> fanny's your aunt</u>
<u n="357" who="S0179" trans="overlap">er <pause dur="short"/> oh that's the hotel</u>
<u n="358" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0179">oh no there's probably worse places</u>
<u n="360" who="S0058">yeah and I guess you you know if you wanna go to Newcastle you wanna stay somewhere rubbish <pause dur="short"/> ha you know? <anon type="place"/> good enough <pause dur="short"/> I was thinking that <anon type="place"/> itself is has got some really nice stuff</u>
<u n="361" who="S0179" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Actually no <pause dur="short"/> actually yes</u>
<u n="362" who="S0058">you can go in the red at the next left yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0179">I know I know</u>
<u n="364" who="S0058">it's very confusing round here</u>
<u n="365" who="S0179">it is confusing</u>
<u n="366" who="S0058">it's really badly er</u>
<u n="367" who="S0179">as in I've got lost on a number of occasions</u>
<u n="368" who="S0058">it's badly signposted</u>
<u n="369" who="S0179">well when I say lost</u>
<u n="370" who="S0058">ha <pause dur="short"/> I'm not entirely sure at a given moment exactly what to do next <pause dur="short"/> ha probably</u>
<u n="371" who="S0179">no no <pause dur="short"/> more to the point not being able to not managing to make it to where I was planning on making it</u>
<u n="372" who="S0058">oh right <pause dur="short"/> you've got it you've made it to somewhere and you knew where you were</u>
<u n="373" who="S0179">are we  Are we  planning to going straight on? Right</u>
<u n="374" who="S0058">I think she was planning on taking her time</u>
<u n="375" who="S0179">yes <pause dur="short"/> ah there's a couple down there but ah they might be disabled</u>
<u n="376" who="S0058">all my favourite places are round here so I'm trying to</u>
<u n="377" who="S0179">mm</u>
<u n="378" who="S0058">hopefully it's not going to be too busy <pause dur="short"/> see everyone's flood now which is gonna be great</u>
<u n="379" who="S0179">yeah there'll be some spaces <pause dur="short"/> this is my favourite bit cos it's a bit separate</u>
<u n="380" who="S0058">yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0179">not sure those dungarees a good look</u>
<u n="382" who="S0058">hmm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="383" who="S0179">yep <pause dur="short"/> thank you</u>
<u n="384" who="S0058">or that very very see-through T-shirt</u>
<u n="385" who="S0179">what?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0058">yeah there's loads along here</u>
<u n="387" who="S0179">I didn't notice the T-shirt <pause dur="short"/> I was trying to avoid hitting them</u>
<u n="388" who="S0058">the the the friend yeah the friend of the girl in the dungarees</u>
<u n="389" who="S0179">ooh there's ones up there actually</u>
<u n="390" who="S0058">there's loads <pause dur="short"/> ha that's it <pause dur="short"/> far corner <pause dur="short"/> truly you are your father's son</u>
<u n="391" who="S0179">well you're might as well if you can</u>
<u n="392" who="S0058">hmm mm</u>
<u n="393" who="S0179">as in this we wouldn't have to be in <unclear/> space <pause dur="short"/> yep</u>
<event desc="sound of car door opening"/>
<u n="394" who="S0179">that'll do</u>
<u n="395" who="S0058" trans="overlap">yep <pause dur="short"/> cool</u>
</body>
</text>
