<text id="SMRU">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:18:58</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-10-02</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0426 S0427</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Office at work</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Colleagues</relationships>
		<topics>Rugby Payers, Rugby World cup, Wales Rugby, football partnership</topics>
		<activity>Rugby</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, Explaining, Inquiring, complaining, advising, announcing, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T06</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0426">
				<exactage>60</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cairo</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Egypt</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Nottingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>17 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Professor</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0427">
				<exactage>64</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>Welsh</nat>
				<birthplace>Tredegar</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Wales</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Wales and England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South Walian</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Loughborough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>40+</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>wales</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>wales</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>wales</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Italian -- level unspecified; French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified; Some Welsh -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0426">talking of Uruguay</u>
<u n="2" who="S0427">yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0426">you know I go the erm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> the gym?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0427">oh I used to be a member there I didn't know that you were a member no</u>
<u n="5" who="S0426">yeah oh yes yes</u>
<u n="6" who="S0427">oh right okay</u>
<u n="7" who="S0426">and the other day I went in and I looked at the pool you know you can see the pool in from the reception?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0427">yes yes</u>
<u n="9" who="S0426">and you couldn't see the water</u>
<u n="10" who="S0427">why not?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0426">cos huge guys in there I mean they were triangular these blokes</u>
<u n="12" who="S0427">oh right</u>
<u n="13" who="S0426">enormous blokes</u>
<u n="14" who="S0427">right</u>
<u n="15" who="S0426">and I came into the we were all taking showers so I thought what language are they speaking?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0427">and?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0426">and I thought this it's kind of Latinish</u>
<u n="18" who="S0427" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0426">you know Latin? <unclear>I thought</unclear> are they Romanian? but they came out and heard a bit more and they were speaking <trunc>Span</trunc> er Latin American Spanish and I worked out that they were two Uruguayans and they were rugby people but the fact it turns out that they're not the main Uruguayan rugby they're the under twenty-ones</u>
<u n="20" who="S0427">oh and they're over here touring as well are they?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0426" trans="overlap">that's right that's right</u>
<u n="22" who="S0427">well well well</u>
<u n="23" who="S0426" trans="overlap">they must have a there must be a corresponding</u>
<u n="24" who="S0427" trans="overlap">yes there could well be erm <pause dur="short"/> because Uruguay's population is tiny it's like Wales' you know it's only three million or something like that I mean the fact that they won the World Cup at football twice</u>
<u n="25" who="S0426"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0427">I mean I know it was before the war and everything but</u>
<u n="27" who="S0426" trans="overlap">yes but none the less</u>
<u n="28" who="S0427">to won it twice and to have won it in Brazil as well bet there're still elderly Brazilians who remember that date</u>
<u n="29" who="S0426" trans="overlap">oh yes <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's right the poor goalkeeper</u>
<u n="30" who="S0427">mm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0426">alright so the er <pause dur="short"/> the way groups are and the way the points are awarded</u>
<u n="32" who="S0427">mm still everything to play for</u>
<u n="33" who="S0426">what would Wales need to do to just need to beat Australia?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0427">if we beat Australia it doesn't matter what England do because we would've won every game <pause dur="short"/> but if Australia beat England <pause dur="short"/> england can't qualify as as I remember rightly</u>
<u n="35" who="S0426">is this</u>
<u n="36" who="S0427">they only have one game left they can't possibly get as many points then as Wales</u>
<u n="37" who="S0426">is it the case that Wales have only got one game but England have got two games left?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0427">yes England have got to play Australia on Saturday not not tomorrow no sorry it is tomorrow it is tomorrow and then they have to play another game <trunc>I</trunc>I think that must be Uruguay</u>
<u n="39" who="S0426">uhu</u>
<u n="40" who="S0427">I don't think they've played Uruguay so it must be Uruguay I think erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0426" trans="overlap">one two three four five</u>
<u n="42" who="S0427" trans="overlap">it's four games they have to play</u>
<u n="43" who="S0426">so four games five <unclear/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0427" trans="overlap">it's five in a group <pause dur="short"/> so who's in it? Wales Australia England Uruguay and Fiji</u>
<u n="45" who="S0426" trans="overlap">Fiji</u>
<u n="46" who="S0427">okay well</u>
<u n="47" who="S0426">I suppose there's no chance of getting er ticket for either the Australia game or the er semi-final if they get through is it <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0427" trans="overlap">quarter-final</u>
<u n="49" who="S0426" trans="overlap">quarter-final</u>
<u n="50" who="S0427">would be after this erm no I don't even know where the erm <trunc>th</trunc> Wales Wales Australia is at Twickenham that that'll be sold out I don't even know where the quarter-final if if it if Wales get to is being played</u>
<u n="51" who="S0426">were it to be at the Millennium does your debenture help you at all?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0427">no no this is run by an entirely different <trunc>com</trunc>company erm if it were under the <pause dur="short"/> if Wales were running the World Cup and we were the host nation then I think</u>
<u n="53" who="S0426" trans="overlap">oh because we're not the host nation</u>
<u n="54" who="S0427">then I think tickets would go to debenture ticket holders on a first on a first choice basis</u>
<u n="55" who="S0426" trans="overlap">right right <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="56" who="S0427">but although perhaps unfairly Wales have had <pause dur="short"/> two games in the Millennium Stadium <pause dur="short"/> when</u>
<u n="57" who="S0426" trans="overlap">even though they're not co-hosts</u>
<u n="58" who="S0427">no they're not co-hosts er well</u>
<u n="59" who="S0426" trans="overlap">that is unfair then isn't it?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0427">well I totally I think I know what the answer is England wanted the World Cup and they need to garner support</u>
<u n="61" who="S0426">oh so okay <pause dur="short"/> so this'll <unclear/> both from</u>
<u n="62" who="S0427" trans="overlap">so I think this was done this this was done a deal well we'll vote for you to have the World Cup</u>
<u n="63" who="S0426"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0427">but obviously we'll want a few games played at the Millennium</u>
<u n="65" who="S0426" trans="overlap">sure sure</u>
<u n="66" who="S0427">now Wales wanted to play Australia at the Millennium</u>
<u n="67" who="S0426">right</u>
<u n="68" who="S0427">but er the English organisers wouldn't have that</u>
<u n="69" who="S0426">okay</u>
<u n="70" who="S0427">in fact er Gatland the Welsh manager actually teased the English and said</u>
<u n="71" who="S0426" trans="overlap">ah right right</u>
<u n="72" who="S0427">if you think you're so good why don't you come and play us at the Millennium Stadium?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0426" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah yeah right right</u>
<u n="74" who="S0427">and they wouldn't it would have been naive to have gone for that bait <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0426"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes quite <pause dur="short"/> yes that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0427" trans="overlap">so no</u>
<u n="77" who="S0426">it's a loss even though they played at Twickenham <unclear/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0427">well yes but I wouldn't want to play that game again because I</u>
<u n="79" who="S0426" trans="overlap">it was pretty nip and tuck</u>
<u n="80" who="S0427">yeah and erm I think there is a sense in which probably England lost it more so than Wales won it</u>
<u n="81" who="S0426" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> well certainly at the end when they did that but then you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0427" trans="overlap">yeah I like I thought it was a courageous thing to do and and he'd be a national hero if if it had come off</u>
<u n="83" who="S0426" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <unclear/> as well</u>
<u n="84" who="S0427" trans="overlap">I think I think the really big mistake was throwing to the front of the line-out which means you're only five yards from the touchline the Welsh forwards just piled in and drove them over then and then it was a throw-in to Wales play out time game won you know? <pause dur="short"/> but the this Saturday tomorrow</u>
<u n="85" who="S0426" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0427">England can't afford to lose they're out I think if they lose tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> and I should be praying to a god</u>
<u n="87" who="S0426"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0427">to a god I don't believe in</u>
<u n="89" who="S0426"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0427">I shall be singing</u>
<u n="91" who="S0426" trans="overlap">well temporarily you might believe just for the sake of</u>
<u n="92" who="S0427" trans="overlap">singing singing in the praises of the Australians yeah? <pause dur="short"/> and erm I shall be <trunc>g</trunc> you know getting all the voodoo stuff all the</u>
<u n="93" who="S0426" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="94" who="S0427">anything anything that'll get</u>
<u n="95" who="S0426" trans="overlap">that's right</u>
<u n="96" who="S0427">you know the er the right result</u>
<u n="97" who="S0426" trans="overlap"><unclear/> that's right</u>
<u n="98" who="S0427">yes exactly</u>
<u n="99" who="S0426">though watching it is of course <pause dur="short"/> er exciting in in part but we've had this conversation before <pause dur="short"/> the stoppages and the impenetrability of the rules</u>
<u n="100" who="S0427" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> I don't enjoy watching rugby as much as I did in the seventies <pause dur="short"/> mind you that that <trunc>wa</trunc> I was biased by that wonderful Welsh team in the seventies</u>
<u n="101" who="S0426" trans="overlap">yes sure sure</u>
<u n="102" who="S0427">but it it it's become a much more confrontational impact game</u>
<u n="103" who="S0426">true</u>
<u n="104" who="S0427">you find three-quarters now a lot of the tactics are about how can you break attack</u>
<u n="105" who="S0426" trans="overlap">yes yes yes</u>
<u n="106" who="S0427">and go through rather than how can you go around the man</u>
<u n="107" who="S0426" trans="overlap">yes that's right but</u>
<u n="108" who="S0427" trans="overlap">I can't remember the last time I saw a genuine sidestep</u>
<u n="109" who="S0426">that's right yes well surely they happen but very occasionally</u>
<u n="110" who="S0427" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah but erm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0426">I think but there is that issue about the lack of flow which is</u>
<u n="112" who="S0427">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0426">games which flow are much more attractive the other thing I suppose is <pause dur="short"/> your <trunc>sen</trunc> my sense the activity looks arbitrary</u>
<u n="114" who="S0427">mm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0426">it's only the scrum to somebody coming fresh to a game they see people hunkering down that way it looks completely arbitrary</u>
<u n="116" who="S0427">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0426">why that way of distributing the ball? why seven men rather than two or eight or twelve?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0427" trans="overlap">take eight men each in a scrum yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm I don't know the history of that erm <pause dur="short"/> I mean in rugby league for instance it's not it's not eight men</u>
<u n="119" who="S0426" trans="overlap">sure</u>
<u n="120" who="S0427">it's it's six and the scrum's just become a way of restarting the game</u>
<u n="121" who="S0426" trans="overlap">it is it's a forward it's a forward</u>
<u n="122" who="S0427">it's not even contested anymore the scrum in rugby league</u>
<u n="123" who="S0426" trans="overlap">that's right and that makes the game flow</u>
<u n="124" who="S0427" trans="overlap">it does yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0426">it doesn't look arbitrary it's a way of restarting so</u>
<u n="126" who="S0427" trans="overlap">I mean uh and in some respects although I'm not a huge fan of rugby league whenever I watch it I I find the games more satisfying to watch in some respects</u>
<u n="127" who="S0426" trans="overlap">sure <unclear/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0427" trans="overlap">I I don't have the emotional interest <unclear/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0426" trans="overlap">no sure sure it's just a game but it <unclear/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0427" trans="overlap">but as something to watch yes I quite enjoy I I think rugby has become far too technical</u>
<u n="131" who="S0426">yes</u>
<u n="132" who="S0427">there are far too many <pause dur="short"/> mistakes <trunc>so</trunc>sorry not mistakes far too many technical infringements that are either a half penalty or full penalty</u>
<u n="133" who="S0426" trans="overlap">that's right</u>
<u n="134" who="S0427">and games are being decided by referees' interpretations of the laws and goodness knows what else you know?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0426" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> that's right and interpretations which are divisible or intelligible to most people in the <trunc>aud</trunc> in in the audience</u>
<u n="136" who="S0427">I mean there's one</u>
<u n="137" who="S0426" trans="overlap">not even visible there's</u>
<u n="138" who="S0427" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="139" who="S0426">say something will happen in some very very close engagement which you can't see and only the people on the field can see so it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0427" trans="overlap">I don't think referees don't understand half the time what is going on in the front row</u>
<u n="141" who="S0426"><unclear>I don't I don't</unclear></u>
<u n="142" who="S0427">and there's one rule there's one rule it's a full penalty I think if you don't bind properly right?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0426">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0427">if you don't bind properly so the the hooker is in the middle he has to bind properly on his props and his props have to bind properly on him and they can't do certain other things but then the more I think about it well if you're not bound properly then you can't be as effective pushing forward as a scrum unit so if you don't want to bind properly let them get on with it</u>
<u n="145" who="S0426" trans="overlap">that's true yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0427">why why why issue a penalty for not binding properly?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0426">presumably a lot of other things in the scrum aren't just about technicalities but about safety</u>
<u n="148" who="S0427">some of them are about safety which is why they don't allow them to clash anymore because often when they allowed them to charge in they'd go down and you'd you'd you could get people with snapped necks and things like</u>
<u n="149" who="S0426" trans="overlap"><unclear/> anyway</u>
<u n="150" who="S0427">yeah they do but now they</u>
<u n="151" who="S0426" trans="overlap"><unclear/> frightening when you see them</u>
<u n="152" who="S0427">I agree but now when they tend to go down that way <pause dur="short"/> but you know</u>
<u n="153" who="S0426">well there is still a safety element to pivoting</u>
<u n="154" who="S0427"><trunc>whi</trunc><trunc>whi</trunc>which is why you can't have contested scrums unless you've got specialist props and hookers playing they won't allow it if if for any reason you haven't got erm you've got an injury and you haven't got a specialist sub who's prop to come on to replace the injured prop the scrums must be uncontested</u>
<u n="155" who="S0426">well who would decide that?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0427">well it's decided</u>
<u n="157" who="S0426" trans="overlap">if someone is qualified or <trunc>disqualify</trunc> unqualified</u>
<u n="158" who="S0427">well it's it's known if someone is a prop yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0426" trans="overlap">okay yeah okay it's known</u>
<u n="160" who="S0427">just like just like when you look at the bench in football you know that's the goalkeeper</u>
<u n="161" who="S0426">oh right he or she's wearing something <unclear/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0427" trans="overlap">you know it it it it's clear who is a prop or not</u>
<u n="163" who="S0426" trans="overlap">well if it's a huge bloke <unclear/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0427" trans="overlap">no no no no you must of played as a prop you know</u>
<u n="165" who="S0426">okay</u>
<u n="166" who="S0427">in your career you can't you can't suddenly be a big bloke who's pressed into service</u>
<u n="167" who="S0426">okay right</u>
<u n="168" who="S0427">not at not at the elite level rugby anyway</u>
<u n="169" who="S0426">well again that's that's you know</u>
<u n="170" who="S0427">but it's frustrating because you pay a lot of money to go and see it and the number of times a scrum is reset and then it's reset and then the referee'll say no that was an infringement that's people slipped and then he'll move it five yards left or right you know and you're thinking hang on that's two minutes of my playing time that's gone by there you know? so I do find it immensely frustrating</u>
<u n="171" who="S0426" trans="overlap">true true</u>
<u n="172" who="S0427">and and as yet they haven't found an answer to it</u>
<u n="173" who="S0426">it might well be I don't know what it's like watching club rugby probably it's very unpopulated but if it wasn't for the nationalisms involved and the long history of glamour in some senses of the word</u>
<u n="174" who="S0427" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0426">then rugby wouldn't have the same prestige that it has now</u>
<u n="176" who="S0427">no I think that's right I mean if you look at New Zealand particularly New Zealand and to an extent Wales it is the national expression of their of their culture in some respects or part of their culture</u>
<u n="177" who="S0426" trans="overlap">yes sure <pause dur="short"/> sure sure</u>
<u n="178" who="S0427">because particularly in New Zealand it's the only game they really care about</u>
<u n="179" who="S0426">that's right</u>
<u n="180" who="S0427">in Wales football is getting stronger and stronger which you know which worries the rugby</u>
<u n="181" who="S0426" trans="overlap">true <pause dur="short"/> it's a secularise football</u>
<u n="182" who="S0427" trans="overlap">fraternity</u>
<u n="183" who="S0426">it's a not a nationalistic even though they're happy when the national team does well cos it's very unusual</u>
<u n="184" who="S0427">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0426">but it's it doesn't it's not so holy as the rugby is it's more <unclear/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0427" trans="overlap">no but no it isn't it but the problem I think er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is that young boys and girls they see the Bales of this world</u>
<u n="187" who="S0426" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="188" who="S0427">they see Swansea playing against</u>
<u n="189" who="S0426" trans="overlap">sure sure</u>
<u n="190" who="S0427">City and Chelsea and all those and they grow up more likely to become good football players and not rugby players and</u>
<u n="191" who="S0426" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="192" who="S0427">we need we need youngsters coming through into rugby and and the other thing too is that I don't know Swansea perhaps get twenty-five thousand watching a game down there on a Saturday <pause dur="short"/> you you</u>
<u n="193" who="S0426" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> but against Neath you</u>
<u n="194" who="S0427">no no <pause dur="short"/> you'd get hundreds you know if you're lucky</u>
<u n="195" who="S0426"><trunc>o</trunc>of course in a sense <pause dur="short"/> something like rugby and Wales is er immune to that and the idea of rugby in Wales</u>
<u n="196" who="S0427">mm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0426">the nature the symbolic element of rugby in Wales</u>
<u n="198" who="S0427">yeah <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0426">it it would still survive as this symbolic thing whether anybody played it or not more or less just like hurling I suppose</u>
<u n="200" who="S0427">yes it it would survive for quite some time but we might become you know distinctly second or third class at it erm and eventually then it would it would it would go under because you wouldn't be able to <trunc>sust</trunc></u>
<u n="201" who="S0426" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="202" who="S0427">and we've only got four professional clubs as it is</u>
<u n="203" who="S0426">that's true</u>
<u n="204" who="S0427">and our best players would end up having to play abroad and even if abroad was in England you know? erm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0426" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0427">there's a big difference between having your best players playing in Wales and having them as kind of a diaspora which is what the South Sea Islanders have found</u>
<u n="207" who="S0426" trans="overlap">well you know <unclear/> that's right that's right</u>
<u n="208" who="S0427" trans="overlap">they can't keep their very best players in</u>
<u n="209" who="S0426" trans="overlap"><unclear/> of course they can't</u>
<u n="210" who="S0427">cos they're they're too poor you know?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0426">but some cultural icons don't <pause dur="short"/> it's helped if there's quote success for them</u>
<u n="212" who="S0427">yes yes</u>
<u n="213" who="S0426">but it doesn't sum up well maybe rugby is not the same but say something like the Gaelic language for example you don't need to have that many people speaking it for it to be</u>
<u n="214" who="S0427" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="215" who="S0426">still be culturally important</u>
<u n="216" who="S0427">it can be culturally important but er you take Gaelic for instance and it's virtually dead</u>
<u n="217" who="S0426">it's dead</u>
<u n="218" who="S0427">it's virtually dead</u>
<u n="219" who="S0426" trans="overlap">it's an academic language</u>
<u n="220" who="S0427">whereas I think I think more preferable would be for it to be this symbolic cultural icon and be a living entity</u>
<u n="221" who="S0426" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> that's right that's right <unclear/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0427">if you see what I mean and Wales can't rest on its</u>
<u n="223" who="S0426">laurels</u>
<u n="224" who="S0427" trans="overlap">rugby <trunc>roo</trunc> laurels really</u>
<u n="225" who="S0426" trans="overlap">no no okay</u>
<u n="226" who="S0427">erm it needs to keep attracting young people into the game as as with the case for any sport of course</u>
<u n="227" who="S0426">but didn't it survive in the sense of popularity and prestige quite a long time in well the last ten years of pretty dismal international?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0427">well as soon as it went professional which was what the late in the nineties wasn't it I think? we had a very torrid time you know we were losing more matches in a season than we were winning erm <pause dur="short"/> and we there were some pretty heavy defeats I mean there was a tour to South Africa where I think South Africa beat us ninety-nine points to nil or something like that</u>
<u n="229" who="S0426" trans="overlap">what? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0427">and it took a while Wales were slow to come to grips with professionalism and during that time it virtually destroyed a very healthy club system</u>
<u n="231" who="S0426" trans="overlap">right right</u>
<u n="232" who="S0427">and what came in place there used to be five regional teams now and then there were four and there was all the squabbling and there was the renaming and all the rest of it and I don't think the Welsh rugby union was particularly well led and there's the usual tribal conflicts in Wales and places like France and England just marched ahead if us Scotland struggled enormously too</u>
<u n="233" who="S0426">well France and England would've had more capital more <pause dur="short"/> investors willing to capitalise <unclear/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0427" trans="overlap">it's more sponsorship er and there's just more money so you can pay the better then you can pay well</u>
<u n="235" who="S0426" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0427">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0426">but in spite of that dip</u>
<u n="238" who="S0427">they come out I mean in in starting in two thousand and five they did the Grand Slam they hadn't done it for a long time</u>
<u n="239" who="S0426">mm mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0427">and they've they've won the Championship and had more Grand Slams since then so the last ten years has in some respects been you know the best ten years they've had since the seventies <pause dur="short"/> you might not call it well I don't know they might become known as another golden period I mean</u>
<u n="241" who="S0426" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0427">who knows but it they have been very successful and of course erm four years ago they came within an ace of getting in the final of the World Cup</u>
<u n="243" who="S0426">mm mm mm mm</u>
<u n="244" who="S0427">you know erm and but</u>
<u n="245" who="S0426" trans="overlap">but those things matter for keeping <pause dur="short"/> keeping the flame burning as it were it would burn</u>
<u n="246" who="S0427" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0426"><unclear/> anyway but it'll flare up if the the team is successful on the pitch</u>
<u n="248" who="S0427"><trunc>pe</trunc>people were immensely proud of what Wales did in the last World Cup you know it was it was played in the Southern Hemisphere it's tough to go there anyway and we came within a whisker of getting to the final I don't think we would've beaten New Zealand but you know we we came within a whisker of getting there</u>
<u n="249" who="S0426">mm</u>
<u n="250" who="S0427">and people were enormously proud of that erm <pause dur="short"/> and they want they want Wales to get out of this group you know?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0426">yeah that'll be <unclear/> that's right that's right</u>
<u n="252" who="S0427" trans="overlap">going out at the group side yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's right <pause dur="short"/> and if if we win it</u>
<u n="253" who="S0426">well the</u>
<u n="254" who="S0427" trans="overlap">if we no if we win the group</u>
<u n="255" who="S0426" trans="overlap"><unclear/> oh the group oh</u>
<u n="256" who="S0427" trans="overlap">no if we win the group</u>
<u n="257" who="S0426">then you're guaranteed a less bad opponent than otherwise</u>
<u n="258" who="S0427" trans="overlap">yeah more likely people that we can beat</u>
<u n="259" who="S0426">right</u>
<u n="260" who="S0427">you know the</u>
<u n="261" who="S0426">right</u>
<u n="262" who="S0427">the the Scotlands or the not that they'll be easy but the Scotlands or the France or the Irelands and we don't have to play</u>
<u n="263" who="S0426" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah New Zealand that's right</u>
<u n="264" who="S0427">New Zealand in the quarter-finals someone like that you know?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0426" trans="overlap">is it not already decided who?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0427">it is decided it's it's like er the winner of Group A plays the runner-up in some other group but I I don't know I'd have to look it up in the paper <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0426">yes so it's</u>
<u n="268" who="S0427">but that is all because I do know that if England win the group <pause dur="short"/> I'd go so far as to say they're virtually guaranteed a place in the final</u>
<u n="269" who="S0426">given that they that the comparative property</u>
<u n="270" who="S0427" trans="overlap">they'll play at Twickenham and you know they will they <trunc>wi</trunc> they'll look at a team like France or Ireland or Scotland whoever it is and think we can beat you you know?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0426" trans="overlap">that's right that's right that's right that's right</u>
<u n="272" who="S0427">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0426">although who knows you know? erm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0427" trans="overlap">well it would be wonderful for the non</u>
<u n="275" who="S0426"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0427">for the non-English among us so to speak who who who never fail to enjoy the hubris and the schadenfreude</u>
<u n="277" who="S0426">this is a</u>
<u n="278" who="S0427" trans="overlap">of an English defeat</u>
<u n="279" who="S0426">almost equally as important as pleasure in your own team winning isn't it?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0427">almost <trunc>I</trunc>I shall be a very very happy man tomorrow if if Australia beat England <pause dur="short"/> I should be exceptionally happy</u>
<u n="281" who="S0426"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's a good index of what these things mean isn't it? that another team you take</u>
<u n="282" who="S0427" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="283" who="S0426">as much pleasure in almost</u>
<u n="284" who="S0427" trans="overlap">yeah and yet when it comes to World Cup football and England are playing I don't know Italy</u>
<u n="285" who="S0426">mm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0427">I I really don't care very much you know?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0426" trans="overlap">exactly that's right yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0427">if anything if anything my idea of heaven is Brazil playing like gods and winning it</u>
<u n="289" who="S0426" trans="overlap">that's right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0427">but that was shot to pieces in the last World Cup</u>
<u n="291" who="S0426" trans="overlap">yes yes quite</u>
<u n="292" who="S0427">I mean <trunc>Bra</trunc>Brazil can't even play the beautiful game any longer</u>
<u n="293" who="S0426" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes</u>
<u n="294" who="S0427">you know what what is the world coming to?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0426">they can barely play the game by by all accounts</u>
<u n="296" who="S0427">and today's paper say that Wales are eighth in the world in football which I find staggering and Brazil are seventh now Brazil seventh and Wales eight or eight or nine whatever it is</u>
<u n="297" who="S0426" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="298" who="S0427">no no no no there's something wrong there</u>
<u n="299" who="S0426">that's right that's right</u>
<u n="300" who="S0427">that can't be right</u>
<u n="301" who="S0426">yes on the basis on the coefficients they use</u>
<u n="302" who="S0427">well yes but I think that's just you know lies statistics and all the rest of it</u>
<u n="303" who="S0426" trans="overlap">well alright okay and it is managed by FIFA and you might want to say well okay that will tell you</u>
<u n="304" who="S0427" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0426">what it all means</u>
<u n="306" who="S0427">yes indeed</u>
<u n="307" who="S0426">well good a good bit of footy watching and rugby watching over the weekend</u>
<u n="308" who="S0427">yeah there's more European qualifying stuff coming up isn't there? for the football?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0426" trans="overlap">oh that's pretty dire though isn't it?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0427">well I don't I don't know Wales I know need one point to be sure of qualifying and</u>
<u n="311" who="S0426">oh right oh that's good</u>
<u n="312" who="S0427">yeah that will be first tournament they've <trunc>qualifor</trunc>qualified for since nineteen fifty-eight</u>
<u n="313" who="S0426" trans="overlap">fantastic</u>
<u n="314" who="S0427" trans="overlap">well it's fantastic for the football fans but from a rugby point of view</u>
<u n="315" who="S0426" trans="overlap">well alright okay</u>
<u n="316" who="S0427" trans="overlap">you know yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0426">it has this negative possibility of taking over</u>
<u n="318" who="S0427" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0426">who have they beaten in their group or who have they met in their group?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0427" trans="overlap">well I don't know they're playing the likes of Montenegro aren't they?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0426" trans="overlap">okay right</u>
<u n="322" who="S0427">but but I think they beat Belgium and something like that</u>
<u n="323" who="S0426" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="324" who="S0427">who or drew with them or beat them at home they've got some good results amongst it you know?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0426" trans="overlap">right but this is one of the first or the first time that the European Championships</u>
<u n="326" who="S0427" trans="overlap">yeah it's been expanded hasn't it? yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0426" trans="overlap">it's been expanded to <pause dur="short"/> mm thirty-six rather than thirty-four or something <unclear/> like that</u>
<u n="328" who="S0427" trans="overlap">I've I've no idea but it's <pause dur="short"/> but that's why you get things like Germany versus erm Monaco or Germany versus San Marino or something like that I mean it's</u>
<u n="329" who="S0426">I think there there's always been those things but there are more of them now</u>
<u n="330" who="S0427" trans="overlap">there are more of them now cos you get the Faroe Islands and Gibraltar and all the rest of it as well</u>
<u n="331" who="S0426" trans="overlap">the the Faroe Islands <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0427" trans="overlap">oh are they are they a World Cup?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0426">they're surprisingly okay</u>
<u n="334" who="S0427">oh yes they're eleventh in the World Cup rankings aren't they?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0426"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0427">yes</u>
<u n="337" who="S0426">well you may laugh but they beat the Netherlands can you believe it?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0427">I do find that difficult to believe</u>
<u n="339" who="S0426" trans="overlap"><unclear/> they do</u>
<u n="340" who="S0427">er erm this was</u>
<u n="341" who="S0426" trans="overlap">I mean they're the new middle-class comparatively</u>
<u n="342" who="S0427">oh</u>
<u n="343" who="S0426">but the the seriously not middle-class are the Uzbekistans of this world</u>
<u n="344" who="S0427">ah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0426">they're in there as well so I mean <unclear/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0427" trans="overlap">oh goodness me I I</u>
<u n="347" who="S0426" trans="overlap">it's extraordinary</u>
<u n="348" who="S0427">I can't keep pace with it really but there we are</u>
<u n="349" who="S0426">that's right</u>
<u n="350" who="S0427">have a good weekend</u>
<u n="351" who="S0426">same to you</u>
<u n="352" who="S0427">and erm</u>
<u n="353" who="S0426" trans="overlap">oh before we go</u>
<u n="354" who="S0427">yeah?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0426">er well I'll turn this off because</u>
<u n="356" who="S0427">right</u>
<u n="357" who="S0426">I was going to say</u>
<u n="358" who="S0427">we must have about getting on for half a dozen recordings?</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
