<text id="SMY5">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:10:03</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-07-11</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0439 S0440</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>car</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Work, family, friends, social. food</topics>
		<activity>Having a catch-up</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0439">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern - Non-accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0440">
				<exactage>58</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich, Norfolk</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Norfork</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Thrapston (Northants)</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>26</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Examinations Manager in Secondary School</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0439">what the bottled fruit?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0439">yeah they're really nice and they're also just erm good to have in the winter aren't they?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and they're nice desserts to have with cream</u>
<u n="6" who="S0440">yeah get some</u>
<u n="7" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's brilliant to have they're brilliant to have in the erm erm I was thinking this the other day what's</u>
<u n="8" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0439" trans="overlap">the difference between single cream and double cream? is it just</u>
<u n="10" who="S0440" trans="overlap">it's just the fat</u>
<u n="11" who="S0439" trans="overlap">basically the same as skimmed milk? and yeah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0440" trans="overlap">it's the it's the fat content yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0440">it's only the fat content double cream single cream separates <trunc>eas</trunc> well double cream <trunc>separ</trunc> I dunno one of them is erm good for whipping you can whip double cream but you can't whip single cream there's not enough fat</u>
<u n="15" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="16" who="S0440" trans="overlap">to hold it single cream is supposedly nicer but it doesn't taste as good</u>
<u n="17" who="S0439">you mean nicer as in like healthier?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0439">oh okay</u>
<u n="20" who="S0440">it doesn't taste as good I don't think it does anyway</u>
<u n="21" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0440">we came here last time we brought all this and we froze a few of the raspberries in fact I've got some raspberries if you wanna take them back for your freezer</u>
<u n="23" who="S0439">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0440">yeah?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0439">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did <trunc>de</trunc> she did she defrosted the freezer bless her and you know it didn't take that long but she was just the way she went it was just so irrational why she had to do it</u>
<u n="26" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="27" who="S0439" trans="overlap">on the Tuesday</u>
<u n="28" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0439">and she always er she always moans that she's poor</u>
<u n="30" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0439">and then she goes out and spends like twenty pounds in Home Bargains</u>
<u n="32" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and you it's just like because they're bargains and you're just like er that yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0440" trans="overlap">they're not bargains are they?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well they are they're cheap but they're just crap she doesn't need like she bought chocolate covered rice cakes it's like why did you need to buy chocolate covered? that's a nice house</u>
<u n="36" who="S0440">I've been looking at it yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0439" trans="overlap">erm yeah why would you need to <trunc>wh</trunc>why do you need to buy were you in your list of things that you needed? no <pause dur="short"/> she and erm I turn around and she like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was coming up last night</u>
<u n="38" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0439">and erm I said to her I said oh why don't you know why don't you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> come into town and come to the <anon type="place"/>? there's you know there's fireworks and everything and she was like er we could do but we're not I was like yeah but have you even asked him if he wanted to go to the <anon type="place"/>? and she went and she was like well no because I don't want to we're just gonna go we're gonna have dinner somewhere <pause dur="short"/> and I was like you they never do anything <pause dur="short"/> like last time he came up they went to <anon type="place"/> village and you're like yes you know nice daytrip out but not the highlight of the week is it?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0439">and like this is you know it was a really nice evening if she come then she could have come and met some of my friends she could have had a good night you know they don't have to stay late they could have just gone to seen the fireworks at ten o'clock and then sodded off but no they it's just they don't like she just doesn't do anything <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0440" trans="overlap">miserable bitch</u>
<u n="43" who="S0439">who?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0440">woman on the horse normally if you slow down for them they you know</u>
<u n="45" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah they wave don't they?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0440">uhu</u>
<u n="47" who="S0439">well why are there like hundreds of horses out today?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0440">dunno</u>
<u n="49" who="S0439">anyway yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just needs to do <trunc>some</trunc> and her mum right I like I love <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is awesome but she drives up every Thursday to come and do yoga with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then they drive to the gym</u>
<u n="50" who="S0440">bloody hell</u>
<u n="51" who="S0439">I know I was like isn't that a bit far away? and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said oh no it's not it's only like erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>t</trunc> half an hour or something I was like you drive half an hour to go to yoga? well forty minutes or something it must be forty minutes cos like she her mum works in <anon type="place"/> so <pause dur="short"/> and she's like yeah I so why would you do that? why would she drive forty minutes there then forty minutes back to go to yoga? <pause dur="short"/> we don't bond once a week</u>
<u n="52" who="S0440">we do when you come home to us we</u>
<u n="53" who="S0439" trans="overlap">true</u>
<u n="54" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0439">actually yeah we did bond last Friday as well didn't we?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0440">yeah we do bond occasionally don't we?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0440">when I come back from <anon type="place"/> tomorrow I may pop in and see you</u>
<u n="59" who="S0439">ah erm I'm out tomorrow</u>
<u n="60" who="S0440">oh are you? great thanks</u>
<u n="61" who="S0439">sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm going to <anon type="place"/> to meet up with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think erm she I told her that you bought her the bath soaps and stuff and she went oh your mum's so lovely like</u>
<u n="62" who="S0440" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0439">her parents like it's her birthday next</u>
<u n="64" who="S0440">oh</u>
<u n="65" who="S0439">next weekend</u>
<u n="66" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and so I'm going up to <anon type="place"/> on Friday night</u>
<u n="68" who="S0440" trans="overlap">are you?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0439">and then erm coming well just staying over</u>
<u n="70" who="S0440" trans="overlap">so did you tell did you tell her that your mum was suffering from depression as well?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="72" who="S0440">oh</u>
<u n="73" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well like she knows</u>
<u n="74" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0439">like she she knows that I went through stuff last year</u>
<u n="76" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0439">and she's she's been so grateful she's just like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're the only person who really like understands what I'm going through none of my other friends understand and I was like well yeah that's fine I <pause dur="short"/> you know I'm not <trunc>j</trunc> haven't and she's like you always know what to say and I'm like because there's nothing right you know there's no right answer</u>
<u n="78" who="S0440">there isn't no</u>
<u n="79" who="S0439">you've just got to stay <pause dur="short"/> you've just got you know <pause dur="short"/> there's no right answer on how to fix it but she's getting better and she's gone back to work <pause dur="short"/> erm she got diagnosed with chronic fatigue syndrome again</u>
<u n="80" who="S0440" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0439">so she's gone to a <trunc>phys</trunc> a fatigue clinic I dunno what a fatigue clinic is</u>
<u n="82" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0439">but erm she's gone to there and she's gonna be seeing them once a week and she went back to work for two hours and no she went back to work for four hours on Monday and she said that was a bit too much so she's gone I think for three hours or something</u>
<u n="84" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="85" who="S0439">but it was like her boss <trunc>patroni</trunc> like really patronised her and she goes <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> let's sit down and discuss this cos we don't want you making yourself ill again <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like what? I do not I did not make myself ill you just dumped too much crap on me <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah so I think I'm gonna meet her in tomorrow in <anon type="place"/> and just have a little catch up</u>
<u n="86" who="S0440">where does she <trunc>wor</trunc> where did she go to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0439">what do you mean where does she go to the</u>
<u n="88" who="S0440" trans="overlap">well did she just go down from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0439" trans="overlap">she just goes down from <anon type="place"/> she gets on the <anon type="place"/> tube it's pretty good actually it's like a bus that goes from <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> and costs like ten pounds I think? not even ten pounds I think</u>
<u n="90" who="S0440" trans="overlap">how much is your train?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0439">nine ninety-five</u>
<u n="92" who="S0440">that's not bad is it?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0439">no it's alright</u>
<u n="94" who="S0440" trans="overlap">is that the that's return?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's off-peak</u>
<u n="96" who="S0440">you can't drive it</u>
<u n="97" who="S0439" trans="overlap">but er</u>
<u n="98" who="S0440">can you?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0439">no I would I would never drive to <anon type="place"/> it makes no logical sense especially when it's only like yeah ten pounds to go by train and it's really quick it's something like only fifty minutes <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <pause dur="long"/> so I'm gonna go and meet her I think <pause dur="short"/> erm but then they also have this erm thing on at <anon type="place"/> for the <anon type="place"/> which is I <trunc>g</trunc> a rugby-themed day?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0440">uhu</u>
<u n="101" who="S0439">for the World Cup so I don't know whether to go to that in the morning and then go and see her in the afternoon or something</u>
<u n="102" who="S0440" trans="overlap">but they had one of those in Paris when we were there</u>
<u n="103" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0440">when the Paris World Cup was being held</u>
<u n="105" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="long"/> so</u>
<u n="106" who="S0440">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0440">is gonna move to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0439">oh really?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0440">yeah <pause dur="short"/> leaving Paris and coming back to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0439">he didn't come back to us then?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0440">well we don't want him do we really cos we got <pause dur="short"/> we got enough props as such but also he's not gonna be as fit and he's thirty odd so</u>
<u n="113" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0440">you know yes he was very nice but do we really want him back?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="116" who="S0440">don't think so</u>
<u n="117" who="S0439">oh I love Lawes or Courtney <pause dur="long"/> yeah but they've got the summer off haven't they now? so</u>
<u n="118" who="S0440">yeah Myler's been dropped from the England squad so</u>
<u n="119" who="S0439">but he's so good</u>
<u n="120" who="S0440" trans="overlap">good I know I know and</u>
<u n="121" who="S0439" trans="overlap">his kicking is one of the best in the <trunc>champi</trunc> in the league</u>
<u n="122" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I know I know I know and Danny Cipriani they don't know whether he's gonna be in the team because he's still having his drink-drive charge</u>
<u n="123" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0440" trans="overlap">over him and if</u>
<u n="125" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and who was the one who got</u>
<u n="126" who="S0440" trans="overlap">if he gets pulled out then Myler has lost all the conditioning</u>
<u n="127" who="S0439">who was the one who erm <pause dur="short"/> the rugby player this week who got done for sexual assault or last week or something? he got charged with it didn't he?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0440" trans="overlap">what what an England an England one?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0439">no was he a Maori?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0440">oh no no he was a yeah Maori yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0439">was he? yeah he was a New Zealander didn't he?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0439" trans="overlap">he charged with it</u>
<u n="134" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0439">bit dangerous</u>
<u n="136" who="S0440">but he doesn't play anymore so</u>
<u n="137" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh does he not? I thought he would've <trunc>pla</trunc></u>
<u n="138" who="S0440" trans="overlap">well he doesn't play for New Zealand anymore is</u>
<u n="139" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0440" trans="overlap"><unclear>probably</unclear> is this the <anon type="place"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah this is the <anon type="place"/> I like their food here they do good stuff</u>
<u n="142" who="S0440">we could sit outside don't have to sit inside today</u>
<u n="143" who="S0439">we could sit outside</u>
<u n="144" who="S0440">it's gonna be really really yeah coffee out there be a nice a one</u>
<u n="145" who="S0439" trans="overlap">god it's busy isn't it?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0440">oh no there isn't any room up there</u>
<u n="147" who="S0439">oh no what are we gonna do? you can't park there mum</u>
<u n="148" who="S0440">I'm not going to</u>
<u n="149" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0440">I'm gonna turn round</u>
<u n="151" who="S0439">oh god let's dread who we're gonna bump into <pause dur="long"/> that's the problem with <anon type="place"/> you always bump into people</u>
<u n="152" who="S0440">uhu <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0439">oh <pause dur="short"/> how's erm oh how's erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> by the way?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0440">I don't know I haven't seen her since she went to Prague I haven't</u>
<u n="155" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0440">I've got to pop and see her</u>
<u n="157" who="S0439"><vocal desc="misc"/> okay erm bless her I I hope she had a good holiday</u>
<u n="158" who="S0440">mm look at these gorgeous plants aren't they fab?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0439">they are pretty cool what are they?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0440">they're big they're all they're they're olive trees</u>
<u n="161" who="S0439" trans="overlap">they're olive trees</u>
<u n="162" who="S0440" trans="overlap">they are yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0439">I guess it is called <anon type="place"/> that makes sense</u>
<u n="164" who="S0440">yeah mm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0439">they are pretty cool <pause dur="short"/> oh no maybe it's not warm enough to sit outside it might be</u>
<u n="166" who="S0440">it might be don't <trunc>kno</trunc> no it isn't</u>
<u n="167" who="S0439">no I'd rather sit inside</u>
<u n="168" who="S0440">uhu <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0439">if it was just a little bit sunnier</u>
<u n="170" who="S0440">I came here with Olive er with Olive?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0439">with Olive <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0440">I came I came here with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just before <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s funeral</u>
<u n="173" who="S0439">did you?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0439">can't believe that was like a month ago now</u>
<u n="176" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah no</u>
<u n="177" who="S0439" trans="overlap">unbelievable he's he's been dead for two months that's really scary</u>
<u n="178" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I know that is very scary yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it must it still it still must be so surreal mustn't it?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0440">that's what she she said the other day she said I just can't get used to the fact that the door isn't gonna open and he's not gonna walk through it</u>
<u n="181" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah he's just not here anymore it's weird</u>
<u n="182" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="183" who="S0439">but <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> she'll be alright she's got a lot of support so</u>
<u n="184" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah mm half of the time</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
