<text id="SMYJ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:20:01</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-06-20</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0326 S0329</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In a car driving from Cambridge to London</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Cambridge, houses, plans for the future, thesis, university, Oxford, family, living arrangements</topics>
		<activity>Mother and son talking about the future during a drive between Cambridge and London </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, Inquiring, Advising, Announcing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0326">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>12</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0329">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>English</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>50</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Literary Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2>French</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0326">er yeah I mean the one thing is that I've actually already submitted what I was gonna do</u>
<u n="2" who="S0329">oh</u>
<u n="3" who="S0326">cos you had to and I thought that was like there's no real way they can force me to do them I reckon</u>
<u n="4" who="S0329">no <pause dur="short"/> of course not</u>
<u n="5" who="S0326">erm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0329" trans="overlap">so you submitted what?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0326">well that so well what I submitted was</u>
<u n="8" who="S0329">I can't believe you're in your final year next year</u>
<u n="9" who="S0326">two literature papers <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0329">what do you do in those literature papers?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0326">well the options aren't that good that's the thing for the literature erm I chose The Odyssey which is the it's just about The Odyssey</u>
<u n="12" who="S0329">how fantastic</u>
<u n="13" who="S0326">er and the Metamorphoses</u>
<u n="14" who="S0329">how fantastic</u>
<u n="15" who="S0326" trans="overlap">by Ovid</u>
<u n="16" who="S0329">what's sort what sort of writing?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0326" trans="overlap">cos they're very they're very sort of like <pause dur="short"/> they're things I already know vaguely a little bit about that's all</u>
<u n="18" who="S0329">well you mean that's why you chose them or that's why they're boring?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0326">well they're I mean they're not boring obviously but they're not erm</u>
<u n="20" who="S0329">I just think to do</u>
<u n="21" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0329">an in-depth paper</u>
<u n="23" who="S0326">and to read the whole thing in</u>
<u n="24" who="S0329" trans="overlap">will just be <pause dur="short"/> fantastic</u>
<u n="25" who="S0326">and then the other thing I picked was a was a thesis</u>
<u n="26" who="S0329">so that you select your own?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0329" trans="overlap">and just write a long paper how long is it?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0326">ten thousand</u>
<u n="30" who="S0329">really? as many as ten thousand?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0329">I <trunc>thi</trunc> well I think you'll definitely get a lot out of that</u>
<u n="33" who="S0326">yeah so do I but I don't know what the <trunc>f</trunc>fuck to do one on</u>
<u n="34" who="S0329">why don't you do?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0326" trans="overlap">see that's the problem er but</u>
<u n="36" who="S0329" trans="overlap">why don't you do?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0326" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="38" who="S0329">James why don't you do Ulysses and Ulysses? or is that always is that a common one?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0326">no but but that's too much overlap of my other paper if you see what I'm saying</u>
<u n="40" who="S0329">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0326">erm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0329">but presumably somebody tutors you for that?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0329" trans="overlap">you know</u>
<u n="45" who="S0329">so you</u>
<u n="46" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah you do</u>
<u n="47" who="S0329">you <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="48" who="S0326">and you've got</u>
<u n="49" who="S0329" trans="overlap">discuss with</u>
<u n="50" who="S0326">before you get a tutor</u>
<u n="51" who="S0329" trans="overlap">with goldilocks</u>
<u n="52" who="S0326" trans="overlap">though you pick something <pause dur="short"/> anyway but the problem is that those options I mean I don't do any philosophy</u>
<u n="53" who="S0329">those what?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0326">if I do those options</u>
<u n="55" who="S0329">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0326">means I don't do philosophy</u>
<u n="57" who="S0329">what? oh <pause dur="short"/> how do you feel about that?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0326">well I would I think I would like to do it so they're not what I thought was that I would do a dissertation about Plato <pause dur="short"/> but that's really fucking hard on the one hand</u>
<u n="59" who="S0329">what and dissertation is not the same as thesis?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0326">I mean it er yeah it's the same thing but then I thought I would do one</u>
<u n="61" who="S0329">oh that is quite a good idea <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0326">then I thought I would do one about mm sort of Plato but taking it from a literature</u>
<u n="63" who="S0329">well if you've got</u>
<u n="64" who="S0326" trans="overlap">point of view</u>
<u n="65" who="S0329" trans="overlap">ten thousand words you have got quite a lot of</u>
<u n="66" who="S0326">so I could so something like erm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0329">I think you should do that I think it's a</u>
<u n="68" who="S0326" trans="overlap">well I had this one idea about katabasis which is going into the <trunc>undergrou</trunc> underworld and er in literature in Greek literature and philosophy</u>
<u n="69" who="S0329">so glad you did this subject isn't it so fantastic?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0326">yeah but but then what I was thinking the other day is that I'll just do the Plato module <pause dur="short"/> and and do a and drop either The Odyssey or the Metamorphoses</u>
<u n="71" who="S0329">right</u>
<u n="72" who="S0326">and do a do do a thesis about the more about literature <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="73" who="S0329" trans="overlap">oh I see that is quite fine-tuning of</u>
<u n="74" who="S0326">cos the thing about</u>
<u n="75" who="S0329">I think well look <pause dur="short"/> er but it's <trunc>ver</trunc> it's individual and you probably you're just gonna have to live with thinking it through for for the summer</u>
<u n="76" who="S0326">but the but the problem is</u>
<u n="77" who="S0329" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="78" who="S0326">I need to start working now</u>
<u n="79" who="S0329">yeah but it doesn't <pause dur="short"/> it it doesn't <pause dur="short"/> what you're deciding what you're thinking about is all interconnected so you'll be doing the work anyway and doing the work will help you doing the reading will help you erm reach a decision will help you develop your ideas you can't you won't have any ideas just you know staring into space it comes from things firing off each other erm <pause dur="short"/> I did a thesis for my finals and I did it on a philosophical subject and erm and I really <pause dur="short"/> I think that if you're going to do a long essay like that it's actually <pause dur="short"/> a philosophical subject is better than a pure literary subject I couldn't have written ten thousand words on a</u>
<u n="80" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah but the one</u>
<u n="81" who="S0329" trans="overlap">pure literary subject</u>
<u n="82" who="S0326" trans="overlap">the thing is I had an ideas for literature was about <pause dur="short"/> quite about sort of you know that poet Cavafy?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0326">Cavafy</u>
<u n="84" who="S0326">Cavafy or that's the</u>
<u n="85" who="S0329">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0326">yeah and like his <unclear>reception</unclear> of Greek literature I don't <trunc>b</trunc> I really don't know that much about him I just thought he sounded cool</u>
<u n="87" who="S0329">erm yeah and I saw you've been reading Mendelsohn's translations new translations <pause dur="long"/> you need to go to America and you need to meet my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I think you have met him briefly and you need to get him to introduce you to Daniel Mendelsohn <pause dur="long"/> erm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0326" trans="overlap">so then that's the thing so if I did a philosophy paper <pause dur="short"/> I would <trunc>w</trunc> I don't really wanna drop the Metamorphoses cos then I wouldn't do any Latin</u>
<u n="89" who="S0329">no I think you're too literary I think you'd have to do</u>
<u n="90" who="S0326">and also my teacher who I really like is the course director of that at and I he's think he's I think he's really good</u>
<u n="91" who="S0329">yeah so okay so those decisions are firm and the it's just a you were just working <trunc>arou</trunc> I don't understand</u>
<u n="92" who="S0326">so basically what I'm definitely going to do is the Metamorphoses the the being human <pause dur="short"/> and then</u>
<u n="93" who="S0329">being human as in</u>
<u n="94" who="S0326">that's the X paper</u>
<u n="95" who="S0329">right</u>
<u n="96" who="S0326">and then either <pause dur="short"/> either a thesis and Odyssey</u>
<u n="97" who="S0329">thesis?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0326">and Odyssey or a thesis and Plato</u>
<u n="99" who="S0329">thesis and Odyssey <pause dur="long"/> well <pause dur="short"/> you can't make your <trunc>mi</trunc> you're not gonna make your mind up by the time you come back today it's just those this is what you're thinking about over the summer <pause dur="short"/> that's the way it that's what you have to look and how you have to think about it and what have you said that you're doing?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0326">erm Metamorphoses Odyssey <pause dur="short"/> being human and thesis with you have a backup cos <trunc>qui</trunc> apparent quite often people will set out to do a thesis and there's no argument there so they have to do an exam so well my fifth option is Plato <pause dur="long"/> what was your <trunc>th</trunc>thesis?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0329">on the imagination <pause dur="short"/> so I did erm I've still got it somewhere</u>
<u n="102" who="S0326">let's have a look at that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0329">I looked at it not that long ago well <trunc>ma</trunc> you know in the last ten years couldn't understand a word</u>
<u n="104" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> erm yeah so I did it <pause dur="short"/> I did how far back did I go? erm <pause dur="short"/> it was <pause dur="long"/> Plotinus that's how far back I went theories of the sublime <pause dur="short"/> it was Plotinus <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0326">I don't really know him <pause dur="short"/> you didn't do anyone called Pseudo-Longinus?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0329"><trunc>s</trunc> er yeah I did I did <trunc>Long</trunc></u>
<u n="108" who="S0326" trans="overlap">that's as far back I know about the sublime</u>
<u n="109" who="S0329" trans="overlap">yeah I did him Plotinus and I don't know about the Pseudo</u>
<u n="110" who="S0326">well that's probably because since you did it he's become disputed</u>
<u n="111" who="S0329">oh right</u>
<u n="112" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0329">Longinus I used to call him Longinus Plotinus er and I went then I started doing <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> I did a bit of eighteenth-century Edmund Burke theories of the sublime and picturesque and then what were are we doing at fifty? erm and then <pause dur="short"/> the nineteenth-century Wordsworth and Coleridge cos I was just obsessed with Wordsworth and Coleridge that was my big obsession when I was</u>
<u n="115" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0329">I can't remember anything about them now <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I don't I went through an entire er school without reading any Wordsworth</u>
<u n="118" who="S0329">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can I can believe that you know I didn't read any Wordsworth at school and it's not very palatable for <pause dur="short"/> younger people <pause dur="short"/> coleridge and Shelley however</u>
<u n="119" who="S0326">did Coleridge</u>
<u n="120" who="S0329">are exciting <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0326">oh man I just er really er am really er indecided undecided</u>
<u n="122" who="S0329">you really are undecided? yeah but the thing is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you don't actually have to make up your mind and at the moment and you <trunc>ca</trunc> and you're not in a position to so just do lots of reading in the summer</u>
<u n="123" who="S0326">I know but I mean part of the thing is like if you do The Odyssey you're supposed to have read The Odyssey by the time you get there</u>
<u n="124" who="S0329">well you're going <trunc>d</trunc> read it</u>
<u n="125" who="S0326">are you <trunc>n</trunc>no if I I oh I might read some of it but</u>
<u n="126" who="S0329">read it I'm gonna read I'll read it with you</u>
<u n="127" who="S0326">in Greek</u>
<u n="128" who="S0329" trans="overlap">I've never read it</u>
<u n="129" who="S0326" trans="overlap">well in Greek?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0329">well obviously I'm not gonna read it in Greek but <unclear/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah but do you know slow do you know how long it takes to read something in Greek? <pause dur="short"/> in <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we should listen to the news actually I wonder what's been happening it is fascinating what's happening in Greece</u>
<u n="133" who="S0326">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0329">I bought the Daily Express just because it I dunno <vocal desc="laugh"/> the headline about diabetes that's really all <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thinks about <pause dur="short"/> er wait I'm going where am I going?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0326">you're going to <anon type="place"/> babes</u>
<u n="136" who="S0329">is it up here? oh eleven totally was just dreaming</u>
<u n="137" who="S0326">yeah what am I gonna do when I finish <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0329">erm <pause dur="short"/> I thought you were gonna go to America and do some studying there <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0326">I dunno</u>
<u n="140" who="S0329">have you had any you must be <pause dur="long"/> or a</u>
<u n="141" who="S0326">I thought I'd take a gap year</u>
<u n="142" who="S0329">yeah take a gap year</u>
<u n="143" who="S0326">what would I do during that? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0329">yeah you're gonna have to earn some money that's for sure <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's the real thing what the fuck do you do for money? how are you gonna get any?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0326">I don't need very much though</u>
<u n="146" who="S0329">erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0326">tutor Latin or something like that</u>
<u n="148" who="S0329">well</u>
<u n="149" who="S0326">I dunno really</u>
<u n="150" who="S0329">tutor Latin well yeah you definitely would be able to do that <pause dur="long"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> must be this one <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0326">cos I could like <trunc>t</trunc> I don't know really</u>
<u n="152" who="S0329">what were you gonna say?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0326">you can do lots of little jobs and get a bit of money and tutor Latin erm <pause dur="short"/> make coffee and work in a bar and then do a useful internship somewhere</u>
<u n="154" who="S0329">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0326">I don't know about where</u>
<u n="156" who="S0329">well you could definitely go the <anon type="place"/> is gagging for you</u>
<u n="157" who="S0326">what would that actually involve doing?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0329">fuck all</u>
<u n="159" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> well they have proper paid interns erm <pause dur="short"/> you know you would in it's a <trunc>ser</trunc> a very serious it's not like at the <anon type="place"/> where you just write in like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and say I worked in <anon type="place"/> you know as a cocktail waitress <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0329">erm the <anon type="place"/> takes it very serious but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is well every time I see her she says send <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to me I want I want to <pause dur="short"/> interview him but I mean she would she's a</u>
<u n="163" who="S0326">what would do they ask you like what what books do you like?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0329">erm <pause dur="short"/> they're really really stiff interviewers erm <pause dur="short"/> and interning there is I think it's like a year-long job or something and erm you know probably get people who <pause dur="short"/> er had done more education than you you might be too young you might be not educated enough but it's hard to believe given <unclear/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but you know it wouldn't be it it wouldn't be something where you did <trunc>m</trunc>made <trunc>s</trunc> coffee in the mornings</u>
<u n="165" who="S0326">yes</u>
<u n="166" who="S0329">erm <pause dur="long"/> you'd be generally involved in the running of the paper and erm <pause dur="long"/> not coffee-making you know <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0326">see I a thing I thought about doing it and that would be to do a <trunc>Te</trunc> do a TEFL thing</u>
<u n="168" who="S0329">oh yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0326">and then actually <trunc>ha</trunc> I can't really speak any other languages</u>
<u n="170" who="S0329">you can hardly speak English <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0326">and do like three months trying to learn <pause dur="short"/> sort of three months in Germany a few months in France a few months in Spain or something</u>
<u n="172" who="S0329">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> you mean and fund it with your TEFL?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0329">are you is your relationship with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> forming your thoughts as well? were you</u>
<u n="175" who="S0326" trans="overlap">well erm not at not at the moment <pause dur="long"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s quite up for not living in like England though</u>
<u n="176" who="S0329">is she? <pause dur="long"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="177" who="S0326">maybe I'll see what courses they have for that <trunc>yea</trunc> er erm at the sort of</u>
<u n="178" who="S0329">at the <unclear>Sorbonne</unclear>?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0326">er no at the British School of Athens or American School of Athens and then we could look</u>
<u n="180" who="S0329" trans="overlap">I definitely think you should see what your options are academically and you know you can get all sorts of scholarships like a Fulbright and that kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> er all the all the really clever people I was at <anon type="place"/> with got Fulbright scholarships to go and study at Yale and</u>
<u n="181" who="S0326">I'm not that clever though</u>
<u n="182" who="S0329">well neither were they <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think you're perfectly clever enough and anyway you know there are all these scholarships and it would be worth investigating what what sort of what there is <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> cos that would be</u>
<u n="183" who="S0326" trans="overlap">but part of the reason part of the reason for erm waiting to <trunc>appl</trunc> a year to to apply for this <unclear>More</unclear> school is that I'll have a long piece of writing to send them <pause dur="short"/> and I will erm have my results <pause dur="short"/> cos I don't think I I'd <trunc>prob</trunc> I'm pretty sure I didn't get a first this year</u>
<u n="184" who="S0329">well you can this is the kind of thing that you must discuss with your supervisors</u>
<u n="185" who="S0326" trans="overlap">well that's what my supervisor said when I suggested that</u>
<u n="186" who="S0329">oh</u>
<u n="187" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I want to do that he said that would be a good idea</u>
<u n="188" who="S0329" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0326" trans="overlap">because of this and this and this</u>
<u n="190" who="S0329">really? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0326">but he did say to me that I should definitely be thinking about doing the <unclear>More</unclear></u>
<u n="192" who="S0329">yeah I</u>
<u n="193" who="S0326" trans="overlap">and when I mentioned America he said there's only two good places</u>
<u n="194" who="S0329">yeah you told me yeah but remind me</u>
<u n="195" who="S0326">Princeton <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>Sou</trunc> South California? University of South California</u>
<u n="196" who="S0329">oh really? that would be a laugh Princeton you'd have to live in New York</u>
<u n="197" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0329">my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is just going off to take up a job at the history department at Princeton University and I've got lunch with her on Monday and she's got a flat in</u>
<u n="199" who="S0326">at New Jersey?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0329">in no in</u>
<u n="201" who="S0326"><unclear/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0329">erm Tompkins Square New York</u>
<u n="203" who="S0326" trans="overlap">how did she get that? <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0329">er she got it through some <trunc>ac</trunc> some academic swap thing</u>
<u n="205" who="S0326">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0329" trans="overlap">er where hang on where am I going? hang on darling erm <pause dur="long"/> yeah you're fucking well-positioned in terms of connections for further education with your your dad being <trunc>prop</trunc> you know a proper academic <pause dur="short"/> and your mother being just super plugged in <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0329">I did actually have a chat with a classicist at with the main classics guy at Princeton</u>
<u n="209" who="S0326">yeah it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s erm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0329">yeah yeah it's yeah something to do with her</u>
<u n="211" who="S0329"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s nephew</u>
<u n="212" who="S0326">he told me to go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0329">yeah <pause dur="long"/> I think it's clear that you want to <trunc>u</trunc>use your <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>stud</trunc> you know studying provides you with an opportunity and an excuse to erm expand your life and your and your world you can go into <trunc>souther</trunc> Southern California you can go to Sao Paulo you can go wherever you want to study when you get out of the world of studying it becomes a little bit more <pause dur="short"/> it's a good place to be in the your twenties <pause dur="short"/> I think I wouldn't be in a hurry to provided it can be funded</u>
<u n="214" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0329">well</u>
<u n="216" who="S0326" trans="overlap">but that's why he like my teacher said like funding is a lot less competitive in America because there is so much more money</u>
<u n="217" who="S0329">yeah there's a lot more money yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="long"/> yeah I mean one of the things that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s really pissed with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <trunc>abou</trunc> it would be good if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> comes to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think you two have got lots in common <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> looks er he just looks at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had a you know <trunc>caree</trunc> a burgeoning career as a academic as an academic he was teaching philosophy at <anon type="place"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> he was making great progress with his thesis he was all set to have that kind of life and he <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gave it up and he just well just totally lost interest thought everybody who was doing academic philosophy was very third rate I think it's partly because</u>
<u n="218" who="S0326">but that's what I but that's what I er it seems like that to me something the people who <pause dur="short"/> who just <trunc>car</trunc> er continue with it studying cos they couldn't think of er anything else to do</u>
<u n="219" who="S0329">well it's like I don't think it's like that in your subjects <pause dur="short"/> I do think it's like that in other subjects in that erm <pause dur="long"/> and also I I think it's like that in this country and I don't particular think it's like that</u>
<u n="220" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I but I think it's like that at <anon type="place"/> but especially because</u>
<u n="221" who="S0329">oh yeah of course <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0326" trans="overlap">no but because it</u>
<u n="223" who="S0329" trans="overlap">is utterly parochial</u>
<u n="224" who="S0326">but also it it's just because people were this is what the people who are actually more interesting are someone who <trunc>li</trunc> went to a less cool university but then became a really good <trunc>ac</trunc> cos they've discovered that they actually really like their thing</u>
<u n="225" who="S0329">who's the they?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0326">this hypothetical person <pause dur="short"/> the thing about people at <anon type="place"/> is that they that's always been what they're good at in school</u>
<u n="227" who="S0329">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0326">I mean what I'm saying is people who go on whose thing hasn't always been being good at school who have actually discovered a subject are <trunc>m</trunc>more will always be much more interesting people</u>
<u n="229" who="S0329">erm <pause dur="short"/> when I went I haven't told you about when I went to get a <trunc>c</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> from <anon type="place"/> have I?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="231" who="S0329">it was a sunny day and I hadn't really been round <anon type="place"/> and spent the day there and we went and had lunch in Hugh Fearnley-Whittingstall's <pause dur="short"/> er restaurant there and <pause dur="short"/> it's a really proper city full of and it's got a proper vibe and I really suddenly saw how difficult it was for you at <anon type="place"/> to go to a place where there was just like some some <trunc>hi</trunc> a high street there's just high street shops and there's no kind of vibe and like any vibe there is is locked away in your college</u>
<u n="232" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0329">whereas <pause dur="short"/> you know and <anon type="place"/>'s a proper big city and I think when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gets back from Berlin he's gonna he's paying rent and I think he'll just go down to <anon type="place"/> and live in his I'll show you a picture of his house oh except I've left my phone behind he's got this astonishing house <pause dur="long"/> but yeah but</u>
<u n="234" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I can't really get out of <anon type="place"/> quick enough now like</u>
<u n="235" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well you know <pause dur="short"/> also appreciate the amazing experience of being in the in the architecture of <anon type="place"/> that is not going to be repeated and that is I mean I suppose <pause dur="short"/> being pissed off with it is part of the experience but <pause dur="short"/> I didn't like being in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0326">yeah but even <anon type="place"/> it's it's like ten times bigger there</u>
<u n="237" who="S0329" trans="overlap">yeah I didn't like being in <anon type="place"/> when I was married I didn't <vocal desc="laugh"/> but I really didn't like it when I was a student but I still walked around it thinking oh this is this is at least this is these are beautiful buildings at least I'm not depressed in Birmingham</u>
<u n="238" who="S0326">yeah <pause dur="long"/> did you hear from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0329">erm on his birthday <pause dur="short"/> you know his friends took him to Budapest? did you know that?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="241" who="S0329">so we he was supposed to go to Berlin today erm and erm and then he said to me oh my friends say that I need to pack and be ready to go to Berlin on Wednesday I won't be here for my birthday erm but I don't know where I'm going I don't think I'll need my passport but I've got to pack it anyway because I'll be going straight to Berlin from wherever it is somebody did blow the secret that it was erm it was Budapest so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> flew <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to Budapest erm <pause dur="short"/> and then they flew him from Budapest to Berlin</u>
<u n="242" who="S0326">right</u>
<u n="243" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that is a really nice present <pause dur="long"/> <shift new="singing"/> it's too late baby it's too late <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0326" trans="overlap">is it raining?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0329">is it raining? I don't know what are those drops if they're not rain?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0326">you haven't got the wipers on?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0329" trans="overlap">is that it's a is that a philosophical question? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0326" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0329">the pain in my arm is so bizarre <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it is just I can't you know when you hit your funny bone?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0329">that's what it's like all the time</u>
<u n="252" who="S0326">better start laughing or it'll go away</u>
<u n="253" who="S0329">they're signing me in for I'm going to have some cortisone injections and I cannot wait <pause dur="long"/> <shift new="singing"/> it's too late <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I bet it's gonna I can this is the day everybody leaves <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0329">say that again</u>
<u n="256" who="S0326">it's the day when everybody leaves</u>
<u n="257" who="S0329">oh is it?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0329">so it's gonna be crowded with mums and dads</u>
<u n="260" who="S0326">I didn't tell you I saw dad yesterday</u>
<u n="261" who="S0329">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0326">oh my days he's got a ponytail</u>
<u n="263" who="S0329">oh my days <vocal desc="laugh"/> did you <trunc>s</trunc> go round to see him?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0326">he invited me to go I thought it would just be like he wanted to go to have dinner I thought it would just be me him and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but it was some of his friends and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0329">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> and who were his friends?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0326">erm this is the wife was called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this teacher Irish guy</u>
<u n="267" who="S0329">Irish guy?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0326">who taught him at er <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0329">an old guy?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0326">he's only a bit older than dad</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="271" who="S0329">er and you can't remember his name?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="273" who="S0329">you didn't take <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0326">are you crazy?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0329">well why wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0326">cos he's got a fucking ponytail</u>
<u n="277" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> how long is his ponytail?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0326">like with middle of like the shoulder blades</u>
<u n="279" who="S0329">how embarrassing <trunc>y</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> did you say dad what's with the ponytail?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I was telling <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she's like I don't know what to do I'm like cut it off in his sleep please I'm not seeing him again till he gets rid of it</u>
<u n="281" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> er hang on what <trunc>di</trunc> what did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> say?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0326">she just said I know like she with the head like what the fuck?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0329">well at least you can talk to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can you talk to her?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0326">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s quite <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s lols <trunc>le</trunc> see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s more funny</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="285" who="S0329">you're lucky that you've got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> imagine if the <trunc>sh</trunc> there wasn't her</u>
<u n="286" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> it's so grim <pause dur="short"/> I couldn't say anything all dinner I was too in shock</u>
<u n="287" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0326">and too embarrassed cos I had to leave the house with him</u>
<u n="289" who="S0329">who cooked?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0326">no we went to a restaurant</u>
<u n="291" who="S0329">oh you went to a restaurant? oh they must be so loaded with money what er restaurant did they go to?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0326">er I I went er like you know that Greek one erm near near <anon type="place"/> or where <anon type="place"/> used to be up the towards <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0329">oh my god</u>
<u n="294" who="S0326" trans="overlap">like <anon type="place"/> or something?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0329"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0326">yeah <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0329">that's like one of the world's most expensive restaurants</u>
<u n="298" who="S0326">I know I went there with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s family <pause dur="long"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0329" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says they're having loads of work done in the house</u>
<u n="300" who="S0326">yes yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0329">but that it's still rubbish <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> is it still rubbish?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0326">well it's still a fucking bombsite</u>
<u n="303" who="S0329">so it's impossible to tell</u>
<u n="304" who="S0326">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well if they have er loads of money cos haven't they didn't buy a house at <anon type="place"/> which is retarded</u>
<u n="305" who="S0329">say that again</u>
<u n="306" who="S0326">I guess they have money so they didn't buy a house in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0329">I don't understand why they didn't if they had money</u>
<u n="308" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I thought the whole plan was they would sell their house and buy one in <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/> that's where dad's like I can can't I can gonna get a little flat</u>
<u n="309" who="S0329">and they haven't bought a house?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0326" trans="overlap">that at some point they decided not to buy a house in <anon type="place"/> and just get spend all their money in London</u>
<u n="311" who="S0329">and how often are they going to be in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0326">erm <pause dur="short"/> most of the year</u>
<u n="313" who="S0329">and what happens to their house when they're not there?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0326">I suppose they just do some of those academic swap things with someone in <anon type="place"/> or somewhere somewhere else</u>
<u n="315" who="S0329">well can you really not stay in dad's house? you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> why if you were <trunc>ha</trunc> <trunc>ha</trunc> you know if I rented out my house <pause dur="short"/> could you <trunc>t</trunc> would he make would he let you two be homeless?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0326">I dunno</u>
<u n="317" who="S0329">what do you feel about that?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0326">I don't wanna stay in that house I would rather find somewhere else to live</u>
<u n="319" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0329">why don't you want to stay in there? they're not there</u>
<u n="322" who="S0326">I don't know I just don't I just don't want to</u>
<u n="323" who="S0329">that's what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says but I mean what happens if I said I really need to rent the house out? I really need I've got to do it <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="324" who="S0326">right you you know what you could why don't you rent your house out <pause dur="short"/> to me <pause dur="short"/> and two of my friends? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0329">what two of your friends?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0326"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> needs somewhere to live <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> needs somewhere to live</u>
<u n="327" who="S0329">you think I'm gonna fucking rent my house to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/> are grown up now <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no I'm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but that way you wouldn't have to move all your shit you know? cos where would you put everything if you rented that out to a family? and you think you think the damage <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is gonna do compared to having like a family in there <pause dur="short"/> it's children</u>
<u n="331" who="S0329"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I mean er just for an example <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0329">no it would be like renting my house out to students they wouldn't they would</u>
<u n="334" who="S0326" trans="overlap">they're not it's</u>
<u n="335" who="S0329" trans="overlap">it would be trashed</u>
<u n="336" who="S0326" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> lives with grown up people <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s learnt to live with grown up people <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0329">where is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> living at the moment?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0326">I'm not actually sure she's been she's been in Miami a lot</u>
<u n="339" who="S0329">what's she been doing in Miami?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0326">I think she has a boyfriend there</u>
<u n="341" who="S0329">how is she earning any money?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0326">she's er a hostess there at a hotel</u>
<u n="343" who="S0329">what?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0326">she works as a hostess at a hotel</u>
<u n="345" who="S0329">what hotel?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0326"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0329">erm it's an idea <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> how much do you think I could charge?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0326">erm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0329" trans="overlap">what if it was just one of them?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0326">I reckon you could charge six hundred and seven hundred for the big one for <trunc>t</trunc> for <pause dur="short"/> for them to be able to afford it <pause dur="short"/> charge more otherwise but</u>
<u n="351" who="S0329">so for example next <pause dur="short"/> if I rented out one room <pause dur="long"/> yours or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <pause dur="long"/> I dunno</u>
<u n="352" who="S0326">it's hard to rent out one room though cos there would <trunc>s</trunc> there's empty rooms</u>
<u n="353" who="S0329">well they're not empty are they because you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are coming back all the time although I don't know how much <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will come back <pause dur="long"/> erm</u>
<u n="354" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I mean the problem with me is I don't actually rent my room all year round</u>
<u n="355" who="S0329">I know <pause dur="short"/> well look <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the truth is that I am <pause dur="short"/> probably going to go and live in France next year <pause dur="short"/> and that is that is the plan from the autumn <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>ha</trunc></u>
<u n="356" who="S0326" trans="overlap">what about your job?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0329">and I'll give my job up <pause dur="short"/> I it's I haven't said anything because it is <pause dur="short"/> there's quite a lot of fine-tuning to do I've been in discussions with work I erm <pause dur="short"/> I</u>
<u n="358" who="S0326" trans="overlap">won't you be totally bored though?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0329">no I won't be <trunc>t</trunc> at all bored for a second because I'll be developing my it would be other strings to my bow I'm slightly you know if I stay at the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's all it is that's all my life that's all my professional life for me and I've explained that to you I really needed to earn money to have a salary and a job when you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were growing up because having to to provide a roof over your heads and look after you but that you're grown up now or you're getting grown up you don't need parenting in the same way and so my need for a kind of salaried job is erm is lessened and I don't really find yes that's it's not erm <pause dur="short"/> you know I'd like to</u>
<u n="360" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0329">expand my life the <trunc>d</trunc> it seems pointless to me just going in every day into the office when you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and when I don't need to come home and cook for your and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that life is over I know that both you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> want me to <unclear/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0326" trans="overlap">no I don't mind <trunc>c</trunc> you go</u>
<u n="363" who="S0329">erm <pause dur="short"/> and I thought that actually this year is quite a good year because <trunc>y</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will be very much in <anon type="place"/> let's just say I</u>
<u n="364" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0329" trans="overlap">did it for a year</u>
<u n="366" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that's like</u>
<u n="367" who="S0329" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will be very much in <anon type="place"/> we can meet in the holidays either in France or in London the house will still be going <pause dur="short"/> erm but it will be where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I come back to so it wouldn't really be</u>
<u n="368" who="S0326">well what's happening to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house? it's sold?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0329">he's I think he's going <trunc>ye</trunc> I the idea is that he's going to sell it but this is what I mean about the fine-tuning we don't we had both our houses valued the other day guess what our house is worth?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0326">what?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0329">just have a little guess at what the estate agent said I could put it on the market for</u>
<u n="372" who="S0326">eight hundred thousand?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0329">have another guess</u>
<u n="374" who="S0326">a million?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0329">have another guess</u>
<u n="376" who="S0326">one point two million?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0329">one point two five million</u>
<u n="378" who="S0326">that's totally insane I don't</u>
<u n="379" who="S0329" trans="overlap">totally insane</u>
<u n="380" who="S0326" trans="overlap">makes me feel sick</u>
<u n="381" who="S0329">erm it makes me feel really rich <vocal desc="laugh"/> except that I can't access that money <pause dur="short"/> erm you know it's meaningless unless somebody gives me one point two five million obviously I've got a mortgage and the rest of it <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> er so we're you know we've got to work out ways of releasing some of the money so that I don't need my salary from work <pause dur="short"/> to keep me going through the next couple of years while I find <trunc>anoth</trunc> <trunc>oth</trunc>other ways of earning money <pause dur="short"/> yeah then oh fucking hell there might be a bit of a lean period erm but I think this is the time to do it <pause dur="long"/> but <pause dur="long"/> yeah like I say the fine <pause dur="short"/> the fine-tuning the actual practicalities not just the fine-tuning the practicalities how it is possible how it is manageable it's all very very much in the air so it's not <pause dur="short"/> it's not really we're not able to have a <pause dur="short"/> proper discussion about it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0326">so you're thinking what you could get somewhere and if you then rent out to</u>
<u n="383" who="S0329" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="long"/> I've got to I've actually got to write down the options and it might be that I need to to to talk to someone who can you know a proper financial advisor <pause dur="short"/> because one option would be that I would sell <pause dur="short"/> like say ten percent of my house to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> he pays for everything in France <pause dur="short"/> and supports me in France but he owns ten percent of my house and I've got money that's one I quite like that idea but er some people that I've spoken to</u>
<u n="384" who="S0326" trans="overlap">but his house must be worth like fucking forty-five mill then</u>
<u n="385" who="S0329">his house is worth two two point one</u>
<u n="386" who="S0326">I don't think that you could sell that house for that much money</u>
<u n="387" who="S0329">well I must admit I don't really think so either but that's</u>
<u n="388" who="S0326" trans="overlap">and they say I saw this article and it's just like <pause dur="short"/> it was really sad actually they were saying it was and they an interview with an estate agent and then another interview with someone who lives like sort of like has grown up and lived and is poor in east London and the estate agents are like <pause dur="short"/> their like teeth are like dripping with like money and greed and they're like <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>ta</trunc> the way they're talking is so repulsive and you have these people talking about their like trying to struggle here <pause dur="short"/> the estate agents</u>
<u n="389" who="S0329" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="390" who="S0326" trans="overlap">just here it's like party time man <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0329">no I know but the <trunc>p</trunc>poor person I mean I'm a poor person in in <anon type="place"/> it's just that my house suddenly is worth an incredible</u>
<u n="392" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0329" trans="overlap">amount of money</u>
<u n="394" who="S0326">but it hasn't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hasn't but they haven't been able to sell their house have they?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0329" trans="overlap">no they've sold it</u>
<u n="396" who="S0326">they've sold it</u>
<u n="397" who="S0329">they have now sold it so she'll be and that was one point two five <pause dur="long"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> it cos so that was another option that I would be thinking you know if if <pause dur="short"/> there was just a possibility that if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I didn't if it ever became too difficult for us to pool our resources in some way that I might strike out on my own but I don't think that's gonna happen but if I did you know I've got options I could sell the house</u>
<u n="398" who="S0326"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <trunc>t</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was quite funny about people who came to look at her house she just said they were so rich and they were all sort of quite <vocal desc="laugh"/> quite like shocked because her <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house is a bit like you know lived-in</u>
<u n="399" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know lived-in yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they'd come in in like suits and in snakeskin shoes and like turn their nose up</u>
<u n="401" who="S0329">I know</u>
<u n="402" who="S0326">it's gonna be so horrible to live there in five years in that area don't you think? <pause dur="short"/> it already is a bit</u>
<u n="403" who="S0329">I don't know it's hard to tell I quite you know I like what's been happening in our street for example or next to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the two houses next to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are like</u>
<u n="404" who="S0326">no but it's the kind of people around <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="405" who="S0329">yeah well the thing is I also don't need to have a house in <anon type="place"/> because you're not at school there you know that I it is an option to <pause dur="short"/> erm sell up buy a three-bedroom flat in <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> you know er there are there are total options <pause dur="short"/> er but I think it's I think it's a good <pause dur="short"/> er it's a good year to start exploring them <pause dur="long"/> anyway <pause dur="short"/> don't say anything to well not that you will see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but don't say anything to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> don't say anything to your friends cos it's not <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> it's all un un up in the air <pause dur="long"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I were saying last night when we go and live in France we're gonna get a dog <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm so excited</u>
<u n="406" who="S0326" trans="overlap">what's gonna happen to the tortoises?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0329">I've got a home for the <trunc>tor</trunc> but the next our next door neighbours really really they it was like all their Christmases had come at once when they got to</u>
<u n="408" who="S0326" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="409" who="S0329">look after our tortoises and I I can definitely offer them next door</u>
<u n="410" who="S0326">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> won't have that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0329">or I'm gonna take them to his house in in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0326">they won't survive that it's a student house <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0329">good point you think someone's gonna come home late at night and think there's some pies and put them in the oven?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0329">oh I'd like a nice crusty pie <pause dur="short"/> don't you think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s thin?</u>
<u n="416" who="S0326">yeah he's thin</u>
<u n="417" who="S0329">do you think he looks good did you say?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah he looks thin</u>
<u n="419" who="S0329">he looks thin yeah he's lost ten kilos <pause dur="short"/> do you think I look thin?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0326">you always look thin</u>
<u n="421" who="S0329">do I always look thin? oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0329">I did bring you up well <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> anyway what did you have to eat at <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0326">it's not very I <unclear>imagine</unclear> it's not not a good restaurant <pause dur="long"/> erm I just had some prawns</u>
<u n="425" who="S0329">that's such a New York thing to do isn't it? go out to eat in a restaurant instead of</u>
<u n="426" who="S0326">well they've got I to be I guess they can't use their house cos it's</u>
<u n="427" who="S0329" trans="overlap">oh I see</u>
<u n="428" who="S0326" trans="overlap">a building site it's like <pause dur="short"/> it's like we always get Turkish kebabs</u>
<u n="429" who="S0329">and</u>
<u n="430" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I don't know why you'd go to that restaurant when you could go to so much better ones <pause dur="short"/> for the same price</u>
<u n="431" who="S0329">how is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> must be</u>
<u n="432" who="S0326" trans="overlap">she's</u>
<u n="433" who="S0329" trans="overlap">quite old now</u>
<u n="434" who="S0326"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is incredibly boring</u>
<u n="435" who="S0329">incredibly boring?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0326">you know whether she should send <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> to a private school or a state school?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0329">beg your pardon?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0326">talking about school to send <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> to</u>
<u n="439" who="S0329">oh my god that sounds like pulling teeth</u>
<u n="440" who="S0326">I know man I couldn't get out of there quick enough</u>
<u n="441" who="S0329">you are so lucky I got divorced Jesus Christ <vocal desc="laugh"/> aren't you?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0329">I could see that coming <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> also this weather I haven't got my umbrella <pause dur="short"/> it was so beautiful and sunny in <anon type="place"/> and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> god it's it's really it's fantastic here it's like being on a summer holiday and he said this is the first day the sun's come out <vocal desc="laugh"/> the whole year that I've been here <pause dur="short"/> he did have a fantastic year <pause dur="short"/> and it's quite odd isn't it because he's finished the whole first year at university and he's still only eighteen</u>
<u n="444" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="445" who="S0329">and he's with like his friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is twenty looking at her I mean being twenty-one quite soon she took a year off and is has an autumn birthday but they're er at the same in the same year at university that's why he seems so young immature</u>
<u n="446" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="447" who="S0329">I've always been longing for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to grow up <vocal desc="laugh"/> I and I think that's because he seems er younger than his cohorts</u>
<u n="448" who="S0326">I was younger than my cohort that I mean er er</u>
<u n="449" who="S0329"><vocal desc="misc"/> what did you say?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0326">I've always been the youngest though</u>
<u n="451" who="S0329">yes you're one of the youngest as well although not if you took a year out</u>
<u n="452" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I know but I also to me with my <trunc>frien</trunc> friendship</u>
<u n="453" who="S0329" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0326" trans="overlap">group</u>
<u n="455" who="S0329">well because you were friends with people who were the year above you weren't you?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="457" who="S0329" trans="overlap">at school and then have you seen much of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> been in touch with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0326">erm <pause dur="short"/> not not not <trunc>f</trunc> I think</u>
<u n="459" who="S0329" trans="overlap">not</u>
<u n="460" who="S0326">I think maybe like a week ago I when I was going to Mexico and she asked me what I was doing <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0329">maybe I'll get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a cake in <anon type="place"/> that's the thing to do</u>
<u n="462" who="S0326">well but there's no good cake shops in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0329">aren't there any sort of dinky? isn't there a dinky?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0326">there's like a famous bakery called <anon type="place"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says it's really bad</u>
<u n="465" who="S0329">mm okay I think I'll go to <anon type="place"/> and get some macaroons on the way back <pause dur="short"/> I mean she's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s had such a terrible terrible time I don't know whether I told you but her daughter <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has been sectioned do you know what that is?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0329">erm I mean the she to be sectioned is very very very serious erm and she's you know naked walking up and down the streets wailing <pause dur="short"/> erm er absolutely out of her head accusing her dad of raping her and then the next minute going oh did I just say that? I can't believe that and then wailing and</u>
<u n="468" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0329">erm and she's locked up in a loony bin and not allowed out for a month <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are exhausted and they know that she that's her condition for life and they will have to <pause dur="short"/> it's not like she's going to get better it's not like flu it's you know and that they will have to look after her forever <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> himself is not that well and he's <unclear>seventy</unclear> and <pause dur="short"/> how old is dad?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0326">sixty-three oh not that old</u>
<u n="471" who="S0329">he's two years older than <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then <pause dur="long"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> seems like a teenager <pause dur="short"/> doesn't he? I mean like not in necessarily in terms of looks but <pause dur="long"/> you know his party lifestyle perhaps you don't see his party lifestyle <pause dur="long"/> well why wasn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> there?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0326">well he was working</u>
<u n="473" who="S0329">and sending people to sleep?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm any discussion of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0326">no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has <trunc>m</trunc> texted me recently though while I was in Mexico she says she was like shall we get shall I get you a bit late birthday drink? and I said I'm in I'm in Mexico and she says you're always in fucking Mexico</u>
<u n="477" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0329">oh I'd like to see her haven't seen her for ages haven't been in touch oh I think I might send her a text <pause dur="short"/> she should come round where is she she lives in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0326">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="481" who="S0329">I've got to go to I'm going round to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s tomorrow I'm just going to have to duck and hope that I don't see dad I mean it is just bizarre I spend so much time in <anon type="place"/> road you know where that restaurant is? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="482" who="S0326">oh well you'll be gone in August I will I would actually quite like to go to <anon type="place"/> if you can get me a ticket and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would like to go but I can't go if he's got a a ponytail do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0329">I think I I think you can go if it's just if he's got a ponytail</u>
<u n="484" who="S0326">I can't I literally can't and I don't want to be</u>
<u n="485" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you can you won't have to see him</u>
<u n="486" who="S0326">yeah but I will if he gets me a ticket</u>
<u n="487" who="S0329">did you tell <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="490" who="S0326">she was just like shame shame on you</u>
<u n="491" who="S0329">that's so funny <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> people always say won't you be bored in France? why would I be? I'm never bored anywhere <pause dur="short"/> it's true there are no people there</u>
<u n="492" who="S0326">there's no is there like a is there like a bar or pub or something?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0329">not for about three-quarters of a hour drive <pause dur="short"/> and they're really unglamorous <pause dur="short"/> like it's the most unglamorous part of France really working class grimy and erm uninteresting right I want to come off the next next <pause dur="short"/> but if you came it would be fun</u>
<u n="494" who="S0326">are you going this summer?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0329">supposed to go the second half of August but everything's a bit in the air at the moment <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will be going</u>
<u n="496" who="S0326">cos we could come then I'd like to see it</u>
<u n="497" who="S0329">yeah you should we would like you to see it erm <pause dur="long"/> so have you got no other plans then for this summer?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0326">well I'm definitely going to Greece</u>
<u n="499" who="S0329">when are you going to Greece?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0326">I haven't booked it but probably in September it's cheaper emptier and nicer</u>
<u n="501" who="S0329">yeah you don't wanna go there go in August basically the the real problem is you don't want to go anywhere in August apart from</u>
<u n="502" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0329">Scotland</u>
<u n="504" who="S0326">yeah it's true</u>
<u n="505" who="S0329">erm <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't particularly like being in France in <pause dur="short"/> in August but it's just too hot it's just can't do anything you can't do anything cos he wants to do like gardening he just says you <trunc>wa</trunc> flops by the pool <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> but it's not like</u>
<u n="506" who="S0326" trans="overlap">why don't you get a house in Scotland?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0329">well we might do that too</u>
<u n="508" who="S0326">that would be good you should do that</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="509" who="S0329">I think the <trunc>id</trunc> the idea is really to just throw throw everything up in the air and see where it lands <pause dur="long"/> I need a wee <pause dur="long"/> god it does not take long to get to <anon type="place"/> does it? <pause dur="short"/> whereas <anon type="place"/> just takes forever</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="510" who="S0326">wow it's properly raining isn't it?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0329">yeah we oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> you should get in touch with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> anyway</u>
<u n="512" who="S0326">yeah I'll send him a message later</u>
<u n="513" who="S0329">have you got his number?</u>
<u n="514" who="S0326">I don't think I do</u>
<u n="515" who="S0329">what the fuck is happening here? <pause dur="short"/> erm or he's in <pause dur="short"/> he's on Facebook <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> isn't he? he's a real Facebook person</u>
<u n="516" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I don't really use Facebook</u>
<u n="517" who="S0329">well you might have to get on it in order to be in touch with him or he's gone to Switzerland so I don't particularly want to text him for his number</u>
<u n="518" who="S0326">can't wait for the day when people are not on Facebook and you don't have to go on it</u>
<u n="519" who="S0329">well obviously that's my every day</u>
<u n="520" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0329">but there will come</u>
<u n="522" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0329" trans="overlap">a time won't there?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0329" trans="overlap">I mean it's just but won't it be replaced by something else?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0326">yeah but something not so sort of something more like Instagram or Twitter</u>
<u n="527" who="S0329">so you think you were well lols when you put that on <vocal desc="laugh"/> my picture</u>
<u n="528" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no that not I must say a little bit lols</u>
<u n="529" who="S0329"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I love the way that <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> always like my Instagram pictures they <unclear/></u>
<u n="530" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> where were you then anyway?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0329">at the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0326">what's the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0329">the <anon type="place"/> club it's a club in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> but I was the only person that had lunch with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s a member of the club in fact so is <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> I really want to be a member I was thinking of buying <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a membership for his birthday so <vocal desc="laugh"/> I could get in there but then I thought it's a bit mean to buy someone who can't eat and drink a a membership to a club where that's the only point of going</u>
<u n="534" who="S0326">when's he going to be able to eat again?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0329">I think he'll never be able to eat erm I think pasta and bread that's it <pause dur="short"/> never again <pause dur="short"/> but I don't miss pasta and oh I do miss pasta a bit <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> and rice no no more risottos</u>
<u n="536" who="S0326">or maybe you've got to go to that place in Tuscany and have the goose pasta</u>
<u n="537" who="S0329">oh you she was fucking last thing that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will he'll</u>
<u n="538" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="539" who="S0329">probably spontaneously combust</u>
<u n="540" who="S0329">he can't even</u>
<u n="541" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I mean we got me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I have been invited back there</u>
<u n="542" who="S0329">have you?</u>
<u n="543" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="544" who="S0329">what do you mean invited? what does that mean?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0326">come and stay and eat for free cos they're the the woman loves <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she has this really funny son who's obviously gay who's who loves <unclear>being</unclear> more than anything in the world <vocal desc="laugh"/> when we got back <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sent him like a box of cookbooks and tools and ingredients</u>
<u n="546" who="S0329">ah <pause dur="short"/> she's so nice <pause dur="long"/> how <trunc>mu</trunc> if I'd ordered that cake <trunc>nor</trunc> normal price how much would it have been?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0326">I don't know don't know how big it was or anything</u>
<u n="548" who="S0329">it was fucking big I couldn't carry it it needed two people to carry it <vocal desc="laugh"/> to the car <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>loo</trunc> everything's full I can oh no I don't need to</u>
<u n="549" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="550" who="S0329" trans="overlap">worry about that cos I go to your special little parking place</u>
<u n="551" who="S0326">but yeah today is definitely the day that people get picked up <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0329">so what is the outcome? is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> going to send <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> to</u>
<u n="553" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I think a state school</u>
<u n="554" who="S0329">a state school? oh how <unclear>classy</unclear> <pause dur="long"/> how old is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0326">oh I dunno <pause dur="short"/> twenty-six maybe? I have no idea</u>
<u n="556" who="S0329">that's amazing amazing <pause dur="short"/> and she's living all by herself in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="558" who="S0329">that's pretty impressive <pause dur="short"/> I mean it's true that it's quite astonishing that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> chose that moment to sell <vocal desc="laugh"/> why couldn't he just wait a few years?</u>
<u n="559" who="S0326">well I think that's what he was waiting for but it was <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="560" who="S0329">it looked like she was never gonna pop her clogs how long does he have to wait? yeah I agree <pause dur="short"/> that was another reason why I kind of think this year is a good year to go away cos granny doesn't need me to push her around in a bath chair now</u>
<u n="561" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> is there any water here?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0329">no it was mistake to not buy some in the petrol station but I was so bamboozled by paying first I couldn't kind of <pause dur="short"/> it was confusing <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> if I'd stayed in <anon type="place"/> that's what I would have turned into <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> erm why do I feel very confused?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0326">I dunno I've never seen any of this before</u>
<u n="564" who="S0329">no it's</u>
<u n="565" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0329">we've been <trunc>tur</trunc> I I don't know where the <trunc>fu</trunc> it's because of the <pause dur="short"/> oh no I know where we are <pause dur="short"/> I think I know where we are</u>
<u n="567" who="S0326">I doubt it</u>
<u n="568" who="S0329">well it's cos of all those <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> cones</u>
<u n="569" who="S0326">I've never seen this before it looks quite nice</u>
<u n="570" who="S0329">oh no I think I know where we are</u>
<u n="571" who="S0326">I yeah I know where we are but it's not exactly close to where we need to be</u>
<u n="572" who="S0329">well look this is all I was doing was following the road <pause dur="short"/> I thought you were gonna take me to <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="573" who="S0326">yeah we didn't you have to come in a week otherwise it's a total nightmare we can still do that in the summer but it's not</u>
<u n="574" who="S0329" trans="overlap">did you have er you know what was your last you didn't have <trunc>s</trunc>summer here did you? what was it? fucking hell where am I?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0326">it's we've been to that that's the pub we went to with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> no it's not it's not it's not</u>
<u n="576" who="S0329">it's all been dug up and it's all different isn't it?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0326">yeah you should see what they're doing by the station I must say it looks totally skyscrapers</u>
<u n="578" who="S0329">they just keep trying to build skyscrapers in the village in <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/> country</u>
<u n="579" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0329">erm there's been programmes on the radio about it I mean there's the development and the building they're trying to pretend er throughout the whole of Britain that they're trying to pretend that it's because we need houses but it isn't because there are plenty of <pause dur="short"/> there are plenty of houses ring road <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="581" who="S0326">yeah I mean the reason why they're doing that massive development by the station and is because it's only forty-five minutes away from Kings Cross so it's like a borough of London <pause dur="long"/> I'd definitely never</u>
<u n="582" who="S0329">no</u>
<u n="583" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I went there with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="584" who="S0329">did you? I don't know where the fuck to go <pause dur="short"/> it's totally <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> and it's all diverted traffic that's been diverted so let's just <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and it's</u>
<u n="585" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0329">take that away put me somewhere where I can I think I'll go <anon type="place"/> street <pause dur="long"/> summer rain <pause dur="long"/> okay how about now are you familiar with anything now?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0326">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="588" who="S0329">isn't that your college down there?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="590" who="S0329">what college is that?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0326">that's <anon type="place"/> college</u>
<u n="592" who="S0329"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> diverted traffic maybe I'll just follow the signs</u>
<u n="593" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah follow the sign</u>
<u n="594" who="S0329">diverted <pause dur="long"/> look at these splendid houses maybe this is where people like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="long"/> it's got to be down there hasn't it? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="595" who="S0326">yeah they all look like student student houses <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="596" who="S0329">yeah it's fun being a student even if you're having a terrible time <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="597" who="S0326"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="598" who="S0329">right <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> any ideas?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0326">yeah keep following the diverted traffic I reckon <pause dur="short"/> I reckon <pause dur="long"/> what are you going to get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for his birthday?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0329">erm nothing very much erm I've been trying to get him a pair of trousers but he needed to try them on <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> you know until I release the money out of my house I'm still completely and utterly broke <vocal desc="laugh"/> so <pause dur="short"/> this doesn't look very promising ever been here before?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0326">yeah I've been the <trunc>thea</trunc> the theatre <pause dur="short"/> oh man</u>
<u n="602" who="S0329">oh god misery <unclear/> erm what are you getting him for his birthday? what I thought is that when we're all back you me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> granny we'll all <trunc>ha</trunc> all have a birthday a <trunc>bir</trunc> a birthday day <pause dur="short"/> erm and combine them all because we've all missed everybody's birthdays haven't we?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0326">yeah I suppose so <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="604" who="S0329">I think that would be a good thing to do so it'll have to be</u>
<u n="605" who="S0326">when's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> back from?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0329"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s back quite soon <pause dur="short"/> does that mean you see that no entry sign?</u>
<u n="607" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="608" who="S0329">where is that for?</u>
<u n="609" who="S0326">that road</u>
<u n="610" who="S0329">okay</u>
<u n="611" who="S0326">why don't you do a U though?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0329">where are these are these people queueing to park?</u>
<u n="613" who="S0326">does this say diverted traffic? no what is that sign? <pause dur="long"/> that car's coming back <pause dur="short"/> they're probably keen to turn round I think</u>
<u n="614" who="S0329">they're going into the car park but I don't want to go into the car park</u>
<u n="615" who="S0326">do turn around</u>
<u n="616" who="S0329">can I just <pause dur="short"/> well I'll see <pause dur="short"/> do what that car's done I just don't wanna be queueing for the car park <pause dur="long"/> this is hell on toast <pause dur="short"/> what happens round here?</u>
<u n="617" who="S0326">that's a pub I know lots of people who go to that pub</u>
<u n="618" who="S0329">how could this be diverted traffic?</u>
<u n="619" who="S0326">I dunno I <trunc>j</trunc> back we ought to turn around</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="620" who="S0329">fantastic <pause dur="long"/> oh great <pause dur="short"/> thank you everybody <pause dur="long"/> the students are here</u>
<u n="621" who="S0326">probably yeah <pause dur="long"/> they're quite nice little houses</u>
<u n="622" who="S0329">yeah almshouses I imagine they are right <unclear/></u>
<u n="623" who="S0326">what's an almshouse?</u>
<u n="624" who="S0329">almshouses are houses that were built by the church for erm old people</u>
<u n="625" who="S0326">do they <unclear>fish</unclear> do they still do that?</u>
<u n="626" who="S0329">no</u>
<u n="627" who="S0326">well they should be</u>
<u n="628" who="S0329">it was a sort of movement in in the nineteenth century in fact quite until I don't know very much about it and until quite far up into the erm twentieth century <pause dur="short"/> and that they were a particular sort of architecture like a sort of social housing everyone's going one way and I'm going to go <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="629" who="S0326">thing is now we are like deep in one way <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="630" who="S0329">right okay well at least we know where we are now <pause dur="short"/> don't we?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0329">erm <pause dur="short"/> so I have to I have to take the right-hand turn <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="633" who="S0326">need to get to the other side of town but I don't know how to do that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="634" who="S0329">oh but I was just here was I not? was I not darling? I was just here</u>
<u n="635" who="S0326">have to go left</u>
<u n="636" who="S0329">it's some wanker</u>
<u n="637" who="S0326"><vocal desc="sneeze"/></u>
<u n="638" who="S0329">bless you <pause dur="long"/> I must the diverted traffic signals seem sent to tease one <pause dur="long"/> at times like this aren't you glad that I'm a mother and relaxed? because if you were in a car with a control freak man you'd be totally freaking out at this stage</u>
<u n="639" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> yeah that's <anon type="place"/> college <pause dur="short"/> they have a cricket pitch in their college</u>
<u n="640" who="S0329">do they?</u>
<u n="641" who="S0326">down there <pause dur="long"/> I can keep going all the way then go right you wanna go right</u>
<u n="642" who="S0329" trans="overlap">can you remember what erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was at?</u>
<u n="643" who="S0326">yeah erm</u>
<u n="644" who="S0329" trans="overlap">was it <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="645" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="646" who="S0329">what was it?</u>
<u n="647" who="S0326">it was <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="648" who="S0329">oh <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> all routes except cycles</u>
<u n="649" who="S0326">go for oh I can go that one where the bus is going</u>
<u n="650" who="S0329">oh okay</u>
<u n="651" who="S0326">I reckon</u>
<u n="652" who="S0329">why is that person going the wrong way round the <vocal desc="laugh"/> roundabout on a bicycle? it looks so dangerous</u>
<u n="653" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="654" who="S0329">right says it's a dead end so</u>
<u n="655" who="S0326" trans="overlap">oh my days that's the</u>
<u n="656" who="S0329" trans="overlap">I er ain't going there</u>
<u n="657" who="S0326" trans="overlap">the there's no way that way then we've got to go back where we came <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="658" who="S0329">well I could go along that</u>
<u n="659" who="S0326" trans="overlap">mm oh I doubt that's the right way that's just out of <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="long"/> it's fucking mental we've got it down so perfectly with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> hadn't we?</u>
<u n="660" who="S0329">yeah <pause dur="long"/> erm oh and I don't have my phone with me and <trunc>y</trunc>your phone should be able to do the do a map Google</u>
<u n="661" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0329">Maps</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
