<text id="SN26">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:13:42</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-02-19</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0364 S0420</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Brucefield Farm, Livingston</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Twitter, social media, work</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking sharing uses of social media for work and pleasure</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0364">
				<exactage>33</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Edinburgh</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Scotland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Scotland</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Edinburgh</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Livingston, West Lothian</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Scotland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2.5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>scotland</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>scotland</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>scotland</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Communications Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0420">
				<exactage>32</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>Scotish</nat>
				<birthplace>Edinburgh</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Scotland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Scotland</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Edinburgh</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Edinburgh</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Scotland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>scotland</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>scotland</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>scotland</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Director of Studies</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0364">in a Scottish accent</u>
<u n="2" who="S0420" trans="overlap">so you use so you <trunc>s</trunc> well aye <pause dur="short"/> but you use <trunc>c</trunc> Twitter quite a lot don't you?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0364">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> loads <pause dur="short"/> loads</u>
<u n="4" who="S0420" trans="overlap">but like but is it more for like? personal stuff or or or or for work or for both or what?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0364">ah personal stuff I do it a bit for work <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> so I tweet some <pause dur="short"/> some of my work <trunc>s</trunc> account things but no mostly mostly personal <pause dur="short"/> news <pause dur="short"/> sport</u>
<u n="6" who="S0420">is that what they say is like a primary source or d'you think?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0364" trans="overlap">crazy stuff <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="8" who="S0420">like throughout the day?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0364">erm <pause dur="short"/> d'you know I'll go in and have a look at night I don't sorta look at it in the morning as much now</u>
<u n="10" who="S0420">no</u>
<u n="11" who="S0364">I've got</u>
<u n="12" who="S0420" trans="overlap">not like a breakfast thing or?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0364">in maybe weekends but <unclear>no</unclear> during the week <pause dur="short"/> during the week I'll go on the BBC</u>
<u n="14" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0364">the BBC news app <pause dur="short"/> I'll check that instead <pause dur="short"/> and then pick up stuff from like <pause dur="short"/> pick up stuff from the radio and that so <unclear>no no</unclear> it's more <pause dur="short"/> it's more in the in the evenings actually and like if there's a football game on</u>
<u n="16" who="S0420">yeah I can never understand that how d'you follow something on Twitter?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0364" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="18" who="S0420">cos I know you've got hashtags and stuff but <pause dur="short"/> like how d'you follow a game or follow a a conversation?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0364">well you you <trunc>f</trunc> well you can you can search on the hashtag <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> if you you search on hashtag HMFC <pause dur="short"/> I quite often do that actually I've got a saved search on that and you'll just see anyone anything that anyone has hashtagged that and <pause dur="short"/> you'll see</u>
<u n="20" who="S0420" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>if</unclear></u>
<u n="21" who="S0364" trans="overlap">so then you'll get lots of Hearts stuff</u>
<u n="22" who="S0420">I <unclear>don't get it</unclear> so</u>
<u n="23" who="S0364">erm</u>
<u n="24" who="S0420">you put something back you have to do the same hashtag</u>
<u n="25" who="S0364">yes</u>
<u n="26" who="S0420">in order for other people</u>
<u n="27" who="S0364" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0420">to find it</u>
<u n="29" who="S0364">so like during the World Cup there was <unclear>a lot of that</unclear></u>
<u n="30" who="S0420" trans="overlap">so it's quite organic how it how that happens then?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0364" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> aye <pause dur="short"/> there was loads of hashtags during the World Cup that were like <pause dur="short"/> they had a three digit code <pause dur="short"/> that's it aye so like basically the three initials from each of the teams</u>
<u n="32" who="S0420">uhu</u>
<u n="33" who="S0364">and it would just be hashtag so-and-so V so-and-so</u>
<u n="34" who="S0420">okay</u>
<u n="35" who="S0364">and you could basically follow the game <pause dur="short"/> what everyone was saying so you could look at photos</u>
<u n="36" who="S0420">and was that like in different languages as well?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0364">yeah yeah well aye yeah absolutely during the World Cup yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> so quite a good way of seeing what's going on <pause dur="short"/> quite often I'm on Twitter <pause dur="short"/> there'd be games on Sky that I'm not watching but you can keep track of it</u>
<u n="38" who="S0420">but <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>although</unclear> d'you not find that sometimes sometimes people just post <unclear>stuff</unclear>? <pause dur="short"/> it's like being in the middle of a cloud and people everybody shouting at the same time</u>
<u n="39" who="S0364">well kinda yeah kinda yeah yeah but it's <pause dur="short"/> if it's yeah yeah I've never done it when I've been at an event I've never been at a sports event and sort of done it as well but <unclear>I think it would be quite good</unclear></u>
<u n="40" who="S0420" trans="overlap">like <unclear>everything</unclear> is it not the equivalent of like being in the middle of a crowd and everybody shouting?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0364" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah aye I suppose if you're if there's a penalty shootout for our team that I'm close to or interested in <pause dur="short"/> then the just by <pause dur="short"/> having my network based on all the people that are interested as well it's erm it is kinda like that yeah yeah I've you know if <trunc>some</trunc> if a team scores a goal <pause dur="short"/> I've maybe seen twelve fifteen tweets <pause dur="short"/> of that team having scored you know?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0420">and the news <pause dur="short"/> the same <pause dur="short"/> like getting <trunc>get</trunc>getting news</u>
<u n="43" who="S0364" trans="overlap">what's that? <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah well you'll get lots of different sources'll have their say but <pause dur="short"/> of course for that like <pause dur="short"/> I'm only</u>
<u n="44" who="S0420" trans="overlap">d'you follow d'you follow? like <pause dur="short"/> commentators or like <trunc>col</trunc>?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0364" trans="overlap">a few of them <pause dur="short"/> aye a few of them</u>
<u n="46" who="S0420" trans="overlap">columnists or something?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0364">a few of them <pause dur="short"/> a few of them yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> not so much with er <pause dur="short"/> not so much with the news actually I more just keep it on reliable news outlets but in the sport yeah yeah some decent sports journalists like a lot of the Scottish <pause dur="short"/> lot of the <unclear>SPD</unclear> and BBC like sports journalists <pause dur="short"/> so <unclear>that would</unclear></u>
<u n="48" who="S0420" trans="overlap">and do they do they use it to break stories as well now?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0364">yeah yeah absolutely aye aye so</u>
<u n="50" who="S0420" trans="overlap">like attracted interest like</u>
<u n="51" who="S0364">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0420">breadcrumbs to to that story</u>
<u n="53" who="S0364" trans="overlap">both <pause dur="short"/> both stories <pause dur="short"/> but then also <pause dur="short"/> controversial statements that they probably could put in their stories things like that</u>
<u n="54" who="S0420" trans="overlap">also like they can be a bit more personal about it?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0364" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh aye absolutely <pause dur="short"/> absolutely they you know so Rangers get a lot of <pause dur="short"/> hassle they get you know they get ripped into quite a lot erm <pause dur="short"/> by the journalists</u>
<u n="56" who="S0420">so is it is it is it? d'you think it makes it a danger? or a creates a danger of the news becoming <pause dur="short"/> very subjective then?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0364">yeah <pause dur="short"/> could be but then I dunno</u>
<u n="58" who="S0420">er yeah if yeah if people like</u>
<u n="59" who="S0364">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0420">yourself using it as one of the primary sources of getting news</u>
<u n="61" who="S0364">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0420">d'you think that that poses a danger at all?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0364">well sometimes</u>
<u n="64" who="S0420" trans="overlap">or or or is it even better cos it's so open <unclear>in effect</unclear>?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0364" trans="overlap">I dunno it's quite open isn't it cos? well newspapers have still got a role in setting the news agenda hey so <pause dur="short"/> this almost <pause dur="short"/> well Twitter <trunc>d</trunc> er no it doesn't <trunc>sm</trunc> I don't think it sets the news agenda but <pause dur="short"/> quite often <pause dur="short"/> you'll see journalists using tweets <pause dur="short"/> in <pause dur="short"/> stories</u>
<u n="66" who="S0420">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0364">you so-and-so on <trunc>T</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> you know so you will see stories that are just <pause dur="short"/> oh so-and-so and so-and-so had an argument on Twitter and it will just be quotes from that</u>
<u n="68" who="S0420">no see I'm not I'm not a fan of</u>
<u n="69" who="S0364" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="70" who="S0420">not a fan of that kinda stuff</u>
<u n="71" who="S0364">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="72" who="S0420">like the the have your say sections at the bottom of articles</u>
<u n="73" who="S0364" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0420">and stuff or when they do a <unclear/> <unclear>like</unclear> just send us your</u>
<u n="75" who="S0364">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0420">erm text in tell us what you think it's like well <pause dur="short"/> if I <unclear>felt like</unclear> that I'd speak to one of my mates I wouldn't</u>
<u n="77" who="S0364" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0420">necessarily <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>ask anyone</unclear> to shout out at one time</u>
<u n="79" who="S0364">no interesting aye that's a point but I mean <pause dur="short"/> yeah you could say that you could say that but <pause dur="short"/> I dunno news is subjective anyway huh? I think</u>
<u n="80" who="S0420">well it is it is but it's it's always been seen to be objective</u>
<u n="81" who="S0364">mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0420">whereas Twitter is sort of by its very nature subjective isn't it?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0364">mm <pause dur="short"/> aye</u>
<u n="84" who="S0420">well that's what they want they want sort of er personalised opinions</u>
<u n="85" who="S0364">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no no absolutely well aye and there's the whole thing about like <pause dur="short"/> a re-tweet isn't an endorsement eh? cos it <pause dur="short"/> I would never re-tweet anything dodgy</u>
<u n="86" who="S0420">well cos it opens up to</u>
<u n="87" who="S0364" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0420">to accusations doesn't it? I mean</u>
<u n="89" who="S0364">some people aye <pause dur="short"/> there's quite a lot people have that as a <pause dur="short"/> what's the word? a little disclaimer</u>
<u n="90" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0364">you know <trunc>pers</trunc>personal views only <unclear>and not for use</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> so a lot of BBC journalists will say not the views of my view views not those of my employer</u>
<u n="92" who="S0420">yeah <unclear>so</unclear></u>
<u n="93" who="S0364">and then also like re-tweet doesn't mean an endorsement</u>
<u n="94" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0364">cos it could just be <pause dur="short"/> trying to generate a debate <pause dur="short"/> this is</u>
<u n="96" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0364">what so <trunc>and</trunc> this is what someone says <pause dur="short"/> not I agree with that</u>
<u n="98" who="S0420" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> and so for work though I mean erm <pause dur="short"/> obviously like for <pause dur="short"/> an education that people raise issues and chat about things or</u>
<u n="99" who="S0364">mm mm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0420">maybe <pause dur="short"/> er we have like a group</u>
<u n="101" who="S0364">mm mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0420" trans="overlap">erm every Wednesday at twelve o'clock <pause dur="short"/> we go on Twitter</u>
<u n="103" who="S0364">right</u>
<u n="104" who="S0420">and we'll erm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0364"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0420">and and and for that hour everybody'll tweet using that certain hashtag to discuss a particular topic d'you ever think anything like that in in finance or? communications?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0364" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> not in my not in my job cos it's internal <unclear>eh</unclear> but erm <pause dur="short"/> and I'm trying to think if we've had people no we've had people on erm <pause dur="short"/> the Guardian website <pause dur="short"/> doing like online conversations we do it internally with staff but <pause dur="short"/> not on erm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0420" trans="overlap">all the type of all the type of webinar kind of?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0364">yeah yeah oh but I'll like do I I did a webinar just <pause dur="short"/> not me personally but I was a part of organising a webinar on Tuesday this week yeah yeah so I do <pause dur="short"/> that sort of thing all the time and we do</u>
<u n="110" who="S0420" trans="overlap">and is that through Twitter at all?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0364">no not it's all see the ones that I do are internal and therefore <pause dur="short"/> it would be using our own intranet but yeah we do an online conversation where it's like right this senior leader <pause dur="short"/> someone who's an expert on something</u>
<u n="112" who="S0420">feel free to post <unclear>questions</unclear> and like <trunc>Q</trunc> like a Q and A basically?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0364" trans="overlap"><unclear>huge kind of</unclear> aye <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>onli</trunc> aye online Q and A I quite like them we've not <pause dur="short"/> we've probably not done enough of them I quite like them it's a little bit different to cos the one I did earlier this week was a webinar <pause dur="short"/> which is good you know? but it's a little bit more traditional eh? someone talks through</u>
<u n="114" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0364">slides takes questions <pause dur="short"/> depends what the erm <pause dur="short"/> content is eh?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0420">depends on the I guess on the users' or or the presenters' comfort zone in the technology as well</u>
<u n="117" who="S0364">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0420">cos</u>
<u n="119" who="S0364"><unclear>I</unclear></u>
<u n="120" who="S0420" trans="overlap">Twitter Twitter's a different kind of</u>
<u n="121" who="S0364">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0420">kettle of fish in some ways</u>
<u n="123" who="S0364">yes <pause dur="short"/> well you can get <pause dur="short"/> if you do a webinar you you're in control of the questions and it's sequential eh right?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0364">question <pause dur="short"/> next question</u>
<u n="126" who="S0420" trans="overlap">and you get your presentation first and</u>
<u n="127" who="S0364">yes</u>
<u n="128" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0364">whereas <pause dur="short"/> yeah when we've done these online conversations it's like <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>mm</unclear> people have their questions written in Word <pause dur="short"/> beforehand and they just copy and paste it in</u>
<u n="130" who="S0420">ah <unclear>that's it</unclear></u>
<u n="131" who="S0364" trans="overlap">you know bit three paragraph questions</u>
<u n="132" who="S0420">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but you've <trunc>als</trunc> you've also got the risk of someone trying to someone trying to monopolise the conversation or or</u>
<u n="133" who="S0364">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0420">steer it in a certain way which</u>
<u n="135" who="S0364">aye totally</u>
<u n="136" who="S0420" trans="overlap">maybe doesn't really interest everybody else</u>
<u n="137" who="S0364">yes yes no no absolutely absolutely so no no but not not so much on Twitter and I'm trying to think if our <pause dur="short"/> if our guys have have done that we've not had any leaders doing it but we've got erm social media teams who are</u>
<u n="138" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0364">like we've got accounts <pause dur="short"/> where customers can ask questions and we will like answer them back</u>
<u n="140" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0364">erm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah but I tried using that with Scottish Power <pause dur="short"/> didn't happen</u>
<u n="143" who="S0364">mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0420">that was Facebook not Twitter but erm Scottish Power said leave a message</u>
<u n="145" who="S0364">ah right?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0420"><unclear>that query about your account</unclear></u>
<u n="147" who="S0364">never worked?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0420" trans="overlap">cos <unclear>I was trying to call them</unclear> they haven't responded in a week</u>
<u n="149" who="S0364">aye see that's not that's not good that's not good yeah yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0420">it gives you a negative impression of of them</u>
<u n="151" who="S0364">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0420">if if they're gonna have that service</u>
<u n="153" who="S0364" trans="overlap">aye</u>
<u n="154" who="S0420">then they've got</u>
<u n="155" who="S0364">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0420">to man it <pause dur="short"/> or they've got to have someone</u>
<u n="157" who="S0364" trans="overlap">absolutely</u>
<u n="158" who="S0420">sorting it out yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0364" trans="overlap">absolutely <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah we I've I've used our web chat service a few times it's pretty good</u>
<u n="160" who="S0420">yeah?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0364">but they're the <pause dur="short"/> the worst thing is when you <pause dur="short"/> go to try and use it and get aye you know it's like oh chat to an agent and then you click on it and it doesn't work</u>
<u n="162" who="S0420" trans="overlap"><unclear>it's just redundant</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0364">it needs to be <pause dur="short"/> it can't just be technology for technology's sake it needs to work as well as or be as convenient if not more than <pause dur="short"/> picking up the phone or visiting <pause dur="short"/> a branch or</u>
<u n="164" who="S0420">yeah just having a Twitter</u>
<u n="165" who="S0364">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0420">badge on your on your website doesn't <unclear>mean you're good</unclear></u>
<u n="167" who="S0364">no no absolutely not absolutely not <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> but no no I mean we you know we've got our press office has got a Twitter account and I re-tweet a lot of their stuff so <pause dur="short"/> you know there's enough bad news out there so that if we get some good news out it's good so we</u>
<u n="168" who="S0420"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0364">had couple of things <pause dur="short"/> we well we introduced the first ever <pause dur="short"/> it's like a <pause dur="short"/> a way for blind people to tell what's a credit card and what's a debit card cos erm</u>
<u n="170" who="S0420" trans="overlap"><unclear>what's that then?</unclear></u>
<u n="171" who="S0364">well if if you think if you if you had a <trunc>c</trunc> your cards in your wallet and you</u>
<u n="172" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0364">couldn't see it right you probably couldn't tell what was what</u>
<u n="174" who="S0420">yeah you'd have to stick a sticker on or something</u>
<u n="175" who="S0364">yes <pause dur="short"/> you'd fail <pause dur="short"/> so this is now in <trunc>s</trunc> now some sort of way they've got braille on these cards so you could tell which card's for what account <pause dur="short"/> yeah so that's something we've just managed today so there was a story that we would break <pause dur="short"/> you know we would refit into media <pause dur="short"/> traditional and we'd have a we'd also play it on Twitter so <pause dur="short"/> like the Royal National Institute For Blind People re-tweeted it</u>
<u n="176" who="S0420" trans="overlap"><unclear>yes but</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> blind people? okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0364">Money Saving Expert re-tweeted it so <pause dur="short"/> got quite good coverage you know? <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="178" who="S0420" trans="overlap">maybe more so than a few <trunc>colu</trunc> like couple of column inches at the bottom of a</u>
<u n="179" who="S0364">well yeah yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0420">of an FT article or something aye</u>
<u n="181" who="S0364" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> money Saving Expert a hundred and seventy thousand followers</u>
<u n="182" who="S0420">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so you're gonna get</u>
<u n="183" who="S0364" trans="overlap">it's like massive</u>
<u n="184" who="S0420">you're gonna get some coverage <unclear>huh</unclear>?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0364">absolutely</u>
<u n="186" who="S0420">so I guess it's got some benefits huh?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0364" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah totally</u>
<u n="188" who="S0420"><unclear>I dunno</unclear> I've just found erm <pause dur="short"/> trying to promote like I I've I've had people <unclear>follow my own</unclear> teaching website</u>
<u n="189" who="S0364">mm hm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0420">through Twitter <pause dur="short"/> but I find Facebook far more effective</u>
<u n="191" who="S0364">right for?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0420">for er</u>
<u n="193" who="S0364" trans="overlap">for that</u>
<u n="194" who="S0420">for erm <pause dur="short"/> for promoting er <pause dur="short"/> a page or promoting a</u>
<u n="195" who="S0364" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="196" who="S0420">service or promoting something I find Twitter's good once you've got an established base</u>
<u n="197" who="S0364">right right</u>
<u n="198" who="S0420">to maintain a conversation but I think Facebook's better for <pause dur="short"/> sort of starting that conversation</u>
<u n="199" who="S0364" trans="overlap">mm okay</u>
<u n="200" who="S0420"><unclear/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0364" trans="overlap">see I tend to keep I keep Facebook more to my like <pause dur="short"/> my friends and family <pause dur="short"/> I've tried to be <pause dur="short"/> keep them quite distinct</u>
<u n="202" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0364">my Facebook was just becoming like my Twitter with like <pause dur="short"/> all my football clubs and sports teams and so I've kept it really strict like</u>
<u n="204" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0364">I follow Hearts on Facebook but not erm <pause dur="short"/> maybe Barcelona maybe Juventus but that's about it</u>
<u n="206" who="S0420">see I just yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>I get that</unclear></u>
<u n="207" who="S0364" trans="overlap">cos I started getting I started getting all the updates for all of them on both <pause dur="short"/> which is like</u>
<u n="208" who="S0420">there's too much</u>
<u n="209" who="S0364" trans="overlap">gotta choose</u>
<u n="210" who="S0420">yeah <unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="211" who="S0364" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="212" who="S0420">well see d'you think there will come a point where people have to choose which one they spend their time on or or are people just quite happy to do it? I mean I see the guy next to me at work</u>
<u n="213" who="S0364">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0420">and he's got both pages both tabs open</u>
<u n="215" who="S0364" whoConfidence="low">open</u>
<u n="216" who="S0420">on his <pause dur="short"/> browser the whole time at work</u>
<u n="217" who="S0364" trans="overlap">you you could be right cos they're just trying to <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>f</trunc> they <trunc>st</trunc> they started out differently right but they're <trunc>i</trunc>increasingly trying to do the same thing</u>
<u n="218" who="S0420">yeah keeping people in touch with</u>
<u n="219" who="S0364" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0420">services and</u>
<u n="221" who="S0364">both of them you can now put your location in there</u>
<u n="222" who="S0420" trans="overlap"><unclear>there's yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="223" who="S0364">both of them you can now <pause dur="short"/> add photos Twitter never used to have photos</u>
<u n="224" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0364">you I think Twitter now you can tag people in photos <pause dur="short"/> never used to be able to do that cos Twitter started out really basic hundred and forty characters <pause dur="short"/> what are you doing right now? and it's you know there's no way it's what are you doing right now</u>
<u n="226" who="S0420">no</u>
<u n="227" who="S0364">any more</u>
<u n="228" who="S0420" trans="overlap">no it's so it's discussion groups doesn't it?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0364">you know? I've had some good answers to questions that I've posed on Twitter</u>
<u n="230" who="S0420">but then there's the whole</u>
<u n="231" who="S0364" trans="overlap">what do you know about this? and</u>
<u n="232" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0364">you know you</u>
<u n="234" who="S0420">but then there's the whole thing with trolls and <pause dur="short"/> fake accounts and</u>
<u n="235" who="S0364" trans="overlap">mm mm mm mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I <unclear>have</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> how to prove? how d'you prove an account is real you know? I saw someone asking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that on Twitter and he had to <pause dur="short"/> get a photo from him on the team bus for the next game <pause dur="short"/> to prove that it was him</u>
<u n="236" who="S0420">right</u>
<u n="237" who="S0364">cos someone was like <pause dur="short"/> it's not really you <pause dur="short"/> but it <pause dur="short"/> presumably it was</u>
<u n="238" who="S0420">so why why should they feel under pressure to do it why why even bother</u>
<u n="239" who="S0364" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0420">create an account if you're gonna feel?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0364">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a tricky one it's a tricky one for footballers eh I've seen a lot of them come on and then leave cos <pause dur="short"/> they just <trunc>g</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> like the trolls as you say for for <trunc>e</trunc> for all the positive stuff they get from their own fans <pause dur="short"/> the trolling's just insane like</u>
<u n="242" who="S0420">you just open yourself <pause dur="short"/> you're just open to to abuse basically?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0364">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean I have</u>
<u n="244" who="S0420" trans="overlap">that's a sort of anonymous abuse in some ways</u>
<u n="245" who="S0364">I've seen Hearts players in trouble for like <pause dur="short"/> going to Nando's for tea <pause dur="short"/> you know? they went out for dinner oh you got beat at the weekend you should be training <pause dur="short"/> you don't grudge a guy having his dinner you know? but <vocal desc="laugh"/> but that's</u>
<u n="246" who="S0420">might like to might like to smile whilst he's having his dinner <unclear>you know</unclear></u>
<u n="247" who="S0364" trans="overlap">no that's it yeah yeah exactly <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="248" who="S0420">I <unclear>don't know</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> I I</u>
<u n="249" who="S0364" trans="overlap"><unclear>I know a</unclear> Celtic player who got was it a Celtic player or a Rangers player I can't remember? they lost a game and then he <pause dur="short"/> he took his kid out to the funfair or something over Christmas oh it was a Rangers player after they got they got <unclear>horsed</unclear> by Hibs <pause dur="short"/> and he was like <pause dur="short"/> saying that he was away out <unclear>on</unclear> a nice day and got in trouble <pause dur="short"/> and he and he was raging cos he says you know my work life and family life are</u>
<u n="250" who="S0420">that was two different things</u>
<u n="251" who="S0364" trans="overlap">separate</u>
<u n="252" who="S0420">you wouldn't you wouldn't get angry if like a a salesman lost an account and</u>
<u n="253" who="S0364">mm</u>
<u n="254" who="S0420">he just happened to <pause dur="short"/> well take his kids to the supermarket or something</u>
<u n="255" who="S0364" trans="overlap">exactly exactly but you know? as a footballer you you're not meant to be a <trunc>nor</trunc> <trunc>we</trunc> normal person you're meant to just go and hide for the night you know?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0420">well aye aye <pause dur="short"/> you're seen through very different eyes aren't you?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0364">absolutely <trunc>abs</trunc></u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
