<text id="SN27">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:14:05</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-02-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A pub, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Peanuts, computer games, theme parks, films, border security</topics>
		<activity>Peanuts, computer games, theme parks, films, border security</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0037">shall I open these then?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0037">oh I haven't had these for ages</u>
<u n="4" who="S0115">that is Mr Peanut</u>
<u n="5" who="S0037">what's that  what's that  little dude doing?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0115">he's Mr Peanut <pause dur="short"/> he's uh he's a monkey nut</u>
<u n="7" who="S0037">right</u>
<u n="8" who="S0115">with with legs and arms and <trunc>mono</trunc> uh monocle and a top hat</u>
<u n="9" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and a monocle and a top hat</u>
<u n="10" who="S0115">and and the top hat says Mr Peanut</u>
<u n="11" who="S0037">right</u>
<u n="12" who="S0115">and he's holding a cane</u>
<u n="13" who="S0037">the original Mr Peanut left Italy in the late nineteenth century with his family's peanut recipe and sold his peanuts on street corners in Pennsylvania <pause dur="short"/> Well there you go</u>
<u n="14" who="S0115">mm <pause dur="short"/> wonder if he was Pittsburgh or or uh what's that other place in Pennsylvania?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Don't know you'll have to Google him <pause dur="short"/> uh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> would you like some?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0115">uh yes please <pause dur="short"/> maybe we could uh open it up</u>
<u n="17" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I remember <pause dur="short"/> ah you <trunc>c</trunc> yeah okay</u>
<u n="18" who="S0115">and uh sort of</u>
<u n="19" who="S0037">have you ever played Fairground? Was it Fairground? It was like a <trunc>com</trunc></u>
<u n="20" who="S0115">fairground? What's that?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0037">so <pause dur="short"/> You know Sim City?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0115">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0037">actually <pause dur="short"/> like but Sim City not the Sims</u>
<u n="24" who="S0115">yeah yeah well I had Sim Town <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Think it was like a budget version or something</u>
<u n="25" who="S0037">oh well <pause dur="short"/> same thing <pause dur="short"/> so Fairground was one of them but it was based on a fairground</u>
<u n="26" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0037">and you could do stuff like add extra ice to the Coke <pause dur="short"/> so that like you paid like you put less Coca Cola in <pause dur="short"/> or add more salt to the like the nuts that people wanted Coke <pause dur="short"/> but then sometimes people would get unhappy</u>
<u n="28" who="S0115">oh right it's like a management game innit <pause dur="short"/> played a management game at IT though</u>
<u n="29" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so you had people come into like your your fairground and then if the rides were like if you didn't mend the rides then they would get like injured and get unhappy</u>
<u n="30" who="S0115" trans="overlap">get throw up and stuff <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0037" trans="overlap">or if you're like <pause dur="short"/> if it was boring or if you like built paths that didn't go anywhere they would get really sad and go like like frowny faces</u>
<u n="32" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0037">I liked all that sort of thing</u>
<u n="34" who="S0115">just like real life</u>
<u n="35" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="36" who="S0115">if you closed it for like refurbishment for like all summer or something a lot of people would drive there like they do at the end of that that wonderful film uh National Lampoon's Vacation <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="37" who="S0037" trans="overlap">haven't seen it for ages I'll have to rewatch it</u>
<u n="38" who="S0115">uh they drive there</u>
<u n="39" who="S0037">I was just saying</u>
<u n="40" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the whole point  the whole point  of the their  the their  journey across America</u>
<u n="41" who="S0037">D'you they go to Six Flags or something?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0115">ay?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0037">is it Six Flags? They go to?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0115" trans="overlap">sorry?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0037">where are going?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0115">what d'you mean?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0037">where are they going? On their journey?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0115">they from I think they live in Chicago</u>
<u n="49" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0115">to uh Los Angeles uh a fictional um theme park in California called Wally World</u>
<u n="51" who="S0037">oh right</u>
<u n="52" who="S0115">which is sort of slightly similar to Disney World Disneyland</u>
<u n="53" who="S0037" trans="overlap">because America have like a brand like um uh theme parks that are called Six Flags</u>
<u n="54" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="55" who="S0037">and I went to Six Flags Over Texas</u>
<u n="56" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="57" who="S0037">theme park</u>
<u n="58" who="S0115">no I think Wally World is definitely definitely a Disney copy</u>
<u n="59" who="S0037">mhm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0115">it had um <trunc>M</trunc> uh Molly Moose</u>
<u n="61" who="S0037">oh I see</u>
<u n="62" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh like a a giant moose um which uh which um Chevy Chase punches punches in the nose <pause dur="short"/> um at the end</u>
<u n="63" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't understand why <trunc>peop</trunc> I don't understand why people would wanna go to Disney World</u>
<u n="64" who="S0115">well <pause dur="short"/> it's really for the kids innit and it's fun</u>
<u n="65" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I suppose but like</u>
<u n="66" who="S0115">so they drive there and then they had they got this enormous car park <pause dur="short"/> and then <trunc>f</trunc> they drive right <pause dur="short"/> car park's totally empty <pause dur="short"/> so they drive up right next to the door <pause dur="short"/> no no no they don't they park like miles away <pause dur="short"/> and then they run and then and it plays um it plays the music from uh</u>
<u n="67" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Holiday Road? Is that from that film?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0115">no that's at the beginning this was the end of the film when they've reached the uh</u>
<u n="69" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="70" who="S0115">it plays the music from um you know the slow motion running?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0037">oh yeah Chariots Of Fire</u>
<u n="72" who="S0115" trans="overlap">from um Chariots of Fire <pause dur="short"/> they're running uh towards the gate and then it says um <pause dur="short"/> molly Moose has like a  like a  machine like a speaking Molly Moose</u>
<u n="73" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0115">it says Sorry guys we're closed for refurbishment for three months or something and <pause dur="short"/> and he gets really and punches the moose <pause dur="short"/> and he <trunc>brea</trunc> they break in <pause dur="short"/> and then they start turning on the rides and going on the rides and stuff</u>
<u n="75" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's stupid</u>
<u n="76" who="S0115">and actually they they forced John Candy turns up and they forced John Candy to to take them At gunpoint actually <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="77" who="S0037">weird</u>
<u n="78" who="S0115">yeah um uh he loses it <pause dur="short"/> he that's a <trunc>s</trunc> an aspect of his personality that um</u>
<u n="79" who="S0037">that's a good film is it with John Candy the one where what's it called? Like where he washes his face with his underpants?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0115">that's one of my favourite films that's um Planes Trains Automobiles</u>
<u n="81" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's right</u>
<u n="82" who="S0115">planes Trains And <trunc>Automob</trunc> um</u>
<u n="83" who="S0037">is it?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0115">na uh <pause dur="short"/> different ones like different ones for different different reasons like it's like colours isn't it?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0037">aha <pause dur="short"/> oh hey I know <pause dur="short"/> I know what I would say if someone asked me what your favourite film was</u>
<u n="86" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like you could say your favourite colour is like blue or purple something <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the Big Lebowski? The Big Lebowski is that your favourite film?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0115">well that's that's one of my favourites <pause dur="short"/> I also like um a lot of comedy films like uh Planes Trains Automobiles and uh</u>
<u n="89" who="S0037">that is funny</u>
<u n="90" who="S0115">vacation and uh <pause dur="short"/> dumb And Dumber I like a lot um</u>
<u n="91" who="S0037">mhm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0115">um uh what else is there? Um <pause dur="short"/> and I like like Taxi Driver and <unclear/> I like Usual Suspects a lot</u>
<u n="93" who="S0037">calamity Jane</u>
<u n="94" who="S0115">uh yeah <pause dur="short"/> um like West Side Story</u>
<u n="95" who="S0037">I said Calamity Jane in all seriousness there</u>
<u n="96" who="S0115">jungle Book I like a lot</u>
<u n="97" who="S0037">ay?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0115">I like The Jungle Book at a lot</u>
<u n="99" who="S0037">jungle Book <pause dur="short"/> seven Brides For Seven Brothers?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="101" who="S0037">have you seen that?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0115">think so <pause dur="short"/> it's not really my cup of tea <pause dur="short"/> it's uh</u>
<u n="103" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> breakfast At Tiffany's <pause dur="short"/> I watched that only for the first time the other day</u>
<u n="104" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that's not my cup of tea either but it's alright</u>
<u n="105" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it was quite good</u>
<u n="106" who="S0115">um it's Audrey Hepburn is it?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0037">she's very beautiful in it yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="109" who="S0037"><unclear/> um</u>
<u n="110" who="S0115">what's the plot of that? Is it it it's a guy like she she thinks she's better than the guy or something?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0037">no uh so <pause dur="short"/> it's like uh um</u>
<u n="112" who="S0115">doesn't he? He <trunc>t</trunc> gives a speech doesn't he? He says like You think you're better than me?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0037">well it's a like a girl who's from like a small town girl who's ended up living in New York and like become like a sort of socialite um slash sort of um <pause dur="short"/> she's passing messages on for some like gangster guy who she goes to visit in prison <pause dur="short"/> um she passes on like messages but sort of semi-realizing and obviously like playing the innocent</u>
<u n="114" who="S0115" trans="overlap">hold on <pause dur="short"/> are we talking about um the same film?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0037" trans="overlap">breakfast At Tiffany's</u>
<u n="116" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="117" who="S0037">but then like a guy moves in next door and um sort of falls in love with her and</u>
<u n="118" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I didn't realize it was</u>
<u n="119" who="S0037">but she's sort of <pause dur="short"/> she's got this  she's got this  brother who's in the army um who she wants to support so she's looking for like a rich husband and <pause dur="short"/> but this other guy the guy next door the nice guy loves her and</u>
<u n="120" who="S0115">yeah he does that speech <pause dur="short"/> I've seen the speech that he gives like somewhere but</u>
<u n="121" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and then she sort of says oh I'm I'm nobody I don't need anyone and then like she puts the cat out <pause dur="short"/> she's got a cat and she like chucks him out in the rain</u>
<u n="122" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> she says that she says she doesn't need love</u>
<u n="123" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah and gets the cat and he chases doesn't he?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0037">and like they both like <pause dur="short"/> he looks for the cat and that and then</u>
<u n="126" who="S0115" trans="overlap">doesn't he? He finds the cat and like carries it</u>
<u n="127" who="S0037" trans="overlap">they both  they both  do at the end and then  and then  he <trunc>r</trunc> she realizes that she loves him and it's all <pause dur="short"/> but she would go and have breakfast look in  look in  Tiffany's window when she felt sad</u>
<u n="128" who="S0115">is that a shop?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0037">yeah it's a <trunc>jewelr</trunc> it's a really famous jewellery um</u>
<u n="130" who="S0115">oh right <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know <pause dur="short"/> I never heard of it myself like</u>
<u n="131" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh right Tiffany's</u>
<u n="132" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I I don't know suppose I don't know much about jewellery really</u>
<u n="133" who="S0037">yeah it's a really famous jewellery sort of um like jeweller</u>
<u n="134" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is that in New York yeah?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0037">they've got a big shop in New York I don't know if <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="136" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Cos Breakfast At Tiffany's set in New York isn't it?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0037">yeah it is yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's obviously more to the film than that</u>
<u n="138" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so they don't really  they don't really  have breakfast at Tiffany's in the film?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he's a wet <pause dur="short"/> well she has it like when she feels sad <pause dur="short"/> so if she's been out like partying or whatever but actually she's she's lonely really and <pause dur="short"/> so she like would go and get like a coffee and a croissant or a <trunc>bag</trunc> you know something to eat and like just look in Tiffany's window and made her feel better</u>
<u n="140" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> so it's like a sort of romantic drama then isn't it? Dream of wealth? <vocal desc="laugh"/> Dream of of meeting a rich guy <pause dur="short"/> but that's wrong because um she ends up going with a</u>
<u n="141" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but they go on this date and he he's won like a  he's won like a  ring like in a cracker or some some sort of biscuity cake thing</u>
<u n="142" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0037">and he gets it engraved at Tiffany's for her <pause dur="short"/> like I can't remember exactly <pause dur="short"/> it's a nice film</u>
<u n="144" who="S0115" trans="overlap">could've gone somewhere cheaper but yeah <pause dur="short"/> see what the sentiment is</u>
<u n="145" who="S0037">well they go on date where they do things that they haven't done before like that neither of them have done <pause dur="short"/> so he takes her to the library and shows her like his book <pause dur="short"/> cos he's written a book <pause dur="short"/> some</u>
<u n="146" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> he's written a book has he? Oh right</u>
<u n="147" who="S0037">well he's a writer but he hasn't been able to write for</u>
<u n="148" who="S0115">what's his  what's his  book about?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0037">I can't remember</u>
<u n="150" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0037">but uh it is a nice film but it's not your sort of film I don't think</u>
<u n="152" who="S0115">well it's okay  it's okay  the film</u>
<u n="153" who="S0037">it's a bit like that one <pause dur="short"/> where's the one? Where's the <trunc>wha</trunc> what's the one when?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0115" trans="overlap">sounds alright <pause dur="short"/> I'm not really a <trunc>ro</trunc> don't watch a lot of romantic films but</u>
<u n="155" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't really though <pause dur="short"/> what about that one where they're on a boat? Where she's?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0115">they're on a boat <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> let's narrow this down</u>
<u n="157" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so it's set <pause dur="short"/> she's in the the main character is a missionary</u>
<u n="158" who="S0115">is it is that The <trunc>Af</trunc> The African Queen? With <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="159" who="S0037" trans="overlap">african Queen</u>
<u n="160" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="161" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Rex Harrison?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0115">Burt um <pause dur="short"/> katherine Hepburn and um directed by John Huston</u>
<u n="163" who="S0037">that's right</u>
<u n="164" who="S0115">and with uh Dirk um not Dirk Bogarde uh the a um the American guy <pause dur="short"/> he talks  he talks  in a very rasping way</u>
<u n="165" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know but I can't think of his name</u>
<u n="166" who="S0115">it's uh um <trunc>y</trunc> Humphrey Bogart</u>
<u n="167" who="S0037">Humphrey Bogart that's right</u>
<u n="168" who="S0115">and and they were big they're big drinkers John Huston and Humphrey Bogart</u>
<u n="169" who="S0037">not in the film though</u>
<u n="170" who="S0115">and they they didn't drink any water when they were filming it</u>
<u n="171" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0115">and that's and the that kept them off cos <trunc>th</trunc> like she got like like like dysentery and stuff from drinking water</u>
<u n="173" who="S0037" trans="overlap">she got ill yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0115">um but they and they they never <trunc>dr</trunc> they only drank alcohol so they never got um never got poisoned but uh but she got badly poisoned uh <pause dur="short"/> but um there was a lot of like strop strops she was throwing like strops at them and stuff you know</u>
<u n="175" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> suppose she was a diva</u>
<u n="176" who="S0115">she was a bit a hell of a diva yeah <pause dur="short"/> um she she was on that that blacklist actually uh</u>
<u n="177" who="S0037">what? Oh the communist place?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh anti un-American uh actors <trunc>view</trunc> considered to be potentially communist</u>
<u n="179" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's weird isn't it?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0115">uh they made a blacklist <pause dur="short"/> uh Orson Welles was on there <pause dur="short"/> a few famous guys really <pause dur="short"/> I dunno if Bogart might've been on it I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> um but yeah she was considered a dangerous communist threat</u>
<u n="181" who="S0037">D'you think she was though?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> she was from a wealthy family so</u>
<u n="183" who="S0037">that doesn't mean anything</u>
<u n="184" who="S0115">probably unlikely that she would want to take money from wealthy families since she herself was from a wealthy family <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="185" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0115">I think they went a little bit over the top with the McCarthyism maybe but of course that was the height of the you know Cold War so</u>
<u n="187" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="188" who="S0115">obviously America was kind of scared that uh</u>
<u n="189" who="S0037">well there's a new programme on isn't there called Homeland <pause dur="short"/> that's about like the American</u>
<u n="190" who="S0115">homeland Department of Homeland Security of whatever it's called?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah looks good <pause dur="short"/> the trailer looks good but I don't know if it will be?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they're they're like the coast guard and the sort of <pause dur="short"/> it's it's it's the equivalent of our um Home Secretary sort of?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0037">but the Department of Homeland Security that's surely that's like the <trunc>F</trunc> like the um secret service isn't it? It's the spies and that?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0115">uh is it similar to our MI5?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah I think so <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0115" trans="overlap">internal um internal intelligence whatever <pause dur="short"/> uh <trunc>y</trunc> yeah but is it not uh immigration or or?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so is MI6?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0115">not sure</u>
<u n="199" who="S0037">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> we'll have to watch it</u>
<u n="200" who="S0115" trans="overlap">watched Scarface yesterday</u>
<u n="201" who="S0037">homeland Security actually it is because that's I remember they stamped my passport when I went to New York</u>
<u n="202" who="S0115">homeland Security?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0037">department of Homeland Security thing with a big eagle boof saying I was allowed in</u>
<u n="204" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but that's the <trunc>s</trunc> that's America's like seal or uh <pause dur="short"/> what do they call it?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0037">but they were really <pause dur="short"/> like they were scary <pause dur="short"/> like at the border <pause dur="short"/> eagle that's got like uh arrows <pause dur="short"/> it's got the eagle's got like arrows in one</u>
<u n="206" who="S0037">hand yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115">talon and uh symbolizing power and uh an olive branch</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037">ah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0037">in the other talon symbolizing</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037">peace</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115">the opposite of the arrows yeah um</u>
<u n="212" who="S0037" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> but it was scary at the border like they were like um</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115">yeah they're really yeah you said <pause dur="short"/> they're really intensive aren't they?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037" trans="overlap">they weren't just like How you doing? They weren't they were like What is the purpose of you visit? Like really angry and sort of uh like scary really</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115">yeah it's all it's really cracked up cranked up after nine eleven hasn't it but um</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037">I don't really mind though I think like</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they they might have like</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037">like they can scan all me baggage and all of me organs or whatever they wanna scan really I don't really mind</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115">yeah no I I don't really uh</u>
<u n="220" who="S0037">if they wanna frisk us if they wanna</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I don't mind that either I mean <pause dur="short"/> there's there's a lot of debate at about identity cards and things like that <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037">but I think like even the whole sort of you know people don't like the whole body scanning thing <pause dur="short"/> it's just your body I mean</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like it's I think it's going to happen like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think it's just inevitable and</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well it's enforced in some places isn't it I mean?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0115">I think it's it's it's just it's a logical sort of progression of um of uh technology and security you know</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't care like <pause dur="short"/> but I think you would feel I would</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><trunc>I</trunc> as long as as as long as you've got technology available you're always gonna use it the government's always gonna use it for <unclear/> security</u>
<u n="228" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I think I would be happy being on a plane knowing that everyone had their body scanned</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115">yeah I mean me too <pause dur="short"/> I'd rather have that</u>
<u n="230" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I haven't got a problem with it</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115">yeah I'd rather have the scanning than the danger of like</u>
<u n="232" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115">terrorism on on the plane and uh <pause dur="short"/> this this sort of thing is one of them heated topics isn't it gets people really angry</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it is yeah <pause dur="short"/> you're right</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115">bit like uh immigration or uh the the EU uh</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> religion <pause dur="short"/> oh goodness yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I just need to go to the loo <pause dur="short"/> can I just? Shall I press pause?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah cool</u>
</body>
</text>
