<text id="SN2R">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:38</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0519 S0520 S0521</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Hunsonby, Cumbria</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>coffee machine, removal and storage costs, politics, Labour leadership, idealism</topics>
		<activity>family chatting in kitchen</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, complaining, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0519">
				<exactage>59</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>Irish</nat>
				<birthplace>Dublin, Ireland</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Ireland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Penrith, `</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Recently retired maths teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0520">
				<exactage>32</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birkenhead, UK`</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>India/Thailand/UK (Hunsoney</hab_city>
				<hab_country></hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Transcriber, Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0521">
				<exactage>59</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Walsall, UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Penrith</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Former role as technical esport of development planning in oil industry</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0519">turn this slightly that way oh you can't</u>
<u n="2" who="S0520" trans="overlap">I mean it could just be the specific taste of the coffee but it's kind of a weird there's something weird happening</u>
<u n="3" who="S0519">erm so what I'm thinking is it's not even really strong is it?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0520">it's not strong at all and I put this and I did that</u>
<u n="5" who="S0519" trans="overlap">so no you should where should that be? what's that? that's that's the strength the amount of coffee</u>
<u n="6" who="S0520" trans="overlap">oh I thought that was the groundedness of it</u>
<u n="7" who="S0519" trans="overlap">so keep that up no</u>
<u n="8" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0519">or min max</u>
<u n="10" who="S0520" trans="overlap">min max min max</u>
<u n="11" who="S0519">this is how much it grounds it grinds it in here</u>
<u n="12" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0519">so and then this is the volume</u>
<u n="14" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0519">so you would put it to half and do a double and then you get two reasonably strong ones is what should happen</u>
<u n="16" who="S0520">well that's what I did in there but</u>
<u n="17" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="18" who="S0520">I didn't have that cranked up</u>
<u n="19" who="S0519">okay but</u>
<u n="20" who="S0520" trans="overlap">but but I don't you know</u>
<u n="21" who="S0519">yes</u>
<u n="22" who="S0520">I think it's just not really if you smell the beans it's kind of a bit mm odd you know?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm I don't know erm now what in here we would have to look up on the instructioonies this was like the default setting</u>
<u n="24" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0519">erm and it seems to be oh</u>
<u n="26" who="S0520">I find it with this machine in general though that it's</u>
<u n="27" who="S0519">it's not been quite no I</u>
<u n="28" who="S0520">it's not strong enough for me</u>
<u n="29" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no I agree</u>
<u n="30" who="S0520">and doesn't have a rich flavour there's something a bit dishwatery about it and I don't think I should be like that cos it's quite a good machine</u>
<u n="31" who="S0519">I I wonder if somebody's fiddled with that that should be more middle</u>
<u n="32" who="S0520">naughty people</u>
<u n="33" who="S0519">middle fadiddle let's try that next time</u>
<u n="34" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0519">and I've only moved it a bit that way</u>
<u n="36" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0519">erm so erm yeah I've been feeling a little bit less satisfied with the coffee</u>
<u n="38" who="S0520" trans="overlap">it's just not the best is it?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0519">at in the last while so I've thought</u>
<u n="40" who="S0520" trans="overlap">I thought it was because you put were putting those Taylor's beans in which are English and I thought maybe it's just weak English coffee</u>
<u n="41" who="S0519" trans="overlap">now it no mm no the Taylor's should be good this is on ooh that's not all good either</u>
<u n="42" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I just emptied the cakes but they kind of spilled over in there I mean beans to cup essentially should taste like erm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0519">Starbucks</u>
<u n="44" who="S0520">well yeah exactly even better than Starbucks cos it's not got all the crap in it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0519">mm bit of storage here</u>
<u n="46" who="S0520">mm so is dad sorting the moving out?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0519">he's doing better and erm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you've instructed him</u>
<u n="49" who="S0519">he was very very excited because somebody came in at about one thousand five hundred</u>
<u n="50" who="S0520">see we have the opposite reaction don't we? we're like what's wrong with that person</u>
<u n="51" who="S0519" trans="overlap">that's completely wrong so I told him to ring him back up and then he realised it didn't include VAT or insurance or packing</u>
<u n="52" who="S0520">all or which you would need to include</u>
<u n="53" who="S0519" trans="overlap">all of which you would need to include</u>
<u n="54" who="S0520">dad'll pack it himself <vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="55" who="S0519">having said that we haven't got as much or hardly much kitchen equipment and that's what a lot of the packing is about</u>
<u n="56" who="S0520">yeah fair enough it's the small things we've got a lot of books</u>
<u n="57" who="S0519" trans="overlap">we have got a lot we've got a lot of books so no</u>
<u n="58" who="S0520">but you don't have you're not peel to hoard and crowd things</u>
<u n="59" who="S0519" trans="overlap">chuck in bin</u>
<u n="60" who="S0520" trans="overlap">so you don't no chuck it erm you don't have er you know <unclear/> ornaments and bits of what have you you know the house is quite it's basically just the bookshelves isn't it and then the whatever's in the garage</u>
<u n="61" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah and we don't actually want any of the bin bookshelves</u>
<u n="62" who="S0520">they're from Ikea since circa nineteen seventy or something</u>
<u n="63" who="S0519">exactly</u>
<u n="64" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0519">erm so <event desc="sound of blender"/> <pause dur="long"/> er but you know what can I say? <pause dur="short"/> yeah that looks a little bit better</u>
<u n="66" who="S0520">mm it does</u>
<u n="67" who="S0519">it's pouring more freely whereas we got a little bit of brown and then mostly white</u>
<u n="68" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm the white stuff is the good stuff isn't it?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0519" trans="overlap">that's better no the white is <trunc>cu</trunc> oh the creamy part?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0520">yeah the creamy bit</u>
<u n="71" who="S0519">you like this in it don't you?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0520">go on</u>
<u n="73" who="S0519">and you like sugar</u>
<u n="74" who="S0520">sugar I've got a funny taste in my mouth from it Lavazza deliver no it smells very nice in the bag</u>
<u n="75" who="S0519">just one?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0520">yeah okay <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0519">try that</u>
<u n="78" who="S0520" trans="overlap">give it a go significantly improved</u>
<u n="79" who="S0519">good somebody has</u>
<u n="80" who="S0520">so crank it up</u>
<u n="81" who="S0519" trans="overlap">thought they would fiddle with that and make it better because that used to always be in the middle that was like the default</u>
<u n="82" who="S0520">and what does it do?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0519">erm it's how</u>
<u n="84" who="S0520" trans="overlap">that's the <trunc>grou</trunc> the groundedness</u>
<u n="85" who="S0519">it's how big are your beans? and therefore how grinded does it need to be</u>
<u n="86" who="S0520">oh</u>
<u n="87" who="S0519">and I've always thought the beans that we have are quite small</u>
<u n="88" who="S0520">and that can make an impact can't it? cos then it depends on how the water filters through</u>
<u n="89" who="S0519">so what I did</u>
<u n="90" who="S0520">mini beans</u>
<u n="91" who="S0519">I</u>
<u n="92" who="S0520">those are small beans and those are big beans</u>
<u n="93" who="S0519">and but it's kind of saying move it towards big beans or move it towards small and I moved it towards small</u>
<u n="94" who="S0520">mm mm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0519">and I could just go a teensy bit more I don't want to overdo <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in one go cos I already did turn it</u>
<u n="96" who="S0520" trans="overlap">you could experiment with it couldn't you to set that to different settings</u>
<u n="97" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah erm and now we what had happened it was turned to more there</u>
<u n="98" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0519">see that's the dial thing there</u>
<u n="100" who="S0520">and it's probably like grinding them <trunc>dif</trunc> like</u>
<u n="101" who="S0519">it wasn't it doesn't <trunc>se</trunc>seem like we were getting the full flavour out of it water was going down but nothing else was happening so I'm happy now I'm happier</u>
<u n="102" who="S0520" trans="overlap">happier yes?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0519" trans="overlap">so how are you doing here?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0521">so he wants an extra he said it <trunc>re</trunc> the packing would <trunc>me</trunc>mean it was two days</u>
<u n="105" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0521">because he doesn't want to try and pack everything and drive back to <anon type="place"/> and store it in one day <unclear/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0520" trans="overlap">fair deals fair deals</u>
<u n="108" who="S0519">but what but does he understand that there's hardly any kitchen equipment</u>
<u n="109" who="S0521">I told him that he said it doesn't make any difference it's more to do with the distance that he's got to travel</u>
<u n="110" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0521">so anyway erm it turns out that er it's an extra roughly five hundred</u>
<u n="112" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0521">for packing</u>
<u n="114" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0521">erm and then he he said they they don't put the piano in a crate</u>
<u n="116" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0521">they just wrap it in their protective thingies</u>
<u n="118" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="119" who="S0521">and I said well look I'd rather have a crate he said well that'll be an extra hundred and forty</u>
<u n="120" who="S0520">that's nothing</u>
<u n="121" who="S0519" trans="overlap">that's nothing and is it packed on it flat or on its side?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0521">yes so it it er so that would be stored in the same place he said <trunc>we</trunc> it's a warehouse at a reasonably constant temperature</u>
<u n="123" who="S0519">reasonably</u>
<u n="124" who="S0520" trans="overlap">no dad</u>
<u n="125" who="S0519">no</u>
<u n="126" who="S0520">this is the problem reasonably is not the word</u>
<u n="127" who="S0519" trans="overlap">you're talking you're talking you want an air-conditioned</u>
<u n="128" who="S0520">not only that <trunc>de</trunc> dehumidified</u>
<u n="129" who="S0521" trans="overlap">well I think</u>
<u n="130" who="S0519" trans="overlap">environment dehumidified you can't get the whole thing back and your furniture's damp or you know</u>
<u n="131" who="S0521" trans="overlap">it won't be damp</u>
<u n="132" who="S0520" trans="overlap">I mean it's alright if it's a</u>
<u n="133" who="S0519">no I</u>
<u n="134" who="S0520">well it would be in the winter</u>
<u n="135" who="S0519" trans="overlap">it could be look I'm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0521">no they're not going to let the stuff go damp are they that would be a</u>
<u n="137" who="S0519" trans="overlap">well I don't know but reasonably constant as long as you understand</u>
<u n="138" who="S0520" trans="overlap">research it</u>
<u n="139" who="S0519">exactly what he means by that</u>
<u n="140" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0519">and you know erm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0521">well he means that there's no there's no thermostat that they're putting in there keeping it at a constant temperature</u>
<u n="143" who="S0520">that that sounds dodgy to me</u>
<u n="144" who="S0519">but at but you'd want to know wouldn't you if you're storing your furniture for a long time</u>
<u n="145" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0519">and your piano</u>
<u n="147" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0519">you know if he's saying a reasonably constant that that's fair enough but what temperature is it? how is the how is it controlled?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0519">what is the temperature and erm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0520">and is there a damp issue?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0519" trans="overlap">is is there you know</u>
<u n="154" who="S0520">I mean you're talking about six months potentially that's a long time</u>
<u n="155" who="S0519">that's right</u>
<u n="156" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0519">so you know anyway you you carry on</u>
<u n="158" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0519">and did you understand what the VAT and all that was</u>
<u n="160" who="S0521">yes so it's as it's as you said it's twenty percent on everything then on top of that there's twelve percent for insurance</u>
<u n="161" who="S0519">yes but not on top of the twenty percent? you can do the two separately that's what I understood you don't it's twelve percent of the removal</u>
<u n="162" who="S0520">pre VAT</u>
<u n="163" who="S0519" trans="overlap">not pre VAT and twenty percent of the removal pre VAT pre everything</u>
<u n="164" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0519">so you don't have to pay VAT on your insurance</u>
<u n="166" who="S0520" trans="overlap">so and what's</u>
<u n="167" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that'll be right yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0520">and what's the total cost then?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0521">well I haven't worked it all out yet but it's going to be about two thousand five hundred which is</u>
<u n="170" who="S0519">which is back to where we were</u>
<u n="171" who="S0521">more than the cheapest quote we've got</u>
<u n="172" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0519">but anyway</u>
<u n="175" who="S0521">but I don't know anything about the cheapest quote we've got yet</u>
<u n="176" who="S0519">no that's right at at least we know what this is</u>
<u n="177" who="S0520">I would definitely include the erm storage conditions into you research</u>
<u n="178" who="S0521" trans="overlap">the quality yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0520">I mean I just you know</u>
<u n="180" who="S0519">when we come to the final decision that will be really important</u>
<u n="181" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0520">because the most in <trunc>so</trunc> I mean specially with an instrument even if it requires that you do get it separately and stay with you know keep the cheaper deal but do the piano separately</u>
<u n="183" who="S0521" trans="overlap">we could do that yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0520">the piano is going to suffer in an environment that's not very strictly controlled</u>
<u n="185" who="S0521">no that's right you need</u>
<u n="186" who="S0520">can't be getting cold and warm all the time</u>
<u n="187" who="S0519">you need a piano specialist and a and a special environment for the piano or somebody who is guaranteeing you</u>
<u n="188" who="S0520" trans="overlap">who knows what they're doing yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0519">what that like Pickford's said they sent a piano specialist to the job on the day and they packed it and it went to the same</u>
<u n="190" who="S0520" trans="overlap">how much is Pickford's?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0519">we don't know yet they can't reply till tomorrow</u>
<u n="192" who="S0521" trans="overlap">they're going to give us a quote <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0520">I just like it when people you know we've got it covered we know about piano's we send an expert that's this is music to one's ears</u>
<u n="194" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0519" trans="overlap">to one's ears to one's music to one's piano</u>
<u n="196" who="S0521" trans="overlap">it is er</u>
<u n="197" who="S0520" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="198" who="S0519">what are you doing with the earphones on?</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="199" who="S0520" trans="overlap"><unclear/> as well</u>
<u n="200" who="S0521">oh had I not <unclear>plugged it in?</unclear></u>
<u n="201" who="S0519"><unclear/> cos it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0521">sorry</u>
<u n="203" who="S0519">you can still hear it you've got a big thing on your head</u>
<u n="204" who="S0520">it's a tiny erm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0521" trans="overlap">that's a little bit that's a little but daft isn't it?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0520">difference it was in the jack</u>
<u n="207" who="S0519">yes I know</u>
<u n="208" who="S0520">it was just you know like it's just that extra</u>
<u n="209" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I know that <unclear/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0521" trans="overlap">needs an extra push</u>
<u n="211" who="S0519">I've done it that the children wanted to have a little play and I couldn't make it turn on and it was cos it wasn't quite it the whole headphones weren't in just the little end piece</u>
<u n="212" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0519">and I couldn't I hadn't noticed it so er then eventually I pulled it out</u>
<u n="214" who="S0521" trans="overlap">oh that's right yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0520">it's ideal isn't it? if you've erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> banging on there</u>
<u n="216" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yeah there you go it looks it looks like it's going two three thousandish maybe a little bit more</u>
<u n="217" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0521">for the total packing</u>
<u n="219" who="S0519">three to four thousand</u>
<u n="220" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0519">erm it</u>
<u n="222" who="S0520">well that's sounds erm</u>
<u n="223" who="S0519">it's a lot of money</u>
<u n="224" who="S0521">it sounds</u>
<u n="225" who="S0520">well no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0519">has dad told you what his original estimate was?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0520" trans="overlap">to be fair I'm not really surprised by these things</u>
<u n="228" who="S0519">I'm not but</u>
<u n="229" who="S0520">I mean it's</u>
<u n="230" who="S0519">but guess what dad's original estimate for removals was?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0520">I don't know five hundred or something? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0519">three hundred</u>
<u n="233" who="S0520">three hundred <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0521" trans="overlap">thirty-five quid I thought</u>
<u n="235" who="S0520"><trunc>to</trunc> a tenner <vocal desc="laugh"/> you do wonder why it has to cost that much but I guess the storage is I mean is the storage the main expense? or is it the erm removals that's more expensive</u>
<u n="236" who="S0521">the storage well he he he's quoting thirty-two a week for the storage</u>
<u n="237" who="S0520" trans="overlap">warehouse is really not my favourite word but</u>
<u n="238" who="S0519">it's not mine either <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I just imagine like some horrible dilapidated building</u>
<u n="240" who="S0521" trans="overlap">so they're going to <anon type="place"/> with the storage company were offering a room</u>
<u n="241" who="S0519">dehumidified and</u>
<u n="242" who="S0521" trans="overlap">which is basically the size of a double garage</u>
<u n="243" who="S0519">yeah it's these companies where you get you have <trunc>co</trunc> constant access</u>
<u n="244" who="S0521" trans="overlap">there's the instant access</u>
<u n="245" who="S0520">purpose built storage is what I would mm</u>
<u n="246" who="S0519" trans="overlap">it is purpose mm that is erm this warehouse here</u>
<u n="247" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> some dilapidated factory in <anon type="place"/> somewhere</u>
<u n="248" who="S0521">you're very sceptical aren't you?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0520">I'm sceptical of people that don't that say things like <trunc>a</trunc>approximately the same temperature</u>
<u n="250" who="S0519" trans="overlap">warehouse roughly it'll be alright don't you worry mate</u>
<u n="251" who="S0520">it'll be alright that's not really Scottish accent is it?</u>
<u n="252" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0521">seven forty-two</u>
<u n="254" who="S0519" trans="overlap">Jack the lad is on the case</u>
<u n="255" who="S0520">what are you doing? are you on Excel or something?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0519">I'm on Excel copying my formula down fifty-nine million times</u>
<u n="257" who="S0520">I want you to have an Excel lesson with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doing he'll he'll just</u>
<u n="258" who="S0521" trans="overlap">so here I am trying to do my stuff and it just</u>
<u n="259" who="S0519">he'll sort me won't he?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0520">he's like the king of shortcuts</u>
<u n="261" who="S0519">oh I love him</u>
<u n="262" who="S0521">the erm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0520">he hates watching me use the computer cos I faff faff about and ramble around on it</u>
<u n="264" who="S0519" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="265" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0520">he doesn't like use the mouse</u>
<u n="267" who="S0521">I once had a computer that I could use more or less at er</u>
<u n="268" who="S0519">at</u>
<u n="269" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you should just have one each it's not really an issue</u>
<u n="270" who="S0521">now it's er you know I I can have an hour in between the</u>
<u n="271" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I'm having a I might have a Macbook Air is what I'm thinking</u>
<u n="272" who="S0520" trans="overlap">if you just get yourself a Macbook Air</u>
<u n="273" who="S0519">as long as I don't have to pay</u>
<u n="274" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0521" trans="overlap">you could you could have my dad's actually if you wanted it?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0519">well at the moment all of us well I I don't know I suppose <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does he use it?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0521">no he doesn't I <trunc>di</trunc>discussed it with him I said what about dad's computer he said do you want it?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0520">mm also that blue one that I was using I mean if you just want a word processor</u>
<u n="279" who="S0521">the blue one? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0520">do you remember the blue one? did I have the blue one last time?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0521">I'm not sure about the blue one <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0520">I did have the blue one last time I had this little blue computer that was basically like virtually no specs whatsoever but it was <trunc>na</trunc>natty little thing and it has it's really thin and light and it's ideal for kind of but yeah you should just get a proper one you should definitely have one each cos there's a bit of competitive er rivalry going on <vocal desc="laugh"/> specially now that mum is treasuring for the er</u>
<u n="283" who="S0521" trans="overlap">okay this treasuring seems to be</u>
<u n="284" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0521">a job that grows by the minute</u>
<u n="286" who="S0520">treasuring</u>
<u n="287" who="S0521">you'll be getting an OBE for it soon</u>
<u n="288" who="S0520">OBE <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0521">services <trunc>be</trunc> above and beyond the call of industry</u>
<u n="290" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0520">mm what are you doing?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0519">something weird happened to my copying two people got missed out how can that be?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0520">copy paste is an incredibly unreliable method of doing things I find</u>
<u n="294" who="S0519" trans="overlap">and another one</u>
<u n="295" who="S0520">you get in trouble very easily</u>
<u n="296" who="S0521">just spells trouble</u>
<u n="297" who="S0520">just spells trouble <pause dur="long"/> so was Feds any good last night then?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0521">Feds?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0520">or was he crumbling in the face of?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0521">well he started off a bit shaky I mean it seems like he was nervous or something and then</u>
<u n="301" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="302" who="S0521">and then he lost the first set just so it could have gone either way and then the second set he had this purple <trunc>s</trunc> spell where he was making these huge shots</u>
<u n="303" who="S0520" trans="overlap">purple?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0521">and everybody said oh Federer's back</u>
<u n="305" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="306" who="S0521">but he didn't really keep up the standard</u>
<u n="307" who="S0520">his confidence is waning maybe?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0521">yeah well he was always as little bit like that to be honest it was almost like he only just was good enough to beat somebody</u>
<u n="309" who="S0520" trans="overlap">not like completely domineering yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0521" trans="overlap">he had this huge he had this great knack of being able to just raise his standards</u>
<u n="311" who="S0520" trans="overlap">pull it out of the bag yeah I remember that</u>
<u n="312" who="S0519">just once in a every five it's not done the formula I've got to go through them all and check that the formula is there</u>
<u n="313" who="S0520" trans="overlap">baffled</u>
<u n="314" who="S0519">ridiculous thing</u>
<u n="315" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0521">once in every five?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0519">seriously I've got control V all the way down and I've got a <trunc>ran</trunc></u>
<u n="318" who="S0521" trans="overlap">are you serious? are you serious?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0520">are you sure that that is the most efficient method?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0519">it's the only one dad can tell me</u>
<u n="321" who="S0520">dad</u>
<u n="322" who="S0521">what?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0520">control V all the way down the column like is there not can you not teach it to</u>
<u n="324" who="S0519">you can write a macro or something but you know</u>
<u n="325" who="S0520">make a macro yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0519" trans="overlap">whatever macro smacro</u>
<u n="327" who="S0520"><trunc>ma</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0519">erm so that's not very good is it?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0519">loads of people haven't paid</u>
<u n="331" who="S0520">I think you should revolutionise the system get strict reminder emails and stuff that's what we've done</u>
<u n="332" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="333" who="S0520">friendly but more</u>
<u n="334" who="S0519" trans="overlap">do you do them all one group or? cos I do them all in the group?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0520" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0519">it was only three people but I just thought come on it's three people and you're three month late you can have a group email then you know it's just you three</u>
<u n="337" who="S0520" trans="overlap">well just BCC oh well you could do BCC <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's not really the</u>
<u n="338" who="S0519">I don't care I thought come on do it</u>
<u n="339" who="S0520" trans="overlap">no I'm sure they don't mind either but yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0519">right retreat you have not paid <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0520">so have you seen this picture of the new Labour leader with all these dancers dad? was that in The Times as well?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0521">who?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0520">on the front of The Guardian today there was a picture of this guy Corbyn</u>
<u n="344" who="S0521" trans="overlap">Corbyn</u>
<u n="345" who="S0520">with these with these three young lady dancers</u>
<u n="346" who="S0521" trans="overlap">his cohorts?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0520">no</u>
<u n="348" who="S0521">oh</u>
<u n="349" who="S0520">he's just gone to meet some dancers it's a bizarre picture on like the first day of the leadership you know just like ladies in kind of <trunc>sca</trunc>scampy clothing doing some kind of a dance that he'd met it was a very funny picture to have like</u>
<u n="350" who="S0521">yes</u>
<u n="351" who="S0520">to you know to kick off your reputation it was on the front of The Guardian it was quite funny</u>
<u n="352" who="S0521">okay Guardian is left-wing isn't it?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0520">yeah it's a Labour paper</u>
<u n="354" who="S0521" trans="overlap">they should be they should be pleased with him should they or? <unclear/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0520">erm I haven't really read anything interesting to be honest I think people are a bit confused and erm I'm not sure if The Guardian really knows <trunc>we</trunc> what kind of a stand it wants to take on on the whole thing I mean it's a left-wing newspaper always has been but erm there's left-wing and there's left-wing as they say</u>
<u n="356" who="S0521">yes</u>
<u n="357" who="S0520">I was chatting to some people about it in the train station it was quite funny erm they came and sat at the table when I was waiting and</u>
<u n="358" who="S0521" trans="overlap">today?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0520">I had a paper in front of my with a picture of him</u>
<u n="360" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0520">so we started chatting about it and she was actually a quite smart lady Liberal Democrat</u>
<u n="362" who="S0521">oh yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0520">and er her and her husband so we were discussing whether what the implications were</u>
<u n="364" who="S0521" trans="overlap">well I heard the Lim Dems the Lib Dems were spotting and opportunity cos Labour Party would self-destruct and therefore they</u>
<u n="365" who="S0520">they would become the second party</u>
<u n="366" who="S0521" trans="overlap">would be the de facto er de facto left-wing party</u>
<u n="367" who="S0520">I don't yeah it's a possible scenario I guess I'm not sure about self-destruct</u>
<u n="368" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0520">but it seems to be one of the potentials</u>
<u n="370" who="S0521" trans="overlap">one of the yeah one of the outcomes one of the scenarios</u>
<u n="371" who="S0520" trans="overlap">we were <trunc>di</trunc> well we wondering whether it would signal like a kind of swing to the left overall you now whether it was symptomatic of a like a spirit of the young generation or whether it was less profound than that</u>
<u n="372" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yes the analysis I saw is that the nobody trusted the Labour party to handle the economy</u>
<u n="373" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0521">in the election anyway so whatever the of course that's been always the always the challenge that the Labour party are full of socialist ideas but they can never pay for it</u>
<u n="375" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="376" who="S0521">so I don't think that's changed</u>
<u n="377" who="S0520">well it's quite a big question it's like where the most voters I think aren't that bothered about politics are they? what they're bothered about is paying back their mortgage and erm you know feeling financially secure</u>
<u n="378" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0520">and erm having affordable housing and education you know things that have an immediate impact on their life you know but the general political scene is not of interest to them</u>
<u n="380" who="S0521">no I think you're right</u>
<u n="381" who="S0520">so I just wonder whether such a person can really gain voters because it's very based on idealistic ideas isn't it?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0521">idealistic exactly</u>
<u n="383" who="S0520">mm I'm not sure I don't see it happening particularly</u>
<u n="384" who="S0521">I read Robert Peston's analysis of erm quantitative easing for the people</u>
<u n="385" who="S0520">who's Robert Peston?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0521">which is what Corbyn has recommended and he says it's complete garbage</u>
<u n="387" who="S0520">who is he? is he a Times guy as well?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0521">he's a BBC economics expert</u>
<u n="389" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm okay</u>
<u n="390" who="S0521">so quantitative easing is basically where a bank generates a little bit of cash in a very controlled way because if if they overdo it then the market reacts by saying that they're just inventing money</u>
<u n="391" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="392" who="S0521">which is essentially what Corbyn is saying he said let the bank generate a lot of money so that we can build schools and railways and hospitals</u>
<u n="393" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="394" who="S0521">doesn't make any sense cos nobody's paying for it <vocal desc="laugh"/> so</u>
<u n="395" who="S0520">well how can it just be that?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0521">what do you mean?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0520">how can it be that unviable do you know what I mean? like surely he's been held to task by someone</u>
<u n="398" who="S0521">he is that's why people think that he's in cloud cuckoo land</u>
<u n="399" who="S0520" trans="overlap">that he's a looper</u>
<u n="400" who="S0521">but they don't evidently cos they voted for him I I I think this</u>
<u n="401" who="S0520">maybe it's more what he symbolise I don't know</u>
<u n="402" who="S0521">it's idealistic and <trunc>symbo</trunc>symbolic and all just a protest vote and all of those sorts of things</u>
<u n="403" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="404" who="S0521">I think did you see what Blair said?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0520">no</u>
<u n="406" who="S0521">Blair said before the election actually took place he said er if you're emotionally attached to his ideas you probably need a heart transplant <vocal desc="laugh"/> which was <trunc>ver</trunc>very tactful of him</u>
<u n="407" who="S0520">oh gosh I I imagine they're probably like personal enemies or something though</u>
<u n="408" who="S0521">possibly</u>
<u n="409" who="S0520">because you know <pause dur="short"/> blair was the one who did everything</u>
<u n="410" who="S0521" trans="overlap">but er Mr Blair was held to task for <unclear/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's not very constructive is it? within your own party <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0520">interesting</u>
<u n="414" who="S0521">anyway er twelve twenty plus VAT at twenty percent <pause dur="long"/> when I saw the number come in he said it'll cost seven hundred and twelve pounds</u>
<u n="415" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="416" who="S0521">I thought wow that's cheap and then you got er that is only for removing when you add some more on for storage add more on for VAT you add more on for insurance</u>
<u n="417" who="S0520" trans="overlap">then they just chuck it on the street</u>
<u n="418" who="S0521">you add more on for the piano then suddenly you're up to three thousand</u>
<u n="419" who="S0520">it's like a booking with Easyjet <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0521">yes it is a bit yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0520">so that excited feeling followed by a series of disappointments <vocal desc="laugh"/> ooh it's twelve ninety-nine <vocal desc="laugh"/> and if you if you want to check in that'll cost you another hundred quid</u>
<u n="422" who="S0521">it's yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0520">mm I quite hate that method of advertising actually</u>
<u n="424" who="S0521" trans="overlap">me too</u>
<u n="425" who="S0520">like is there any need whatsoever to advertise prices prior to VAT</u>
<u n="426" who="S0521">well the Americans do that that's</u>
<u n="427" who="S0520">mm they love it</u>
<u n="428" who="S0521">we used to get <trunc>consta</trunc> and even and even if you you know it happens we still get surprised they put quote everything without tax</u>
<u n="429" who="S0520">yeah so strange and then erm menus and stuff you know <trunc>some</trunc> they do that in Europe as well you know you read the whole menu and then right in the bottom there's like a tiny little sentence prices you know not <trunc>su</trunc> still subject to VAT so you get the bill and they and they whack on another twenty percent it's not that</u>
<u n="430" who="S0521" trans="overlap">that's right</u>
<u n="431" who="S0519">mm mm</u>
<u n="432" who="S0520">jolly any more is it?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="434" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="435" who="S0519">right I just need to take those things because that was really a bit scary okay they have paid</u>
<u n="436" who="S0520">it was a nice village that the pub we went to yesterday</u>
<u n="437" who="S0521">called?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0520">erm can't remember but I was thinking about you two and the house and <unclear>our room</unclear> it's much nearer to them than you wanted but erm you know it's nice to see a charming village I don't think <anon type="place"/> is charming it's okay it's sweet it's nice but you know it's fine but this was like you know more of a</u>
<u n="439" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> no no no erm I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> took us there and don't laugh but I I think it's got erm like as soon as you wander out to the edge of it</u>
<u n="440" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0519">you either are overlooking Shell's refinery</u>
<u n="442" who="S0520">oh cool</u>
<u n="443" who="S0519">or there's a motorway</u>
<u n="444" who="S0520">really yeah</u>
<u n="445" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I'm not or both if you're over</u>
<u n="446" who="S0520">yeah well you're yeah</u>
<u n="447" who="S0519">er it was just one of those funny things that I was going oh it's just beautiful here and we just went for a little walk round</u>
<u n="448" who="S0520" trans="overlap">and then you just see <anon type="place"/> or something</u>
<u n="449" who="S0519" trans="overlap">and all you could see was the</u>
<u n="450" who="S0520">yeah no</u>
<u n="451" who="S0519">and it still costs three million pounds to live there</u>
<u n="452" who="S0520">well this is the issue I mean I don't know what south Cheshire is like but where north Cheshire where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> lives is is a bit dominated by those big ugly port town industrial port towns and is incredibly trafficky which I would say are just two big nos</u>
<u n="453" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no two big nos</u>
<u n="454" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0519">you're darn right</u>
<u n="456" who="S0520">so many people everywhere and like Warrington and erm Runcorn it's all not good but erm but the yeah the village looked really nice it was pretty posh lots of posh people and clientele</u>
<u n="457" who="S0521">three five oh six is the final number from</u>
<u n="458" who="S0520">three five oh six mm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0521"><anon type="place"/> Move in <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0520"><anon type="place"/> Move mm and what was the?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0521">cheapest I've got is three thousand and thirty-eight</u>
<u n="462" who="S0520">and who was that?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0521">erm something like er P A to B or something like that</u>
<u n="464" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0520">some creative genius came up with that</u>
<u n="466" who="S0521" trans="overlap">quite an imaginative P A to P A to B imaginative for a</u>
<u n="467" who="S0520">and er what kind of storage facilities do they have?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0521">let's see er if they have any info</u>
<u n="469" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="470" who="S0521">erm</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
