<text id="SN4N">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:43:20</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-30</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0517 S0558</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>(ANON’s home, Fradley, Staffs)</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Old age, climate change, cross country, local community, education, skills show, school show, school</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about children and current issues.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T06</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0517">
				<exactage>47</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sutton Coldfield</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lichfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>14 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Self employed - marketing &amp; Proofing services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- working knowledge; German -- Working knowledge</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0558">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lichfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Sales Rep/ Lunchtime Supervisor</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0517">right there we go it's back on so so er yeah it is dead easy but it's worth doing to be honest</u>
<u n="2" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0517">you know it really is so dunno what that is</u>
<u n="4" who="S0558">gosh no it is</u>
<u n="5" who="S0517">it is yeah so <unclear/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0558">how <trunc>m</trunc>how many are you going to aim to do a week or whatever or is it as and when?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0517">oh as and when I <trunc>d</trunc> it's only the third one <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as and when I'm busy to be honest <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s company sent me <trunc>ano</trunc>another forty-odd page document to proofread</u>
<u n="8" who="S0558">and are you did you catch up last week?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0517">I did yes</u>
<u n="10" who="S0558">did you <unclear/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0517">I did so of course now we're back back to another month aren't we? tomorrow so I've got to start again</u>
<u n="12" who="S0558">oh so it's</u>
<u n="13" who="S0517">it's forty hours a month at the moment</u>
<u n="14" who="S0558">per month</u>
<u n="15" who="S0517">just for the three months so so yeah I'm busy so I haven't really had time <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="17" who="S0517">and I've gotta still finish my Christmas shopping</u>
<u n="18" who="S0558">and are you getting to the gym?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0517">yes but not as much but you know I am feeling a bit rushed are you getting to the gym? have you been to the new one? <unclear>old</unclear></u>
<u n="20" who="S0558">I've been twice</u>
<u n="21" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="22" who="S0558">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0517">well that's better than nothing</u>
<u n="24" who="S0558">yeah it's better than nothing I went Sunday morning</u>
<u n="25" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="26" who="S0558">because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s coach had got a problem with his car got an oil leak</u>
<u n="27" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="28" who="S0558">so he sent sort of a a late apology</u>
<u n="29" who="S0517">oh so it was cancelled?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0558">saying he wasn't gonna be there</u>
<u n="31" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="32" who="S0558">well she could still go and train on her own cos he he still</u>
<u n="33" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0558">he'll send her a programme to follow erm but I said well <trunc>ei</trunc>either go and and train you know at athletics</u>
<u n="35" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0558">or we can go to the gym so we we ended up going to the gym which meant I could exercise and the only time before that was a couple of weeks ago but I just haven't had chance</u>
<u n="37" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="38" who="S0558">you know Tuesday nights he's out Wednesday nights is always Avon we only have one off in three Thursday nights it's either food shopping or</u>
<u n="39" who="S0517">I know</u>
<u n="40" who="S0558">I might be doing like a late at work erm Friday nights he's trampolining</u>
<u n="41" who="S0517">I know and and this</u>
<u n="42" who="S0558">every night of the week</u>
<u n="43" who="S0517">and this time of the year is busy I always think cos you've got other stuff going on and you're trying to get all your Christmas shopping done</u>
<u n="44" who="S0558">well in fact Saturday morning we were both gonna go and do the food shopping and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do you know because I'd been out every night and it's not out having a nice time it's athletics you know</u>
<u n="45" who="S0517">it's <unclear/> yeah yeah ferrying the kids about</u>
<u n="46" who="S0558">wherever erm I said do you know I really could do with being at home and getting on with this washing cos I've done none since sort of the Monday maybe I said so if you go and do the food shop</u>
<u n="47" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0558">I can at least make a start with all of this and you know we were going to decorate the bedroom and then we decided not to?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0517">oh yours?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0517">yes did you <unclear/> for the quote for the en suite?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0558"><unclear/> no no</u>
<u n="53" who="S0517">oh not yet?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0558">we won't do it for erm a couple of years</u>
<u n="55" who="S0517">oh okay okay</u>
<u n="56" who="S0558">cos then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can do some of it</u>
<u n="57" who="S0517">right yes yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0558">erm so <trunc>wha</trunc>what we've done is give it a good clean we've just like washed the walls</u>
<u n="59" who="S0517">oh I think you told me yes yes</u>
<u n="60" who="S0558">I've washed the curtains you know</u>
<u n="61" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0558">er just give everywhere a nice wash down and that so I wanted to finish bits of that and after you know when you just you know when you put your underwear in the drawer and your socks and and you put things in there that shouldn't be in there and you just need to tidy your drawers up?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0517">oh yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0558">oh I <trunc>d</trunc> I just I just wanted to do all that sort of thing cos then <unclear>it</unclear> all feels nice doesn't it then?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0558">so I <trunc>d</trunc> I've sort of been doing bits and I thought I just want to get this finished now</u>
<u n="67" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0558">so I'd got I <trunc>d</trunc> I wanted to strip my bed right back you know with the mattress protectors and everything cos I don't take mattress protectors off</u>
<u n="69" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="70" who="S0558">every week</u>
<u n="71" who="S0517">not very often</u>
<u n="72" who="S0558">erm but I wanted to so blinking all morning was spent just in cycle bed washing you know</u>
<u n="73" who="S0517">yeah I can believe it I know</u>
<u n="74" who="S0558">so erm so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went off shopping</u>
<u n="75" who="S0517">it's getting it dry isn't it?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0558">so what we've decided actually I've gotten all I've gone around the houses three times to get to this point so I do apologise</u>
<u n="77" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0558">he came back from shopping and he said like you I just feel constantly like I'm clock watching and I need to be somewhere</u>
<u n="79" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0558">and all the rest of it <trunc>v</trunc>very <trunc>ver</trunc> I can't even remember the last Saturday night actually cos I remember sitting down at eight o'clock Saturday night to relax and thinking to myself I can't remember the last time I did this</u>
<u n="81" who="S0517">oh really?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0517">do you not sit down most nights eventually?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="85" who="S0517">oh my goodness <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0558">it's it's nine o'clock before I sit down</u>
<u n="87" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0558">because you're either putting a load of washing on</u>
<u n="89" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0558">so you're sorting that out I'm having my shower drying my hair you know er just er <trunc>com</trunc> like coming back from athletics at nine o'clock</u>
<u n="91" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0558">and going out and delivering Avon till nine o'clock the following night</u>
<u n="93" who="S0517">yes yeah it's busy isn't it? <unclear/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0558">it's busy all the time and and</u>
<u n="95" who="S0517">keep thinking it's gonna get easier and</u>
<u n="96" who="S0558">no so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to me do you know? he said I'll take on the shopping he said because every night I drive past Tescos and Aldi so it doesn't hurt for me one night a week</u>
<u n="97" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0558">to stop and pick up the shopping so he's taken on the shopping</u>
<u n="99" who="S0517">well that's very nice I couldn't possibly let my husband do that</u>
<u n="100" who="S0558">well no because he spends too much money</u>
<u n="101" who="S0517">I tell you what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we've jointly shopped</u>
<u n="102" who="S0558">and buys flowers all the time</u>
<u n="103" who="S0517">the last two Saturdays and I've probably have spent double what I would <trunc>norm</trunc> not quite double but not far off</u>
<u n="104" who="S0558"><unclear>I know</unclear></u>
<u n="105" who="S0517">I said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we can't keep doing this you're too expensive</u>
<u n="106" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0517">he just walks around having a lovely time putting absolutely</u>
<u n="108" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0517">everything that takes his fancy into his trolley <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0558">it's so expensive shopping</u>
<u n="111" who="S0517">it is expensive especially when you're shopping with my husband I mean blinking heck that man</u>
<u n="112" who="S0558">and the monotony of it week in week out</u>
<u n="113" who="S0517">we actually tried for the first time how sad is this? to go <vocal desc="laugh"/> the erm the self the little machines</u>
<u n="114" who="S0558">oh the scanner things?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0517">scanners we hadn't <trunc>u</trunc></u>
<u n="116" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0517">have you used them?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0558">yeah once because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was desperate to do it</u>
<u n="119" who="S0517">well I just said I wonder what you know if it will speed us up my problem was and it's probably because it was the first time I'd used em I kept going to put stuff in the trolley without scanning it because I wasn't used to it</u>
<u n="120" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0517">but he did er but anyway we spent an absolute fortune but we did get oh well we did get six bottles of wine as well cos if you bought six it was twenty-five percent off so</u>
<u n="122" who="S0558">oh twenty-five <trunc>poun</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0517">so we did get but you know</u>
<u n="124" who="S0558"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0517">he just spends too much so I couldn't possibly let my husband shop every week</u>
<u n="126" who="S0558">well I said oh yeah you you do that then for a few weeks and we'll see how it goes see whether I feel a bit</u>
<u n="127" who="S0517">see if when the novelty wears off <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0558">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0517">that's what it'll be</u>
<u n="130" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0517">does he need a list though?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0558">no and he's dead good <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he he</u>
<u n="133" who="S0517">I know he is</u>
<u n="134" who="S0558">he hunts all the bargains</u>
<u n="135" who="S0517">I know</u>
<u n="136" who="S0558">where I just go in I'm on a mission I tend to pick the same things up week in week out</u>
<u n="137" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="138" who="S0558">I get distracted by those baskets in the middle cos that's nice shopping isn't it?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0558">oh what's in here?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0517">ah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0558">or in Tescos he doesn't</u>
<u n="143" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't <unclear>just spot</unclear></u>
<u n="144" who="S0558">in the home department</u>
<u n="145" who="S0517">the bargains he just spots the expensive things</u>
<u n="146" who="S0558">oh yeah no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s really good</u>
<u n="147" who="S0517">Tesco Finest we always end up with when he's been shopping</u>
<u n="148" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0517">everything Tesco Finest <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0558">so yeah so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gonna do the shopping and at least then whilst he's doing that you see I always used to on on a Friday night I used to have my washing machine on the go and it all used to be washed and ironed school uniforms</u>
<u n="151" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0558">washed and ironed and back in the wardrobe so of a weekend I didn't have to worry if I didn't wanna get the ironing board out it wasn't a problem I'd do it on the Monday</u>
<u n="153" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0558">cos their at least their uniforms are in the wardrobe but of course I don't get that luxury any more cos I'm sitting at the blinking <anon type="place"/> all night</u>
<u n="155" who="S0517">oh yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0558">so I don't</u>
<u n="157" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0558">and I'm very often coming in from work myself at five half five so then by the time you do something to eat it's time to go trampolining</u>
<u n="159" who="S0517">I know it's a pain it's a pain blinking children <unclear>they need to get on grow up and move</unclear></u>
<u n="160" who="S0558">oh I know but I think to myself do you know it's not for long is it</u>
<u n="161" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="162" who="S0558">they soon grow up and and I remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> going from taking <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to athletics three sometimes four times a week</u>
<u n="163" who="S0517">to then have it not yeah to not doing it at all</u>
<u n="164" who="S0558">no just like that because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> passed her driving test and wanted to take herself</u>
<u n="165" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0558">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> felt</u>
<u n="167" who="S0517">well that's what that'll be like with me with the tennis club once <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0517">well he's <trunc>n</trunc> you know he's got another year yet but er</u>
<u n="170" who="S0558">is he going to get a car then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? has he got plans to get a car?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0517">he has got plans to get a car because he's been he can't afford the insurance but he can <trunc>aff</trunc> he could afford the car cos he's had erm I suppose a <trunc>buil</trunc>a building society account</u>
<u n="172" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0517">from when he was very little and er you know that's got I dunno probably about three thousand pounds in it that was always specifically for a car</u>
<u n="174" who="S0558">his car</u>
<u n="175" who="S0517">really</u>
<u n="176" who="S0558">oh right</u>
<u n="177" who="S0517">and same as same as <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it was just the money that's gone in there that was always specifically for to get a car</u>
<u n="178" who="S0558">see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have but I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s only and and this has just been you know if <trunc>y</trunc>you get birthday money you don't really know what you want</u>
<u n="179" who="S0517">yes <unclear/> put it in there</u>
<u n="180" who="S0558">so you put some away and stuff like that</u>
<u n="181" who="S0517">yeah and</u>
<u n="182" who="S0558">I think they've only <trunc>g</trunc> I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s only got about eleven hundred</u>
<u n="183" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="184" who="S0558">but we've kind of never said that was for a car that's just kind of like a</u>
<u n="185" who="S0517">it's just kind of there isn't it?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0517">it's there I know well I think we did sort of <trunc>sa</trunc> I mean <vocal desc="sigh"/> we're <vocal desc="laugh"/> we're not very good and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> probably won't go but we haven't saved anything for university or anything like that but they're I mean they're they're very lucky my two cos my mum put them you know when my nan's house got sold?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0558">yes</u>
<u n="189" who="S0517">the four sisters got a quarter each of the flat it was er yeah anyway mum had er she had about twenty-five thousand pounds from when nan sold her house</u>
<u n="190" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0517">and she very kindly gave all four grandchildren six thousand pounds</u>
<u n="192" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="193" who="S0517">so there's six thousand pounds that's already growing and I think <unclear>then</unclear> we added I can't remember where it came from <unclear/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0558">didn't your dad leave some money for them?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0517">no we haven't had any money from dad yet because mum's still alive</u>
<u n="196" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="197" who="S0517">we haven't had anything</u>
<u n="198" who="S0558"><unclear>well</unclear></u>
<u n="199" who="S0517">oh I know what it was we <trunc>w</trunc>when they were born you know we took out these baby bonds?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0558">oh yes yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0517">and they hadn't matured yet but the interest was <trunc>s</trunc>so abysmal that when we'd seen the financial our financial adviser he'd said do you know what?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0558">cash them in</u>
<u n="203" who="S0517">cash em in and we'd be better off</u>
<u n="204" who="S0558">that's what we did</u>
<u n="205" who="S0517">doing so er but because they we'd taken one out for each of them we put that with their money from mum so the anyway in effect they've got about ten thousand pounds each in junior ISAs I think they are or whatever they're in I don't know but the financial adviser is investing <unclear>em and</unclear> he says by the time that they're ready to use them that should be quite a nice sum so <unclear>for our</unclear> point of view we're thinking well that'll be a deposit on a house</u>
<u n="206" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0517">or something like that</u>
<u n="208" who="S0558">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0517">so they're very very lucky they've got those</u>
<u n="210" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0517">haven't got anything towards further education but you know we'll worry about that if and when that happens and then they've got money in their building society accounts <trunc>th</trunc>that they've had since they were born</u>
<u n="212" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0517">just like you said</u>
<u n="214" who="S0558">that's growing</u>
<u n="215" who="S0517">birthday money or you know</u>
<u n="216" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0517">dad would put money in every year as pocket money like a lump sum just <trunc>gr</trunc>just growing that that we've always said we'll use that to buy a car with</u>
<u n="218" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="219" who="S0517">but <trunc>obv</trunc>obviously the insurance will be as much as the car</u>
<u n="220" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="221" who="S0517">so we'll end up doing that</u>
<u n="222" who="S0558">but there's these schemes you can get you know there's young driver schemes you can get</u>
<u n="223" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0558">people like erm Motorhouse and people do them you know where like where I got my car from yeah?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0558">and they do like a young driver package</u>
<u n="227" who="S0517">oh okay is that with the black box and things?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0558">I <trunc>d</trunc>I don't know about a black box but er like you buy a car you buy a car and there's like a erm sort of an insurance scheme with it and all the rest of it</u>
<u n="229" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="230" who="S0558">so <trunc>i</trunc>it's worth looking into that sort of</u>
<u n="231" who="S0517">oh okay right yes</u>
<u n="232" who="S0558">the young drivers</u>
<u n="233" who="S0517">well I mean obviously we're still twelve months away</u>
<u n="234" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0517">because by the time he's turned seventeen and started learning how are <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s lessons going?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0558">oh yes really enjoying them</u>
<u n="237" who="S0517">good</u>
<u n="238" who="S0558">but I told you didn't I? about the insurance</u>
<u n="239" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="240" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0517">it was about fifteen hundred just to add him to yours?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0517">mm it's a lot of money</u>
<u n="244" who="S0558">that's just to add him to mine it would be same if he had his own car</u>
<u n="245" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0558">erm so what we will probably end up doing is things like leading up to the summer holiday we'll probably just insure him for a couple of months</u>
<u n="247" who="S0517">right yes yeah when he needs it yes</u>
<u n="248" who="S0558">so he's got access to it when he needs it</u>
<u n="249" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0558">we've said to him if you if you are very definitely thinking of going to university there is no point</u>
<u n="251" who="S0517">there's no point getting a car</u>
<u n="252" who="S0558">having a car</u>
<u n="253" who="S0517">is there? no cos they won't</u>
<u n="254" who="S0558">no point at all</u>
<u n="255" who="S0517">take it with em and then it's just</u>
<u n="256" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="257" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="258" who="S0558">just sit on the drive then</u>
<u n="259" who="S0517"><unclear/> and has he does he want to go to university?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0517">which one does he has he started looking?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0558">erm his favourite at the moment is <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="263" who="S0517">to do what?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0558"><unclear>and there is another one</unclear></u>
<u n="265" who="S0517">what does he want to study?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0558">well initially he was thinking something more along the lines of geographical</u>
<u n="267" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="268" who="S0558">like geography research you know all that sort of thing</u>
<u n="269" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="270" who="S0558">geology type stuff</u>
<u n="271" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0558">geographical that's the wrong word geology yeah but now he's thinking more whether to study history</u>
<u n="273" who="S0517">oh is he doing <unclear/> is he doing history A level?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0558">he's doing history geography biology and IT</u>
<u n="275" who="S0517">yes he didn't do business studies did he?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0558">no he did IT</u>
<u n="277" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="278" who="S0558">but he's thinking that's gonna be the one he's gonna drop</u>
<u n="279" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="280" who="S0558">because we went to the school show</u>
<u n="281" who="S0517">oh yes how was that?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0558">well it's the third time for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the second time for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the first time for me</u>
<u n="283" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="284" who="S0558">so they'd both seen it before</u>
<u n="285" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0558">and had not particularly been inspired on either visit</u>
<u n="287" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="288" who="S0558">erm it's awful to say and wouldn't er oh I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I wouldn't say it to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but if I er knowing what I know now</u>
<u n="289" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="290" who="S0558">if you know what I mean</u>
<u n="291" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0558">if I was their age going to the NEC school show</u>
<u n="293" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="294" who="S0558">I'd be coming away thinking a little bit disillusioned</u>
<u n="295" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0558">is that it? kind of thing don't get me wrong there was some there was some good sort of workshops set up so if you wanted to go down the trade of plumbing painter and decorator bricklayer that sort of thing there was an actual sort of situation set up you couldn't access it but you could see what sort of</u>
<u n="297" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="298" who="S0558">work environment you would be in</u>
<u n="299" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="300" who="S0558">kitchens as well catering they've got you know</u>
<u n="301" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="302" who="S0558">er proper</u>
<u n="303" who="S0517">yes yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0558">kitchens <unclear>catering-type kitchens</unclear></u>
<u n="305" who="S0517">gosh I don't remember that cos I went last year I don't remember that being there</u>
<u n="306" who="S0558">yeah it was up right up</u>
<u n="307" who="S0517">mind you that's not something <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s ever shown an interest in so we but it was it's quite spread out the sections</u>
<u n="308" who="S0558">yes yeah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0517">we've possibly avoided it</u>
<u n="310" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0517">because oh okay</u>
<u n="312" who="S0558">so I thought that was good because for people looking in that area</u>
<u n="313" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="314" who="S0558">they can get a real feel</u>
<u n="315" who="S0517"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0558">for what it's all about but if you wanted to be a hairdresser or a beautician or a florist it was just a stand</u>
<u n="317" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0558">but you know you <trunc>d</trunc> you could go to any local hairdressers or florists and say</u>
<u n="319" who="S0517">and get the same yes</u>
<u n="320" who="S0558">can I come and stand in here for a day and?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0517">yeah I thought there was quite a mix mishmash when I was there last year of some companies that seemed really geared up like people like er JP <trunc>Mor</trunc> what's it <trunc>J</trunc> er are they called JP Morgan?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0558">JP Morgan the bank?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0517">you know really geared up to er talking to them as prospective apprentices and you know they had the current apprentices there and it was all you know and others it was just really wishy-washy and nothing substantial</u>
<u n="326" who="S0558">mm yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0517">I don't know</u>
<u n="328" who="S0558">that's how I felt a bit</u>
<u n="329" who="S0517">mm and and I think as well it was very low budget</u>
<u n="330" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0517">and I think when I've ever obviously I've only ever been to exhibitions on a from a business point of view where you've got companies spending mega amounts of money</u>
<u n="332" who="S0558">yes yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0517">on fantastic stands to woo customers</u>
<u n="334" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0517">because it's all about business whereas this</u>
<u n="336" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0517">there's no money involved this is just but that's for students <trunc>b</trunc> and er it's certainly reflected in the overall look and layout</u>
<u n="338" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0517">and even the</u>
<u n="340" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0517">lighting was bad</u>
<u n="342" who="S0558">I know that that's it you know</u>
<u n="343" who="S0517">it just was it was drab as a show</u>
<u n="344" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="345" who="S0517">I found it very <trunc>d</trunc> and I and as soon as I walked in I thought oh this is dreadful but er you know I <trunc>sor</trunc> <trunc>ha</trunc> sort of had to stop myself and think okay you've only ever been to exhibitions that you've exhibited at</u>
<u n="346" who="S0558">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0517">you've spent thousands on the space and the stand and it's all the latest you know you're trying to get customers</u>
<u n="348" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0517">this is not that at all</u>
<u n="350" who="S0558">and you have you have to put yourself in the shoes</u>
<u n="351" who="S0517">and you have to put that</u>
<u n="352" who="S0558">of a sixteen-year-old</u>
<u n="353" who="S0517">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0558">don't you? yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0517">but certainly there was you know</u>
<u n="356" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0517">there was a huge difference I thought in in the <vocal desc="misc"/> er what's the word? I don't know just <trunc>h</trunc>just how they pitched to the students</u>
<u n="358" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0517">and the quality of them</u>
<u n="360" who="S0558">yeah it wasn't inspiring I didn't think</u>
<u n="361" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="362" who="S0558">I we <vocal desc="laugh"/> we must've been in and out in an hour</u>
<u n="363" who="S0517">well we</u>
<u n="364" who="S0558">we spent longer having a cup of coffee afterwards</u>
<u n="365" who="S0517">did you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0558">and a hot chocolate <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0517">well the thing that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <trunc>g</trunc> took from it last year when we went was that if if you go down the route of wanting an apprenticeship you're much better off getting your A levels behind you</u>
<u n="368" who="S0558">so</u>
<u n="369" who="S0517">and getting your and getting a better level of apprenticeship</u>
<u n="370" who="S0558">yes</u>
<u n="371" who="S0517">just from talking to a few people they all said the same</u>
<u n="372" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0517">that if you've got GCSEs mm yeah okay it's fine if you've got A levels it's just be much much better</u>
<u n="374" who="S0558">see <trunc>y</trunc><trunc>y</trunc><trunc>y</trunc>you did more than us because I wasn't even interested in talking to anybody</u>
<u n="375" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="376" who="S0558">cos I said to them when we went in look if you see something that catches your eye</u>
<u n="377" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="378" who="S0558">just say and we'll stop and we'll go and talk to them</u>
<u n="379" who="S0517">but you had to you had to</u>
<u n="380" who="S0558">but I'm not gonna</u>
<u n="381" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0558">keep saying to you</u>
<u n="383" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="384" who="S0558">because when you ignore me or reject me or say no thank you</u>
<u n="385" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0558">I I feel like it's all a waste of time</u>
<u n="387" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="388" who="S0558">so if you're inspired let me know and we'll we'll talk to them <vocal desc="laugh"/> and he didn't</u>
<u n="389" who="S0517">say anything no</u>
<u n="390" who="S0558"><unclear/> nothing neither of them</u>
<u n="391" who="S0517">well I don't think well it was only <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I took <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so the three of us went I dunno where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was erm and er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would've been the same</u>
<u n="392" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="393" who="S0517">but we literally took him by the hand and made him talk to people</u>
<u n="394" who="S0558">yes</u>
<u n="395" who="S0517">and do you know what? I was pleased we went because I don't know if you remember we had found out about it by accident and do you remember it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> saying that their school they were putting on a busload and taking them</u>
<u n="396" who="S0558">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="397" who="S0517">and erm and I said well that's that's madness why isn't our school doing it? and it turns out our school did do it but it was just by invitation only and I was really quite annoyed cos I thought well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is and I at that point we weren't sure if he was even gonna do A levels</u>
<u n="398" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="399" who="S0517">and I <trunc>re</trunc>remember being a little bit annoyed thinking he would've been an ideal candidate to go on that school trip to the school show why why didn't he get invited?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="401" who="S0517">what <trunc>w</trunc> you know what basis did they? and I was bit annoyed that he hadn't gone however after we had been I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I'm so glad we took him because if he was there with his mates they he wouldn't've spoken to a soul</u>
<u n="402" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="403" who="S0517">and it would've been a complete waste of a day</u>
<u n="404" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0517">but we took him and you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'d say well how about this? <trunc>w</trunc>we'll just go and talk to them cos they're available</u>
<u n="406" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0517">and there was two or three that he came away and you could see he was a bit interested or he'd listened to what they'd said</u>
<u n="408" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0517">we did the erm I don't know whether you saw it in the business section there was one where you could go and pitch an idea to a couple of people it was a bit like Dragon's Den</u>
<u n="410" who="S0558"><unclear>right</unclear></u>
<u n="411" who="S0517">so they had a table full of objects and you had to just basically choose one of the objects compose yourself for two or three minutes</u>
<u n="412" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="413" who="S0517">and then basically do a sales pitch to these two they were lovely lovely girls actually and erm they were really enthusiastic and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was going to do it and then he <unclear>sort of</unclear> no no <trunc>n</trunc>no you know I didn't want to he was all shy and everything and so they said er do it as a family come on so the three of us ended up doing a pitch for some</u>
<u n="414" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="415" who="S0517">ski hat <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had chosen but once he got into it like we sort of started him off and once he got into it you know he was fine and he was</u>
<u n="416" who="S0558">he was yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0517">and they gave him feedback and but it was the sort of thing that we came away and I said if if he'd've gone with the school it would've been a waste</u>
<u n="418" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0517">an absolute waste</u>
<u n="420" who="S0558">I think perhaps they got more involved on the two previous</u>
<u n="421" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0558">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear>one</unclear> the first time <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when they they were at a car show with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0517">oh I remember you saying</u>
<u n="424" who="S0558">do you remember?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0517">and they just sort of saw it and went in as a</u>
<u n="426" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0558">the second time last year <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> took them both whilst I was out with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and this year obviously me</u>
<u n="429" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="430" who="S0558">so I think they may've spoke to people last time <vocal desc="laugh"/> but they wasn't interested this time the only one thing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did come away</u>
<u n="431" who="S0517">did they say it was the same same companies there each year?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0558">yeah they said it they said it was no different</u>
<u n="433" who="S0517">no different</u>
<u n="434" who="S0558">erm the one thing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did come away with <unclear/> <vocal desc="misc"/> was that excuse me he said he thinks he definitely doesn't wanna go into IT</u>
<u n="435" who="S0517">oh really?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0558">he doesn't yeah he said er I can't imagine myself sitting there all day like that looking at a screen</u>
<u n="437" who="S0517">mm mm</u>
<u n="438" who="S0558">he said and he said because of the nature of the work it's always getting better and improving and changing so you're always having to educate yourself</u>
<u n="439" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="440" who="S0558">he said and I don't want to feel like I'm always at school</u>
<u n="441" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0558">when I'm at work</u>
<u n="443" who="S0517">oh well you see erm from that point of view just going in and deciding what you don't want</u>
<u n="444" who="S0558">it's eliminating</u>
<u n="445" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0558">exactly</u>
<u n="447" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0558">it's very useful isn't it?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0558">but erm</u>
<u n="451" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wasn't <unclear/></u>
<u n="453" who="S0517">what does she want to do? has she any idea?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0558">no idea she just doesn't know</u>
<u n="455" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't either really every now and again he'll just go oh I'll just be a full time tennis coach and then he comes back <trunc>t</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0558">the thing is is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="458" who="S0558">she's <unclear/> as you know gone through university for erm sports and whatever it is</u>
<u n="459" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="460" who="S0558">and erm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0517">which one was she at? do you know?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0558">Cardiff</u>
<u n="463" who="S0517">oh <trunc>Car</trunc> right yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0558">and she's erm she's finished now and she's doing a bit of sort of PT work</u>
<u n="465" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="466" who="S0558">and she's earning twenty-five pound an hour</u>
<u n="467" who="S0517">yeah it's quite well paid</u>
<u n="468" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0517">I know the tennis coach here gets twenty pounds an hour for his lessons</u>
<u n="470" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="471" who="S0517"><unclear>I know</unclear></u>
<u n="472" who="S0558">and if it's something he enjoys that's what matters isn't it?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0517">it is what matters and but we've sort of tried to say to him er you know yes as an as an extra thing to do as a part time <unclear/> but the thing about tennis coaching in particular is it's all well not all but a lot of it is weekend and evening work because that's when they're available</u>
<u n="474" who="S0558"><unclear>it's the only thing it's unsociable</unclear></u>
<u n="475" who="S0517">and that's fine when it's when you're a young single you know man</u>
<u n="476" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0517">but the but further on in life</u>
<u n="478" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="479" who="S0517">you're not gonna want to be doing every night and every weekend</u>
<u n="480" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="481" who="S0517">and that's what the current coach I mean he's only twenty-one and you know still lives at home so er he can do it but <trunc>y</trunc>you sort of think well</u>
<u n="482" who="S0558">long term mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0517"><trunc>wha</trunc>what are you gonna do?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0558">not good</u>
<u n="485" who="S0517">you know</u>
<u n="486" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0517">I don't know <unclear/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0558">but then again who knows it's like that open evening for when they moved up to the <anon type="place"/> and they said there will be work out there</u>
<u n="489" who="S0517">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="490" who="S0558">that hasn't yet been invented</u>
<u n="491" who="S0517">I know <unclear/> they'll they'll sort themselves out they'll find a niche but erm don't know what it'll be <unclear/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0558">well I think again on the radio today they've been talking about the the biggest threat is global warming</u>
<u n="493" who="S0517"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0558">never mind terrorists global warming</u>
<u n="495" who="S0517">er yes yeah I heard that myself</u>
<u n="496" who="S0558">so I mean er you know I dunno maybe that field research and</u>
<u n="497" who="S0517">geography is the one yeah <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0558">yeah you know</u>
<u n="499" who="S0517">climate change yeah maybe I don't know <unclear>it's so hard</unclear></u>
<u n="500" who="S0558"><unclear>they say the</unclear> again it was only a brief snippet driving home</u>
<u n="501" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="502" who="S0558">from work but er er again about the impact on our food supply and</u>
<u n="503" who="S0517">oh and the prices of that'll go up as well I heard I did hear that yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0517">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="506" who="S0558">we just don't know do we? really what</u>
<u n="507" who="S0517">no what <unclear/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="510" who="S0558">I mean where was I? I was somewhere but this links onto what I'm about to say anyway it's like for example Christmas birthdays at one time you could buy a dictionary you could buy a bedside alarm clock you could buy a torch</u>
<u n="511" who="S0517">oh I know</u>
<u n="512" who="S0558">you could buy a compass you could buy a calculator</u>
<u n="513" who="S0517"><unclear>I know</unclear></u>
<u n="514" who="S0558">you could buy they're all in one device now</u>
<u n="515" who="S0517">your phone yeah yeah</u>
<u n="516" who="S0558">and I think</u>
<u n="517" who="S0517">soon that'll all be on your wrist <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0558">in the working world yeah in the working world it's the same <trunc>th</trunc>the amount of stuff that is now done by computers and there are just people either just there pressing the buttons</u>
<u n="519" who="S0517">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0558">you know in the working world I think it's going to become limited so there's gonna have to we're gonna have to find other ways and means of earning money in order to live</u>
<u n="521" who="S0517">well</u>
<u n="522" who="S0558">but I don't know</u>
<u n="523" who="S0517">don't know what they might be yet no</u>
<u n="524" who="S0558">because do you know this is fact</u>
<u n="525" who="S0517"><unclear/> oh go on</u>
<u n="526" who="S0558">I learnt this</u>
<u n="527" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0558">by two thousand and thirty-five</u>
<u n="529" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="530" who="S0558">so it's not that far away is it?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0517">yeah twenty odd years twenty years yeah</u>
<u n="532" who="S0558">the average population of people one hundred aged one hundred</u>
<u n="533" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="534" who="S0558">living in this country</u>
<u n="535" who="S0517">go on</u>
<u n="536" who="S0558"><unclear/> I don't know if it's the world or the country actually</u>
<u n="537" who="S0517">probably the country <unclear>then</unclear></u>
<u n="538" who="S0558">probably the country I think one hundred thousand</u>
<u n="539" who="S0517"><vocal desc="gasp"/> how many are there now?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0558">I don't know</u>
<u n="541" who="S0517">I'll be one of them oh no I won't <unclear/> hundred <unclear/> erm</u>
<u n="542" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0558"><unclear>I know</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm yeah one hundred thousand people</u>
<u n="544" who="S0517">gosh <unclear/></u>
<u n="545" who="S0558">the age one hundred by two thousand and thirty-five so the population is increasing</u>
<u n="546" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0558">the work demand is getting smaller we need to find new ways of living</u>
<u n="548" who="S0517">I know</u>
<u n="549" who="S0558">because there's not gonna be the jobs out there <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> keeps telling us I say keeps she's mentioned it a couple of times at school at the moment they must be learning about erm er sort of patterns in erm oh god what's it called when you? generations yeah?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0517">oh okay yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0558">yeah and at the moment we our generation there's a lot of us</u>
<u n="552" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="553" who="S0558">and their generation is very few</u>
<u n="554" who="S0517">is it?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0558">apparently so so they are gonna be heavily loaded with taxes and things</u>
<u n="556" who="S0517"><vocal desc="gasp"/> oh gosh</u>
<u n="557" who="S0558">in order to look after us</u>
<u n="558" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="559" who="S0558">and then the generation that's coming behind <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="560" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="561" who="S0558">I know twofold they were gonna miss out they were gonna after we increase</u>
<u n="562" who="S0517">oh increase yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0558">their taxes et cetera to pay for us and then I think when they get to that sort of age again the <trunc>popula</trunc> er the population is less so they'll suffer</u>
<u n="564" who="S0517">right well I mean</u>
<u n="565" who="S0558">I can't remember now</u>
<u n="566" who="S0517"><unclear/> okay er maybe <unclear/> in age <unclear>I suppose</unclear> the population's not getting less is it? cos of all the immigration</u>
<u n="567" who="S0558">no no no no</u>
<u n="568" who="S0517">but</u>
<u n="569" who="S0558">well yeah</u>
<u n="570" who="S0517">maybe the age the sort of the babies <unclear>that are coming</unclear></u>
<u n="571" who="S0558">yes the <trunc>b</trunc> yeah the yeah that yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="573" who="S0558">the baby booms and everything</u>
<u n="574" who="S0517">cos I know erm <vocal desc="misc"/> mum when she visiting nan the other day she was talking to one of the staff in the home and she said she said well just to let you know I am off to New Zealand for two and a half months erm I did think my mother might pass away when I was on holiday in New Zealand last time but that was three years ago</u>
<u n="575" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="576" who="S0517">and she's still here erm and the the nurse said oh your mother's gonna be here till she's a hundred and five she's a strong one and mother went oh my god no no <vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0558">how often does she go to visit her?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0517">oh er still weekly sometimes twice a week</u>
<u n="579" who="S0558">and does erm?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0517">is it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="582" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's it yeah</u>
<u n="584" who="S0517">oh yeah she's just been away but yeah she still visits her not as often because it's much it's further for her about a forty-five minute drive</u>
<u n="585" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0517">erm and of course you go and nan doesn't speak to you or even wake up or anything so it's she doesn't really know you've been we just go and we feed her a chocolate and that's it still but I thought oh my god I thought mind you where are we? we're into December tomorrow</u>
<u n="587" who="S0558"><unclear>gosh</unclear></u>
<u n="588" who="S0517">so December <trunc>J</trunc> two months and she'll be a hundred and one</u>
<u n="589" who="S0558">I know</u>
<u n="590" who="S0517">I mean you know she <trunc>th</trunc>that's that's coming round quickly a hundred and one</u>
<u n="591" who="S0558">but do you know I mean</u>
<u n="592" who="S0517">but er but she's got no quality of life</u>
<u n="593" who="S0558">there's no quality of life so</u>
<u n="594" who="S0517"><unclear/> zero for her</u>
<u n="595" who="S0558"><trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="596" who="S0517">zero it's awful</u>
<u n="597" who="S0558"><trunc>s</trunc>so with people with people getting older no we're all getting older with people living longer</u>
<u n="598" who="S0517">longer</u>
<u n="599" who="S0558">so with with that do you think that our bodies are going to are are our bodies going to improve with age? therefore your arthritis is is this gonna?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0517">well</u>
<u n="601" who="S0558">is this gonna start er later in life? or will it still start so so you'll be suffering for longer with all these ailments? ailments</u>
<u n="602" who="S0517">well you're probably will won't you? because</u>
<u n="603" who="S0558">yeah so we're gonna have this huge amount of people <trunc>h</trunc> <trunc>h</trunc> living at</u>
<u n="604" who="S0517">I know <unclear/></u>
<u n="605" who="S0558">aged a hundred that are going to have to be looked after</u>
<u n="606" who="S0517">yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="607" who="S0558">by the family or</u>
<u n="608" who="S0517">and if if <trunc>na</trunc>if nan wasn't well if nan wasn't looked after <trunc>sh</trunc>she wouldn't've lasted this long but I mean she's literally she's fed she's washed she's dressed they turn her so that she doesn't get bedsores but she doesn't get out of bed</u>
<u n="609" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="610" who="S0517">she can't do anything herself nothing she doesn't even feed herself</u>
<u n="611" who="S0558">can she hear?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="613" who="S0558">so she's</u>
<u n="614" who="S0517">er she wore a hearing aid for I don't know how long and that's doesn't go in she doesn't have her glasses on because er she's shrunk so much they don't even put her teeth in now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because er</u>
<u n="615" who="S0558">oh that's er what they did with my nan <unclear/> <unclear>teeth in</unclear></u>
<u n="616" who="S0517">because her face has erm</u>
<u n="617" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="618" who="S0517">you know she's shrunk and they're too big for her you couldn't even entertain the idea of getting these things fitted again <unclear>to her</unclear></u>
<u n="619" who="S0558">no no no no</u>
<u n="620" who="S0517">but you you just couldn't even entertain she's got no teeth no no eyes no hearing and she doesn't wake up she's she looks like a skeleton it really is awful it really is</u>
<u n="621" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="622" who="S0517">but</u>
<u n="623" who="S0558">it's no quality of life <unclear/> is it?</u>
<u n="624" who="S0517">you know <unclear/> but they are looking after her well and they keep feeding her and she keeps eating they weigh her they put her in one of those big slings like er</u>
<u n="625" who="S0558">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="626" who="S0517">oh cos we saw did I tell you?</u>
<u n="627" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="628" who="S0517">we saw her the same day we we went to meet the baby see the baby</u>
<u n="629" who="S0558">oh that's right cos you were going <unclear>from there</unclear></u>
<u n="630" who="S0517"><unclear/> one extreme to the other mum I said we've got erm you know <unclear/> five generations now so we said they're so similar aren't they? both neither of them have got teeth <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="631" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="632" who="S0517">neither of them can speak <vocal desc="laugh"/> neither they both sleep <unclear>a lot</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="633" who="S0558">you do go full circle don't you?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they do <unclear/></u>
<u n="635" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="636" who="S0517">it's like the you know with the</u>
<u n="637" who="S0558"><unclear>I know</unclear></u>
<u n="638" who="S0517">the hundred-year-old and the and the week-old and it was so similar and <unclear>mum</unclear> said yes but you feel so much more uplifted when you come away from visiting the baby don't you? and I said yes you do</u>
<u n="639" who="S0558">and is is everything alright now?</u>
<u n="640" who="S0517">yes <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s driving again already</u>
<u n="641" who="S0558">no I mean with your mum and her differences and that?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0517">oh yeah with <trunc>l</trunc> yes yeah it seems to be</u>
<u n="643" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="644" who="S0517">seems to be</u>
<u n="645" who="S0558">everything's good</u>
<u n="646" who="S0517">so that's good yeah</u>
<u n="647" who="S0558">good</u>
<u n="648" who="S0517">but er but no I do know what you mean but then on the other hand <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> with the whole age thing er er you know you'd listen to the news another day and there's so many obese people that and it's putting so much pressure on the NHS that everybody's just gonna die of all their obesity-related diseases</u>
<u n="649" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="650" who="S0517">so I don't <trunc>under</trunc> I can't I can never work out how</u>
<u n="651" who="S0558">predictions are <trunc>th</trunc>there's an element</u>
<u n="652" who="S0517">how it works out really</u>
<u n="653" who="S0558">I know there's statistics you can do anything with figures</u>
<u n="654" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="655" who="S0558">can't you? facts and <trunc>fis</trunc> er figures and it's all about statistics and patterns and all the rest of it but who knows? <vocal desc="laugh"/> nobody knows</u>
<u n="656" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="657" who="S0558">nobody can make all these predictions of this that and the other we could have a blinking pandemic is that the word? next week</u>
<u n="658" who="S0517">oh yeah well <unclear/></u>
<u n="659" who="S0558">you don't know wipe loads of people out and</u>
<u n="660" who="S0517">it was funny when we last saw our</u>
<u n="661" who="S0558">we just don't know</u>
<u n="662" who="S0517">financial adviser who we don't see very often but occasionally and erm he was saying that he'd been er he'd attended a conference fairly recently did I tell you? and he <trunc>t</trunc> he said the erm the speaker was really interesting I think it was er a <trunc>d</trunc>a doctor a medical doctor that er they had at the opening speaker or something at their conference saying that basically er you know medicine has really come on <trunc>m</trunc> you know leaps and bounds and they can keep people alive now you know we're all living longer they can do marvellous things you know with all the transplants and everything else <unclear/> and they were then talking er he was talking about you know erm farmers and food and how we can genetically modify our food and we can change all of this and you know the whole thing he said so erm basically er we're all living longer we've all got the food to sustain us but frankly we can't afford to live longer so over to you lot cos it was the it was the er the conference of the financial advisers <unclear/></u>
<u n="663" who="S0558">right</u>
<u n="664" who="S0517">how are you lot gonna now fund the fact that you know? it's like</u>
<u n="665" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="666" who="S0517">we've done our jobs the doctors the farmers are doing theirs the duh duh duh scientists are doing theirs how are you lot gonna fund it? and er he said yeah we didn't really have an answer cos <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="667" who="S0558">no that's right isn't it?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0517">you know you stop working in your sixties or even seventy and then you've gotta last</u>
<u n="669" who="S0558">sixty-seven is it now? <trunc>retir</trunc> official retirement</u>
<u n="670" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0558">sixty-seven</u>
<u n="672" who="S0517">all that money's gotta last <unclear>well er for my case</unclear> thirty years <unclear/></u>
<u n="673" who="S0558">I know</u>
<u n="674" who="S0517">forty years if nan's gonna be a hundred and five I'll probably be a hundred and ten</u>
<u n="675" who="S0558">god</u>
<u n="676" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="677" who="S0558">oh dear me I dunno if I'd want to be living like your nan is</u>
<u n="678" who="S0517">I wouldn't absolutely not</u>
<u n="679" who="S0558">I'd rather go at</u>
<u n="680" who="S0517">and so er yeah <unclear>and so</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="681" who="S0558">oh I'm not even gonna say an age just in case</u>
<u n="682" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="683" who="S0558">but you know</u>
<u n="684" who="S0517">no she had a really really good life until she was ninety-seven and that you know and what's wrong with that?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0558">ninety-seven <unclear/> <unclear>age</unclear></u>
<u n="686" who="S0517"><unclear>she just</unclear> ninety-seven she was still living on her own but then you know it really went downhill so now it's just like a really long slow death it really is</u>
<u n="687" who="S0558">it's awful isn't it?</u>
<u n="688" who="S0517">it is awful <unclear/></u>
<u n="689" who="S0558">this is where you should be allowed to have an injection or make a decision</u>
<u n="690" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="691" who="S0558">for somebody to have an injection</u>
<u n="692" who="S0517">definitely definitely cos <unclear>no</unclear></u>
<u n="693" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="694" who="S0517">it's not you know no quality of life it is a shame but as I keep telling my mum there's nothing we can do they're not changing it they just she keeps saying why do they keep feeding her? I said because they have to <unclear/></u>
<u n="695" who="S0558">they have to</u>
<u n="696" who="S0517">it's a duty of care</u>
<u n="697" who="S0558">yeah I know</u>
<u n="698" who="S0517">but if she lived on her own she wouldn't be here and then it'd be so much better for <unclear/> she said oh she'd hate it if she could see herself</u>
<u n="699" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="700" who="S0517">you know she would hate it</u>
<u n="701" who="S0558">she would yeah</u>
<u n="702" who="S0517">cos she was always very you know careful with her appearance and</u>
<u n="703" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="704" who="S0517">you know like most people</u>
<u n="705" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="706" who="S0517">it's just a loss of dignity isn't it?</u>
<u n="707" who="S0558">it's awful</u>
<u n="708" who="S0517">it is she just she <unclear/></u>
<u n="709" who="S0558">she's not communicating with anybody</u>
<u n="710" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="711" who="S0558">she's not getting any pleasures of entertainment</u>
<u n="712" who="S0517">nothing she just she just sleeps</u>
<u n="713" who="S0558">it's awful isn't it?</u>
<u n="714" who="S0517"><unclear/> not you know she's not even watching the telly</u>
<u n="715" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="716" who="S0517">just sleeps lies in the bed day and night</u>
<u n="717" who="S0558"><unclear>I know</unclear> awful</u>
<u n="718" who="S0517">very depressing</u>
<u n="719" who="S0558">she's probably not even aware which thankfully cos she's sleeping so much she's not aware of how long she's in bed hopefully</u>
<u n="720" who="S0517"><unclear>yeah</unclear> maybe well <vocal desc="laugh"/> five years now</u>
<u n="721" who="S0558"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="722" who="S0517">and I don't think she's been out of that room for</u>
<u n="723" who="S0558">I mean the thing is now as well it's like she's in this silent world as well</u>
<u n="724" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="725" who="S0558">really inspiring I was at erm <anon type="place"/> hospital last week and there was a lady who was obviously profoundly deaf who had got an appointment</u>
<u n="726" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="727" who="S0558">and er the gist of the conversation with the lady who was with her is erm basically like your <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when she's qualified erm I don't know whether it goes through a central point of wherever but a call is requested that you know er a lady has got an appointment she needs an interpreter</u>
<u n="728" who="S0517">okay yeah</u>
<u n="729" who="S0558">so they met at the hospital and she goes into the appointment with her and does all the sign language</u>
<u n="730" who="S0517">and does the sign language yeah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0558">and all the rest of it and I thought oh</u>
<u n="732" who="S0517">oh see that's the sort of thing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'d like to do</u>
<u n="733" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="734" who="S0517">when she's erm</u>
<u n="735" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="736" who="S0517">I don't know how easy that is to do or how qualified you need to be</u>
<u n="737" who="S0558">well I think</u>
<u n="738" who="S0517">cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s she's only doing the first</u>
<u n="739" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="740" who="S0517">I suppose the first level</u>
<u n="741" who="S0558">right</u>
<u n="742" who="S0517">there are a lot of levels and if it's medical stuff I don't know but she would like to or go into schools and</u>
<u n="743" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="744" who="S0517">help but I don't know how she's going to go about it I don't think she <unclear>doesn't</unclear> yet</u>
<u n="745" who="S0558">is she going to be doing any childcare for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> eventually do you think? cos that'll limit her won't it?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0517">quite possibly</u>
<u n="747" who="S0558">do you think?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0517">I don't know whether any of that's been all sort of <trunc>s</trunc>set in stone because I think I know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has voiced to me I don't think she's said it to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yet but obviously she's more than happy to have <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but you know what she's like come May she wants to go on holiday for three months</u>
<u n="749" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="750" who="S0517">and so she doesn't want to be committed to</u>
<u n="751" who="S0558">no I and I can fully understand that</u>
<u n="752" who="S0517">two or three you know couple of days a week is fine when it suits her</u>
<u n="753" who="S0558"><vocal desc="cough"/> when it suits her yeah</u>
<u n="754" who="S0517">but not when she wants to go to their place in Bulgaria for three months in the summer</u>
<u n="755" who="S0558">personally on a long term basis because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s not gonna be able to phone up a nursery and say can I book <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in for the next two weeks or the next month</u>
<u n="756" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="757" who="S0558">cos you know how precious these places are</u>
<u n="758" who="S0517">oh yeah</u>
<u n="759" who="S0558">if I was her I'd start straight off with the proper <trunc>chil</trunc> not proper I don't mean that</u>
<u n="760" who="S0517">but yeah I know what you mean yes yeah</u>
<u n="761" who="S0558">disrespectful to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but you know because then then if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants to look after <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="762" who="S0517">mm mm</u>
<u n="763" who="S0558">she can say don't send him to nursery today I'll have him</u>
<u n="764" who="S0517">or even if she just <trunc>sai</trunc> well I'll go and pick him up</u>
<u n="765" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="766" who="S0517">and have him till or</u>
<u n="767" who="S0558">I'll yeah I'll pick him up or I'll pick him up earlier or</u>
<u n="768" who="S0517">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="769" who="S0558">yeah personally</u>
<u n="770" who="S0517">I know</u>
<u n="771" who="S0558">if the conversation comes up that's the <unclear/></u>
<u n="772" who="S0517">I mean I I haven't got involved that's not for me</u>
<u n="773" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="774" who="S0517">but erm</u>
<u n="775" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="776" who="S0517">I don't know how that'll go</u>
<u n="777" who="S0558">cos I mean yes financially you know it will be very helpful to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="778" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="779" who="S0558">but equally <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got a good job</u>
<u n="780" who="S0517">yes he has yeah</u>
<u n="781" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got a good job and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s at the time of her life now where she can have a little bit of</u>
<u n="782" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="783" who="S0558">come and go as she pleases she's given up work</u>
<u n="784" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="785" who="S0558">although <trunc>i</trunc> er initially you know it it would be really easy wouldn't it? to say oh let me look after him let me look <trunc>af</trunc></u>
<u n="786" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="787" who="S0558">I love it I love it but five days a week is a hell of a commitment</u>
<u n="788" who="S0517">oh no she wouldn't do that no she wouldn't do that</u>
<u n="789" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="790" who="S0517">definitely she wouldn't even offer that</u>
<u n="791" who="S0558">no no</u>
<u n="792" who="S0517">she did have him the other day all ready for the day</u>
<u n="793" who="S0558">yes</u>
<u n="794" who="S0517">can you just stick that lamp on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? it's getting a bit dark isn't it?</u>
<u n="795" who="S0558">I'm just gonna</u>
<u n="796" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="797" who="S0558">I'm gonna visit the ladies</u>
<u n="798" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="799" who="S0558">is that alright?</u>
<u n="800" who="S0517">that's fine shall I just?</u>
<u n="801" who="S0558">don't pause no because it'll erm</u>
<u n="802" who="S0517"><unclear/> who shall I talk to?</u>
<u n="803" who="S0558">just carry on talking</u>
<u n="804" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="805" who="S0558"><unclear>I'll listen to you</unclear></u>
<u n="806" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="807" who="S0558">just carry on</u>
<u n="808" who="S0517">oh is that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> out walking her dog? no that's not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="809" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="810" who="S0517">no it's not</u>
<u n="811" who="S0558"><unclear/> dog <unclear>haven't they</unclear>?</u>
<u n="812" who="S0517">that's not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="long"/> er it's come up with numbers</u>
<u n="813" who="S0558">yes yes it has</u>
<u n="814" who="S0517">yeah so that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="815" who="S0558">oh excellent</u>
<u n="816" who="S0517">no I thought that was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but it's not</u>
<u n="817" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="818" who="S0517">I haven't seen her in ages have you?</u>
<u n="819" who="S0558">no I don't see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at all really</u>
<u n="820" who="S0517">no I don't even see her in the village in the pub or anything</u>
<u n="821" who="S0558">no no never see her dunno dunno who that dog is on the right he's new not seen him about oh that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> isn't it? with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="822" who="S0517">I don't know</u>
<u n="823" who="S0558">in the purple</u>
<u n="824" who="S0517">oh is it?</u>
<u n="825" who="S0558">I think that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s wife with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but I dunno who the other one is I dunno who that is</u>
<u n="826" who="S0517"><unclear/> <unclear>you're not</unclear> on the dog watching circuit you should know these people <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="827" who="S0558">mm I've not seen them <unclear/></u>
<u n="828" who="S0517">I haven't got a clue who they are look our hedge is coming on isn't it?</u>
<u n="829" who="S0558">it is yeah</u>
<u n="830" who="S0517">isn't it?</u>
<u n="831" who="S0558">every time I drive past I look at it and think oh</u>
<u n="832" who="S0517"><unclear>well</unclear> obviously it's got a way to go but it's coming on</u>
<u n="833" who="S0558">do you speak to your neighbours much?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0517">a little bit</u>
<u n="835" who="S0558">just see them</u>
<u n="836" who="S0517">she came round the other morning <vocal desc="laugh"/> bless her</u>
<u n="837" who="S0558">in the morning?</u>
<u n="838" who="S0517"><unclear/> in the morning they'd been er they'd had the two cars on the drive it must've <unclear/> did we have ice one morning?</u>
<u n="839" who="S0558">yeah we did yeah</u>
<u n="840" who="S0517">it was that morning</u>
<u n="841" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="842" who="S0517">her husband had gone out and he'd gone off to <anon type="place"/> for the day but he had de-iced or done something with the cars before he went and he'd only gone off with both sets of car keys <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="843" who="S0558"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="844" who="S0517">so they</u>
<u n="845" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="846" who="S0517">they've got a spare set of car keys each but they're er each on each other's key ring and he'd gone off with two complete sets of</u>
<u n="847" who="S0558">oh right</u>
<u n="848" who="S0517">of key rings</u>
<u n="849" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="850" who="S0517">down to <anon type="place"/> so she came round could she please er she had no money could she please borrow ten pounds so she could get a taxi into work?</u>
<u n="851" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="852" who="S0517">and then she phoned him and I don't think he was originally gonna be coming back till the next day <vocal desc="laugh"/> but she <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="853" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="854" who="S0517">cos she came back round at teatime to return the ten pounds and said thank you so much</u>
<u n="855" who="S0558">oh bless</u>
<u n="856" who="S0517">erm yes no he had to come back and then he's gotta go to <anon type="place"/> again tomorrow</u>
<u n="857" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="858" who="S0517">and he won't be doing that again</u>
<u n="859" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="860" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="861" who="S0558">de-ice your own car</u>
<u n="862" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="863" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="864" who="S0517">but no they're very nice actually</u>
<u n="865" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="866" who="S0517">they are very nice people</u>
<u n="867" who="S0558">cos are <unclear>they</unclear> children at our school? <unclear/></u>
<u n="868" who="S0517">yes er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s in the boys' year <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="869" who="S0558">oh is she?</u>
<u n="870" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="871" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="872" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s year</u>
<u n="873" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="874" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm</u>
<u n="875" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="876" who="S0517">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s in their in and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is year eight so yeah</u>
<u n="877" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="878" who="S0517">but I erm I haven't been speaking to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but I did text her and yes he has moved back in</u>
<u n="879" who="S0558"><vocal desc="gasp"/> did you say? <trunc>di</trunc> er</u>
<u n="880" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="881" who="S0558">did you refer?</u>
<u n="882" who="S0517">do you know? weirdly</u>
<u n="883" who="S0558">cos I</u>
<u n="884" who="S0517">weirdly enough right because you know she'd told me that he'd moved out?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0558">well er yeah as in he'd up and left</u>
<u n="886" who="S0517"><unclear/> he'd up and left</u>
<u n="887" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="888" who="S0517">that's right so er whichever day that was that you had texted me just like literally an hour or so before I had texted <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just to say oh how are things going? you know er er</u>
<u n="889" who="S0558">right</u>
<u n="890" who="S0517"><trunc>i</trunc>is it alright? do you need not need any help but you know I E</u>
<u n="891" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="892" who="S0517">shall we meet up? or do you need anyone to talk to? type of thing and then you sent me the text saying I've just been delivering Avon and he's answered the door so I thought oh but I was waiting for the reply at which point she did come back and say that erm he'd moved back in I've forgotten how she phrased it and it's on the phone he'd moved back in on the Saturday so it didn't look too weird for the girls erm low key low drama er <trunc>w</trunc> seeing how it goes <trunc>i</trunc>it was really weird</u>
<u n="893" who="S0558">wow</u>
<u n="894" who="S0517">it was almost like it was almost like they'd just sort of gone back to how they were but without having discussed it or anything but the girls surely would've noticed he'd been gone about three weeks <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="895" who="S0558">well I suppose they could say er business something to do with business</u>
<u n="896" who="S0517">yeah who knows yeah</u>
<u n="897" who="S0558">three weeks? that long? <unclear/></u>
<u n="898" who="S0517">well she said well it would be cos this was only recently</u>
<u n="899" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="900" who="S0517">and he'd gone on <unclear/></u>
<u n="901" who="S0558">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came back out right and she got in the car and she went oh it's a bit tense in there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="902" who="S0517">oh really?</u>
<u n="903" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="904" who="S0558"><unclear>cos</unclear> sometimes she sounds like a thirty-year-old woman I swear to god I don't know where she gets her phrases from</u>
<u n="905" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="906" who="S0558">and I went to her why? and she said well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have you got any money? probably not before he even had a chance to answer</u>
<u n="907" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="908" who="S0558">she said erm I'll have to do a probably not so I'll have to do a cheque he said I'll go upstairs and have a look so apparently he ran upstairs had a look and er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said as he was going up the stairs apparently <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> rolled her eyes</u>
<u n="909" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="910" who="S0558">and then he came downstairs and said oh no I haven't got any</u>
<u n="911" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="912" who="S0558">and and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said something like oh no I thought I thought not or something carrying on writing the cheque even though he'd gone upstairs</u>
<u n="913" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="914" who="S0558">to see if there was any money and erm and and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said what are they doing together? she said you've got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> obviously just come from work these are <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s words looking very smart in a dress you know really really lovely and then you've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="915" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="916" who="S0558">she said they just don't go together mum</u>
<u n="917" who="S0517">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s always said that though hasn't she? from the minute she clapped eyes on him</u>
<u n="918" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0517">but erm well he's just a bit of an erm you know he's an old old man really now isn't he? compared to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="920" who="S0558">cos she said to me <trunc>wha</trunc>what does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> see in him? and I said well <trunc>w</trunc>when they first met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I said erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had recently returned to work so she was sort of going <trunc>int</trunc> returning to a new world you know</u>
<u n="921" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="922" who="S0558">coming from being a full time mum and that I said and erm he just happened to be a partner in the company where she was going so sort of a bit of a you know high flyer and all this and that and she'd see him every day looking very smart in his suit and you know well turned out</u>
<u n="923" who="S0517">mm mm</u>
<u n="924" who="S0558">got a good job and you know all the rest of it and and that was probably the attraction at the time</u>
<u n="925" who="S0517">it's different living together isn't it? when he's just falling asleep on the sofa of an evening but I don't so I don't know any more than that <unclear>doesn't just I dunno</unclear> she said low key low drama er but I thought well the girls will've noticed but anyway er</u>
<u n="926" who="S0558">I saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at school today erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hasn't said anything and generally <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will come up to me and</u>
<u n="927" who="S0517"><unclear>cos well</unclear> she tells you everything doesn't she?</u>
<u n="928" who="S0558">yeah she does she does come up to</u>
<u n="929" who="S0517">what year's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? five? four? <trunc>fi</trunc> four?</u>
<u n="930" who="S0558">five now aren't they?</u>
<u n="931" who="S0517">five?</u>
<u n="932" who="S0558">no no no no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s six so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s four isn't she?</u>
<u n="933" who="S0517">year four</u>
<u n="934" who="S0558">erm</u>
<u n="935" who="S0517">so what does that make her? nine?</u>
<u n="936" who="S0558">so she'd be nine</u>
<u n="937" who="S0517">eight or nine</u>
<u n="938" who="S0558">wouldn't she? ten</u>
<u n="939" who="S0517">nine</u>
<u n="940" who="S0558"><trunc>eleve</trunc> yeah so nine this school year wouldn't she?</u>
<u n="941" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="942" who="S0558">but erm</u>
<u n="943" who="S0517">oh I don't know but but it doesn't sound very good with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and his kidneys</u>
<u n="944" who="S0558">I know you were saying is he still doing this renovation?</u>
<u n="945" who="S0517">I think so</u>
<u n="946" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="947" who="S0517">I saw erm where are we? <trunc>y</trunc> only yesterday <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at the football</u>
<u n="948" who="S0558">oh yes</u>
<u n="949" who="S0517">and you know he'd invited the boys round to watch the fight?</u>
<u n="950" who="S0558">yes</u>
<u n="951" who="S0517">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hadn't gone but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had gone</u>
<u n="952" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="953" who="S0517">and he'd said he'd he had opened up a little bit to them about the problem with his kidneys and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said I didn't he didn't really appreciate the full extent but it doesn't sound very good at all and he probably will end up being on the</u>
<u n="954" who="S0558">dialysis</u>
<u n="955" who="S0517">er well on the on the list for erm</u>
<u n="956" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="957" who="S0517">a transplant I mean he's only what? forty-two apparently it's the same sort of thing that Jonah <trunc>Lo</trunc> what's his name? you know the rugby player Jonah <trunc>Lo</trunc>Lomu? you know the New Zealand rugby player that's just died?</u>
<u n="958" who="S0558">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="959" who="S0517">apparently it's the same complaint that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got cos that was a long-term kidney thing</u>
<u n="960" who="S0558">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="961" who="S0517">but <vocal desc="sigh"/> so it doesn't sound very good cos well he's only what? is he forty-two? forty-three? can't be forty</u>
<u n="962" who="S0558">is he the same sort of age as <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="963" who="S0517"><unclear>I think he's</unclear></u>
<u n="964" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s nine years younger than me</u>
<u n="965" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s forty-one but she I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had his fortieth before she did</u>
<u n="966" who="S0558"><unclear>my goodness they</unclear> were in the same school year <unclear/> same school year</u>
<u n="967" who="S0517">I always thought that but he <trunc>d</trunc> he had his fortieth way before her though didn't he?</u>
<u n="968" who="S0558">did he? was <unclear>it</unclear> in the same school year <unclear>though</unclear>? I'm sure they were in the same school year</u>
<u n="969" who="S0517">I you see I always thought that but I remember thinking when they were having their birthdays they can't've been in the <vocal desc="laugh"/> same school year</u>
<u n="970" who="S0558">oh I'll have to find out</u>
<u n="971" who="S0517">I dunno</u>
<u n="972" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="973" who="S0517"><unclear>I know</unclear> but wasn't the school show fantastic?</u>
<u n="974" who="S0558"><vocal desc="gasp"/> <unclear>I tell you I had</unclear></u>
<u n="975" who="S0517">did you see the <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="976" who="S0558">I had to remind myself I was in the <anon type="place"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="977" who="S0517"><unclear/> did you see the erm the write-up in the paper?</u>
<u n="978" who="S0558">no I haven't</u>
<u n="979" who="S0517">oh I think I've recycled my Mercury</u>
<u n="980" who="S0558">the Mercury?</u>
<u n="981" who="S0517">yeah last week's</u>
<u n="982" who="S0558">oh I've still got it</u>
<u n="983" who="S0517">oh yeah there's a write-up in there er really glowing write-up</u>
<u n="984" who="S0558">really?</u>
<u n="985" who="S0517">obviously I mean it was a fantastic</u>
<u n="986" who="S0558"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="987" who="S0517">you did you forgot you were in a school</u>
<u n="988" who="S0558">I know</u>
<u n="989" who="S0517">unbelievable</u>
<u n="990" who="S0558">did you cry?</u>
<u n="991" who="S0517">no I didn't cry</u>
<u n="992" who="S0558">oh I did</u>
<u n="993" who="S0517">did you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="994" who="S0558">yeah I dunno whether it's cos like I know it's man woman but you know he was dying and and</u>
<u n="995" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="996" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="997" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="998" who="S0558">obviously not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the thing is I thought she was brilliant</u>
<u n="999" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0558">the way she was going no no and she was <unclear>like</unclear> really there</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0517"><unclear/> their voices their singing voices were just incredible</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0558">oh my god</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying that a couple of them I don't know which two this was their first year at the <anon type="place"/> they'd moved from other schools</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0558"><trunc>th</trunc>there's a girl</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0517">to come to the <anon type="place"/> just because of its fantastic reputation in the drama I suppose <unclear/></u>
<u n="1006" who="S0558">I know there's a girl because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> mentioned there's a new girl I don't know who the other one is though</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0517">I don't know but <unclear/></u>
<u n="1008" who="S0558">but you know the lead? the <trunc>ma</trunc> the the guy?</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0517"><unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? was his name <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0558">er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1011" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0558">apparently cos he should've had his assessment if you like last year</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0517">of his A level?</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0558">on his performance for his A level</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0558">I don't know why he didn't whether he was away or ill</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0558">I don't know so he was being assessed this year</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0558">and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum and dad when we came <unclear>out</unclear> cos I said oh tell <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she made me cry and her mum was laughing I and I said my goodness the talent is unbelievable</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0517">unbelievable</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0558">and erm I said I'll tell you something I said erm we were talking and I said there's some leads there I said I said if if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was to audition for a <vocal desc="laugh"/> West End spot tomorrow I think he'd get it</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0517">oh gosh his diction was fantastic</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0558"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1025" who="S0517">and and er and so powerful I just couldn't believe it the <trunc>l</trunc> the guy that played the innkeeper oh</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0558">oh god</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0517">I mean how brilliant was he?</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0558">absolutely <trunc>bri</trunc></u>
<u n="1029" who="S0517">he was just</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0558">and her though</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0558">the <trunc>g</trunc></u>
<u n="1033" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0558">like his wife if you like</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0517">both of them</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0558">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0517">but even the little one cos I think cos I mean some of them when <unclear>you came out</unclear> they looked tiny</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0558">she's seven</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0517">the the little one that played the young Cosette?</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0517">I thought well she's earmarked for erm</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0558">cos cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to me do you <trunc>m</trunc>mum she's only year seven</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0517">well and she looked it she was tiny she was a tiny dot</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0558">she was brilliant wasn't she?</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0517">but she was had a lovely voice and I thought oh she'll be she'll be in the leads in a few years to come</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0517">she'll be singing the the lead roles but she was brilliant just</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0558">absolutely brilliant</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1050" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying he thinks that the lower school production is gonna be erm</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0517">The Lion King</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0517">well in the paper it had written what it was they're doing The Lion King and then next year's main one</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0558">big one</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0517">is Billy Elliot</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0558"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1057" who="S0517">so they must have a boy in mind</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0517">to play that lead already that can sing and dance</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0558">well it said that about this one this year didn't they? that er er it you have to be careful obviously what you do each year but</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0558">it was sort of heavily male cast that were suitable for doing</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0558">Les Mis</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0558">but oh my goodness me</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0517">they were unbelievable</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1069" who="S0517">cos I really enjoyed Singing in the Rain last year</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0558">yes</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0517">I thought that was excellent but this one just eclipsed it by a mile I thought it was a fantastic production</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0558">yeah absolutely amazing I could've gone back and watched it again I could've</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0517">I know they were sold out weren't they?</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0517"><trunc>ni</trunc> I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said that they'd</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0558">I mean night one</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0517">they'd made</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0558">standing ovation</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0558">and er apparently <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said every night</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0517">oh there was yeah</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0558">there was</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0517">but I don't know how much money it made I think this was one of the first ones</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1085" who="S0517">he said that had made money</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1087" who="S0517">cos they spend a lot on their props and</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0558">Singing in the Rain lost didn't it?</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0517">it did but I think that was the expense of getting the <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1090" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0517">the rain in <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1092" who="S0558">the water</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said well water's can't cost much can it?</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1095" who="S0517"><unclear/> no but getting it pouring down on a school stage might do <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1096" who="S0558">yeah unbelievable</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0517">but yeah it was really really good</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0558"><unclear>well</unclear> I'm going to actually look at perhaps going to see one of the youth erm things you know the youth the <anon type="place"/> youth?</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0517">oh er in in in the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0558">yeah I'm going to have a look</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0558">and go and visit and</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0558">watch one of them</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0517">cos is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> still keen to? she wasn't in this one cos she was selling the popcorn <unclear/></u>
<u n="1106" who="S0558">yeah she was selling the popcorn no she wasn't in this one because because she's not doing it as a GCSE</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0558">she didn't want to</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0558">give all the time up for the</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0558">the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1113" who="S0517">what did she choose for her options? I don't think I asked you</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0558">history Spanish geography and</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1116" who="S0558">graphic design</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0517">mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="1120" who="S0558">she's quite arty</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0558">she's very good at drawing her art the art teacher Mr <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> desperately wanted her to do art</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0517"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0558"><trunc>m</trunc> for weeks</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0517">that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s form teacher</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0558">oh for weeks <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said leading up she'd come home she'd say oh Mr <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to me again today he's not gonna let me out of the classroom unless</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0558">I definitely do art and lots of little things</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0517">but she's so sporty I don't whether she'd've taken PE</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0558">no she's said she does enough of it outside of school</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0517">right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0558">she didn't want</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0517">that's true</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0517">mm did I tell you about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s cross-country run for the county?</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0558">I know that he hang on you've told me that he was you've told me something tell me again</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0517">what a disaster</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0558">oh no you've not told me then</u>
<u n="1139" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1140" who="S0517">it was just a nightmare</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0558">oh something's just happened to that is it alright? it just lit up</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0517">oh did it?</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0558">or was it cos I touched the table?</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0517">no it's</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0517">no it's still there</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0558">right</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0517">no just erm no oh there's a message on there I don't know what that is er no you know er</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0558"><unclear>what time is it</unclear>?</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0517">he got it's er twenty past three</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0558"><unclear>oh that's</unclear></u>
<u n="1152" who="S0517">what time you have to be?</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0558">that's fine I've gotta pick <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> up at half four from school</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0517">oh have you?</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1156" who="S0517">I've gotta pick <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> up at half five from school</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1158" who="S0517">refereeing course</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0517">and of course the other ones aren't home are they? so</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0517"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh yeah er he did the cos you know he'd done athletics in the? he'd done the fifteen hundred metres in the summer</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0517">and he did the cross he <trunc>ga</trunc>he gave up running he decided it wasn't for him</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0558">right</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0517">he didn't want to do it but he did say well if the school ask me to do cross-country I'll do cross-country so he he ran it for the school <event desc="sound of phone"/></u>
<u n="1167" who="S0558">was that that?</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0517">message I don't know what that is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> he ran it for the school</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0517">and erm he did well and I don't know if I told you but the <anon type="place"/> won</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0517">did I tell you? I can't remember</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0558">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="1174" who="S0517"><unclear/> they went to something else</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0558">cos I didn't know he'd <unclear>give</unclear> it up so you definitely haven't told me</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0517">oh okay oh he gave it up in the summer he decided <unclear>that</unclear></u>
<u n="1177" who="S0558">right</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0517">he didn't really enjoy running but he did the cross-country and he came I think he came third in the cross-country so then he got taken to another one this was for the the district</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0517">all the all the <anon type="place"/> schools and he came he came eighth and the first twelve were asked to represent the county at the inter county run</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0558">right</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0517">so he was in that <event desc="sound of phone"/> is that you?</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0558">I think that might be mine</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0517">is that your news app? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1185" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1187" who="S0558">let's see what's happening in the world</u>
<u n="1188" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1189" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1190" who="S0517">is that what that noise was?</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1192" who="S0517">what are you like?</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0558"><unclear/> I don't know <unclear/></u>
<u n="1194" who="S0517"><unclear/> it sounded like ITV <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is that who you?</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0558">it's BBC</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0517">oh it's BBC</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1198" who="S0517">that's what I meant BBC so the <anon type="place"/> right they had four children <trunc>th</trunc>that oh I've forgot how it worked the top four boys basically with all their positions the <anon type="place"/> won the overall cross-country thing</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0558">right</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0517">so they all came home with medals but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was the only one that got invited to the cross-country county tournament</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0558">right</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0517">is anything happening in the world <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that we should know about? I'll pause my story</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0558">no you carry on and I'll tell you but remind me to tell you it's nothing in the world</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0517">oh okay oh okay <unclear>we're</unclear> okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1205" who="S0558">fine</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0517">so anyway</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's just the <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1208" who="S0517">so we had this thing right? and it was in <anon type="place"/> university so it was up in <anon type="place"/> it was on the Saturday</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0517">his race was two thirty had to be there at one o'clock to register</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0517">what a pain</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0558"><unclear>oh yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="1214" who="S0517">we set off from here at midday just starting to rain torrential by the time we got there got to the university</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0558">the joys of the athletics world</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0517">there was an <trunc>op</trunc>there was an open day on so it was rammed there was nowhere to park I was driving around in the rain finally found somewhere to park we walked out no signs didn't know where we were going saw a field headed that way loads of people mud you know it was ridiculous <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said oh this isn't much fun is it mum?</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1218" who="S0517">I said no it is no fun at all I had my umbrella up my big <trunc>c</trunc> oh so <trunc>eve</trunc> I said to a lady I said er is this the cross-country? yeah she said if you just go round that bend there you'll see all the tents go and register pouring with rain <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went oh I see I see <anon type="place"/> you know they have like those flags?</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0558">yes</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0517">you know those er?</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0558">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0517">you've done all this haven't you?</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0558">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0517">so I sort of peered out from under my umbrella right okay followed him off nobody there you know there was loads of people there nobody official looking</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0558">you know yeah</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0517">nobody I knew so I just said to a man that had a clipboard you know he's here to to to run what year? year nine oh no I'm year seven boys erm try him over there so I went to him he's here to run year nine boys what's his name? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> duh duh duh oh he's not on my list oh what school is he at? I said the <anon type="place"/> oh that's strange he's not on my list doesn't matter that's fine what's his name? wrote it down and put a tick next to it right it's er one o'clock as instructed he said I said well what time do we need to be back here? he said well quarter past two he said do you want to walk the route? I said well we can see it it's er up that hill and down and then up that hill and down you know it didn't look very nice and there was <trunc>p</trunc>plenty of people walking it I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do you wanna walk the route <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? pouring with rain he said no I said er I said no nor me come on we'll go back to the car so we moved the car cos once we knew where we were we could see a space closer so we moved the car quarter past two we went back over there it was so wet the mud was unbelievable cos there'd already been three races and erm we found the man that we'd <trunc>s</trunc> been speaking to and we <trunc>a</trunc>we asked for the bib and he said er what school did you say he was at? I said the <anon type="place"/> oh he said I thought you said the <anon type="place"/> the <anon type="place"/>'s not one of ours where's that? I said <anon type="place"/> he went that's <anon type="place"/> I said I know he said this is <anon type="place"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1227" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1228" who="S0517"><trunc>s</trunc>so I</u>
<u n="1229" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1230" who="S0517">peered out from under my umbrella and still <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had said I could see <anon type="place"/> erm I could see the S at the bottom the tent was obscuring the bit in the middle and I <trunc>s</trunc> could see the shire at the top</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1232" who="S0517">so I I said oh <trunc>g</trunc> I said I'm so sorry I said I'm so sorry we are <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1233" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1234" who="S0517">and he went oh you wanna go over this side laughing you wanna go over there follow me so we <vocal desc="sigh"/> tramping across this mud to this fella and he said that's who you wanna talk to and off he went so I said to this man I said I know it's twenty past two I said I'm really sorry</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1236" who="S0517">I was here at one o'clock but we registered him for <anon type="place"/> for <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1237" who="S0558"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1238" who="S0517">and er he just laughed he went oh they need all the runners they can get in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1239" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1240" who="S0517">he said what's his name? I said well he wasn't on their list but he just wrote him down so I didn't see it as er suspicious he just wrote it down and ticked it he said what's his name? I said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> well he's cos he's on our list</u>
<u n="1241" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1242" who="S0517">and you're late</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1244" who="S0517">so he just handed him a bib he said it's alright we've got the erm the starter the you know the man with the tannoy and and he's <trunc>st</trunc> he was still doing something so you're alright you've got a minute have a little warm up</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0558"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1246" who="S0517">it was so cold I mean it was so cold and it was just sheeting rain and he's there in er in his white blinking Nike top that was</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1248" who="S0517">oh it was ridiculous</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0558">and er was it at that point he thought this is not for me?</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0517">he's just this is not for me I said this is not for me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1251" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1252" who="S0517">I don't know about you I'm out here with my coat and my umbrella</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1254" who="S0517">and there was a girl you know she had her she'd obviously just run and she had her foot out and her ankle was swollen up and St John's Ambulance was tending to her we saw about three girls crying</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0558"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1256" who="S0517">like that had run whether they were crying cos</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0558">goodness me</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0517">they hadn't done as well as they wanted I don't know whatever so I said to him and we could see it getting muddier and muddier and muddier and I said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I said I'm not being funny you're not gonna win this race I said and you wanna play football tomorrow just get round the course don't just don't get round without injuring yourself so he goes for the starting line and I could see him in the corner and I thought oh I'll try and take a picture to show <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but I was not putting my umbrella down</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0517">so I was trying to do it one handed it was a disaster they all started running and I thought well where is he? where is he? where is he? he was right at the very very back I thought <unclear/> that's not like I know there was eighty people <unclear/></u>
<u n="1261" who="S0558"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1262" who="S0517">that's not like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he was right at the back well at the end it turned out I found out he'd fallen over on the starting line</u>
<u n="1263" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1264" who="S0517">he slipped over in the mud on the starting line <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1265" who="S0558">oh bless him</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0517">so I watched him go off cos you know he can he's got stamina and he can run but I watched him go off and he did overtake a handful of people and then I sort of positioned myself <unclear>you know I mean</unclear> you could see most of the course it was up and down hills and then I positioned myself at the finishing stretch and I could make him out and I thought he is right at the back but you know that's okay so these two lads went past <unclear>with er</unclear> it was a sprint finish they were done then I mean I wasn't counting but maybe tenth fifteenth place this lad ran past puking up I mean he had his</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0517">head turned to one side and was literally being sick I thought I <trunc>h</trunc>I had no one to speak to I was there on my own I just thought why are you still running? why? you're not even gonna win</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0558">no it's it's something to do with lactic acid no no that no that's not it happens all the time at athletics right?</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0517">does it? <unclear>I thought</unclear></u>
<u n="1271" who="S0558">yeah they'll be running yeah and er basically they they just put so much pressure on their bodies</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0558">I dunno <trunc>lac</trunc> I dunno if it's lactic acid it's <trunc>someth</trunc> anyway it's hilarious <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because you just see them I and I mean I tell you it's spine-tingling some of the athletes down at</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1275" who="S0558"><anon type="place"/> <trunc>th</trunc>the speed they travel</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0558">it's spine-tingling and they'll just get to the end or whatever they'll go over to side puke up</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0517"><unclear/> well <unclear/></u>
<u n="1279" who="S0558">give a sort of acknowledgement</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1281" who="S0558">so somebody knows to go down</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0558">with a bucket of <trunc>wat</trunc>bucket bucket of water</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0517">and then they're and they're fine</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0558">and then they carry on</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0517">well er he was puking as he running past me</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0558"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1288" who="S0517">I thought that was vile</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0558">oh vile</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0517">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> eventually came in right and bless him he was seventy-fifth out of eighty</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0558">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="1292" who="S0517">so <unclear/> he'd said I'm not gonna come last I said no that's fine you're not gonna come last but he was seventy-fifth so they he took his thing and the man from <anon type="place"/> organising it just said to him <unclear/> that was fantastic he said that you got round that course he said I'm telling you he said you haven't got spikes on your feet have you? he said no <vocal desc="laugh"/> he said I'm telling you the best runner wouldn't've come top fifty in these conditions without spikes on their feet the fact that you've got round in the time that you have is fantastic</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0558">is good</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0517">so he <trunc>ca</trunc> <unclear>he goes</unclear> mum I don't wanna do that again I said no nor me so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1295" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't do cross-country</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0517">we went home we went home and we got back at about four o'clock and literally as we were pulling onto the drive the rain stopped and it cleared up you know and then I think the next night er all the scores came through and I think the winners had done it in thirteen minutes and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had taken sixteen minutes he said he'd fallen over four times and one of the times was when he was going up one of the hills and he'd slid down</u>
<u n="1297" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1298" who="S0517">which you shouldn't laugh I mean you could see why there were girls crying at the end</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0558">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="1300" who="S0517">he wasn't crying and do you know he was barely even really out of breath but he said he couldn't get he couldn't run he couldn't get going but</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0558">well no because he'd just be slipping with flat</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0517">I said to him <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I said four hours we were out of this house and sixteen minutes you were running <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1303" who="S0558">do you know?</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1305" who="S0558">it's like when you go when you go to a competition <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> right <unclear>you er</unclear> admittedly you do only have to be there an hour before</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0558">but the field events generally start off <unclear>yeah</unclear> and you'll have hurdles going at the same time</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0517"><unclear>yeah yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="1309" who="S0558">so if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is doing javelin for example maybe if the competition opens at ten</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0558">you need to be there for nine or ten thirty be there for nine thirty</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0558">she might do javelin at eleven as an example and then she always ends up being in the relay which is the last competition of the day</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0517">oh it's always I remember you saying that in the past <unclear>so you're</unclear></u>
<u n="1315" who="S0558">so you're there all day</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0517">all day I know</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0558">and when the weather's nice don't get me wrong it's <unclear>fab</unclear></u>
<u n="1318" who="S0517">it's nice</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0558">you take a picnic and like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0517">but oh <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1321" who="S0558">you know we'll all sit there and we have a laugh and you know it there's some really nice people er that are part of athletics so the day is great</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0558">it's good fun</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0517">well yeah</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0558">but when</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0517">it's raining</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0558">it's raining and cold</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0558">and</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0517">miserable</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0558">it's completely the opposite</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0517">but it was just so I'd sent I sent erm an email to Mr <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the PE department and I just</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0558">don't ever send us there again</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0517">no I just because he'd wished him luck and he was the only one from</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1336" who="S0517">from the school that had <unclear>gotten chosen I mean the the</unclear> <anon type="place"/> were competing people had driven up from <anon type="place"/> I mean <unclear>it</unclear> was the inter county ones there was they'd come from all over but I thought god why would you come all that way if all takes was like thirteen minutes to run it?</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0517">but anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1339" who="S0558">but yeah</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0517">that's me I'm not a sports person I haven't got the mentality</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0517">but I sent him a I just sent him an email saying look er erm we did take him it wasn't it wasn't our finest moment it and erm I said it turns out he wasn't properly kitted out so our apologies he didn't have the right things <vocal desc="laugh"/> on his feet erm I said all he really wanted was a school tie a <anon type="place"/> cos you know I told you about</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0558">the county tie</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0517">the county tie</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0517"><unclear>so</unclear> but apparently you can't get that for for cross-country and erm Mr <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came back and said you know the standard was really high well done to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it was fantastic he said and I'll I'll enquire about the tie cos he really deserves one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1347" who="S0558">oh bless</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0517">but we haven't heard any more but you know cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll take PE as erm a GCSE in year ten but they've completely cut the list of all the sports and you know if you get you know if you if you do anything at county level</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0517">it's an automatic top marks twenty-five points for</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0517">that particular thing? they've taken cross <trunc>cant</trunc> country off the list</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0558">oh so there's no point</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0517">so there's absolutely no point</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0517">and and this year having done it for the county this year doesn't count cos he's not in his GCSE years</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0517">so he didn't get a tie gets no points from it it was the <trunc>mo</trunc> the photo we've got</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1360" who="S0517">he was black</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1362" who="S0517">he was head to foot black we had nothing with us to even clean him up he got back in the car it took me three attempts to get my car seat cleaned <unclear>up</unclear></u>
<u n="1363" who="S0558"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1364" who="S0517">er the mud had caked into the leather</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0558">oh my goodness yes if <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="1366" who="S0517">I was gutted</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0558">if you do do any more in the event</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1369" who="S0558">I've always take something to put on your seat because</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said I bet people were laughing at you you must've stuck out like a novice at a <trunc>b</trunc> you know there was people there that were so geared up for it</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0517">in their waterproof trousers and their</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0558">wellies and</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1375" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1376" who="S0517">and I was so not geared up for it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said I bet you just looked ridiculous like a</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1378" who="S0517">there's a one that's never done this <unclear/> I'm embarrassed to say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I had my cream jeans on</u>
<u n="1379" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1380" who="S0517">I had my sheepskin boots up to my knees</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1382" who="S0517">and I had my coat down to but that bit between the top of my boots and my <unclear>bum were covered in mud</unclear></u>
<u n="1383" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1384" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1385" who="S0558">and sheepskin boots as well</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0517">I know</u>
<u n="1387" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1388" who="S0558"><unclear/> wellingtons let alone sheepskin <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1389" who="S0517">the the sheepskin boots cleaned up really nicely</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0517">the jeans had to go</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0558">goodness me</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0517">through the wash twice oh it was a disaster <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just couldn't <trunc>belie</trunc></u>
<u n="1394" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1395" who="S0517">he said he'd gone off to play tennis in the bubble at <anon type="place"/> in the nice warm bubble</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0558">oh dear</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0517">I said yeah it's alright for you I said me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1398" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1399" who="S0517">have been through the mill I said and I didn't even run <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I said</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0558">I want to be waited on hand and foot for the rest of the evening</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0517"><unclear/> <trunc>athleti</trunc> er cross-country is not for us <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as a family <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1402" who="S0558">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> no it's not for us draw a line</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0517">we're gonna stick with tennis</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0558">draw a line</u>
<u n="1405" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1406" who="S0517">much more civilised anyway what was happening at the in the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1407" who="S0558"><unclear>at school</unclear> I've got to say who's the new arrival?</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0517">oh my <unclear/></u>
<u n="1409" who="S0558"><unclear>do likey</unclear></u>
<u n="1410" who="S0517">isn't he lovely? I only got him on erm</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0558">he's lovely</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0517">Friday when I was in the garden centre with mum at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1413" who="S0558"><unclear>I likey</unclear></u>
<u n="1414" who="S0517">he's cute isn't he?</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0558">what's his name?</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0517">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wanted to call him Fred I said you can't call a penguin Fred it's got to start with a P but so he hasn't got a name yet he is lovely he's and he was and it was Black Friday so there was twenty-five percent off him</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0558">very lovely I do like him</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0517">and I got a new erm plaque for the kitchen</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0558">oh yes I did see it but I didn't read it cos I haven't got my glasses on</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1421" who="S0558">the one to the right of the sink?</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0517">yes er it's it's only a temporary one cos it's refers to Christmas it says erm I'm dreaming of a white Christmas but when the white is all gone I'll drink the red</u>
<u n="1423" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1424" who="S0517">I thought that's very apt <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1425" who="S0558">I like I'd leave it up all year round</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0517">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1427" who="S0558">just put something over the word Christmas</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1429" who="S0558">I'm dreaming of a</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1431" who="S0558">a white week</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0517">a white spring</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1434" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1435" who="S0558">I would yeah I would just laminate</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0517"><unclear/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1437" who="S0558">you'd laminate one for the spring one for the autumn one</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0517">one for the <trunc>s</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> one for the summer <unclear/></u>
<u n="1439" who="S0558">you've got your <unclear/> and just just laminate it</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0558">in nice fancy writing</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1443" who="S0558">and just Blu-Tack it over the word Christmas when appropriate</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0517">mm that's a good idea <event desc="sound of phone"/> oh who's that? <unclear/></u>
<u n="1445" who="S0558">right reminder</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0517">is this from the school?</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0558">this is from school</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0517">so is that what my message will be as well?</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0558">it will be</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0558">reminder cashless catering opt-in forms</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0558">due in by Wednesday <trunc>tha</trunc> what do you think of that?</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0517">well</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0558">I don't know if I want my children's thumb fingerprint <unclear/></u>
<u n="1456" who="S0517"><trunc>f</trunc>fingerprinted</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0558">do you know? do you know? do you know?</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>what</unclear>? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1459" who="S0558">I reckon you go to Easygym yeah?</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0558">and when you go in what do you do? you put your thumbprint on</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0517">oh yes <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said that</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0558">schools you know</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0558">you could picture this is the requirement</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0517">and later in life when they're in trouble they'll be able to</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0558">this is the government</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0517">I said that to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1469" who="S0558">absolutely</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0517">I said I said do we do we think our children are erm you know if they get fingerprinted now when they're at school when they do something naughty later in life they'll be able to <vocal desc="laugh"/> find out <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0558">well it can also eliminate them remember but I do think this is the government encouraging this system</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0558">by ways of because eventually cos you know they were talking about ID cards and a lot of people are er oppose it?</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0558">well <trunc>thi</trunc>this is the same casual way</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0517">it's the same thing isn't it? I know</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0558">isn't it?</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0517">I know</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0558">eventually everybody that goes through school they'll have</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0517">oh yes yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0558">I tell you my <unclear>witch</unclear></u>
<u n="1482" who="S0517">er <trunc>d</trunc> well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s had erm</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0558">things are working again</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0517">the cash <trunc>th</trunc>the er the <trunc>s</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got some sort of fingerprint system for one of the holiday parks I forget what it's for but they've had a few people complaining</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0517">about not er er</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1488" who="S0517">not even about the fingerprints just about stupid things like well not stupid but cross-contamination you know if somebody's got a a cold and they put their finger on and then the next person puts their finger on or somebody's allergic to</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0558">I can understand that</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0517">or if somebody well yes somebody's allergic to nuts and the person that's just swiped through but I mean you touch everything all the time don't you?</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0558">well you touch everything it's no different to touching a machine</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0558">in the gym or wherever is it? or er</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0517">or the handrail as you're going up the stairs <unclear/></u>
<u n="1495" who="S0558">anything yeah so</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0517"><unclear/> over the top but erm</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0558">it is a bit over the top but at Easygym I have noticed that when you register</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0558">a picture of you comes up and your details I don't know whether I like that</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0517">well yes but it's the same when you go to Virgin and when it was a <unclear/> as soon as you swipe your card through</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0558">but that's only for the <unclear>customer</unclear></u>
<u n="1502" who="S0517">your picture's for them to see isn't it?</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0558">for the staff to see</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0517">oh <unclear>well</unclear> it comes up?</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0558">yeah this is like as you walk up the stairs you could look at the screen and I could see</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0558">we've just booked in if I'd got my glasses on</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0517">oh what sort of details?</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0558">date of birth and everything</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0517">oh really? oh no I wouldn't be happy with that</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0558">no so when they register I'm gonna I'm gonna take my glasses next time I go and I'm gonna look and if there's information on there I don't like like address and date of birth I'm gonna ask for it to be <trunc>m</trunc> removed for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I don't want it because it's there</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1513" who="S0558">until the next person books in</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0517">oh really?</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0558"><unclear>well</unclear> I don't like that</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0517">that's not a very good system</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0558">er particularly when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had stuff taken out of his locker</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0517">yeah no <unclear/></u>
<u n="1519" who="S0558">so there are</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0517">you should have a word with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about that <unclear/></u>
<u n="1521" who="S0558">yes I'm gonna have a word <trunc>b</trunc>before he logs me on</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0517">but all of the security and the implications aside it's a bit of a pain for us because if you remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mother gives us bags and bags of cash for the dinner money for the boys she goes to the bank and gets pound coins</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0558">oh does she?</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0517"><unclear/> ten <trunc>pou</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gets ten pounds a week <unclear>cos he's in er</unclear> whatever year he's in and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear>is on</unclear> seven pounds a week</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0558"><unclear>er</unclear> for their lunch?</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0517"><unclear>and she</unclear> for their lunches every week and she gives it er to us in bags of cash now I just hand it over because she's adamant he's to get ten pounds a week and then he's got some money for dinners if he needs it she's adamant so I hand it but he doesn't always spend it on school dinner money</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0558">so he gets like forty pound a month from his?</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0517">from his granny for for his lunch</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0558">she's so lovely isn't she?</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0517">she is she is when you've got eight grandchildren it's a lot</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0558">is she out of hospital now? is everything alright?</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0517">yes she came out on erm</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0558">oh good good</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0517">Friday yes so but but from our point of view I'm not sure how that's gonna work unless we just give her their bank details and say well keep giving it to them and then they can have their cards registered cos they've got little current accounts</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0517"><unclear>with</unclear> just you know that they put their paper round money into and stuff</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0517">and then because if I if it's coming off my <trunc>car</trunc> I don't know how it's gonna work because they get their dinner money from granny in pound coins but they don't always spend it on</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0558">dinner money</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0517">like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> takes sandwiches</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0558">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to me he thinks he might <trunc>s</trunc> no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to me she thinks she might start <trunc>ea</trunc> taking sandwiches again</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0517">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> takes sandwiches but sometimes he'll have a sausage roll or a few potato wedges or or if he's stopping for something after school and it's gonna be longer</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0517">he might buy himself something at break and have his sandwiches and then he won't be so starving <unclear/></u>
<u n="1545" who="S0558">like today</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0517">on a Monday with his referee course but so it's a <trunc>p</trunc>it's it's a pain for us the cashless system we'll just have to work out how to do it with erm the money she gives them</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0558">yeah well if they want the forms back by Wednesday I'd better sit and read it properly I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s glanced at it</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0517">all the all the form was cos I sent it back with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and you can do one for both of them you basically just put their name on the form and <trunc>s</trunc>and and sign it to say you agree</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0558">cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to me cos I said oh I don't know if I like that idea she said well if you if you're against it if you write in and then if enough parents write in to say they're against it they won't be able to do it</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0558"><unclear>mm it's a</unclear> mm</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0558">good point</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0517">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did have a <unclear>little moan</unclear> and then we sort of we signed it and sent it back</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0558">well I still haven't got round and I was going to do it this morning and I haven't I still think it is wrong that we should be paying for the boys to go to and from school</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0517">oh I know</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0558">because it's compulsory education</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0517">I know education I know but who are you gonna write to? the council? the the the <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1559" who="S0558">well initially I'd phone the lady up</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0517">the the in the transport department</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0558">our contact</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1563" who="S0558">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1564" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1566" who="S0517">yeah you can yeah</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1568" who="S0517">erm</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0558">erm and say I know we're a couple of months in and it's just you know what it's like you always think you're gonna do it the next day</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0558">but I just think it's wrong that they should have to pay</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0517"><unclear>that they have to</unclear></u>
<u n="1573" who="S0558">because it is compulsory I can understand if they choose to stop on</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0517">to stop on in the sixth form <unclear/></u>
<u n="1575" who="S0558">then that's different</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0558">but it's compulsory education and down the road she gets her money back she</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0517">who does?</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> down the road</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0517">oh does she?</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0558">claims gets the money back for her boys going to college</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0517">how?</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0558">well</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0517">is that just because they're a low income family?</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0558">well I don't know are they? he's on a fairly good pension I believe so I don't know if they are</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0517">did they used to get free dinners? no?</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0558">not that I'm aware of</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0517"><unclear/> that's usually the <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1589" who="S0558">yeah <unclear/> not that I'm aware of</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0517">have you not asked her how she claimed it back?</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0558">no I need to ask her</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0517">you do really</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0558">because I remember hearing her her phone rang and sometimes I just work the walk the length of the church if we come out the same time</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0558">and erm I heard her say but yeah it's a lot of money isn't it? transport there and back every day blah blah blah blah</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0517">where do they get the bus to? where's the college <unclear>bus come in</unclear>?</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0558">well I think they get the bus to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1598" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0558">or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> drops em</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0558">and then they get picked up by the college bus from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1602" who="S0517">oh okay okay</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0558">but to and from <anon type="place"/> every day she's having to pay</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0517">well it's one pound twenty same as we pay cos it's the standard</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0558">yeah but I think she's claiming it back she gets it reimbursed</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0517">well you do need to find out how then</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0558">I do</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0517"><unclear/> fifty quid a month isn't it?</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0558">it's a lot of money</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0517">fifty quid a month</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0558">I know</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0517">I give the money to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in advance so he's got it for the week and then half the time he's not on the bus</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0558">I <trunc>gi</trunc>I give <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the money er</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0517">or he uses <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s bus pass cos</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> isn't on the bus</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0558">yeah every weekend I give <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> ten pound coins and</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0517">coins and me and ten twenty Ps</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0517">and then I don't get it back</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0558">and it goes in his pocket</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0517">when he <vocal desc="laugh"/> doesn't use it</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0558">no neither do I</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0517">and I know I know <trunc>h</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will give him his bus pass if he's not on the bus home and then occasionally</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll stop for something after school badminton or whatever and I'll pick him up</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0517">and I'll say that's one pound twenty please</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1630" who="S0517">and he'll say yeah mum and that's that <vocal desc="laugh"/> I hand it over and that's the last I see of it but yes</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0558">oh but erm talking about attitudes and things like that erm was telling me</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1633" who="S0558">that erm apparently some of the things that erm <unclear>he says</unclear> to his mum is dreadful</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0517">all the names get blanked out <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're fine</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0517">the whole lot</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0558">erm yeah</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0517">really?</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to me if you could hear what he calls his mother</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0517">really?</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0558">and says she said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it is dreadful</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0517">well why is he allowed to get away with it?</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0558">I don't know</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0517">that's terrible</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0558">she never told me what but she said it is dreadful <trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> what what he calls her is so disrespectful and rude and insulting</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0517">well I have heard little things I mean I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said one time the comments <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had made about his mum just at parents' evening cos you know those narrow stairs you have to go up and down</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0558">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0517">from from they always have the parents' evening in the same corridors don't they?</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0517">but he'd said about oh well if my mum was on the stairs nobody else'd be able to fit in type of thing which is very mean</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0558">mean?</u>
<u n="1654" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1655" who="S0558">I was gonna say then but true</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0517">true I know but</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0558">but yeah</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0517">I know but if you start hearing your own family <unclear/></u>
<u n="1659" who="S0558">but she's not that big is she?</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0517">no she's not</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0558">erm but er yeah so I don't er</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0517">oh how is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0558">she's not very good I don't see her very often</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0558">the last time I saw her we got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I got copped again in Tesco's drinking coffee erm</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0517">really?</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0558">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> come in they're like</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0517">oh there you are again you two</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you two again</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0558">anyway it was just before <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went back to work so a few weeks ago erm and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <trunc>ca</trunc> was that when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came in?</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0517">who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0558">no that was the <trunc>ti</trunc> oh no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was there then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was home</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0558">so that was <trunc>w</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then that's the time I saw them I've had a coffee with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> once since then before he went back to work he's back at work now and he's Monday to Friday now</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0558">so it's gonna be er <trunc>ha</trunc> it's gonna have to be a beer</u>
<u n="1678" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1679" who="S0558">it's gonna have to be a beer so erm yeah I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos she came to join the queue to get drinks and that and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were there so they'd got their drinks I was just getting my drink and erm I said oh hello <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> how are you? as you do and straight away she goes oh well not very good erm I think it's the same with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1680" who="S0517">but I mean it's how many years now? <unclear>is it</unclear>?</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0558"><vocal desc="sigh"/> where were they going?</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1683" who="S0558">music</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0517"><unclear/> car yeah music <unclear/> well I don't know but he's</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0558">erm who was it who was going away? was it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s year?</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0517">oh to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0558">yeah it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> year wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0517">could've been</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0558">cos they were there with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1690" who="S0517">oh it could've been and that's year five and what's she in now? ten</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0558">year six <anon type="place"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0517"><anon type="place"/> and she's in ten</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1694" who="S0517">so that's four years</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0517">she's been putting up with it</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0558">and she said he's no <trunc>diff</trunc> you know</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0517">well you <trunc>n</trunc> he doesn't leave the house does he?</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0517">and he won't speak to her</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0558">he doesn't wanna get up in the mornings</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0517">that's awful to have to live with</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0558">yeah I said to her I said well she said I'll go into him and say are you gonna get up now <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? and he ignores me I said well I'd stop going in to him then</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0517">and me</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0558">I said I wouldn't</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0517">stop <unclear>cooking</unclear> for him</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0517">after four years of that?</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0517">drive you mad</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0558">but erm she herself isn't very well what is it she said? I think she said she might have polyps or something</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0558">I can't remember now but she herself had just been to the doctors</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0517"><unclear>oh dear</unclear></u>
<u n="1715" who="S0558">so she's not <trunc>ver</trunc> you know she's</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0558"><unclear/> suffering a bit herself bless her</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0517"><vocal desc="misc"/> aw</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0558">but erm I saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1720" who="S0517">oh yes yeah</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0558">and erm I <trunc>d</trunc> I I think there's been some sort of fall out I don't know whether</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0517">between the brothers?</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0558">between the brothers I don't know whether it's</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0517">or the sisters-in-law</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0558">between the brothers <unclear>but</unclear> the sister-in-law's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just said basically I'm not putting up with her any more</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0517">with?</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1728" who="S0517">oh really?</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0558">just not putting up with her any more she said she's terrible you get together and mood swings she ignores people she turns up late she said er you know er she said <trunc>I</trunc>I've just had enough of her she said and I said oh that is such a shame</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0558">because all living so close</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0517">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0558">and then they've got the holiday homes together that is er she said I think she did say there's been no fall out as such</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0517">it's just she's at the end of her tether with it</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0558">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s just had enough they don't help in any way</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0517">oh with <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0558">no they don't help at all oh and what was that? did they all go down for Christmas dinner or something? oh yeah they went down for Christmas dinner I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went down for Christmas dinner</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0558">cos normally <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> always has them</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0517">okay</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0558">cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum is no longer here</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0558">and she said if my mum knew I was leaving them on their own she'd turn in her grave type thing yeah?</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0558">so er I think it must've been they must've asked or I dunno how it came about but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went down there and erm I can't remember what happened but there was a big hoo-ha at the table</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0558">I think</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0517">on Christmas Day?</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0558">yeah on Christmas Day</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0517">oh typical <vocal desc="laugh"/> family do then?</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0558">and I I dunno who I can't she did tell me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but I can't remember and I'm not even gonna try and dig deep and find it</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0558">cos it's just not there but there was a big hoo-ha erm and they don't have anything</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0517">much to do with them</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0558">they didn't even realise how bad <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0517">oh no</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0558">because they have very little contact with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1760" who="S0517"><unclear/> live round the corner</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0558">I know</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0517">well you just don't see him about the village do you? he's just</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0517">I haven't seen him for years</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1766" who="S0517">no oh what a shame</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0558">I know</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0558">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s settled in her job</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0517">oh gosh</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0558">she's down</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0517">is she in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0558"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1774" who="S0517">oh <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0558">yeah working for you know the erm one of the shopping channels I think it's the craft one or something</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0517">oh right yes yeah</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0558">she's erm like an er <trunc>pr</trunc>production type assistant or something but er it's all</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0517">oh so she's enjoying it?</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0558">last time I spoke to well text <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> anyway which was a</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0558">couple of weeks into her job she was thoroughly enjoying it</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0517">oh good</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0558">met some really nice people</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0517">has she got a boyfriend?</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0517">no?</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0558"><unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was taking her down on the weekend</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0558">to her er thing her new little house and boyfriend was supposed to be going down on the Saturday and stopping the weekend</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0558">but it all fell apart</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0517">oh dear</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0558">so on the morning that they were going</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0517">yeah <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1795" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> turned up to get these bits we were giving her and I said oh I half expected <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to be with you you know in high spirits</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0517">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1797" who="S0558">and he went I've just left the house literally shouting at her get out of bed</u>
<u n="1798" who="S0517">oh no</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0558">I said oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she's leaving home today he said I know he said as I was doing it I knew it was wrong he said but</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0517">ah</u>
<u n="1801" who="S0558">the last couple of days he said all she's done in <trunc>lay</trunc> is laying in bed and I said to her this morning you know I said here's me going to get the van coming to get this stuff that you've very <trunc>kin</trunc> you know you know</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0558">you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have very kindly given her she should be here and saying thank you and I said don't worry about that she's already thanked us when she come round to look at it</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0558">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was here at the same time then so she thanked <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well erm I said so don't even give that a second thought but I thought she would be so excited she'd be out of bed he said I know he said and I've just left er the house balling at her</u>
<u n="1806" who="S0517">is this because it's fallen out fallen apart with her boyfriend then?</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0558">well he said part of it he thinks er he said part of it I think is her and the boyfriend have fallen out and I went oh no and he went yeah</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0517">how old is she? twenty-one?</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0558">no no no no erm</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0517">she must be if she's just finished uni</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0558">yeah <trunc>sh</trunc> yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> celebrated her twenty-first this year because was one of the girls sixteen? yeah because they're going away they're going away at Christmas he's booked a holiday for the three girls and</u>
<u n="1812" who="S0517">three girls and him?</u>
<u n="1813" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to go away abroad it's very nice</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0517">oh lovely</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0558">yeah he booked it earlier in the year before he was ill erm so I think he's still going I don't know but he was showing me where they're going and that</u>
<u n="1816" who="S0517"><unclear>right</unclear></u>
<u n="1817" who="S0558">and I said oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that'll be so lovely that er that is real relaxation</u>
<u n="1818" who="S0517">mm mm</u>
<u n="1819" who="S0558">he said well that's what I thought he said I dunno how many more holidays I'm gonna get with em</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0558">you know</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0558">so he thought he's got all his money now everything's settled and everything but erm yeah so he was a bit cross with her</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="1825" who="S0558">and I think he felt awful because it is the day she's leaving home and all the rest of it</u>
<u n="1826" who="S0517">mm yeah I know it's just one of those <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1827" who="S0558">but</u>
<u n="1828" who="S0517">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="1829" who="S0558">we've all done it ain't we?</u>
<u n="1830" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1831" who="S0558">I said to him we've all been there we've got all got cross with them when it's just as they're about to go to bed or just as they're about to leave the house</u>
<u n="1832" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1833" who="S0558">to go and play with their friends</u>
<u n="1834" who="S0517">like me yesterday just as <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1835" who="S0558">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1836" who="S0517">going away for the weekend oh</u>
<u n="1837" who="S0558">I said we've all done it it's part</u>
<u n="1838" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1839" who="S0558">it's part of isn't it?</u>
<u n="1840" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1841" who="S0558">you don't feel guilty about it you know</u>
<u n="1842" who="S0517">but she's enjoying the job now she's down there and settled?</u>
<u n="1843" who="S0558">yeah she's settled</u>
<u n="1844" who="S0517">good</u>
<u n="1845" who="S0558">and met some really lovely people cos it's very brave of her isn't it? really</u>
<u n="1846" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1847" who="S0558">you know</u>
<u n="1848" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1849" who="S0558">completely I mean you did it didn't you? you went to university and</u>
<u n="1850" who="S0517">I did yeah</u>
<u n="1851" who="S0558">but erm sort of going into the working world</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0558">and he said one of the one of the problems <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has and has always had in any new environment she goes into she's very often alienated by other women he said and I think it's because she's tall she's blonde he said but once they once people get through that <unclear/> and</u>
<u n="1854" who="S0517">yeah realise that she's a nice girl</u>
<u n="1855" who="S0558">realise that she's</u>
<u n="1856" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="1857" who="S0558">a nice girl it's absolutely fine but she always has that</u>
<u n="1858" who="S0517">they probably just feel a bit intimidated when they see her don't they? I mean she's</u>
<u n="1859" who="S0558">I said I said well she's tall she's blonde you know they probably feel intimidated by her</u>
<u n="1860" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1861" who="S0558">but then once they've spoke to her so he said always</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1863" who="S0558">she's gonna have these first two or three days to get through</u>
<u n="1864" who="S0517">do the other two girls get that? cos they're all tall blonde and beautiful</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did you see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on stage? in the show <unclear/></u>
<u n="1866" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="1867" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> always gets involved</u>
<u n="1868" who="S0517">oh okay yes yeah</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0558">in the productions I don't know whether she's took it but she's in them anyway</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0517">right yeah</u>
<u n="1871" who="S0558">I don't know whether she's took it erm but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> no she's never got involved erm I don't know but <unclear/> girls</u>
<u n="1872" who="S0517">but you know they are all lovely girls</u>
<u n="1873" who="S0558">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1874" who="S0517">and they're all blonde and they're all tall</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0558">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1876" who="S0517">and they're all slim and they're all beautiful</u>
<u n="1877" who="S0558">er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s lost some weight he's lost about a stone</u>
<u n="1878" who="S0517">has he?</u>
<u n="1879" who="S0558">mm he's lost about a stone that's just</u>
<u n="1880" who="S0517">is that after his?</u>
<u n="1881" who="S0558">through changing his eating habits mm</u>
<u n="1882" who="S0517">after his erm</u>
<u n="1883" who="S0558">after his heart attack</u>
<u n="1884" who="S0517">heart attack oh good for him</u>
<u n="1885" who="S0558">so erm yeah</u>
<u n="1886" who="S0517">mind you he wasn't overweight though was he?</u>
<u n="1887" who="S0558">no he wasn't overweight but <trunc>y</trunc>you can kind of tell</u>
<u n="1888" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1889" who="S0558">he just doesn't look as broad</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1891" who="S0558">and his face looks slimmer</u>
<u n="1892" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0558">but he looks really healthy</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0517">oh good</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0558">so he's obviously doing all the right things</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0517">oh good I'm pleased he's <unclear>eating well</unclear></u>
<u n="1897" who="S0558">I don't think he's really enjoying being in the office all day cos he can't go back to <unclear>firearms</unclear></u>
<u n="1898" who="S0517">he can't go back to it no</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0558">no he's office-bound</u>
<u n="1900" who="S0517">but then he hasn't got long before he can retire</u>
<u n="1901" who="S0558">eighteen months</u>
<u n="1902" who="S0517">eighteen months?</u>
<u n="1903" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1904" who="S0517">is that the same for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1905" who="S0558">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1907" who="S0558">no sorry <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got two years and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got two and a half</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="1909" who="S0558">cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> goes do you know I remember having a conversation with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just shows doesn't it? how things can change long long time ago and we were laughing at school one day about the fact that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> finishes six months before and this was long before any of their marriage problems I'm going back years and we were laughing about it and he said oh yes and I'll be standing on the corner of <anon type="place"/> waving him off to work</u>
<u n="1910" who="S0517">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1911" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1912" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1913" who="S0558">waving him off to work and you know in the sort of like you know he said mind you he said knowing you two he said I'll be surrounded with debt he said and you two will all be like organised and erm I <trunc>s</trunc> very often reflect on that conversation</u>
<u n="1914" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1915" who="S0558">and think the change that's taken place</u>
<u n="1916" who="S0517">oh yeah have they have have they got divorced now? is it?</u>
<u n="1917" who="S0558">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1918" who="S0517">they have?</u>
<u n="1919" who="S0558">it's all official now</u>
<u n="1920" who="S0517">it's all gone through?</u>
<u n="1921" who="S0558">yeah oh yeah it's been a while now</u>
<u n="1922" who="S0517"><unclear/> sorted</u>
<u n="1923" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="1924" who="S0517">gosh</u>
<u n="1925" who="S0558">it's been a while mm</u>
<u n="1926" who="S0517">do the girls still speak to her?</u>
<u n="1927" who="S0558">not really</u>
<u n="1928" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1929" who="S0558">they don't want anything particularly erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1930" who="S0517">the little the youngest?</u>
<u n="1931" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="1932" who="S0517">yeah little sixteen</u>
<u n="1933" who="S0558">even <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't I think when we saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at the show earlier in the year and she came down to speak to us erm she was saying about she was gonna go and do some travelling</u>
<u n="1934" who="S0517">oh right</u>
<u n="1935" who="S0558">and she said it's the first time she's ever not had many conversations I don't text her</u>
<u n="1936" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1937" who="S0558">she doesn't text me so I have <trunc>n</trunc> er unless I bump into her</u>
<u n="1938" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1939" who="S0558">you know in the shop or wherever erm and she said oh and it's the first time she's ever <unclear/> she said oh she said well as the girls don't really you know are are <trunc>bo</trunc> that bothered about seeing me I thought I'd go travelling and do some work abroad</u>
<u n="1940" who="S0517">gosh well you know I mean she brought it on herself but that's awful really isn't it? it's very sad is that you pinging?</u>
<u n="1941" who="S0558">that's me</u>
<u n="1942" who="S0517">look at you on the pulse of whatever's going on in the world <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1943" who="S0558">I tell you no <unclear/></u>
<u n="1944" who="S0517"><unclear/> you can't see without your glasses <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1945" who="S0558">I can't see a thing I'm getting <unclear>worse</unclear> do you know what I have to say now? I said it I said it to somebody</u>
<u n="1946" who="S0517">you need to put those on a <trunc>str</trunc> on a chain round your neck</u>
<u n="1947" who="S0558">I said it to somebody at work I said cos I've started to this is happening to me quite a bit now and I'll say to people <vocal desc="misc"/> oh excuse me what does that say?</u>
<u n="1948" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1949" who="S0558">and then I'll go I can read</u>
<u n="1950" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1951" who="S0558">it's just that I can't see I haven't got my glasses with me cos it's happening</u>
<u n="1952" who="S0517">I can read</u>
<u n="1953" who="S0558">I do</u>
<u n="1954" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1955" who="S0558">I do I said to somebody at work today I said I say oh I can read</u>
<u n="1956" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1957" who="S0558">I can read</u>
<u n="1958" who="S0517">just so you're sure</u>
<u n="1959" who="S0558">I just can't see</u>
<u n="1960" who="S0517">what time is it? oh it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="1961" who="S0558">oh it's erm it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's collecting today so <unclear>can she get to change her place for Brownies</unclear> <unclear/> that is <unclear>really the person not the dog</unclear></u>
<u n="1962" who="S0517">Brownies? <unclear/></u>
<u n="1963" who="S0558">do you know I nearly went to pick <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> up</u>
<u n="1964" who="S0517">and you don't need to?</u>
<u n="1965" who="S0558">yes no no problem</u>
<u n="1966" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1967" who="S0558">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> text me</u>
<u n="1968" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1969" who="S0558"><unclear/> problem <unclear/></u>
<u n="1970" who="S0517">so what is it she's doing? duke of Edinburgh?</u>
<u n="1971" who="S0558">right <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s doing it <unclear/></u>
<u n="1972" who="S0517">duke of Edinburgh</u>
<u n="1973" who="S0558">D of E</u>
<u n="1974" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1975" who="S0558">I better just let <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> know to remind her hadn't I?</u>
<u n="1976" who="S0517">you better had</u>
<u n="1977" who="S0558">cos she's expecting me to pick her up</u>
<u n="1978" who="S0517">have you got a signal <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1979" who="S0558">yes flew straight out</u>
<u n="1980" who="S0517"><unclear>really</unclear>?</u>
<u n="1981" who="S0558">same network but erm remember cos I'd forgotten remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> picking you up tonight what time is it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1982" who="S0517">it's four o'clock <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1983" who="S0558">oh yes so she'll get it do you know I'd forgotten <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was picking em up</u>
<u n="1984" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1985" who="S0558">I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'll pick you up later well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s doing D of E</u>
<u n="1986" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1987" who="S0558">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s doing D of E and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> text me last week because D of E was starting out to be on a Tuesday she text me as D of E has moved to a Monday night would you like to share lifts?</u>
<u n="1988" who="S0517">well why didn't you share on a Tuesday?</u>
<u n="1989" who="S0558">I dunno so er</u>
<u n="1990" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1991" who="S0558">I just didn't question it I just said yes that would be fine <unclear>but</unclear> well I'm not gonna suggest it but if as she has suggested it I'll go with it</u>
<u n="1992" who="S0517">yeah oh</u>
<u n="1993" who="S0558">erm</u>
<u n="1994" who="S0517">mm I haven't I haven't seen <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to speak to in ages</u>
<u n="1995" who="S0558">I saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a couple of weeks ago</u>
<u n="1996" who="S0517">is <trunc>sh</trunc> did you invite her to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1997" who="S0558">yeah I have</u>
<u n="1998" who="S0517">is she coming?</u>
<u n="1999" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="2000" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="2001" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2002" who="S0558">I did <trunc>be</trunc> er because I saw her a couple of weeks ago</u>
<u n="2003" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="2004" who="S0558">erm because she sent a text to say she's got a job</u>
<u n="2005" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="2006" who="S0558">she's got a job she sent a text miracles do happen</u>
<u n="2007" who="S0517"><trunc>y</trunc> ah I think you told me that</u>
<u n="2008" who="S0558">do you remember me telling you that?</u>
<u n="2009" who="S0517">I think you told me that <unclear>when</unclear> we were going <unclear/></u>
<u n="2010" who="S0558">that's right and she said about a coffee before she starts</u>
<u n="2011" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="2012" who="S0558">well lunch before she starts</u>
<u n="2013" who="S0517">was it in the was it in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="2014" who="S0558">that's right so I text back</u>
<u n="2015" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2016" who="S0558">erm that I was working but I would pop down and join em</u>
<u n="2017" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="2018" who="S0558">for a quick coffee well I didn't know because I don't know why because she's never been before but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had been invited</u>
<u n="2019" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="2020" who="S0558">so of course <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was talking about <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2021" who="S0517">oh I see I see I see</u>
<u n="2022" who="S0558">and I said oh would you like to come?</u>
<u n="2023" who="S0517">has she been?</u>
<u n="2024" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="2025" who="S0517">has <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> been?</u>
<u n="2026" who="S0558">she's been once I think</u>
<u n="2027" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="2028" who="S0558">a long long time ago so yes she's going to come</u>
<u n="2029" who="S0517">oh okay so are you just letting people sort their own lifts out?</u>
<u n="2030" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="2031" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="2032" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="2033" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="2034" who="S0558">cos I can't erm</u>
<u n="2035" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="2036" who="S0558">I'm just gonna text everybody the</u>
<u n="2037" who="S0517">the postcode</u>
<u n="2038" who="S0558">postcode and</u>
<u n="2039" who="S0517"><unclear>well I imagine</unclear> I'll take <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then I'll be full</u>
<u n="2040" who="S0558">yeah well I'll have <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and possibly <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'ll go with whoever it is she's taking on her own</u>
<u n="2041" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="2042" who="S0558">just thinking from the village who else is there? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'ll probably go in one</u>
<u n="2043" who="S0517"><unclear>oh well if she's got</unclear> <unclear/> yeah they'll all go together</u>
<u n="2044" who="S0558">erm</u>
<u n="2045" who="S0517">do you see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the other <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? <unclear/></u>
<u n="2046" who="S0558">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> might be coming</u>
<u n="2047" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="2048" who="S0558">with three others</u>
<u n="2049" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="2050" who="S0558">so I don't know who they are er but it will depend on <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> whether he's about</u>
<u n="2051" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="2052" who="S0558">and I said well if all else fails bring the girls with you if they want if it means</u>
<u n="2053" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2054" who="S0558">if you really want to come and you can't purely because of that just bring the girls with you</u>
<u n="2055" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="2056" who="S0558">it's not like they're gonna run round and</u>
<u n="2057" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="2058" who="S0558"><trunc>ri</trunc> have a riot</u>
<u n="2059" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2060" who="S0558">er <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm</u>
<u n="2061" who="S0517">gosh did she say did she give a maximum number? or not?</u>
<u n="2062" who="S0558">well she'd said the JCB was fifty ladies</u>
<u n="2063" who="S0517">she did and she said that was too many didn't she?</u>
<u n="2064" who="S0558">too many</u>
<u n="2065" who="S0517"><unclear>we</unclear> just don't know how they</u>
<u n="2066" who="S0558">well we've got twenty-two</u>
<u n="2067" who="S0517">and <unclear>like</unclear></u>
<u n="2068" who="S0558">possibly twenty-six if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> comes</u>
<u n="2069" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="2070" who="S0558">erm and then if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> brings another one so <trunc>s</trunc>say if we end up with twenty-seven you can guarantee seven people'll drop out</u>
<u n="2071" who="S0517">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2072" who="S0558">so that'll be twenty</u>
<u n="2073" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="2074" who="S0558">which is just nice</u>
<u n="2075" who="S0517">which is a nice number yeah</u>
<u n="2076" who="S0558">so</u>
<u n="2077" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="2078" who="S0558">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hasn't got back to me yet you know my Irish friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="2079" who="S0517">oh yes yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2080" who="S0558">I've text <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos er over the years again I've told her about it</u>
<u n="2081" who="S0517">about it and not gone</u>
<u n="2082" who="S0558">when we meet up for coffee she hasn't got back to me yet</u>
<u n="2083" who="S0517">I don't need to buy anything though <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> so twenty people'll be good <unclear/></u>
<u n="2084" who="S0558"><unclear/> the ladies</u>
<u n="2085" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2086" who="S0558">the ladies' night out</u>
<u n="2087" who="S0517">oh it'll be nice</u>
<u n="2088" who="S0558">erm no I don't really need to buy anything but er I will buy something I need to buy actually secret Santa for dinner ladies</u>
<u n="2089" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="2090" who="S0558">so I'm gonna buy some of them gloves</u>
<u n="2091" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="2092" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2093" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="2094" who="S0558">I'm gonna buy a pair of them erm</u>
<u n="2095" who="S0517">that's a good idea</u>
<u n="2096" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="2097" who="S0517">actually <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had to do a secret Santa last year but he hasn't mentioned it this year <unclear/></u>
<u n="2098" who="S0558">oh he could get that from there</u>
<u n="2099" who="S0517">yeah well it depends if it's a man or a woman <unclear/> it's usually just</u>
<u n="2100" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2101" who="S0517"><unclear/> he he got told who he was buying for last year</u>
<u n="2102" who="S0558">is this <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="2103" who="S0517">and then I went out and bought obviously</u>
<u n="2104" who="S0558">is he enjoying his job? <unclear/></u>
<u n="2105" who="S0517">er yes he is he is erm</u>
<u n="2106" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="2107" who="S0517">it's just all the driving really</u>
<u n="2108" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="2109" who="S0517">that he doesn't like and he doesn't like staying away from home much but he his enjoying the job</u>
<u n="2110" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="2111" who="S0517">yeah I don't know how long he'll stay he was talking about in the spring looking for something else just for those reasons the driving and stopping away from home but one of the other senior management team has left recently and the chairman not the chairman the chief exec whoever <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s boss is the chief exec</u>
<u n="2112" who="S0558">the man who was employed the same time as <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="2113" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="2114" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="2115" who="S0517">the Scottish man yes er has been <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said you know as soon as <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the the HR director had left he was sort of sounding <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> out cos er apparently they're putting together some plan to float the business and and the chief exec's basing his all of his thing on having a stable senior management team</u>
<u n="2116" who="S0558">oh right</u>
<u n="2117" who="S0517">so he doesn't want them to be leaving so he was trying to sound <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> out was he going to get a job so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said obviously I didn't say it I <trunc>w</trunc>I was maybe thinking about it because that would just be madness at this stage but he was also tempting him with you know once we've had the once it's floated you know there will be an opportunity for you to be given some equity in the business and you know how they dangle these carrots don't they?</u>
<u n="2118" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="2119" who="S0517">to try and keep you there so</u>
<u n="2120" who="S0558">but do they want an investment in return?</u>
<u n="2121" who="S0517">I don't think they did I think it was</u>
<u n="2122" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="2123" who="S0517">just gonna be a you know an issue of shares</u>
<u n="2124" who="S0558">right</u>
<u n="2125" who="S0517">for him</u>
<u n="2126" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="2127" who="S0517">er I I don't really know I mean it's not happened yet but</u>
<u n="2128" who="S0558">so are the family thinking of selling then? when you say floating are the family thinking of selling?</u>
<u n="2129" who="S0517">no I don't think they're selling I think it's just a way of of raising some extra money to do some more erm renovation works I think</u>
<u n="2130" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="2131" who="S0517">I don't really know I don't think they're they're ever gonna sell it as such just float it on the</u>
<u n="2132" who="S0558">right</u>
<u n="2133" who="S0517">stock exchange but they would still have the majority of the shareholdings I think I don't know so it was one of those whereby you could <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said he could see that he was just trying to sound him out</u>
<u n="2134" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="2135" who="S0517">and also dangle a carrot because he's basing all of his strategy on having a stable senior management team</u>
<u n="2136" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="2137" who="S0517">and of course <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s his right-hand man really as the</u>
<u n="2138" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="2139" who="S0517">operations manager so anyway we'll see</u>
<u n="2140" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="2141" who="S0517">but it is it's just the driving he's done a lot done about a hundred thousand miles on that car and it's not three years old yet</u>
<u n="2142" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="2143" who="S0517">it's a very good car though</u>
<u n="2144" who="S0558">I was gonna say it's a good car though it'll</u>
<u n="2145" who="S0517">very reliable</u>
<u n="2146" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="2147" who="S0517">it's been I mean it was serviced again on Friday and it didn't need anything doing to it</u>
<u n="2148" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="2149" who="S0517">I mean it has its oil changed and it it has new tyres and that's been about it</u>
<u n="2150" who="S0558">and if you think the majority majority is motorway anyway which is</u>
<u n="2151" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="2152" who="S0558">good for the car</u>
<u n="2153" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="2154" who="S0558">isn't it?</u>
<u n="2155" who="S0517">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="2156" who="S0558">you know like it might be clocking the mileage up but</u>
<u n="2157" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="2158" who="S0558">in the way of engine damage or that</u>
<u n="2159" who="S0517">yes yeah <unclear>yeah true</unclear></u>
<u n="2160" who="S0558">you're not gear changing every couple of minutes are you?</u>
<u n="2161" who="S0517">no not unless he's stuck in traffic or when he gets to <anon type="place"/> he gets stuck behind you know tractors</u>
<u n="2162" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="2163" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2164" who="S0558">stuck behind a tractor</u>
<u n="2165" who="S0517">yeah but no he is still enjoying it so that's good that's good</u>
<u n="2166" who="S0558">so you know what you should do for the week as <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s not here? you should turn that picture round because he's in here watching you <unclear>look</unclear></u>
<u n="2167" who="S0517">I know he is look at him</u>
<u n="2168" who="S0558">he's there with his cheeky smile</u>
<u n="2169" who="S0517">with that lovely smile <unclear>well</unclear> that's how I like him look he looks he looks <trunc>an</trunc>angelic there doesn't he?</u>
<u n="2170" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2171" who="S0517">and nice I'm happy to look at him when he's like that</u>
<u n="2172" who="S0558">I can't imagine him being any different</u>
<u n="2173" who="S0517">really? yes</u>
<u n="2174" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2175" who="S0517">you wanna live with him <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2176" who="S0558">does he have any like er like er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s never had any like erm strops or anything er he's never he's never like stormed off or banged a door or I can imagine <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> could</u>
<u n="2177" who="S0517"><trunc>w</trunc>would yeah <trunc>n</trunc> er no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not really</u>
<u n="2178" who="S0558">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="2179" who="S0517">he just gets he just he just irritates other people like if he's <trunc>i</trunc>if he's er got a bit of one on him he just niggles everyone and winds his brother up</u>
<u n="2180" who="S0558">oh does he? yeah</u>
<u n="2181" who="S0517">that's what he does but he doesn't necessarily strop or slam doors or</u>
<u n="2182" who="S0558">no no I haven't had any of that</u>
<u n="2183" who="S0517">but they do have they do have fights</u>
<u n="2184" who="S0558">do they?</u>
<u n="2185" who="S0517">sometimes that get can get a bit physical</u>
<u n="2186" who="S0558">really?</u>
<u n="2187" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes</u>
<u n="2188" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="2189" who="S0517"><unclear/> god I'm too short now</u>
<u n="2190" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="2191" who="S0517">to be dragging them apart <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2192" who="S0558">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2193" who="S0517">they're both a lot bigger than me</u>
<u n="2194" who="S0558">I'd shut the door and leave em to it if I was you</u>
<u n="2195" who="S0517">I do sometimes it's just I don't like to listen to it you know? <unclear/></u>
<u n="2196" who="S0558">on the understanding if there's any damage then they pay for it</u>
<u n="2197" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="2198" who="S0558">if they can't control their</u>
<u n="2199" who="S0517">and they clean up their own blood no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2200" who="S0558">tempers</u>
<u n="2201" who="S0517">there's been no blood</u>
<u n="2202" who="S0558">not yet</u>
<u n="2203" who="S0517">but er it's not often but you know sometimes I do think god</u>
<u n="2204" who="S0558"><unclear/> dinged again <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="2205" who="S0517">I know you you've got like your finger on the pulse <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="2206" who="S0558">I tell you popular me</u>
<u n="2207" who="S0517">you are</u>
<u n="2208" who="S0558">oh it's I think it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> from work oh BBC News</u>
<u n="2209" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2210" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="2211" who="S0517">are you enjoying your new phone?</u>
<u n="2212" who="S0558">don't know who it is I do I like it I don't use half the things that are on there still only text receive why is it saying <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="2213" who="S0517">did you get your emails sorted out on there?</u>
<u n="2214" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="2215" who="S0517">oh didn't you?</u>
<u n="2216" who="S0558">no for some ridiculous it's asking me to say hi to Google hi Google bye</u>
<u n="2217" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2218" who="S0558">hello bye <event desc="sound of phone"/> that's probably cos we pressed it earlier I bet has that been open all that time then?</u>
<u n="2219" who="S0517">I don't know</u>
<u n="2220" who="S0558">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="2221" who="S0517">so why couldn't you get your emails?</u>
<u n="2222" who="S0558">right what's happening is my emails will come in</u>
<u n="2223" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="2224" who="S0558">I'll read it and I'll delete it and then I've got this on refresh every hour</u>
<u n="2225" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="2226" who="S0558">so it's almost like when it picks up a signal or the hour or whatever the emails come back in so</u>
<u n="2227" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2228" who="S0558">it's not allowing me to delete</u>
<u n="2229" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="2230" who="S0558">from this and also it's not sending cos I do you <trunc>g</trunc> <trunc>g</trunc> oh no it can't track now I <unclear/></u>
<u n="2231" who="S0517">I didn't get the one that I didn't get the one you'd sent I saw it</u>
<u n="2232" who="S0558">it just said failed in fact I think I've since deleted it let's have a look I think I have sent</u>
<u n="2233" who="S0517">who's your who's your email provider? <trunc>O</trunc> is it <trunc>Oran</trunc>? no who are you with? Talktalk? who was you with? BT?</u>
<u n="2234" who="S0558">Tesco</u>
<u n="2235" who="S0517">is that what your email address is?</u>
<u n="2236" who="S0558">no my email address is BT sorry BT for email</u>
<u n="2237" who="S0517">your <trunc>e</trunc>your <trunc>e</trunc>your emails are with BT?</u>
<u n="2238" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="2239" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="2240" who="S0558">so I don't know why it won't let me delete</u>
<u n="2241" who="S0517">who have you asked to look at it?</u>
<u n="2242" who="S0558">I asked the IT man at work</u>
<u n="2243" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="2244" who="S0558">and even he was laughing and saying I can't understand it</u>
<u n="2245" who="S0517">have you been back into the shop?</u>
<u n="2246" who="S0558">no that's what I need to do I think</u>
<u n="2247" who="S0517">go back into the phone shop and let them get them to set it up for you</u>
<u n="2248" who="S0558">I need <trunc>tha</trunc> er that's what I said to I mean er I I'm just flicking through <trunc>th</trunc> all these in white I've deleted all them once</u>
<u n="2249" who="S0517">how weird</u>
<u n="2250" who="S0558">they're all there yesterday I've deleted em all see so if I</u>
<u n="2251" who="S0517">that's weird isn't it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="2252" who="S0558">I can either go like oh I can either go like that</u>
<u n="2253" who="S0517">yeah and deleted yeah says deleted</u>
<u n="2254" who="S0558">oh god <unclear>okay</unclear> right so let's er Brantano right? so I can either do that</u>
<u n="2255" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="2256" who="S0558">delete</u>
<u n="2257" who="S0517">delete</u>
<u n="2258" who="S0558">delete</u>
<u n="2259" who="S0517">or <trunc>d</trunc> yeah same as this on here</u>
<u n="2260" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2261" who="S0517">is there a erm?</u>
<u n="2262" who="S0558">but it'll come back</u>
<u n="2263" who="S0517">is there an app? a BT email app you could download and do it through that?</u>
<u n="2264" who="S0558">I don't know</u>
<u n="2265" who="S0517">because on that phone there I've got the I've got my emails exactly the same as you but I don't use mine <trunc>becau</trunc> I've got a Hotmail account and I downloaded the app look app and it all goes through there in fact <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> shall I turn this off? and I'll show you yeah?</u>
<u n="2266" who="S0558">no have we?</u>
<u n="2267" who="S0517">well yeah we can we'll turn that off now</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
