<text id="SN8K">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:21:17</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0255 S0317 S0318</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON's home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Skiing, kitchens, planning permission, children (adult), university, drinking alcohol, work, LinkedIn, psychometric testing, parties/celebrations, weather, Facebook, telephones, spam telephone calls, punctuation rules, CV’s, email providers, computers, Internet, conspiracy theories, British Armed Forces, Air Cadets, airplanes, helicopters, flying, wars, cars, modified cars, hypochondriac, rugby, sewing, hobbies, Rainbows (Girl Guiding), Christmas, moving house.</topics>
		<activity>Chatting with close friends over a bottle of wine</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, requesting, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0255">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Boston, Lincs</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Boston/London/Peterborough</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>account manager - sales</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0317">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Peterborough</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Anglia</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Peterborough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>48</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Incomes team leader</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0318">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South East (London)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Peterborough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>32</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Senior manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0317">I saw your pictures that you put on the other day on the er the the snow and everything I didn't know</u>
<u n="2" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0317">cos I had to look twice cos I didn't know if you were out there and I thought</u>
<u n="4" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="5" who="S0317">I'm sure she's not cos we've just spoken to her <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0255">yeah no no I wasn't out there I just erm somebody put it on Facebook saying it was snowing in <unclear>Alduex</unclear> and I was like er so I just thought I'd share the share the pictures so everybody that's a a skier goes oh it's snowing it's snowing I mean it's not obviously <trunc>e</trunc>enough to ski on at the minute but starting now that's fairly good</u>
<u n="7" who="S0317">ah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0255">and they're saying it's gonna be a really cold winter here so hopefully it will be over there as well</u>
<u n="9" who="S0317">oh</u>
<u n="10" who="S0255">and then we'll get out there mind you I won't be able to ski I don't think for a while <unclear/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0317" trans="overlap">well I was gonna say you're not gonna be able to are you?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0255">no no that's the thing cos they put it back three weeks that adds three weeks on the recovery so when I go out it'll it'll be six weeks after the op so</u>
<u n="13" who="S0317">right</u>
<u n="14" who="S0255">I might be able to potter that's my plan if I can just to see</u>
<u n="15" who="S0317" trans="overlap">just be careful</u>
<u n="16" who="S0255">yeah oh yeah I'm I'm not gonna go mad</u>
<u n="17" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0255">but</u>
<u n="19" who="S0317">is it the après ski? isn't that what they call it? the bar? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I'll probably do a lot of that mm yeah because the kids are coming out erm at Christmas with us erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gonna be out there I'm then going out eighteenth of January with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> no eighteenth of December with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0317">uhu</u>
<u n="22" who="S0255">and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s coming out on the twenty-third I think she's out for five days then she's going back and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s going back with her and we're staying out for New Year</u>
<u n="23" who="S0317">oh lovely</u>
<u n="24" who="S0255">so yeah mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0317">be nice</u>
<u n="26" who="S0255">mm yeah I mean even if I don't get to ski I'm quite happy tucked up with a book <pause dur="short"/> and just reading a beer</u>
<u n="27" who="S0317">ah it'll be lovely</u>
<u n="28" who="S0255">yeah it'll be fine</u>
<u n="29" who="S0318">this is in the place you bought isn't it?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0255">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went out in the summer and put a new kitchen in</u>
<u n="31" who="S0317">ah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0255">so that's good cos there was only a couple of cupboards and this sort of big surface thing to work on and that was about it so we went into Wicks and said we've got a very little space for a very little kitchen you know as in there's only a couple of and we we worked it all out we managed to get quite a lot in and did tall erm cupboards the top one's going right to ceiling</u>
<u n="33" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0255">but so just going round the corner</u>
<u n="35" who="S0318">mm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0255">so there's gonna be a lot more space so that's good it'll be good</u>
<u n="37" who="S0318">that's the problem with ours isn't it?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0318">we haven't got enough space we need</u>
<u n="40" who="S0317" trans="overlap">more cupboards</u>
<u n="41" who="S0318">we were persuaded against having additional working <trunc>sp</trunc>space weren't we?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0317">cupboards</u>
<u n="43" who="S0318" trans="overlap">by the designer</u>
<u n="44" who="S0317">cupboards</u>
<u n="45" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0318" trans="overlap">well <trunc>c</trunc>cupboards</u>
<u n="47" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0318">er cos he said oh no you want it you want it all you know clean lines and all that stuff</u>
<u n="49" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0318">but it wasn't very practical in the end we were oh okay then cos we wanted to have a cupboard you know where the the fridge is?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0318">on the other side and erm <pause dur="short"/> we ended up not having it and we</u>
<u n="53" who="S0317">regret it</u>
<u n="54" who="S0318">regret it</u>
<u n="55" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0318">cos</u>
<u n="57" who="S0317">it's a huge kitchen and we can't really store anything <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0255">yeah well that's it</u>
<u n="59" who="S0317" trans="overlap">drives me mad</u>
<u n="60" who="S0255">yeah I mean our place er the you know the bungalow we've got no storage anywhere because we knocked out where it was storage as part of the old bungalow and made it into part of a room which carried on back with all the other rooms then</u>
<u n="61" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0255">so we've got no cupboards we've got obviously not got an under the stairs cupboard or anything like that</u>
<u n="63" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0255">and you find it's the things like where do you put your mop and bucket? and where do you put your hoover? and there used to be a big cupboard in the bathroom in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s bathroom and we used to put everything in there like an airing cupboard <pause dur="short"/> and then when we had that taken out and made it into a wet room so there's still a bath there but she's got the shower</u>
<u n="65" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh right</u>
<u n="66" who="S0255">that that was the cupboard basically so that's where the the shower is now and all of a sudden where do we put the hoover? where do you put the mop? where do you put this? where do you put?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0255">and even down to the sheets for your bed and the towels cos they were all in there so you've suddenly got to find room for everything</u>
<u n="69" who="S0317">yeah you'll have to have an extension</u>
<u n="70" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0255">yeah we tried that well we didn't try it since then but yeah <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> whatever they just they weren't very <trunc>im</trunc> very <trunc>u</trunc> pleased with the idea of us building</u>
<u n="72" who="S0317" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> extending further</u>
<u n="73" who="S0255">no not extending at all really we had to really fight to get what we got we wanted we want</u>
<u n="74" who="S0317" trans="overlap">cos it's not like it impacts on anybody else cos you don't look over anyone</u>
<u n="75" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="76" who="S0317">and you're low and</u>
<u n="77" who="S0255">well they said it would it because it was the same look it <trunc>nee</trunc> looked the same as the bungalow next to it or the two bungalows next to it</u>
<u n="78" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0255">then we couldn't change the look of it and we said but we're next to a house</u>
<u n="80" who="S0317" trans="overlap">but you're going backwards</u>
<u n="81" who="S0255">yeah but we're next to a house and if you look all up and down the whole street</u>
<u n="82" who="S0317">they're all different anyway</u>
<u n="83" who="S0255">it's there's chalet bungalows</u>
<u n="84" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0255">there's semi-detached there's terraced houses there's detached there's everything all mixed up on that top road</u>
<u n="86" who="S0317">oh there is</u>
<u n="87" who="S0255">erm and we actually wanted to go up as well not into necessarily a house but up into the roof but actually make it higher</u>
<u n="88" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0255">so we had the top floor would have been <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I my like bedroom</u>
<u n="90" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0255">erm en suite and a dressing room sort of idea and then come across and then have the other side as all walk in loft space</u>
<u n="92" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0255">so we wanted to do all that and they wouldn't let us and</u>
<u n="94" who="S0317">oh <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0255">we wanted to do things with dormer windows and they wouldn't let us because nobody else had them and we found out loads of people had put in for them but they'd all got told no cos nobody else was had had them</u>
<u n="96" who="S0317" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="97" who="S0255">it's like if you'd let us all have them everybody will have one</u>
<u n="98" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0255">and then they'll all match so <pause dur="short"/> no we had a lot of trouble</u>
<u n="100" who="S0318">funny thing this planning innit?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0317">you're definitely at the mercy of them</u>
<u n="103" who="S0255">mm did you have problems when you were doing the conservatory?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0317">no cos we didn't ask for it</u>
<u n="105" who="S0255">didn't you?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0317">we didn't need well we were told we didn't need it</u>
<u n="107" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0317">because it's to do with the square meterage of floor space</u>
<u n="109" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0317">and it not being a permanent building</u>
<u n="111" who="S0318" trans="overlap">and there was already one there wasn't there?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0317">and there was one there already yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0255">oh right yeah so you were sort of replacing something that was already there</u>
<u n="114" who="S0317">yeah it was a tad bigger but</u>
<u n="115" who="S0255">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0317">only by a couple of feet wasn't it really?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0255">yeah I remember we we hadn't put in for planning permission and the guy started building it cos ours is goes right across the back doesn't it? if you remember</u>
<u n="118" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0255">we put in but then <trunc>wi</trunc> somebody was er saying actually you know you ought to put in cos if they find out and you er okay yeah we'll put in if we do need to so we put in for planning permission and then the woman came round to look at the garden look at the area and I'm thinking this was half-built do you know what I mean? and we're still putting in for planning permission so I was saying ah yes erm and she said I'll meet you round the back and she started walking round the bungalow I'm going through the house thinking what do I do what do I do? and I can't ring <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos there's nothing he can do he's away and er er er</u>
<u n="120" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0318" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0255">and I went out the back she went oh I see you started building it and I said yes oh did they tell you you didn't need planning permission at first? I went yes she went mm and then somebody said maybe you did I was like yes <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah but she <trunc>w</trunc> she was very adamant no more nothing else no more building and</u>
<u n="123" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0255">that's that so <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0255">now I mean it's plenty big enough for us now it's just that they made us go in in the middle bit so you've got the bungalow and then it goes in a bit where the dining room and back door is</u>
<u n="127" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0255">and then it goes back out again and they said that was because you could see it from the road whereas if it went in I think that was again we were just like what? you know so yeah again where we would have maybe put a big cupboard or something</u>
<u n="129" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0255">we couldn't</u>
<u n="131" who="S0318">oh dear so maybe we should have asked for planning permission</u>
<u n="132" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0255">I don't know</u>
<u n="134" who="S0317">I don't know as I said it was there before wasn't there so?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0255" trans="overlap">things are <pause dur="short"/> yeah things are probably changed I <trunc>d</trunc> I don't know what</u>
<u n="136" who="S0318"><unclear/> planning permission?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0317">well we bought the house and it was surveyed and everything things like that get picked up at that point don't they?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah that's right yeah cos it'll be on the deeds and what you can and can't have</u>
<u n="139" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0255">so yeah they would've noticed it</u>
<u n="141" who="S0317">okay so <unclear/> wouldn't have let us have it without she says with crossed fingers</u>
<u n="142" who="S0255">mm mm</u>
<u n="143" who="S0318">oh well we're not moving are we?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0317" trans="overlap">it's up now it's too late <vocal desc="laugh"/> no we're not moving so</u>
<u n="145" who="S0255">I think they've relaxed quite a lot now on what they'll allow for planning and <anon type="place"/> are different</u>
<u n="146" who="S0318" trans="overlap"><unclear/> didn't they say that they were allowing more for <trunc>conserve</trunc> that sort of thing because</u>
<u n="147" who="S0255" trans="overlap">I think yeah yeah we <trunc>hea</trunc>heard something like that</u>
<u n="148" who="S0318">because of the issues of people not being <unclear/> and housing and all the rest of it?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0317" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah like you are you <anon type="place"/> here?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0317">no</u>
<u n="152" who="S0255">you're <anon type="place"/> as well are you?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0317" trans="overlap">we're <anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0255">right okay yeah <trunc>whe</trunc> cos where does it</u>
<u n="155" who="S0317">it's <trunc>st</trunc> it's the other side of the erm the road isn't it? it starts</u>
<u n="156" who="S0255">oh is it? I don't know</u>
<u n="157" who="S0317">yeah it starts the other side of the road</u>
<u n="158" who="S0255">oh okay</u>
<u n="159" who="S0317">that's <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0255">mm cos they're different again to what <anon type="place"/> would let you have</u>
<u n="161" who="S0317">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0318">next door's got that they've got a conservatory in the one over the way haven't they? after <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sorry I'm pointing the wrong way</u>
<u n="163" who="S0317">I was gonna say which way are you going that way? yes they have yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0318">they've got a conservatory</u>
<u n="165" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0318">and nobody's moaned about it</u>
<u n="168" who="S0317">well we don't really interfere with anybody do we? cos it's this side of the the only person would be <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and we're <trunc>con</trunc></u>
<u n="169" who="S0318">well it's not cos the flat roof</u>
<u n="170" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0318">that way</u>
<u n="172" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="173" who="S0318">it's this side we're not overlooking anyone are we?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0317">no</u>
<u n="175" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="176" who="S0318"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0317">no we're not</u>
<u n="178" who="S0255">been at work today?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0318">yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0318">yes</u>
<u n="182" who="S0255">is that down in</u>
<u n="183" who="S0318" trans="overlap">driving down driving down the A1 and the four two one</u>
<u n="184" who="S0255">oh <anon type="place"/> way</u>
<u n="185" who="S0318">yeah <anon type="place"/> way</u>
<u n="186" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0318">I'm I'm car sharing now though</u>
<u n="188" who="S0255">right</u>
<u n="189" who="S0318">got a little car sharing buddy</u>
<u n="190" who="S0255">have you?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0318">so I drive one day</u>
<u n="192" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0318">he drives another day and then it we're either of us are usually in London then</u>
<u n="194" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0318">so it's <trunc>a</trunc> it's averaging two days a week so or one day a week</u>
<u n="196" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0318">it's not making a massive difference but it's</u>
<u n="198" who="S0317">every little helps doesn't it?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0318">yeah well it's a hundred miles off the</u>
<u n="201" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0318">off the clock that you don't do</u>
<u n="203" who="S0255">yeah and you're not actually having to do the driving which gets tiring as well</u>
<u n="204" who="S0318" trans="overlap">not doing the driving and it's not costing me any money so</u>
<u n="205" who="S0255">yeah mm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0318">but we're both in London tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> he's bagged himself a desk and I said well I'm not in that case I shall work from home in the morning</u>
<u n="208" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0318">which is <pause dur="short"/> code for have a lay in</u>
<u n="210" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0317">that'll be nice</u>
<u n="213" who="S0255">they say that where I work it's sort of none of the sales team work Fridays because they all say they all work from home on a Friday like yeah work from home idea it's like yeah I'm sure they're very busy</u>
<u n="214" who="S0317">are you still at <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0317">you were looking to get out weren't you at one point?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0255">mm thinking about it</u>
<u n="218" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="219" who="S0255">no I'll stay there now I think</u>
<u n="220" who="S0317">mm yeah for a while</u>
<u n="221" who="S0255">been thinking <unclear/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0317">was that your Linkedin profile had an alarm on it that came up?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0255">yeah says it's six years</u>
<u n="224" who="S0318" trans="overlap">that <unclear>worked</unclear> congratulate <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> six-year anniversary</u>
<u n="225" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0317" trans="overlap">have you really been there six years?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0317">have you?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0317">blimey</u>
<u n="231" who="S0255">yeah I know</u>
<u n="232" who="S0317">where did those go?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0255">don't ask me no yeah I've been there six years cos I've got a few people sent through <trunc>congra</trunc>congratulations I thought well I'm not actually in there at the moment am I? <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos I'm off with this but yeah thanks but yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0318">er cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been six years at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0317">oh</u>
<u n="236" who="S0318">it was on the same link</u>
<u n="237" who="S0317">I got it six months</u>
<u n="238" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> six months how's the new job going?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0318" trans="overlap">have you passed your probation?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0317">not yet <pause dur="short"/> no cos I worked there didn't I for <pause dur="short"/> nearly two months before I was proper</u>
<u n="241" who="S0318" trans="overlap">so is it six months' probation is it?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0317">six-month probation yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0255">mm I think if you were there temporary and then they said stay permanent then there's a fair bit</u>
<u n="244" who="S0317" trans="overlap">I had to apply for it and go through the the interview process</u>
<u n="245" who="S0255">oh right</u>
<u n="246" who="S0317">and the stupid tests they made us take</u>
<u n="247" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="248" who="S0318">what the <trunc>psycho</trunc> the psychology ones?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0317">there were like boxes and you had to move the boxes round and like how many <trunc>box</trunc> and then there was the mirror image tests and <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0318" trans="overlap">that's a that's a IQ test</u>
<u n="251" who="S0255" trans="overlap">oh god</u>
<u n="252" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah blimey that was really hard</u>
<u n="253" who="S0318">what was your IQ then?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0317">I don't know</u>
<u n="255" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0317">well I thought you saw the thing that came out from it didn't you?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0318">that didn't have an IQ on it though?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0317">no they were psychometric testing wasn't it? you have to look at them</u>
<u n="259" who="S0318" trans="overlap">what all those words that came about as a result of you moving boxes around?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0317">that and answering questions as well so</u>
<u n="261" who="S0318">that was able to tell that you were sort the sort of person you were from</u>
<u n="262" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0318">how you do boxes and mirror images that's a bit amazing</u>
<u n="264" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0318" trans="overlap">that's true do you not have to answer questions with answers like proper ones?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0317">yeah which ones you know it's like are you</u>
<u n="267" who="S0318">this</u>
<u n="268" who="S0317">in this situation are you more this? or are you more that? or</u>
<u n="269" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah and you have to put in more like this or more like that yeah yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0317" trans="overlap">and you have to do all of that sort of business</u>
<u n="271" who="S0255">yeah yeah and that gets the sort of the profile bit doesn't it?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0317"><unclear/> it's a bit bit scary how close they are</u>
<u n="273" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0317"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I laughed when I saw it</u>
<u n="275" who="S0255" trans="overlap">I yeah I've had it done in the past and it's</u>
<u n="276" who="S0318">what's bob on?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0317">bob on <pause dur="short"/> they were right bob on</u>
<u n="278" who="S0255">Fen talk <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0318">Fen talk I've never heard of it</u>
<u n="280" who="S0317">I don't know where that's come from</u>
<u n="281" who="S0255">bob on</u>
<u n="282" who="S0317">yeah I know a lot of people that say bob on</u>
<u n="283" who="S0318"><unclear/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0317">bob on I think it's <anon type="place"/> more than Fen I don't know</u>
<u n="285" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0318">mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0317">one of these colloquialisms</u>
<u n="288" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0318">so we had loads of people round didn't we last Saturday?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0317">yeah before</u>
<u n="291" who="S0255">week before</u>
<u n="292" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0318">week before has it been two weeks?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0317">yep</u>
<u n="296" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0317">it sure has</u>
<u n="298" who="S0255">yeah I saw pictures</u>
<u n="299" who="S0318" trans="overlap">fortunately it didn't rain for the evening</u>
<u n="300" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="301" who="S0318">it rained all day and then it cleared about four o'clock didn't it?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="303" who="S0318">so we was alright so it was a bit cold but</u>
<u n="304" who="S0317">and it was a bit soggy underfoot as well</u>
<u n="305" who="S0318">bit soggy</u>
<u n="306" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0318">but considering it was October</u>
<u n="308" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0318">we did alright</u>
<u n="311" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0317">mm mm we had a couple of fires outside didn't we?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0318">yeah managed not to burn down the fence</u>
<u n="314" who="S0255">that's always a good start</u>
<u n="315" who="S0318" trans="overlap">or the house <pause dur="short"/> everyone seemed to have a good time</u>
<u n="316" who="S0255">that's good I <trunc>s</trunc> I saw pictures of you with the cake on Facebook</u>
<u n="317" who="S0318"><unclear/> chocolate cake</u>
<u n="318" who="S0317">they were my sister's cake</u>
<u n="319" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0317">a little light sponge yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="322" who="S0318">size of a breeze block</u>
<u n="323" who="S0317">oh it was funny cos we hadn't bothered we weren't gonna bother with the cake</u>
<u n="324" who="S0255">no no</u>
<u n="325" who="S0317">and she said to me a few days before have you got a cake? and I was like nah I'm not gonna bother</u>
<u n="326" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="327" who="S0317">I'll make you one</u>
<u n="328" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> right</u>
<u n="329" who="S0317">bloody thing was enormous</u>
<u n="330" who="S0318">I think she was thinking on the base there's gonna be loads of people that'll all want a slice</u>
<u n="331" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0317">yeah but it all went up rather than out it went up it was this huge tower and it weighed a tonne</u>
<u n="333" who="S0318">it was a bit heavy</u>
<u n="334" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0317">a little light sponge cake <pause dur="short"/> but it was lovely</u>
<u n="336" who="S0255">yeah nice idea</u>
<u n="337" who="S0317">we got a picture out of it didn't we?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0318">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0255">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can see it's there twenty-five years together</u>
<u n="340" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yep</u>
<u n="341" who="S0317">yes</u>
<u n="342" who="S0255">that's really nice actually I cos I saw the picture on erm <pause dur="short"/> the picture on Facebook as well see I love Facebook cos you just get you see everything and anything <trunc>ev</trunc>even if you don't want to see it sometimes admittedly but</u>
<u n="343" who="S0318" trans="overlap">I don't like it <pause dur="short"/> what was I saying about Facebook the other day that it's funny how you you you don't see people for ages and ages and ages</u>
<u n="344" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0318">and but you think like you are seeing them and you know what they're doing cos you see them on Facebook</u>
<u n="346" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0318">so it's like you <pause dur="short"/> you might not have spoken to them for a for years but it doesn't feel like it you feel like you've spoken to them</u>
<u n="348" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah no because you a lot of people put on what they're doing on a day-to-day basis</u>
<u n="349" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0255">every week or so they put something on they're doing this going there</u>
<u n="351" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0255">so you actually get and get to see like they're having their grandkids and</u>
<u n="353" who="S0318">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0255">you're actually you're involved in with their life aren't you?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0255">whereas normally we'd meet up with people</u>
<u n="357" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0255">you know and then</u>
<u n="359" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0255">have a big catch up or you'd ring people</u>
<u n="361" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="362" who="S0255">I used to do that when I first moved to <anon type="place"/> erm cos obviously I moved away from everybody and I used to do that each week about on one night I'd ring somebody or you know somebody or somebody and just you know have an hour on the phone</u>
<u n="363" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0255">erm and just have a really good catch up you don't do that anymore</u>
<u n="365" who="S0317">no</u>
<u n="366" who="S0255">you always think you tend to think oh I'll send a text rather than ring somebody you send a text and then you get an answer back at some point and</u>
<u n="367" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="368" who="S0255">it's the personal connection that's gone isn't it?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0317">mm when we first got to moved in and we moved to <anon type="place"/> it was the phone box at the end of the road</u>
<u n="370" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="371" who="S0317"><vocal desc="laugh"/> in those days <pause dur="short"/> I'm going down to ring mum</u>
<u n="372" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0317">with your bag of ten Ps</u>
<u n="374" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes I used to come down with you didn't I? <trunc>whe</trunc>when when it was dark</u>
<u n="375" who="S0317">feed the <unclear/> book</u>
<u n="376" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0318">it was on the edge of a park which was a bit dodgy</u>
<u n="378" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0318">so I used to</u>
<u n="380" who="S0255">yeah particularly as it's lit up and you're stood there</u>
<u n="381" who="S0318">I used to come down and stand outside</u>
<u n="382" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0255">yeah that's right and you're preoccupied with who you're talking to and what you're doing and yeah next thing you know you've got some</u>
<u n="384" who="S0318" trans="overlap">and usually you were getting guilt-tripped weren't you?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0317">by my mum yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0317">but no funny you know the old phone boxes</u>
<u n="388" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="389" who="S0317">I don't think the kids would know how to use a phone box these days I don't know if there is any</u>
<u n="390" who="S0255">no there's not many now</u>
<u n="391" who="S0318" trans="overlap">there's still a few not many not many of the old ones like the red ones</u>
<u n="392" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="393" who="S0318">you don't see that you only <trunc>s</trunc> places you see them are in these heritage</u>
<u n="394" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="395" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0318">er villages don't you?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="398" who="S0318">sort of like all the preservation orders they've got on them</u>
<u n="399" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="400" who="S0318">but no it's funny cos they all all the people in the village oh got to keep their phone box and they have</u>
<u n="401" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0318">they have big preservation order to keep it keep it red</u>
<u n="403" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="404" who="S0318">and all that and nobody uses it</u>
<u n="405" who="S0317">no</u>
<u n="406" who="S0318">but nobody uses landlines anymore</u>
<u n="407" who="S0255">no <pause dur="short"/> no apart from the people trying to</u>
<u n="408" who="S0317" trans="overlap">not very often</u>
<u n="409" who="S0255">trying to tell you that the erm the government have got a scheme and you can have a boiler when you get your PPI money you won't even need to spend that will you?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0317">the advantages of being ex-directory</u>
<u n="412" who="S0255">oh we are and and we're telephone preference service as well</u>
<u n="413" who="S0318">but you still get them?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0317" trans="overlap">and do you still get them?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0255">oh yeah we get them</u>
<u n="416" who="S0318" trans="overlap">we don't get many</u>
<u n="417" who="S0317" trans="overlap">no we not on the landline I get them on the mobile</u>
<u n="418" who="S0255" trans="overlap">we get it's the recorded delivery the recorded messages now that we get and it there's one that we seem to be stuck on and they ring the fax number first and then literally about four minutes later it rings ours so you know to ignore it the fax nothing happens but then the main phone one goes and I just leave it and it always cuts into the same sort of point government scheme which says you can borrow on PPI not PPI government scheme for new boiler and and you can't get hold of it you can't do anything and find out who it is or try and block it because it just comes up it's international or withheld</u>
<u n="419" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="420" who="S0255">or it's something like that</u>
<u n="421" who="S0318">I had a guy ring me up the other day at on my mobile</u>
<u n="422" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0318">on my work mobile whilst I was at work and said it rang and I went hello and there was silence and then obviously cos it's one of these diallers isn't it?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0317" trans="overlap">and wait for the call centre</u>
<u n="425" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0318">and then <trunc>c</trunc> and then I got connected to him he goes hello hello he said <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0318">he goes hello and he goes he goes I'm calling about your PPI</u>
<u n="430" who="S0255">uhu</u>
<u n="431" who="S0318">got a PPI I said er can I ask where you've got this number from?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="433" who="S0318">and he goes erm well I got this number from er er there we have a a <trunc>colle</trunc> data collection link I said oh right so who is who is it who's given you my number why?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0318">and and he said he said well I just need to take your details sir but you're telling me I've got a PPI claim?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0318">so how do you know that? well I I er I said oh you must know so you don't know then?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="439" who="S0318">so you don't know who I am so how have you got hold of this number?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0318">so he goes er and he goes so why are you calling me? I just basically took the mickey out of him for about ten minutes</u>
<u n="442" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0317"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="445" who="S0318">and got him more and more annoyed</u>
<u n="446" who="S0317"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="447" who="S0318">and then in the end I just hung up</u>
<u n="448" who="S0255">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh it is annoying</u>
<u n="449" who="S0318">I took a leaf out my dad's book he does that</u>
<u n="450" who="S0317">yeah your dad does that all the time doesn't he?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0318">can I ask where you happen to have got my? do you realise that's a breach of the Data Protection Act?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0255">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0318">my son works for the insurance fraud bureau you know he keeps wheeling that one out</u>
<u n="454" who="S0317" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> he does doesn't he? as if that makes a lot of difference with the people he knows</u>
<u n="455" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah no exactly no</u>
<u n="456" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yes exactly works for the insurance fraud people</u>
<u n="457" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0318">oh dear</u>
<u n="459" who="S0317">no I only get them on my mobile we haven't so far we don't</u>
<u n="460" who="S0318">the only person that rings you on the landline</u>
<u n="461" who="S0317">is my mother</u>
<u n="462" who="S0318">is your mother</u>
<u n="463" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0255">yeah my mum rings me on the landline</u>
<u n="465" who="S0318">yeah my mum mum rings on</u>
<u n="466" who="S0255" trans="overlap">from her landline</u>
<u n="467" who="S0318">the landline I use it to ring my mum and that's about it <pause dur="short"/> innit?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0255">my mum rings me on the mobile on her mobile and says oh hello I haven't got many minutes can you ring me back? and I think who's the mother and who's the child you know? it's normally kids who ring and go I've got no credit and <trunc>te</trunc> ring me</u>
<u n="470" who="S0317" trans="overlap">it's usually the other way round</u>
<u n="471" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0317">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> all those years and <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah exactly</u>
<u n="474" who="S0318">just say change your plan then</u>
<u n="475" who="S0255">that's what I've said to her but oh well no that's too much hassle and it's not very much a month and it's like you could quite easily get oh no no no</u>
<u n="476" who="S0317"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0255">okay worse than that she'll chat to you for a minute on it and then she'll go I've got to go cos I'm saving my minutes because I know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s going to ring me and then I've got to ring her about something something <trunc>i</trunc> you're saving your minutes for somebody else you know I don't even get your minutes mother <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0317"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0255">oh it's funny</u>
<u n="480" who="S0317">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> rings me on it doesn't she? but she's got this you you can talk for fifty-nine minutes</u>
<u n="481" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0317">so she'll go she'll sort of go oh hang on I've gotta go we're on fifty-eight minutes hang on</u>
<u n="483" who="S0255">and then rings you back</u>
<u n="484" who="S0317">and then she rings back right so de de de de de de</u>
<u n="485" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0317">but yeah no I speak to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0255">mm I think you have to have the <trunc>lo</trunc> the landline for your broadband don't you?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0318">yeah there was a thing I read on this is on Linkedin again erm it said five things not to put on your résumé</u>
<u n="489" who="S0255">right</u>
<u n="490" who="S0318">cos obviously it was American</u>
<u n="491" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="492" who="S0318">and the first thing was you don't put your erm don't put your address</u>
<u n="493" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="494" who="S0318">on your résumé</u>
<u n="495" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="496" who="S0318">it's not necessary</u>
<u n="497" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0318">and also they will economically profile you <pause dur="short"/> so like they'll work out where you live</u>
<u n="499" who="S0317" trans="overlap">they'll see where you live</u>
<u n="500" who="S0318">and see so whether they want that sort of person who lives in a neighbourhood like that they don't want</u>
<u n="501" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0318">erm the next thing was you don't put erm <pause dur="short"/> email address you need to don't use a cable provider's email address</u>
<u n="503" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="504" who="S0318">because that's <trunc>s</trunc> a sign that you're really old</u>
<u n="505" who="S0255">oh right</u>
<u n="506" who="S0318">so if you've got an AOL dot com</u>
<u n="507" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="508" who="S0318">it was saying or or any other cable provider serving like BT</u>
<u n="509" who="S0317" trans="overlap">BT <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0318">yeah right so I'm thinking so yeah I put my address on there I put my email and then the other one was oh and the other reason for the address was they <trunc>wor</trunc> can work out how far away you are from</u>
<u n="511" who="S0317">mm mm</u>
<u n="512" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0318">the place and then rule you out from a commuting point of view</u>
<u n="514" who="S0255">mm mm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0318">erm the email address oh the double the double <pause dur="short"/> the double space after a period or what well that means a full stop</u>
<u n="516" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0317">oh right</u>
<u n="518" who="S0318">cos they don't</u>
<u n="519" who="S0317">don't put them in?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0318">don't put them in because that's something that we had a big row about this at work the other day yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0317">I thought you were supposed to</u>
<u n="522" who="S0318">yes so I I'm sitting there so so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> comes up to me and some of the researchers are saying there's a big issue here with where is you know do you put two spaces after a full stop? and I went yes you do well that's not what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does and er and then we were all looking at all these different reports and some people do and some people don't</u>
<u n="523" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="524" who="S0318">and erm I looked up we've got an <trunc>e</trunc> report standards document like this is how you should lay it out</u>
<u n="525" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah how you do it yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="528" who="S0318">and in there it's a bloody single space innit right?</u>
<u n="529" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0318">it's all single spaced ah I don't so I looked it up on I googled it</u>
<u n="531" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="532" who="S0318">and I looked it up <pause dur="short"/> and it said that's the English spacing</u>
<u n="533" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="534" who="S0318">and it's the French spacing there's actually all different terms for all these different styles</u>
<u n="535" who="S0317" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="536" who="S0318">and apparently it's it's to do with <pause dur="short"/> typing on a typewriter</u>
<u n="537" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0317" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="539" who="S0318">it's going out of fashion <pause dur="short"/> and now it's now the accepted standard is one space</u>
<u n="540" who="S0317">ah</u>
<u n="541" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="542" who="S0318">and by having two spaces after a full stop before you type your next letter</u>
<u n="543" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm you show your age</u>
<u n="544" who="S0318">you're showing your age</u>
<u n="545" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="546" who="S0318">or showing that you were trained to type on</u>
<u n="547" who="S0255">see I was never type</u>
<u n="548" who="S0318">on a typewriter</u>
<u n="549" who="S0255">I've never done double spacing <pause dur="short"/> at all</u>
<u n="550" who="S0317">I've only done it because just through the college courses and stuff and them and them saying this is how</u>
<u n="551" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah and it's something that they teach in universities</u>
<u n="552" who="S0317">yeah in university how to do your</u>
<u n="553" who="S0318">yeah in universities essay writing</u>
<u n="554" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0318">is apparently something they teach</u>
<u n="556" who="S0317" trans="overlap">double spacing yeah</u>
<u n="557" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="558" who="S0318">but it's not it's apparently going out of</u>
<u n="559" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0318">phase erm but that's <trunc>wh</trunc> that was double spacing</u>
<u n="561" who="S0255">yea</u>
<u n="562" who="S0318">so email double something I do double spacing</u>
<u n="563" who="S0255" trans="overlap">address email and double spacing</u>
<u n="564" who="S0318">okay so that's three and then what was the other ones? <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what they were now <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> there was five <pause dur="short"/> oh landline</u>
<u n="565" who="S0255">oh don't put a landline</u>
<u n="566" who="S0318">landline</u>
<u n="567" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0318">that's what led me to <trunc>co</trunc> start it in the first place</u>
<u n="569" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="570" who="S0318">yeah landline who has a landline anymore? that's a definite sign you're old if you've got a landline</u>
<u n="571" who="S0255" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0317">but like you said you have to have a landline now to have broadband</u>
<u n="573" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah but you don't expect people to phone you on it</u>
<u n="574" who="S0317">er I suppose <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0318">and the other one was erm to do with your skillsets but I can't quite remember how that was but it was the way you write</u>
<u n="576" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="577" who="S0318">what your skills are but it's like you know you shouldn't be putting these things on cos it</u>
<u n="578" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0318">you don't put your age on</u>
<u n="580" who="S0317">no</u>
<u n="581" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="582" who="S0318">but that it screams how old you are based on the fact that you've provided a cable provided email address so it said if you've got a cable one get it redirected to a Gmail account <pause dur="short"/> use something like modern</u>
<u n="583" who="S0317" trans="overlap">but they can work out how old you are <pause dur="short"/> mm I've got Hotmail does that count? <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos I always thought Hotmail was alright</u>
<u n="584" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah no Hotmail yeah that's erm</u>
<u n="585" who="S0317">was a no no</u>
<u n="586" who="S0255">I don't yeah I think there's Hotmail that is</u>
<u n="587" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah you see I I</u>
<u n="588" who="S0255">sort of scam things isn't it? and you get loads of Hotmail accounts and stuff but I think it's probably quite trendy</u>
<u n="589" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah touch wood I've not had any scams so</u>
<u n="590" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="591" who="S0318">have you heard of a guy called Alan Turing?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0317">yes</u>
<u n="593" who="S0318">he's the guy that invented the computer</u>
<u n="594" who="S0317" trans="overlap">computer yeah</u>
<u n="595" who="S0318"><unclear/> and there's a film about him</u>
<u n="596" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="597" who="S0318">at the moment which is <trunc>fo</trunc></u>
<u n="598" who="S0317" trans="overlap">just about to come out</u>
<u n="599" who="S0318">stars <trunc>Benedi</trunc>Benedict Cumberbatch and cos he was homosexual</u>
<u n="600" who="S0317">mm he killed himself</u>
<u n="601" who="S0318" trans="overlap">and he killed he ah well this is the thing we were talking about this at work <pause dur="short"/> we were saying did he actually</u>
<u n="602" who="S0317" trans="overlap">or was he knocked off?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0318">he killed himself he killed himself by eating a pie an apple laced with cyanide right? <pause dur="short"/> cos apparently he had a big thing about he had a big obsession around the whole Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs and the poison apple thing going on</u>
<u n="604" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="605" who="S0318">and when he was found he was found in bed and there was a half-eaten apple by the side of his bed</u>
<u n="606" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="607" who="S0318">and the <trunc>app</trunc> but the apple was never tested for cyanide but that's what he died of cos when they tested his blood</u>
<u n="608" who="S0255">and the half-eaten apple means <pause dur="short"/> like a <trunc>s</trunc>sudden death doesn't it? cos you'd you'd finish it if you were</u>
<u n="609" who="S0318"><trunc>su</trunc><trunc>su</trunc>supposedly this is the story</u>
<u n="610" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="611" who="S0318">and I was sitting there at work and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who who's at work goes he says yeah that's why Apple the apple logo is half-eaten apple and I went is that right? he goes yeah apparently that is the story is that the Apple logo</u>
<u n="612" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="613" who="S0317">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="614" who="S0318" trans="overlap">which is a half-eaten apple is is a tribute</u>
<u n="615" who="S0317" trans="overlap">to him?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0318">to Alan Turing <unclear/> apple</u>
<u n="617" who="S0255" trans="overlap">oh right oh as in <pause dur="short"/> apple products not not</u>
<u n="618" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah you know the apple</u>
<u n="619" who="S0255">I was <trunc>th</trunc> I was just trying to picture what the Gala apple label was like or the Pink Lady apple thinking do they all have half-eaten apples on it?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0318" trans="overlap">no no Apple computers</u>
<u n="621" who="S0255">oh right</u>
<u n="622" who="S0318" trans="overlap">Apple computers</u>
<u n="623" who="S0255">oh right</u>
<u n="624" who="S0318">right? so I went is that right? and so I looked it up so I looked up Alan Turing and apparently he <trunc>sin</trunc> there is a he did die he was found</u>
<u n="625" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="626" who="S0318">in bed next to a half-eaten apple</u>
<u n="627" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0318">so at the time there was this speculation that that's what happened but there's been a loads of stuff since saying suggesting that actually he <trunc>pro</trunc> he probably didn't because <pause dur="short"/> there's all this thing about he was persecuted and you know all the rest of it</u>
<u n="629" who="S0255" trans="overlap">oh mm</u>
<u n="630" who="S0318">but apparently at the time he he the way he was with people he was kind of yeah whatever he wasn't bothered about it</u>
<u n="631" who="S0255" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="632" who="S0318">and he was remarkably cheerful in the two or three days before he was fine and then on the</u>
<u n="633" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0318">the cos it was a Bank Holiday weekend he put in a list of everything he was going to do the following week he left it on his desk</u>
<u n="635" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="636" who="S0318">which was his habit to do</u>
<u n="637" who="S0317">ah so was he bumped off then?</u>
<u n="638" who="S0318" trans="overlap">apparently he always er he always ate an apple before he went to bed</u>
<u n="639" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="640" who="S0318">and often he left it half-eaten right?</u>
<u n="641" who="S0317">oh right</u>
<u n="642" who="S0255">oh</u>
<u n="643" who="S0318">when they examined the body it wasn't the impression was that it wasn't a sudden <pause dur="short"/> cyanide ingestion</u>
<u n="644" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="645" who="S0318">it was gradual and apparently he was a bugger for doing experiments at home chemical experiments</u>
<u n="646" who="S0317">oh right</u>
<u n="647" who="S0318">and he was doing plating and there was <trunc>le</trunc> there was cyanide in in one of the rooms and they reckon it was actually</u>
<u n="648" who="S0255" trans="overlap">oh no yeah</u>
<u n="649" who="S0318">he inhaled it it was an accident</u>
<u n="650" who="S0317" trans="overlap">ah it was an accident</u>
<u n="651" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="652" who="S0318">he didn't actually</u>
<u n="653" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="654" who="S0318">he didn't kill himself</u>
<u n="655" who="S0317" trans="overlap">I was going to say it's a conspiracy somebody actually in the secret service bumped him off or something</u>
<u n="656" who="S0318">no no they reckon</u>
<u n="657" who="S0317" trans="overlap"><unclear/> oh right</u>
<u n="658" who="S0318">no no not not at all so <pause dur="short"/> there you go</u>
<u n="659" who="S0317">did you find out whether the Apple logo is because of that?</u>
<u n="660" who="S0318">well so then I looked <unclear/> then they said about the Apple logo as well in in the Wikipedia thing</u>
<u n="661" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="662" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="663" who="S0318">which obviously isn't always true but it said that erm</u>
<u n="664" who="S0317" trans="overlap">must be it's Wikipedia</u>
<u n="665" who="S0255">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="666" who="S0318" trans="overlap">he was asked erm you know that er oh what's his name? what's the guy? Stephen Fry</u>
<u n="667" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="668" who="S0318">asked <trunc>S</trunc> asked Steve Jobs who was the founder of Apple computers</u>
<u n="669" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="670" who="S0318">said and asked him is that is it true? this rumour that</u>
<u n="671" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="672" who="S0318">and Steve Jobs turned round and said god I wish it was</u>
<u n="673" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="674" who="S0317">oh right</u>
<u n="675" who="S0318">but it was an accident it was <unclear>pure coincidence</unclear></u>
<u n="676" who="S0317" trans="overlap">it was a coincidence</u>
<u n="677" who="S0318" trans="overlap">it was pure coincidence</u>
<u n="678" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="679" who="S0317">but it's a good <unclear>quite a cool story</unclear></u>
<u n="680" who="S0318">but it's a good little erm</u>
<u n="681" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0318">story though</u>
<u n="683" who="S0255">but then if Steve Jobs had said yes it is then surely the descendants of matey would have said we want some royalties for using our logo</u>
<u n="684" who="S0317" trans="overlap">want some money yeah</u>
<u n="685" who="S0255">and it's trademarked and</u>
<u n="686" who="S0318">I don't know if he had any descendants</u>
<u n="687" who="S0255">no?</u>
<u n="688" who="S0318">cos he wasn't married cos he was gay</u>
<u n="689" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="690" who="S0318">didn't have any kids</u>
<u n="691" who="S0317" trans="overlap">he might have had <pause dur="short"/> no but he he's got his brothers and sisters he might have nephews</u>
<u n="692" who="S0318">yeah but they're not his descendants are they?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0255">no but they would have been an an heir wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="694" who="S0317" trans="overlap">well family</u>
<u n="695" who="S0255">get Heir Hunters on to it</u>
<u n="696" who="S0318">mm</u>
<u n="697" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="698" who="S0255">find the hunt find the family</u>
<u n="699" who="S0317">that's good that is</u>
<u n="700" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="701" who="S0318">you watch Heir Hunters?</u>
<u n="702" who="S0317">ah it's a good programme it's very exciting when they're after something</u>
<u n="703" who="S0318" trans="overlap">how how can you be watching Heir Hunters?</u>
<u n="704" who="S0317">I was didn't work for a few weeks did I before? between Christmas and when I went back to work</u>
<u n="705" who="S0318">god</u>
<u n="706" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="707" who="S0317">daytime telly is rubbish</u>
<u n="708" who="S0318" trans="overlap">crap</u>
<u n="709" who="S0255">it is you have to really eek out and find something don't you?</u>
<u n="710" who="S0317" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you do</u>
<u n="711" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="712" who="S0317">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the Long Lost Family has went from daytime to er</u>
<u n="713" who="S0318">they're all ex-coppers as well you I don't know if you've noticed</u>
<u n="714" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah they are all yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0318">all the Heir Hunters</u>
<u n="716" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="717" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="718" who="S0318">they're all ex-policemen</u>
<u n="719" who="S0255">mm are they?</u>
<u n="720" who="S0318">of a certain type</u>
<u n="721" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0255">you'd be good at that though <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="723" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="724" who="S0255">investigative mind</u>
<u n="725" who="S0317">you'd love that</u>
<u n="726" who="S0255">yeah finding people</u>
<u n="727" who="S0318">what driving around the countryside all the time?</u>
<u n="728" who="S0317" trans="overlap">no doing the research</u>
<u n="729" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah the research bit</u>
<u n="730" who="S0318">I wouldn't mind that that job</u>
<u n="731" who="S0255">oh yeah no that and I'd like that</u>
<u n="732" who="S0318" trans="overlap">I bet you I bet you that's a bit of a grind though</u>
<u n="733" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="734" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="735" who="S0318">it's it's like a lot of things innit it's it's only interesting for a certain amount of time</u>
<u n="736" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I love looking and trying to find stuff out and then when you do find the trail or find what you're trying to sort out from it</u>
<u n="737" who="S0317">yeah it's such</u>
<u n="738" who="S0318">but the internet is an amazing thing for that what you can find out</u>
<u n="739" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="740" who="S0318">and what you can do</u>
<u n="741" who="S0317" trans="overlap">definitely</u>
<u n="742" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="743" who="S0318">do you remember that the guy I erm that aeroplane?</u>
<u n="744" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="745" who="S0318">so when I was in the air cadets</u>
<u n="746" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="747" who="S0318">flew a little have I <trunc>s</trunc>told you this story? if I have I'll shut up</u>
<u n="748" who="S0255">I'll tell you if you have when I get to a bit I remember</u>
<u n="749" who="S0318" trans="overlap">alright so <unclear/></u>
<u n="750" who="S0317" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> then you'll see how much <trunc>a</trunc> she was listening to</u>
<u n="751" who="S0318" trans="overlap">an aeroplane erm called a Chipmunk which was a little training aeroplane this was back in the eighties ninety early eighties</u>
<u n="752" who="S0255" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="753" who="S0318">and these were really old aeroplanes then and it was down at <anon type="place"/> and it's the first time I'd ever flown ever not even been in a big plane</u>
<u n="754" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="755" who="S0318">and it's etched in my <pause dur="short"/> memory <pause dur="short"/> and erm when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went flying with cadets we were talking about I said oh I remember my first trip blah blah blah</u>
<u n="756" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="757" who="S0318">and erm when you you get a little book when you're in the cadets a little book of all your things that you do you record everything</u>
<u n="758" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="759" who="S0318">wherever you go and it's like a little flight log in there so you can record all your flights <pause dur="short"/> and erm most cadets if they're worth their salt they keep their</u>
<u n="760" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="761" who="S0318">three eight double two it's called it's a little book and I've still got mine and then</u>
<u n="762" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="763" who="S0318">he obviously had his and said and I will show you my little three eight two so I pulled this book out and I was looking at all the different this and I <trunc>j</trunc> and I just said I wonder what happened to that plane</u>
<u n="764" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="765" who="S0318">I wonder if it got scrapped cos they all got scrapped in the in the mid-nineties they retired them all sold them all off privately</u>
<u n="766" who="S0255">right</u>
<u n="767" who="S0318">so I knew that much so I wonder if they're wonder what they did with it and I just started looking on the internet and I <pause dur="short"/> like old aircraft and old and I found a website that was all it's every single military aircraft that was ever flown</u>
<u n="768" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="769" who="S0318">erm the <trunc>re</trunc> it was all listed they're all listed so some sad person</u>
<u n="770" who="S0255" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="771" who="S0318">has spent hours and hours listing every single type but going back yonks</u>
<u n="772" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="773" who="S0318">we're talking back into the nineteen thirties and ridiculously old</u>
<u n="774" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah goodness</u>
<u n="775" who="S0318">so I thought oh blimey so I I said type <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> Chipmunk sure enough there was a big list of <unclear/> Chipmunk and cos I had the serial number of the aircraft in my little book so I'm looking and I found the serial number for this thing</u>
<u n="776" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="777" who="S0318">yeah yeah paid off nineteen ninety-six de de de er sold to and then it had erm or re-registered USA and it had a number</u>
<u n="778" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="779" who="S0318">which was the American <trunc>A</trunc> Federal Aviation Authority serial number so you know every aircraft has a serial number?</u>
<u n="780" who="S0255" trans="overlap">right yeah</u>
<u n="781" who="S0318">I thought bloody hell it went to a it's gone to an American it's been re-registered in America</u>
<u n="782" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="783" who="S0318">I wonder what happened to that I wonder if there's a website like this in for America</u>
<u n="784" who="S0255" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="785" who="S0318">so I went Federal Aviation Authority like</u>
<u n="786" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="787" who="S0318">Aircraft Registrations to put that it in</u>
<u n="788" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="789" who="S0318">and I <trunc>f</trunc> I stumble found a website eventually and again it's like all you just put in a code and it comes up this aircraft is a <trunc>s</trunc> is a Chipmunk blah blah and it said it's in Florida and it's registered to this guy</u>
<u n="790" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="791" who="S0318">and and it gave a town <pause dur="short"/> I thought bloody hell it's somewhere in <anon type="place"/> I wonder if I could find this bloke</u>
<u n="792" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="793" who="S0318">so and this do you remember?</u>
<u n="794" who="S0317">I do yeah</u>
<u n="795" who="S0318" trans="overlap">it took me about three hours</u>
<u n="796" who="S0255">really? yeah</u>
<u n="797" who="S0318">but I I ended up going from I wonder what happened to that aeroplane to</u>
<u n="798" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="799" who="S0318">knowing it was at a certain airport</u>
<u n="800" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="801" who="S0318">it was owned by a lawyer</u>
<u n="802" who="S0255">right</u>
<u n="803" who="S0318">an attorney</u>
<u n="804" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="805" who="S0318">I knew where he lived I had a picture of him <pause dur="short"/> yeah and I had his email address</u>
<u n="806" who="S0255">well was it was it a cable provider?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0317">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="808" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="809" who="S0318">probably so no it was his law firm address cos he was an attorney of law</u>
<u n="810" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="811" who="S0318">and obviously on the I found the business</u>
<u n="812" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="813" who="S0318">the business had a website and that's where I found his picture he was on there</u>
<u n="814" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="815" who="S0318"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I think his name was</u>
<u n="816" who="S0317">can't remember</u>
<u n="817" who="S0318">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and erm I though oh I'll email him so I emailed him said oh you you probably think it's a bit weird</u>
<u n="818" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="819" who="S0318"><trunc>mail</trunc> you know emailing you out the blue but I flew your <trunc>bu</trunc> your you're your plane that you've still got</u>
<u n="820" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="821" who="S0318">dah de dah de dah blah blah blah and I said I'd love to see some pictures if you've got a picture of it that'd be great</u>
<u n="822" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="823" who="S0318">and he wrote back to me and <trunc>s</trunc> erm about a really long email said it's</u>
<u n="824" who="S0255" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="825" who="S0318">said it was in an air-conditioned hangar in in er <trunc>Ta</trunc>Tampa or somewhere in Florida he says</u>
<u n="826" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="827" who="S0318">and it's it's a real popular aeroplane on the on the <trunc>fl</trunc> on the airshow circuit</u>
<u n="828" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="829" who="S0318">takes it off and does airshows with it all over the place erm he said I'm looking for some cadet memorabilia if you've got anything like that so I sent him a load of PDF</u>
<u n="830" who="S0255">copies of yeah yeah</u>
<u n="831" who="S0318" trans="overlap">files of old posters and stuff from which he could he could obviously get printed off</u>
<u n="832" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="833" who="S0318">but I think he got the impression I was a pilot cos the way he was talking to he's <trunc>ai</trunc> he was an ex-navy</u>
<u n="834" who="S0255">oh right cos you said I flew your plane</u>
<u n="835" who="S0318" trans="overlap">I <pause dur="short"/> I flew in the plane it was my first flight</u>
<u n="836" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="837" who="S0318">was in your plane I think he thought I actually flew it</u>
<u n="838" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="839" who="S0318">he said you'll have to come over when you come over you can take her up and</u>
<u n="840" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="841" who="S0318">I don't</u>
<u n="842" who="S0317" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="843" who="S0255">yeah which which do you press to start the engine again?</u>
<u n="844" who="S0318" trans="overlap">and he's teaching his he's teaching his son to fly and he sent me three pictures of him and his lad</u>
<u n="845" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="846" who="S0317">oh</u>
<u n="847" who="S0318">so the only thing he'd done he'd put in a a <trunc>tran</trunc> a new transponder in it</u>
<u n="848" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="849" who="S0318">which was required under their regulations he said everything else is</u>
<u n="850" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="851" who="S0318">all original even the paintwork and it looks just like I remembered it</u>
<u n="852" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="853" who="S0318">and then the weirdest thing was I went I went I was telling people about this at the squadron</u>
<u n="854" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="855" who="S0318">and in the mess there's a big picture an oil painting of a Chipmunk that the CO who was the CO when I was a cadet back in the eighties</u>
<u n="856" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="857" who="S0318">when he left he presented that to the squadron</u>
<u n="858" who="S0255" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="859" who="S0318">and it was he'd got it commissioned it was an original oil painting</u>
<u n="860" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="861" who="S0318">of a Chipmunk in flight and the bloody serial number on his er plane is the same plane</u>
<u n="862" who="S0255">wow</u>
<u n="863" who="S0318">how weird is that? it was spooky wasn't it? like</u>
<u n="864" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="865" who="S0318">that's <pause dur="short"/> that's the plane</u>
<u n="866" who="S0255">I thought you were going say that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then got a looked and his first flight</u>
<u n="867" who="S0317">was the same <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="868" who="S0255" trans="overlap">was the same one as it had ended up being somewhere and yeah</u>
<u n="869" who="S0317">no</u>
<u n="870" who="S0255">yeah you had told me no you hadn't told me before really</u>
<u n="871" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="872" who="S0318">I must have bored a few people with that story</u>
<u n="873" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="874" who="S0317">you don't bore people <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="875" who="S0255">no you don't bore people</u>
<u n="876" who="S0318">I almost believed you then for a moment</u>
<u n="877" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I was actually swallowing wine that's why it maybe didn't sound and sincere as it should</u>
<u n="878" who="S0317"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="879" who="S0255">you don't bore people <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="880" who="S0318"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="881" who="S0255">is that better?</u>
<u n="882" who="S0317"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="883" who="S0255"><trunc>sh</trunc>shall I let me just practise it a bit</u>
<u n="884" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="885" who="S0255">is it you don't bore people <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="886" who="S0318" trans="overlap">it's er for the benefit of the tape <pause dur="short"/> for the benefit of the tape <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has just decided to walk out the room</u>
<u n="887" who="S0317"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="888" who="S0255">you don't bore people <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah it's getting the intonation right isn't it?</u>
<u n="889" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="890" who="S0317">ah god I was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s car out on the thing the other day</u>
<u n="891" who="S0255">oh yeah</u>
<u n="892" who="S0317" trans="overlap">I'm sure it gets lower and lower every day</u>
<u n="893" who="S0255">yeah it does</u>
<u n="894" who="S0317"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="895" who="S0255">yes</u>
<u n="896" who="S0317">he can't get it much lower surely</u>
<u n="897" who="S0255">well</u>
<u n="898" who="S0318" trans="overlap">it'd be good if it didn't have wheels on it <unclear>or little wheels</unclear></u>
<u n="899" who="S0317">actually yeah yeah no he's erm he's on about getting a BMW now as well to have as a a drifter car but make it road legal so he can actually drive that as a daily drive</u>
<u n="900" who="S0317">right</u>
<u n="901" who="S0255">which before he had a BMW didn't he? as his daily drive as well as the Corsa</u>
<u n="902" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="903" who="S0255">and then after that he had a red Corsa as well as his blue <trunc>co</trunc> oh I don't know yeah he's just he's normal <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he I tell he played rugby last week erm for <anon type="place"/> he got man of the match</u>
<u n="904" who="S0317">oh wow</u>
<u n="905" who="S0255">he was really chuffed cos he's never had that before</u>
<u n="906" who="S0317">I have to say I <unclear>don't think I'd want</unclear> him coming hurtling at me he's not <unclear>not exactly tiny</unclear> is he?</u>
<u n="907" who="S0255" trans="overlap">and he and he did a no I know well he he shared a link there's the the match write up and he was mentioned in it twice</u>
<u n="908" who="S0317" trans="overlap">oh oh bless him</u>
<u n="909" who="S0255">erm and it says something about powerful centre <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I thought oh yeah and he made a something that made I don't know going through these people and whatever</u>
<u n="910" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="911" who="S0255">yeah and then he scored a good try and man of the match</u>
<u n="912" who="S0317" trans="overlap">oh good on him</u>
<u n="913" who="S0255">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know bless him like yeah he is big I forget how big he is cos he's just he's my baby isn't he? you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="914" who="S0317" trans="overlap">well you're used to him aren't you? yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah he's he's not</u>
<u n="915" who="S0255" trans="overlap">but then er</u>
<u n="916" who="S0317">you know you can see it's it's not you know he's just well-built he you know it's muscles isn't he? his frame</u>
<u n="917" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah he's started going to the gym now taking it a lot more he was going anyway on and off</u>
<u n="918" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0255">but he's taken it a lot more seriously now and eating lots of chicken and rice and</u>
<u n="920" who="S0317">oh right so he's beefing up as well</u>
<u n="921" who="S0255">yeah yeah so but he's doing it slowly so he actually builds up <trunc>ra</trunc> he doesn't want to get like big muscle or do this or do that</u>
<u n="922" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="923" who="S0255">erm cos he got a little bit of a belly come in and he decided that he was gonna take rugby a lot more seriously this year cos the whole team are they're last year they were doing really well they nearly went up a league</u>
<u n="924" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="925" who="S0255">erm but now they didn't quite make it to go up but they're saying this year they're starting from beginning of the the year really with that as an aim</u>
<u n="926" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="927" who="S0255">so they're playing really well and he's really enjoying it which is the main thing</u>
<u n="928" who="S0317">oh bless</u>
<u n="929" who="S0255">he's moving house this weekend</u>
<u n="930" who="S0317">oh is he? really?</u>
<u n="931" who="S0255">yeah yeah cos <trunc>y</trunc>you know he's in the flat at <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="932" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="933" who="S0255">erm he's decided he he doesn't want to be in a flat anymore cos he said there's people upstairs and downstairs with kids</u>
<u n="934" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="935" who="S0255">and he said yeah there's feet running about but he doesn't feel like he can ever turn his music up a little bit at night time <trunc>w</trunc> cos the kids'll probably be in bed</u>
<u n="936" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="937" who="S0255">and he said you go up and down the stairs and there's doors banging and</u>
<u n="938" who="S0317">oh no</u>
<u n="939" who="S0255">so he's erm he's found a place out at <anon type="place"/> you know just the other side of <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="940" who="S0317" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="941" who="S0255">three-bedroom house</u>
<u n="942" who="S0317">uhu</u>
<u n="943" who="S0255">erm yeah it's got so it's got a garage which he wants for his cars</u>
<u n="944" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="945" who="S0255">and to be able to tinker on his car it's got a <trunc>g</trunc> a garden and drive and all that so</u>
<u n="946" who="S0317">ah brilliant</u>
<u n="947" who="S0255">yeah so he's he's er sorting that out he's gonna be moving Saturday</u>
<u n="948" who="S0317">oh wow</u>
<u n="949" who="S0318" trans="overlap">blimey</u>
<u n="950" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="951" who="S0317">cor it's all <unclear>grown up</unclear> isn't it?</u>
<u n="952" who="S0255">I know</u>
<u n="953" who="S0317">what happened to our babies?</u>
<u n="954" who="S0255">I know that's what I was thinking like your two they've gone off haven't they? uni</u>
<u n="955" who="S0317">yeah yeah we went to see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't we last weekend?</u>
<u n="956" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="957" who="S0317">cos it's his birthday this weekend</u>
<u n="958" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="959" who="S0317">erm but he's off to his girlfriend's and we went last last Sunday and took him out for Sunday lunch and</u>
<u n="960" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="961" who="S0317">so he's having a ball absolutely having a ball</u>
<u n="962" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah oh that's good</u>
<u n="963" who="S0317" trans="overlap">funnily enough out out of the two of them I thought <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would be the one who would be the partying and what have you</u>
<u n="964" who="S0255" trans="overlap">party <trunc>pa</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="965" who="S0317">and that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would be the</u>
<u n="966" who="S0255">quite studious</u>
<u n="967" who="S0317" trans="overlap">no I'm twenty-three I don't do things like that</u>
<u n="968" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="969" who="S0317"><vocal desc="laugh"/> other way round <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="970" who="S0255" trans="overlap">really? yeah well I've seen <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has put on all things about she's what is it? she sprained her back</u>
<u n="971" who="S0317">yeah had a phone call</u>
<u n="972" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="973" who="S0255">Sunday Sunday night?</u>
<u n="974" who="S0318">yes</u>
<u n="975" who="S0317" trans="overlap">from her friend</u>
<u n="976" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="977" who="S0317">hello Mrs <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> this is whatever her name is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friend we're just taking her to casualty</u>
<u n="978" who="S0255" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="979" who="S0318">don't worry</u>
<u n="980" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="981" who="S0317">oh god</u>
<u n="982" who="S0318">I don't want you to worry but</u>
<u n="983" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah and it's not like they're twenty miles up the road</u>
<u n="984" who="S0317" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="985" who="S0255">Wales is a fair way isn't it?</u>
<u n="986" who="S0317">and this was oh probably about quarter to nine nine-ish on Sunday night</u>
<u n="987" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="988" who="S0317">something like that I'm thinking I've had a drink</u>
<u n="989" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="990" who="S0317">I can't drive yet</u>
<u n="991" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="992" who="S0317">oh my god what are we going to do?</u>
<u n="993" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="994" who="S0317">we'll have to ring you know we'll have to do this and then that that and it's</u>
<u n="995" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="996" who="S0317">four and a half hours and</u>
<u n="997" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="998" who="S0317">so <pause dur="short"/> yeah bless her</u>
<u n="999" who="S0255">yeah I must admit I've been watching all her her calamities</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0317" trans="overlap">makes me anxious</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0255">I loved your comment though when she said about erm she wasn't feeling very well and you said something about it being uni flu or freshers' flu</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0317">freshers' flu yeah go running home</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah gargle with alcohol</u>
<u n="1004" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1005" who="S0255">I thought that was brilliant</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0317">yeah they well know that when they they have freshers' week</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0317">they they all come down with what's <trunc>kno</trunc> what they all call freshers' flu</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0317">and it's because they're not sleeping they're drinking a lot</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0317">their diet's rubbish</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0317">and you're suddenly in close proximity</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0317">with people that you haven't so the germs come in</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0318">and they all come out</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0317" trans="overlap">and they all go down they all go down with colds</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah well it's like when they start school isn't it?</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0255">the the <trunc>ju</trunc> primary school and</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0317">it's a herd thing isn't it?</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0255">yeah this is it yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0317" trans="overlap">so yeah so yeah she she went down with that but yeah then her her back sort of kind of overtook her and her feet</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0255">yeah she's <trunc>hu</trunc>hurt her foot and yeah</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0318">she's a hypochondriac</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0317">she's on the right course</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0255">yeah yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> drama queen</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0317">oh yes</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0318" trans="overlap">the drama queen</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0317">oh yes</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah that's the same as <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1033" who="S0317">oh god</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0255"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'ll be telling you three days later about this little paper cut little paper cut on her finger look it's still really sore can you see it? you can just about see it look</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0317" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1036" who="S0255"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> walks in and only just mentions when you say why are you holding your neck? well I thought it was a neck injury at rugby but I didn't want them to get a stretcher so I jumped up and said it was fine and then I was running round the pitch thinking where am I going? and they took me off for a bit said I was a bit concussed but I got back on again</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0317"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1038" who="S0255"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s going it's a little paper cut can you not see? it's really sore bless her</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0317" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah that's a bit like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1040" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0317">yeah it's er saying that but no he's he's enjoying he's doing the foam parties and clubbing and drinking and</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0317">he was a bit hungover he was like four o'clock in the morning <unclear><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> called</unclear></u>
<u n="1044" who="S0318">yeah he wasn't exactly the brightest he's been</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0317" trans="overlap">he said <unclear/></u>
<u n="1046" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you're like hey happy birthday good to see you keep it down keep it down <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1047" who="S0317">so yeah bless him</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0317">but I'm glad he is cos when he when he went off I said to him <pause dur="short"/> don't be a twenty-three-year-old boring person</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no no no no</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0317">this is the only time you'll do this</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0255">yeah let your hair down</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0317">forget it let your hair down be a child go with it</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0255" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0317">and he's kind of taken it on board</u>
<u n="1056" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1057" who="S0255">yeah yeah you can never tell he's your son at all my dear I can never remember you doing anything like that</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0317">well cos you know neither of them really drank</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0317">at all he didn't</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0317">you know and I had I had to give <trunc>mu</trunc> erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a mummy talk</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0317">erm when she <trunc>p</trunc> and I said to her look I'm not saying don't drink</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0317">have a good time I said but</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0317">just remember you are not used to drinking</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0317">so you can't drink a couple of bottles of wine and some loads of <trunc>sh</trunc> vodka shots I said cos you could kill yourself</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well yeah that's right</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0317" trans="overlap">cos your body is not used to it</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0255" trans="overlap">or be in a situation you really don't want to be in because you can't you don't know what's happening and the next day you're thinking did something happen?</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0255" trans="overlap">you know yeah it's yeah</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0317">so you know I said you just need to be careful</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0317">you know to get to that level you have to kind of ease into it</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah ease yourself in gently</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0255">this is how you do it</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0317">so but she hasn't but I think it <pause dur="short"/> it threw her enough that she's not really drank she's drank</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0317">but she's not drank enough and she didn't drink for nearly a week after that little episode</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0255">yeah I mean I I <trunc>reme</trunc> she put that on Facebook I think cos somebody somebody bought her a drink of water didn't they? and somebody somebody said</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1087" who="S0255">oh say thank you to I can't remember who to say thank you to I can't remember what he looks like <vocal desc="laugh"/> bless her</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0317">so I think it sort of spooked her enough</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0317">that she's er she's not really I'm sure she she is drinking but she's not drinking to that point</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0255" trans="overlap">I think yeah I think most kids at somewhere between fourteen and twenty-four have that one time when they get so drunk that they are so ill and that actually does make them stop and think it doesn't mean they're not gonna get drunk doesn't mean they're not gonna get hangovers or be sick again or anything but they're actually just a little bit aware of you can't just throw it constantly down your throat cos actually your body's gonna go er no</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0317">I've had enough now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1093" who="S0255">yeah had enough yeah</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0317">but yes</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0317">but she she's home October</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0255">got half-term</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0317" trans="overlap">half-term yeah they've got a reading week there's only her course and another course out of the whole uni that have got the a reading week</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0255">okay</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0317">and most of them the others who although although they've got reading weeks they they're not allowed to leave the uni</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0255">really?</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0317">whereas she her course have been allowed to leave</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0317">so she's coming home</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0255" trans="overlap">you would've thought half-term they would have let people go</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0317">well a lot of unis don't have half-terms</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0255">oh don't they?</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0317">no it's not something</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0255" trans="overlap">oh right oh they have longer Christmas breaks and Easter breaks then yeah</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah she's <trunc>ho</trunc> she finishes the twelfth eleventh twelfth</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0317">whatever it is eleventh I think it is</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0317">erm so she'll come home on the twelfth of December and then she doesn't go back until I think they've got like four weeks</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0317">something like that so</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0255">suppose it makes sense cos people are coming from all over so to be going backwards and forwards for half-term and this holiday that holiday it makes sense to have a longer break</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0317">but er so no she's she's coming back but I won't see her cos I'm away</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0255">oh right? where are you doing?</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0317">I'm going to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1123" who="S0255">are you? god I spent my teenage years gowing up there</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0317" trans="overlap">Costa Costa Skeg</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0317"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1127" who="S0255">yeah yeah it's a lot better than Skeggy</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0317">oh it's lovely actually</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0317">it really is lovely and the beach there is gorgeous</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0255">yeah oh I know yeah</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0317">and now <unclear/> a bit it's er oh yeah it's my with my sewing ladies</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0317">it's our retreat</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0255">mm sounds nice</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0317" trans="overlap">I go and sew and drink and eat sew and drink and eat</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0317">sew and drink and eat really</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0318" trans="overlap">I've explained this to people at work and they don't understand</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0317">I know a lot of people look at me and go you do what?</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0255">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1142" who="S0318">my wife's going away for a week what's she gonna do? she's gonna go sewing</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0255">what?</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0317" trans="overlap">what for the whole week? er yeah</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0317">it's like alright</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0318" trans="overlap">it's like but what do they do really?</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0317">well what do you do in the evenings? sew</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0318">sew</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0255">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1151" who="S0317">what all day? what? pretty much</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0317">go into the early hours of the morning</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0317">there is a lot of eating and drinking and talking that goes along with it</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0317">and we do have a scream we have a ball</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0317">but yeah mainly sew <vocal desc="laugh"/> mm okay</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0255">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="1161" who="S0318">you should <trunc>ta</trunc> you should sign up for this recording thing <unclear/></u>
<u n="1162" who="S0317">oh no you'd never no you cos the whole tape you'd just be a cacophony of noise</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0255" trans="overlap">just cackling</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0317">yeah and a lot of cackling yeah</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0255" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1166" who="S0317">yeah cos we come from all over</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0318" trans="overlap">think of the hours you'd get though</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0317">you'd get a lot of hours</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0318" trans="overlap"><unclear>they'd all be</unclear> old people</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0317">well me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are the babies</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0255">mm so are these people that you know that you've got together with or people that have joined club and that's how you've got to know them?</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0317">it's kind of</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0318"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="1175" who="S0317">I I know them through <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1176" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0317">and it's been erm <pause dur="short"/> we've got a lady from <anon type="place"/> a lady from <anon type="place"/> and then the rest are from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1178" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0317">and some of them have come because they know other people that have joined sewing groups</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0317">or they've known them via other groups</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0317">that they've joined the the two ladies from <anon type="place"/> and and <anon type="place"/> they met one of the other ladies on a retreat cos you can go away for sewing weekends and stuff</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0317">they met erm years ago</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0317">and it's part of you know someone so I'm gonna bring my friend along and that</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0255" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0317">and that's how we've we've all kind of get together so we don't really see each other a lot</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0317">just when we go away and it's</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0255">how many of you are going?</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0317">there's eight of us</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0317">that go erm we used to be part of a bigger group and it got up to about fifteen</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0317">but it was too many and they start getting</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0317">you know factions and then there's little cliques and then they start getting bitchy and</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0317">it just got all too much <trunc>har</trunc> like hard work and I just said I'm not gonna bother doing that again I'm not</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0317">you know it took away the fun</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0255">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0317">of doing it so</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0318">just got rid of all the bitchy people</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0317">so a few of us went</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0317">well let's do it ourselves and start again</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0317">but we'd made a a a decision that it will be the eight and only the eight</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0318">yeah</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0317">and if any others come because they're going away again in March</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0317">I can't go for the whole time</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0317">erm but they're not gonna like put somebody whereas the other group</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0317">would put somebody else in oh my friend'll come great you know whereas this one it's like</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah so you've got the set people</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0317" trans="overlap">we either all go or</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0317">it'll be however many can go</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0255">yeah that's nice yeah</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0317" trans="overlap">so we don't erm</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0255"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying next year look at maybe doing a weekend away</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0255">go and do something erm she was saying round us all up and stuff and I said</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0255">well yeah but she said not this year</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0255">but maybe next year look at doing something</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah is she alright? I haven't seen her for ages</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0317">I see her pictures on Facebook and I keep</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0255">I know yeah you keep looking yeah</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0317" trans="overlap">I stalk her on Facebook every now and again but other than that I've not</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah erm she's been sent down to be tested to see if she's eligible or suitable for erm it's it's something it's like a spinal erm <pause dur="short"/> energising something something or other gives a <trunc>si</trunc> just signals to the spine</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0255">er to the spinal column and should help her with all the pain and the problems she's getting but erm the doctor that's recommended her to go down for it has said I don't know at all if you're eligible but some of the things that we've got here look like that sort of thing they the that is known to help but you if you go down and get assessed it may be just no or it may be something</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0317" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0255">and then you have to look and think if you want to have it done</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0255">erm so she's gonna go that's <anon type="place"/> way she's going to go and have a look at that</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0317" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0255">yeah and she's erm <pause dur="short"/> she's been referred to be for an urgent hysterectomy as well so she's having</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0317" trans="overlap">oh right is she? oh bless her</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0255">yeah having problems with that so she's been a bit but she's lost loads of weight she's sort of she put a load on again I mean the drugs don't help her cos she has to take</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0317" trans="overlap">I was gonna say yeah she takes a lot of drugs doesn't she bless her?</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0255" trans="overlap">she takes so many yeah erm but then she gets as soon as she gets back on Slimming World and she just started doing all that again and</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0255">she's lost a lot of weight again but</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0317">cos that'll make a lot of difference to her back</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0317">but if you're taking the drugs it's difficult</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0255">yeah I think she struggles a bit to be honest</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah oh bless her</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0255">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0317">mm so <trunc>you</trunc>you're not about at Christmas then to do a a famous Christmas</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0317"><unclear>carolling</unclear> Christmas thing</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0255">no no because erm</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0317"><unclear>we'll have to</unclear> do it the New Year when it's boring</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0317">you know that horrible miserable part in the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1266" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah end up doing doing something</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0255">trouble is though <trunc>r</trunc>right through the ski season we'll probably be out there in the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1269" who="S0317" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1270" who="S0255">but once we get through the spring thing we will</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0255">I said that to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos he's working away in <anon type="place"/> at the moment</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0317">mm mm</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0255">erm and he's done a I mean he might be back Saturday he's not sure if he's even gonna be back this weekend and the next few weekends so normally I'd do it end of November cos everyone gets December gets busy</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0255">and I usually say right let's have this meal and do</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0255">but he's probably not gonna be here well he won't be here so there's no point</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0317" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0255">no point doing it and there's December he's away first week in erm a course in Manchester</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0317">mm mm</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0255">and then he's here for a week then but he's working at <anon type="place"/> and getting ready to go out back out to France so he's gonna be buying loads of bits and</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0317">right</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0255">er stuff to take out and getting everything</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah does he drive out then or?</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0255">yeah he's gonna go out er with two mates they've gone out a couple of times with him erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="1287" who="S0317">takes a while to get there though doesn't it? cos it's well right</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah it's about eleven or twelve hours door to door that's on Eurostar but we've got one of them that one of the guys that goes out we've got him on the insurance</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0317">right</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0255">for the van so they take it in turns for driving</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0317">oh that's alright then</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0255">and then erm yeah we'll drive back we'll probably leave the van out there all season we we might do</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0255" trans="overlap">I'm not sure we left it out for a while last time</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0255">and then just flew back and left it</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0317" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1298" who="S0255">yeah and drive it back again</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0255">but then you sort of think oh you know obviously <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> needs something to drive when he's here</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0255">so we're umming and ahhing whether to get a vehicle out there but it's all the expense of a second vehicle do we do that or do we just keep that out there I don't know</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0317">I don't suppose hiring for all a long time</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0255">no that would be quite expensive really</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0255">so <pause dur="short"/> yeah we've got the Porsche but you don't really want to take that out when it's winter</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0317">not really not really snowing <unclear>kind of</unclear> vehicle is it?</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0318" trans="overlap">not really a snow car is it?</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0255">no exactly no</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0317" trans="overlap">it's a sunny car that one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1312" who="S0255">yeah it is yeah so I don't know we'll see I mean last year we took it out and we left it out there for quite a while</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0255">flew back and forth and then just took it back again</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0255">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was out there most of the time cos he didn't have that much work so he was out a lot and I was backwards and forwards</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0255">whereas this year I think he's gonna be busier whereas I'm I'm planning to get out at weekends even if he's not gonna be around I my plan is I'm gonna get out there and do weekends</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0255">anyway</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0255">erm and then he'll come out or I'll stay out for a week and then he'll come out and join me</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0318" trans="overlap">is it all is it all sorted now you said you've done the kitchen and is there much more to do?</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0255">erm yeah well the bathroom I think we we're umming and ahhing about doing that cos we'd quite like to get a washing machine in there</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0255">otherwise we have to go down to the laundrette at the bottom erm</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0317">I've seen you've got a little</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0317">even if it's only a little one cos you get small ones can't you?</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0255">yeah yeah that's it but it's just umming and ahhing how to do it cos there's a a shower over the bath but it's a really really good shower so at the moment we're thinking we're not gonna change that that'll be probably next summer if we're going to do something</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0255">we'll do that we want to put some wood flooring or something down but again we we haven't done that yet and we're gonna wait and see and decide what we're doing</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0255">we need to change the heating there erm so there's a few bits and bobs really and paint it through but that again will probably spring time after it</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0317">I was gonna say you need to do that when the <unclear>thaws</unclear> happen don't you I suppose?</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0255">yeah yeah this is it</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0317">ah lovely</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0255">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0317">what's up with you? feed me I'm starving</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0318">he looks like a starving cat doesn't he?</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah he does doesn't he?</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0255">he's wasting away</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0317">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah so is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doing alright still? cos she's at the <anon type="place"/> isn't she now?</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> really doing well yeah she's at really really enjoys it</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0317" trans="overlap">she settled alright?</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0255">sorry?</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0317">she settled alright?</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0255">yeah yeah really enjoys it erm gets on really well with all the team et cetera erm and her boss actually said to her a few weeks back there's going to be some deputy EO positions coming up</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0317">oh right</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0255">I'm just telling you now so you can be ready I I recommend you go for it I think you you'd be really good and</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0317">uhu</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0255">so she just put in for that there's four or five positions</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0317" trans="overlap">oh excellent</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0255">so she's just applied and shown an interest in that</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0318">excellent</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0255">but what she says she wants to do she doesn't want to end up being an EO like team leader</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0255">but she's quite happy to do the deputy side but she wants to get into she said there's there's like the fraud department</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0255">which she said looks really interesting</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0255">when they did the <trunc>in</trunc> er the initial training they were talking about the different departments people came in and told them what was going on and she said the fraud thing just sounded so interesting and there's so many different departments there's there's one that does all the forces stuff and there's one that does this and one that does that</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0255">so she but she said that looked really good so for her she said she'll try and get this deputy thing do that for a while and then from that look at going into</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0255">you know one of the other departments</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0318">fraud</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0255">yeah that's it she said that looks really interesting and that <unclear>I mean</unclear> that would be what I would do</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0255">looking and checking and sorting and et cetera so <pause dur="short"/> yeah so she's really really enjoying though really enjoying it</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0317">no plans to move out then? she's happy</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0255">no no no why would why would she want to go anywhere? as she keeps saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1373" who="S0317" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> happy at home</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0255"><trunc>oh</trunc> her view is you know she's not had a serious boyfriend before and and as and when she's at at some point she said there's people that are interested in me now but I'm not really interested in them</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0255">there's people that I know would just want to have bit of fun but I'm not interested in that</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0255">she said at some point I'll meet someone and hopefully that'll be the person I'll settle with we'll have a relationship and that'll be that if it doesn't work then you know somebody else will but she said I'm not gonna jump about but she said as and when I'm with somebody then I'd see we will get a place together and until then she said I don't want to move out I'm quite happy and I suppose that's fair enough you know</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0317">ah cool</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0255">fair enough when you draw your pension we'll tell you maybe then you should have gone by now but</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0318">mm</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0317">when she draws her pension she'll be looking after you</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0255" trans="overlap">to be fair <pause dur="short"/> she will to be fair she looks after <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when we're not there</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0255">you know and and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> looks after her so it works well</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0255">and she's she's quite happy flying round doing all her skating and</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0317">yes yes</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0255">yeah skating work and and cos where she's working it's flexi time so that works for her ideal</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0255">she'll get up in the morning go and have a skating lesson at seven and finishes at eight and rather than having to rush off and get to work for quarter to nine like she used to</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0255">she might think actually I'm gonna stay on for another half an hour to an hour and and finish and then go into work a bit later</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0317">right</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0255">or she can think alright I've had enough now and just go straight into work so</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0255">she said it it works really well</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0317">excellent</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0255">it works really well</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0317">brilliant</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0317">I'm glad she's got the skating anyway</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0255">yeah yeah she's a she's a</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0317">is she still doing erm erm</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0255">Rainbows?</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0255">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah she is she's she had a bit of a spell being a bit fed up with it cos she she hates doing the accounts</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0255">she doesn't like doing all the admin side that's not her at all</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0317" trans="overlap">no they're a pain a hassle</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0255">yeah erm and she's always struggling to <trunc>fi</trunc> try and find a leader or another leader so she can get more girls and blah blah blah and</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0255">you get the young leaders which are fine but you know like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1414" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0255">they're going off to uni you get them</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0255">for that little <trunc>ti</trunc> which is fine that's what that's part of their</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0255">yeah what they're doing and that's fine and and she just has this huge waiting list because there's not one in <anon type="place"/> there's not one in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1420" who="S0317" trans="overlap">no so there's not many about is there?</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0255">no and she said most of the girls are from <anon type="place"/> at the moment</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0317">oh right</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0255">erm yeah but she says it's phases there were most from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1424" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0255">and now it's loads from <anon type="place"/> so she said you know it does turn around</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0255">she does enjoy doing it every time she sort of says about oh I might stop doing it and</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0255">but then she sort of says but not yet cos I do enjoy doing it and</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0255">yeah so she does</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0317">cool</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0255">oh yeah she does</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0318">you know when you've had enough of doing that sort thing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1435" who="S0255">yeah it's like you with the cadets wasn't it? you</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0318">yeah</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0318">although I might be going back mightn't I?</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0317">yeah but you're not gonna go back as a <pause dur="short"/> officer are you? CO thingymebobby are you?</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0318">no</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0317">squadron officer that's what I was looking for</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0317">don't go out</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0255">he said no I'm just sat looking through the window</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0317">no he does that yeah</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1449" who="S0317">it's when it's raining I'll open the door and he'll look out of it</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0318" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1451" who="S0317">and he'll go I'm not going out and he'll go to a different door and it's like it's raining outside of that one as well as this one</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0255" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh that's funny <pause dur="short"/> so what might you be going back doing?</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0318">I dunno I I was talking to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about it and I needed the break</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0318">erm and but I've <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to give it up completely cos it's a fantastic organisation</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0318">and I do get a lot out of it</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0318">erm <pause dur="short"/> I do miss it a bit er but I don't miss being in charge of the squadron so</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0318">I just emailed the guy who's in charge of of the area the wing and said I'm interested in coming back I don't want to be a squadron CO I've done that for five years thanks</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no yeah</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0318">did quite well <pause dur="short"/> I'd rather do something else so I can either come back and just be an a squadron officer er on the squadron</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0255">mm mm</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0318">but <trunc>I</trunc>I've you know I don't want to be in charge so erm the <trunc>er</trunc> but and there's a risk you know that because of my work I'm unlikely to be able to get very far away from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1466" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0318">so that kind of <trunc>re</trunc> I don't want to go back to one one five</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0318">but I said I could do you know but that restricts me really to fifty-one which is the <anon type="place"/> squadron</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0318">or at a push possibly <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1472" who="S0317" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1473" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0318">five eleven which I know the lady that's running that one is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we used to <trunc>wo</trunc> we used to be in one one five and I get on well with her so</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0318">so that might be a possibility so I could go there I said or if you if you wanted me to do something at wing level which is like a a more of a staff post</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0318">and it's more likely to be <pause dur="short"/> it's not you're not committed to the same evenings</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah the timing it yeah</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0318">and it's more likely to be weekends</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0255" trans="overlap">cos you'd probably struggle with that yeah</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0318">than it is</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0318">evenings so</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0318">but I <trunc>le</trunc>I emailed him left a message and er he rung me last night and said do you want to meet up for a chat in London on next week</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0318">so we're meeting on Wednesday</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0318">and we'll have a chat I'll see what he's got to say really</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0318">I I said that</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0317">you quite like the training role though wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0318">yeah I would cos there's there's a training team</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0318">and doing something with the training team would probably be good cos that's down at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1497" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0318">which is where they're based now and so but that's not too far away</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0317" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0318">that's only about forty-five minutes erm and at the weekend that wouldn't be a problem</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0255">mm that's it if you go and say the ideas of what you want to do I I think if you started doing just going in as some sort of officer er to somewhere once a week I think cos you'd actually run one you'd either you'd be seeing how things are doing you'd you'd be almost like stepping up without meaning to because you're so used to doing it</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0318" trans="overlap">I think you're right</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0255">and you've got the once a week every single night you have to be back from <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="1504" who="S0317" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0318" trans="overlap">have you been coaching her?</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0255">has <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said all this?</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0317" trans="overlap">I haven't I haven't said a word and I haven't said had this conversation with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at all</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="1509" who="S0318">well you're right you're right <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're right I mean and that is the that is the worry and the I I <trunc>wo</trunc> sort of thing I'll be saying is the concern is that if I go into a squadron</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0317">it's that expectation as well because he's been so <trunc>succe</trunc></u>
<u n="1511" who="S0318" trans="overlap">that expectation</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0317">you know the success he had before maybe</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0318" trans="overlap">I've been successful</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0317">looking at you doing it with them</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0318">yeah</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0318">they'll be thinking oh wow we've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he you know was like erm</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0318">wing field champions and</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0318">this champions and that <trunc>champ</trunc> and it wasn't all down to me it was a team effort</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0318">erm and <pause dur="short"/> and I don't want that pressure you know?</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no and also</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0318">or or I'll go somewhere and they'll go oh he's arrived so you can take over now erm or</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0318">they'll be so so crap that it that I'll feel compelled to do it</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0318">cos it's so shit</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0255">or you can have somebody sort of keeping it all to themselves and not letting you get involved as in no no no I'm running this and almost like</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0318">well yeah</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0318">I don't I yeah I I don't think that would happen so I'm not cos there</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0317" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0318">as I say there's a limit on the the squadrons I could do anyway I mean the other thought was I could in theory go to a squadron that's local to where I'm working</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0317">right</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0318">but then</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0317">different wing though is it?</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0318">no no it's</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0317" trans="overlap">oh same wing is it?</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0318"><unclear/> through cos you've got <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> and</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0317">yeah <anon type="place"/> yeah <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1544" who="S0255" trans="overlap">all those places round there so</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0255">if if you're doing something once a week on a week night that means you've got to be in a certain place by a certain time</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0318">yeah</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0255">whether that's more local to here</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0318" trans="overlap">and also that makes you you have a long day then don't you? cos you don't get any break at all which</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah no</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0318">you know if I if I was doing that I'd be going to work in the morning working all day and then</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0318">staying late because it doesn't start till seven then going to where you would go er it'd be like on the way home let's say it was <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1554" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0318">cos there's a squadron there or <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> squadron</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0318">which is near the <pause dur="short"/> airship sheds at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1558" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0318">erm <pause dur="short"/> you know you go there and then you're not home till <pause dur="short"/> ten thirty eleven o'clock I'd only want to do that one night a week</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0318">and then I'd I I kind of get the impression that I'd get bored I'd get fed up with that pretty quick</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0318">and also if if that particular day like you say</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0318">I've got to be in London I've got to go somewhere else with work</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0318">then I'm not doing it at all so</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0318">how's that gonna work out? so I the I I'm er I'm more attracted to and I'm hoping he wants me to do something at a more senior level in</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0318">in the wing training team or <unclear>something like that</unclear> so</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0255">well the thing is is if you go <trunc>i</trunc>in and say the ideas of what you do and think and want to do and there's nothing actually at the minute it might be six months before something comes up</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0255">but rather than get stuck into a squadron somewhere and be doing something that actually you're gonna end up in a year or or <trunc>s</trunc> time saying I don't want to do this anymore cos it's just how it was before</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah exactly yeah</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0255">yeah just wait you know you've got Christmas and <unclear>winter</unclear></u>
<u n="1580" who="S0318" trans="overlap">well I've said I'm I've said it won't be until New Year anyway</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0318">I don't want to come back now</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0318">so it'll be in the New Year</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0255">cos you need to go and buy all <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s Christmas presents and that's very time consuming</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0318" trans="overlap"><unclear>and erm</unclear></u>
<u n="1587" who="S0317">it is</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yes absolutely</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0317">takes him hours</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0318">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah so yeah that might happen don't know</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0317">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0318" trans="overlap">I don't know</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0318">I could go to Cyprus couldn't I?</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0255">are there cadets in Cyprus?</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0318" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1598" who="S0317">they went out to erm Ascension Islands as well didn't they?</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0318">yeah but you have to be special to get out there</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0317" trans="overlap">well if you're on wing</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0255">oh</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0318">I'm not that special</u>
<u n="1603" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1604" who="S0318">I'm like a hill climber</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0318" trans="overlap">you have to be one of the A T crowd</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0317">are you not one of the?</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0318">no</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0317">the in crowd</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0318">but erm</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0255">you'll have to see what comes to you</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0318" trans="overlap">it's funny like this time last year <pause dur="short"/> erm I was I can remember having a conversation that you wouldn't catch me doing anything at wing level no I wouldn't do that</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0318">well why would I want to do that? couldn't see it <pause dur="short"/> but it's funny how you change</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0317">well it's what suits you at what</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0318">at the time</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0317">at the time isn't it really?</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0317">so</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0318">so we'll see</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0318">but I do miss it what I you know as somebody was saying to me that you you know do you are you missing it? I don't I miss the social side of it you know the fact that you er you <pause dur="short"/> get <trunc>frie</trunc>friendly with people don't you?</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0318">become your mates so you've got this group of people you know</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0318">and then you're not seeing them anymore</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0318" trans="overlap">so I miss that I miss the <trunc>ki</trunc> the kids as well cos</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0318">they do they are so energising some of them</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0318">and they're so full of <pause dur="short"/> fun and life</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0318">it does make you it does cheer you up you'd have to be a real miserable git not to</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0318">not to get cheered up by them <pause dur="short"/> so I miss that and I miss some of the stuff some of the stuff we did was pretty cool you know?</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0318">flying in helicopters <pause dur="short"/> pretty cool stuff wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0318">yeah</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0318">sitting in <pause dur="short"/> sitting in sitting in the pilot seat of a <trunc>je</trunc> a Boeing seven seven five seven hanging out the window</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0317"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1651" who="S0318">erm playing with guns</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0318">all that sort of stuff not so sure about that camping under a canvas sheet in a bush</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0317" trans="overlap">no you never were very fond of that one was you?</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0318">not really into that whole green thing</u>
<u n="1656" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1657" who="S0317">how to survive with a billy can</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0318">yeah you see that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> loved all that</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0317" trans="overlap">a plastic thin bag</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0318"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> loved all that he loves all the field craft stuff where go out and you've gotta <trunc>s</trunc> you know you've got all your gear</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0317">survival</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0318">survive the weekend feel the pressure</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0318">sort of like erm <pause dur="short"/> you know you've all your shelter and stuff and then you've got to heat up heat up your food <pause dur="short"/> in the old hexi stove and</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0318" trans="overlap">boil in a bag rice and in your billy can</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0255" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0318">but it's all really cold</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0317">you preferred four star hotels four poster bed</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah that's who it is</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0317">white linen sheets and a</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0318">no if I have to be anywhere I'll do it</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0317">and a three course meal served to you with a bottle of wine</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0255">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0318" trans="overlap">if I had to <trunc>s</trunc> if I had to rough it if I had to rough it I'll rough it in the officers' mess</u>
<u n="1676" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1677" who="S0318">I mean that's bad enough the beds aren't very nice in that place the mattresses are very thin they're usually collapsed you know</u>
<u n="1678" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1679" who="S0318">so and they're very spartan</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0255">food's good though</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0318">the transit accommodation is pretty pretty rubbish in those places</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0318">but yeah the food's alright</u>
<u n="1684" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1685" who="S0318">and the bar's good bar's always good</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0318">and the bar is incredibly cheap</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0318">I'll have a pint of beer my man</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0318">that'll be eighty pence please really?</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0318"><trunc>re</trunc> hang on let me buy everyone a drink</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0255">I'm trying to remember where we went we went to a ball <pause dur="short"/> was that a ball you came to? I don't I can't even remember who it was we went with and it was somewhere and it was in it must have been in some <trunc>R</trunc>RAF place but it wasn't like the RAF but it was somebody I don't know how it worked but anyway but we had like the mess bar</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0318">no</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0318">it's <trunc>j</trunc> you just reminded me of something else though</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0255">we had the mess bar but it you sort of going up and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was going up ordering rounds and no I don't think it was you cos <trunc>e</trunc> it it was we went as <trunc>gue</trunc> we knew it was either <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or somebody that we knew and it was their friends so I was a case of yeah</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0255">just as we went like that and it was a case of going up there and ordering brum brum brum brum brum brum brum and then it was</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0318" trans="overlap">cheap yeah</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0255">sort of four <trunc>pou</trunc></u>
<u n="1704" who="S0318">four pound fifty please</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0255">four pound something and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> kept coming back going</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0318" trans="overlap"><unclear>seventy pence</unclear></u>
<u n="1707" who="S0255">and then he kept being again and every time he went it was a different price that was the other thing as well</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0317" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1709" who="S0255">it went up and down a bit for the same round of drinks each time it was either fifty P more or <trunc>thir</trunc>thirty P less or some yeah towards the end of the night it got cheaper and cheaper so it was just oh right okay then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1710" who="S0318">I was gonna say and what does you <trunc>m</trunc> that prompted me to <trunc>s</trunc> was that</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0318">you went and flew in the Dakota</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0255">oh yes I went and flew in a Dakota <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ha</trunc></u>
<u n="1714" who="S0318">at the Britain <trunc>fly</trunc> memorial flight</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0255" trans="overlap">I did yes</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0318">and I was very jealous</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0317">he went home the other day didn't he?</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0318">I was very jealous</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah a lot of people were</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0318" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0255">a lot of people are</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0318">I've been in the Dakota</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0318">and sat in the cockpit</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0318">but I've not actually flown it</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0255">no we went up to the cockpit when it was flying we were just going over <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1729" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0317" trans="overlap">oh wow</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0255">and I was like going oh look there's <anon type="place"/> and there's yeah but yeah it was absolutely amazing and cos we had the the Spitfire flew one the wing</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0255">and it went under the other wing and that was because the erm the people the family of the guy that flies the Spitfire they were actually on the the sortie that we were on</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0317">oh</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0255">so that was why he <trunc>we</trunc> nobody else had the Spitfire apart from us</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0318">lucky lucky</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0255">oh I tell you it was <trunc>abso</trunc> and I touched the Lancaster cos we got pictures of me touching the Lancaster</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah we've done that</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0317">yeah we did that in <unclear/> stick around in the <unclear/> haven't we?</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0317">taking photos and stuff</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah we could've gone in that and looked but because it was all set up ready to fly <trunc>c</trunc> we weren't allowed to go in it but</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0317">ah</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0255">but I'm like can I just touch it? can I can I can I just touch it? and that was with you you remember <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> from the ball?</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0255">yeah cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s obviously Battle of Britain</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0255">engineer or whatever so yeah it was a open day at RAF <anon type="place"/> er a family day rather so every you went on there was all this stuff going on</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0255">and stands and stalls but the people that were with the Battle of Britain memorial people were in that separate bit</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0318">yeah</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0255" trans="overlap">and nobody else was allowed to come through that apart from us so we were all in there and we were the ones that were allowed to go and have the flights in the Dakota</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0317">mm wow</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0255">and we had erm like they were doing tours round</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0255">inside the hangar with all the the planes but obviously <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just said ah come on you know and he just took us in and there's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I got pictures of <trunc>ne</trunc> Spitfires and <trunc>ha</trunc> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1760" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1761" who="S0317">yeah we we were lucky weren't we? with the cadets we got up close and personal</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0317">we'd be on the other side of the rope <trunc>sa</trunc> oh you</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that's it</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0317">all the public were behind the rope and we were this side of it</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0318">it was quite cool yeah</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0318">all the cadets were allowed to go</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0317" trans="overlap"><unclear>you've got an advantage</unclear></u>
<u n="1771" who="S0255">well exactly yeah I <trunc>w</trunc>well I mean flying in the Dakota it was just</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0317" trans="overlap">it's who you know isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0255">it was humbling really was cos you're sat there all strapped in and we they'd got the headphones for some of us so that the you know</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0255">go and listen to the headphones you could hear what was being said but it's just that drone that you hear</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0255">and it when you watch the the films on telly you know the war planes going and everyone's sat in it <unclear/> in the back of it and it actually it felt like that it was vibrating and you just thought those poor lads that were just sat in it going off and</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0318" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0255"><unclear/> they sat in it you know we <trunc>o</trunc> we obviously did a a loop we were up for about twenty minutes but you think god just imagine being in it and going and</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0318">mm</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0255">and there's actually the some of the graffiti when they were cleaning it and doing it</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah inside</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0255">they found graffiti inside that they wrote when they went and it's just like wow</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0317">amazing</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0255">yeah it was amazing</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0317"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1788" who="S0255" trans="overlap">it really was <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0318">my last little trip was in erm a Lynx wasn't it? we did a a Lynx trip that we had to load of cadets <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> went to <anon type="place"/> we took them to <anon type="place"/> and we had the army air corps that flew into <anon type="place"/> got permission from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1790" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0318">we arranged it for them to come <trunc>o</trunc> cos the army for some reason the <trunc>ar</trunc> air force can't seem to do this but the army have got a Lynx a helicopter that's specially allocated to fly cadets</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0255">right</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0318">so you ring them up</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1795" who="S0318">and say hi I've got a load of cadets want to go flying in your helicopter</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1797" who="S0318">are you available on the fourteenth of August? and they go <pause dur="short"/> yeah well where are we coming to and they say have you got fuel?</u>
<u n="1798" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0318">and I say well if we go to this airbase they'll have fuel okay right</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1801" who="S0318">we'll sort that out fill in this form it's one a well easy form to fill in</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0318">send it back and we'll book it and you're like it can't be that easy</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0317">book it in French</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0318">but you know with the air force</u>
<u n="1806" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0318">it just doesn't happen you just</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0318">I don't understand why the air force can't do the same thing but the army appear to have he said what he did say was <pause dur="short"/> you know we are the aircraft is tasked to do this job but</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0318">obviously if something else comes up that's more important then you get binned</u>
<u n="1812" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1813" who="S0318">I said well that's a given you know</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0255">yeah that's right yeah need to go and invade China or something</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0318" trans="overlap">and erm</u>
<u n="1816" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1817" who="S0318" trans="overlap">we did erm <pause dur="short"/> we did er we arranged for cos we was at <anon type="place"/> last year and I was running the camp and <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> was a bit there's not a lot going on there it's a bit rubbish <pause dur="short"/> so we arranged for the helicopter to come in there</u>
<u n="1818" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1819" who="S0318">and er I'd rung this guy up and he said yeah we can do the the Tuesday I think he said we could do so so we hadn't told we said we won't tell the cadets</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0318">what we're doing because we don't want them to get them to get all excited and then it gets binned</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah something happens</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0318">cos you know weather's bad</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1825" who="S0318">aircraft goes US aircraft gets retasked happens all the time erm you know that's it it's you know you don't want to get them all worked up so we told them all</u>
<u n="1826" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0318">cos you have to print a programme of what we're doing for the week a sort of activity plan so we printed <trunc>i</trunc>in the afternoon it was a big cat adventure</u>
<u n="1828" who="S0255">mm mm</u>
<u n="1829" who="S0318">they were all like what's that?</u>
<u n="1830" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1831" who="S0318">a big cat adventure <pause dur="short"/> don't is that is that like <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1832" who="S0255">yes yes safari</u>
<u n="1833" who="S0318" trans="overlap">so they were all a lot of them were convinced it was <anon type="place"/> the safari park we're gonna go to the safari park big cat adventure</u>
<u n="1834" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="1835" who="S0318">so anyway on the Tuesday morning he rings me and says we've been retasked</u>
<u n="1836" who="S0255">ah no <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1837" who="S0318">he says I'm he says I'm ever so sorry but we some general is going somewhere and we're the backup aircraft</u>
<u n="1838" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1839" who="S0318">if the general's if his helicopter and the bloody general came to our place another Lynx helicopter landed on the <unclear/></u>
<u n="1840" who="S0255" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="1841" who="S0318">it was really annoying erm <pause dur="short"/> and er he said I can come on Wednesday if you want</u>
<u n="1842" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1843" who="S0318">I said <pause dur="short"/> I said well we're going to the museum at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> he said well I can come in the afternoon I'll come at four o'clock if you want</u>
<u n="1844" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1845" who="S0318">he said we'll fly them up until when it gets dark</u>
<u n="1846" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1847" who="S0318">and I'm like are you sure?</u>
<u n="1848" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1849" who="S0318">cos I'm thinking you would let the air force fly at four o'clock it's sleep time</u>
<u n="1850" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1851" who="S0317">it's time to go home don't you know</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0318" trans="overlap">time to go home</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0317">show me the mess</u>
<u n="1854" who="S0318" trans="overlap">so we're gonna so these guys were gonna fly from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1855" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1856" who="S0318">which is down in <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> you know it's like other side of <anon type="place"/> and they were gonna fly all the way over to <anon type="place"/> having refuelled somewhere and come to us at four o'clock in the afternoon to fly all the cadets into the evening and then fly all the way back</u>
<u n="1857" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1858" who="S0318">and we were like that's I was pretty impressed with that</u>
<u n="1859" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1860" who="S0318">so I said okay then so we yeah alright if you can do that he <trunc>s</trunc> he said yeah</u>
<u n="1861" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0318">yeah not a problem we'll do it we'll come tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> he said obviously I'll ring you in the morning I'll ring you tomorrow when</u>
<u n="1863" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah make sure you're not retasked or</u>
<u n="1864" who="S0318">so erm <pause dur="short"/> next day comes I'm on like tenterhooks and we we had to tell the kids</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1866" who="S0318">the big cat adventure was <pause dur="short"/> not this is what the big cat <trunc>ad</trunc> so we we arranged everything them going swimming and doing other things</u>
<u n="1867" who="S0255" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="1868" who="S0318">and then so we said so the big cat adventure was actually the Lynx helicopter but he's coming tomorrow so so so fingers crossed he's coming tomorrow</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0318">so sure enough we got a phone call erm interestingly enough one of the guys whose mate was erm one of the guys on the camp his mate was er he's involved in something to do with the radar</u>
<u n="1871" who="S0255">oh right</u>
<u n="1872" who="S0318">er a UK radar</u>
<u n="1873" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1874" who="S0318">so he can see what's going on all over the UK and he rang in rung in and said do us a favour and that it's can you see any Lynxes coming this way?</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1876" who="S0318">and he said yeah there is a Lynx coming in your</u>
<u n="1877" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1878" who="S0318">it's heading towards you I think that's the that's yours</u>
<u n="1879" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1880" who="S0318" trans="overlap">so we knew he was coming before he actually rang us</u>
<u n="1881" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah oh that's good yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1882" who="S0318">and then we and then we got in and did and he <trunc>ra</trunc> he flew <trunc>i</trunc> all the cadets</u>
<u n="1883" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1884" who="S0318">and there was about forty cadets</u>
<u n="1885" who="S0255">wow</u>
<u n="1886" who="S0318">he flew all of them <pause dur="short"/> and then he flew er all the staff</u>
<u n="1887" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1888" who="S0318">and then he even flew the glider squadrons based at <anon type="place"/> they were doing a training night that night a ground training flight and they all came and hung around</u>
<u n="1889" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0318">and he took them for a flight as well but the thing is they're all like adults</u>
<u n="1891" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1892" who="S0318">so they had one seat left and I'd already been up once with the cadets cos all <trunc>ea</trunc> one adult went up with the with a load of cadets</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> with each group yeah</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0318">and there was one space left on the on the flight the last flight of all these glider pilots on</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0318">and they said oh do you wanna you know do you wanna have another go? so I said yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'll have another go</u>
<u n="1897" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1898" who="S0318">and he proper threw it around</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> grown-ups</u>
<u n="1900" who="S0318">because they were <trunc>gro</trunc> all grown-ups</u>
<u n="1901" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1902" who="S0318">and they were all like pilots so he was like really wanging it around in the air and that's and then he said do you wanna we'll do a photograph</u>
<u n="1903" who="S0317">oh excellent</u>
<u n="1904" who="S0318" trans="overlap">he said we can either do a static on the ground or if you want we'll come and hover behind you so</u>
<u n="1905" who="S0255" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> that's lovely that is yeah I bet all the kids have got that and that's just</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0318" trans="overlap">it's not I mean it was getting dark so the light wasn't great but</u>
<u n="1907" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah oh even so yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0318">it was brilliant that and that is</u>
<u n="1909" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1910" who="S0318">that is so weird standing there and you got this huge the noise of the helicopter</u>
<u n="1911" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm yeah the</u>
<u n="1912" who="S0318">right behind you</u>
<u n="1913" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1914" who="S0318">the wind and everything and you <trunc>co</trunc> but don't turn round</u>
<u n="1915" who="S0255" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1916" who="S0318">yeah pretty special</u>
<u n="1917" who="S0255">been on that a few times haven't you? cos they came to <anon type="place"/> as well didn't they?</u>
<u n="1918" who="S0318">well that's the that the last that was the one at <anon type="place"/> and then I</u>
<u n="1919" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1920" who="S0318">I I've spoke to him again cos er <trunc>we</trunc>we well would you mind doing something next year and he said yeah just give us a call so like early in the year I rang him and we arranged it for it was in May I think wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1921" who="S0317">yeah just before you finished wasn't it I thought <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="1922" who="S0318" trans="overlap">it was the last one of the last things I did</u>
<u n="1923" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1924" who="S0318">went up and had a flight in the helicopter</u>
<u n="1925" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1926" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1927" who="S0318">it wasn't as exciting as the previous one at <anon type="place"/> though it was <unclear/></u>
<u n="1928" who="S0255">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1929" who="S0317"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1930" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1931" who="S0317">a lot of them have probably been on a lot more rides</u>
<u n="1932" who="S0318">no that was interesting cos we went to <anon type="place"/> and we'd set it all up for <anon type="place"/> and then on the we arrived on the day and erm they suddenly said oh we've got some of our new air traffic controllers</u>
<u n="1933" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> can they practise on you?</u>
<u n="1934" who="S0318" trans="overlap">they need they need a they need to have a flight in an aircraft <pause dur="short"/> around the base to get signed off</u>
<u n="1935" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1936" who="S0318">it's part of their signing-off process I don't know <unclear>what it is about</unclear></u>
<u n="1937" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1938" who="S0318">and we're like would you mind if they went on your helicopter that you've got? this is the air force asking us would you mind if we borrowed your helicopter?</u>
<u n="1939" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1940" who="S0318">I'm like <pause dur="short"/> I said well I said I don't mind as long as all the cadets get to fly first</u>
<u n="1941" who="S0255" trans="overlap">get their go yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1942" who="S0318">cos that's what we've arranged it</u>
<u n="1943" who="S0255">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="1944" who="S0318">yeah yeah that'll be right I'm thinking and I want a go as well so</u>
<u n="1945" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1946" who="S0318">so we worked it so that all of the staff got in</u>
<u n="1947" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1948" who="S0318">erm we said to the we said to the you know to the it was a bit we were a bit put out by the fact that they'd suddenly jumped four more people in</u>
<u n="1949" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm not impressed</u>
<u n="1950" who="S0318">but we <trunc>ma</trunc> we managed to pull it off</u>
<u n="1951" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1952" who="S0318">so we left to say we're doing <pause dur="short"/> one last flight for the the actual RAF so we did them a favour as well</u>
<u n="1953" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1954" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1955" who="S0318">so yeah but you don't get to do stuff like that do you?</u>
<u n="1956" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1957" who="S0318">anywhere else</u>
<u n="1958" who="S0255">no <pause dur="short"/> that's what it's all about</u>
<u n="1959" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1960" who="S0255">experience isn't it? getting those experiences</u>
<u n="1961" who="S0318">yeah</u>
<u n="1962" who="S0317">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="1963" who="S0255">that's the thing I I we're taking quite a lot of photos and stuff like that but even looking at the photos it's it's never going to replace what's in here inside</u>
<u n="1964" who="S0317">no</u>
<u n="1965" who="S0318">no it doesn't the actual feeling</u>
<u n="1966" who="S0255" trans="overlap">and it's yeah</u>
<u n="1967" who="S0318">the actual</u>
<u n="1968" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1969" who="S0318">yeah the experience is <trunc>un</trunc> is yeah</u>
<u n="1970" who="S0255">cos when I when I when I think about actually flying in that I can feel it all in my body again <trunc>i</trunc> how it felt to be sat and the vibrations and the noise and the air</u>
<u n="1971" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="1972" who="S0255">and it's a sensation and you you get that sensation again</u>
<u n="1973" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1974" who="S0318" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1975" who="S0255">yeah <pause dur="short"/> amazing</u>
<u n="1976" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1977" who="S0318">pretty cool</u>
<u n="1978" who="S0317">mm</u>
<u n="1979" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1980" who="S0317">yeah so I went</u>
<u n="1981" who="S0318">cos I used to one of the guys is er on the BBMF</u>
<u n="1982" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1983" who="S0318">er I was <trunc>pre</trunc> saying to your mate erm</u>
<u n="1984" who="S0255">to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1985" who="S0318"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> what's it what did they call him? they gave him a name didn't they? the snail or something like that</u>
<u n="1986" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah they gave him</u>
<u n="1987" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1988" who="S0318">slope or sloth sloth was it? I don't know some name they gave him</u>
<u n="1989" who="S0255" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1990" who="S0318">but he was I was I actually went into cadets in <anon type="place"/> with him</u>
<u n="1991" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1992" who="S0318">and he's ended up as a squadron leader flown Tornadoes for all of his career</u>
<u n="1993" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="1994" who="S0318">and he's flown for all of his career which is quite unusual</u>
<u n="1995" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1996" who="S0318">but you know from when he started he started as a <trunc>nav</trunc>navigator for Tornadoes</u>
<u n="1997" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1998" who="S0318">and stayed flying he always wore a flying suit and he's ended up this is kind of the end of his <pause dur="short"/> career is he's flying</u>
<u n="1999" who="S0255">I wore a flying suit</u>
<u n="2000" who="S0318">yeah</u>
<u n="2001" who="S0255">yeah did you see?</u>
<u n="2002" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="2003" who="S0255">not everybody did but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I decided we wanted to</u>
<u n="2004" who="S0317"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2005" who="S0255">well <trunc>y</trunc> they said cos you had to have long sleeves on arms and legs and stuff like that and it was really really hot so we went in shorts and t-shirts and took jeans and said oh we'll do that and then they started saying you have to have proper boot things and and then somebody came out and they were wearing the flying suit and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> why are they wearing that? why are they wearing that? well obviously they didn't have anything long legs and you've gotta have your legs covered <pause dur="short"/> oh well we certainly can't go back to the car which was sort of you know ten yards away we certainly can't go back to the car and get them can we <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? no no we need a flying suit we need a flying suit she goes so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sort of rolls his eyes oh yeah right come on then goes he takes us off can we please have two flying suits please for you know for these young ladies? and I need boots too yeah yeah yeah yeah so that's it and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s going oh can I keep it? can I keep it? and she's getting the helmet on and it's like oh this is mad absolutely mad</u>
<u n="2006" who="S0317" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="2007" who="S0255">no it was a really good day but that was back in July so that was when</u>
<u n="2008" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2009" who="S0255">I hadn't been off that long and I was just I was down the lake all the time cos it was</u>
<u n="2010" who="S0317" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="2011" who="S0255">lovely sunny weather <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was working away the caravan was down there and I just stayed down there the whole time just really stepped off the world and just thought you know</u>
<u n="2012" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="2013" who="S0255">and then she said oh do you you wanna do you wanna come? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> goes do you wanna go for a flight in the Dakota? and I was saying cos he said something about the Dakota and I was saying ah hang on I know what that is I know what that is it was in a film it was in a film and he was going what and I said hang on hang on and I was going Driving Miss Daisy no no that wasn't that that was a car and I said Memphis Belle and he's like yeah that's right and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s going oh my god you're gonna get brownie points now you're gonna get a better time than me cos you actually knew what it was I didn't know what it was she said</u>
<u n="2014" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2015" who="S0255">really funny but no I knew what the Dakota was <pause dur="short"/> yeah <trunc>he</trunc> yeah it was just amazing day beautiful weather as well so it was just</u>
<u n="2016" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah it was hot then wasn't it?</u>
<u n="2017" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2018" who="S0317">nice</u>
<u n="2019" who="S0255">it was nice</u>
<u n="2020" who="S0318">mm</u>
<u n="2021" who="S0317">we went we went to <anon type="place"/> we landed up in the <anon type="place"/> that we drank in Rapide</u>
<u n="2022" who="S0318">yeah the <unclear/> Rapide</u>
<u n="2023" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2024" who="S0317">and that was just like a go-kart really wasn't it? it was quite</u>
<u n="2025" who="S0318">it was an experience getting in that</u>
<u n="2026" who="S0317" trans="overlap">simple it was amazing</u>
<u n="2027" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2028" who="S0318">cos the floor <pause dur="short"/> it was like that it was <unclear/></u>
<u n="2029" who="S0317" trans="overlap">cos you you sat up here <vocal desc="laugh"/> so you sort of had to clamber up to the top</u>
<u n="2030" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2031" who="S0317">and they made you sit in certain places cos I had to level the weight out <pause dur="short"/> so we were right at the front weren't we? <pause dur="short"/> in the window</u>
<u n="2032" who="S0318" trans="overlap">yeah I was sat at on on the pilot's shoulder virtually</u>
<u n="2033" who="S0317">you were one side I was the other so we both had a window</u>
<u n="2034" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="2035" who="S0317">erm but yeah it was incredible</u>
<u n="2036" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="2037" who="S0317">we were like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="2038" who="S0255">yeah no I know</u>
<u n="2039" who="S0318">it was canvas thing wasn't it?</u>
<u n="2040" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="2041" who="S0318">by plane</u>
<u n="2042" who="S0255">mm that was</u>
<u n="2043" who="S0318"><vocal desc="yawn"/> it was pretty amazing</u>
<u n="2044" who="S0317">we was going home weren't we? and they leapt out last flight of the day we'll do it cheaper if you want to do it</u>
<u n="2045" who="S0255">yeah yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> but you can get I mean we we see these things and look at them and it's a real experience just to see them and to maybe get in them or or fly in them <pause dur="short"/> talking to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s sister <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's eighty-eight and I was chatting to her and saying oh yeah and I went and did this and this and oh yeah cos I worked on them in the war I was making these bits in that factory doing this and I was and then I was working on that and you think and you suddenly forget actually you know it was day to day life</u>
<u n="2046" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="2047" who="S0255">people were actually working on these building the maintaining them and and you don't forget that for me it was just like wow go and see it go in it or but actually for her it was her normal life working on on these planes</u>
<u n="2048" who="S0317" trans="overlap">yeah yeah mm mm</u>
<u n="2049" who="S0318">that reminds me I can remember my dad taking his dad grandad</u>
<u n="2050" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="2051" who="S0318">to er cos my grandad worked on the railways for years and years and years that was the big job he had was the railways and when we first moved up to <anon type="place"/> and <trunc>na</trunc>nan and grandad still lived in <anon type="place"/> erm obviously the <anon type="place"/> railway is a steam railway you know and so when they came up dad said oh oh I'll take you out to see the steam rail it's going to be nostalgic you know he'll like that you know he took him down there and he went bloody <trunc>sa</trunc> I bloody couldn't stand it bloody dirty horrible thing I hated it re re</u>
<u n="2052" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2053" who="S0318">oh okay</u>
<u n="2054" who="S0255">yeah so we look at things in a different way don't we? yeah mm</u>
<u n="2055" who="S0317">yeah</u>
<u n="2056" who="S0318">I need to sort my suit out for tomorrow</u>
<u n="2057" who="S0255">yeah I was just gonna say I need to I need to go home I'm helping <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> pack tomorrow he said it won't take long I haven't got a lot I thought you'd be surprised when you start emptying your cupboards and your you know you've got all these different bits and he said I've only got a few clothes yeah what about your kitchen stuff and your this and your that</u>
<u n="2058" who="S0318"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had a while trailer full of stuff</u>
<u n="2059" who="S0317">yeah and that was just in going into one room mind you we could've got it in the car if we'd have packed it better it was just the fact we were taking the bike which he's not used yeah I could've done</u>
<u n="2060" who="S0318">what with him as well?</u>
<u n="2061" who="S0317">yeah I could've packed it I didn't pack fully I could've packed it</u>
<u n="2062" who="S0318">you didn't do your Tetris thing?</u>
<u n="2063" who="S0317">no cos I knew we'd got the trailer so I didn't need to</u>
<u n="2064" who="S0255"><trunc>te</trunc> oh that's when you yeah spatial awareness I find that I can just put that and just do that and just like ooh yeah it's only when you open the doors the other end and everything flies out it's like catch</u>
<u n="2065" who="S0317">fall out yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
