<text id="SN97">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:30</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-06</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0282 S0283</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>At the speakers’ home in Frimley Green, Surrey</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Bulbs. Gardening. Gardening accidents. Cutting logs. IT connections. Parents. Gas bills</topics>
		<activity>Husband and wife talking about activities in the garden during their week off</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T06</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0282">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Stratford-upon-Avon</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>self employed</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0283">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Civil servant</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0282">how many bulbs did you buy in the end?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0283">I bought two hundred snowdrop bulbs and that's four different varieties of snowdrops fifty of each so I think we put them in the little verge at the front and I think we put them in clumps of about ten <pause dur="short"/> lots of about twenty of about ten just dotted around and then hopefully they'll all come up in the spring and hopefully they'll propagate or whatever the word is <pause dur="short"/> and then over time we'll just have a complete snowdrop lawn wouldn't that be lovely?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0282">that would be lovely what kind of snowdrops did you are they particular kinds?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0283">oh I can't remember some big some small some double some single <pause dur="short"/> don't know</u>
<u n="5" who="S0282">did you just go for quantity or did you go for the kind that are more attractive?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0283">no no the</u>
<u n="7" who="S0282" trans="overlap">because they're taller or double featured or whatever</u>
<u n="8" who="S0283" trans="overlap">no there were four different kinds that were on sale and I thought I'd get some of each of them</u>
<u n="9" who="S0282">and when are there are arriving?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0283">hopefully they are arriving in the next day or so</u>
<u n="11" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="12" who="S0283">so that's another task that we can <unclear/> by the end of the week</u>
<u n="13" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and do they have to go in straight away</u>
<u n="14" who="S0283">they don't have to go in straight away they do have to go in sooner rather than later</u>
<u n="15" who="S0282">I can't remember when we put bulbs in last year</u>
<u n="16" who="S0283">we tend to put them in quite late we tend to put them in in sort of November</u>
<u n="17" who="S0282">when it's dark and wet and cold</u>
<u n="18" who="S0283">when it's dark and wet and cold so this time we'll do in October when it's dark and wet and cold</u>
<u n="19" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="20" who="S0283">and the trees or the tree is arriving on Wednesday or Thursday</u>
<u n="21" who="S0282">and where are you going to put that?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0283" trans="overlap">almond tree <pause dur="short"/> I think we should put the almond tree slightly in front of the <pause dur="short"/> plum tree</u>
<u n="23" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="24" who="S0283">so under the underneath the apple tree</u>
<u n="25" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="26" who="S0283">it says you can't have it near a peach tree</u>
<u n="27" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="28" who="S0283">but we haven't got a peach tree so it doesn't really matter if you have it near a peach tree then they cross pollinate and your almonds taste of peaches</u>
<u n="29" who="S0282">no that that can't be true</u>
<u n="30" who="S0283"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well</u>
<u n="31" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that can't be true <pause dur="short"/> that doesn't make sense at all</u>
<u n="32" who="S0283">that's what it says on the internet and the internet never lies</u>
<u n="33" who="S0282">yeah right <pause dur="short"/> that can't be true <pause dur="short"/> we've got a nectarine tree but that's never done anything</u>
<u n="34" who="S0283" trans="overlap">no that's <pause dur="short"/> no I know but that's probably because it's too close to the almond tree <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0282">no it's never have almonds in it <pause dur="short"/> it's just never done anything because it's lazy or something I don't know or it's a boy tree or something</u>
<u n="36" who="S0283">anyway erm so yeah so the bulbs are coming this week and they're <pause dur="short"/> the tree is also coming this week I think the tree <pause dur="short"/> should go as I say slightly in front of the erm <pause dur="short"/> of the plum tree but it needs a lot of sun</u>
<u n="37" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="38" who="S0283">erm but that means that we can't have the soft fruit</u>
<u n="39" who="S0282" trans="overlap">unless we have it at the front of the lawn</u>
<u n="40" who="S0283">we could <pause dur="short"/> well it gets a lot of sun there</u>
<u n="41" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0283">er but it only gets sun until <pause dur="short"/> halfway through the day it doesn't get evening sun <pause dur="short"/> and we need to put <unclear/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0282" trans="overlap">is there anywhere that gets sun all day? <pause dur="short"/> I don't think there is</u>
<u n="44" who="S0283">probably not which is a bit of a pain isn't it?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0282">we've got such a big plot and yet there isn't a bit which does get sun all day</u>
<u n="46" who="S0283" trans="overlap">no I know erm <pause dur="short"/> and we also need to work out where to put the cherry tree</u>
<u n="47" who="S0282">which cherry tree?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0283">the cherry tree in the pot</u>
<u n="49" who="S0282">oh right okay I thought we were gonna put it where it stands?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0283">okay but it's so well no I thought erm that the almond tree might look might nice with the plum tree at the top of the garden <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but again that would mean that we'd need to move all soft fruit</u>
<u n="51" who="S0282">aren't we gonna put all the nuts together?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0283">what nuts have we got?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I thought we were going to put the nuts?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0283">what other nuts have we got?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0282">well walnut</u>
<u n="56" who="S0283">what walnut?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0282">the walnut down in that corner</u>
<u n="58" who="S0283">what walnut?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0282" trans="overlap">the one that got eaten by the date but no is it a walnut? no it's not a walnut no I didn't buy a walnut in the end because apparently it poisons everything within ten metres of it <pause dur="short"/> no sorry that was a mulberry tree I bought a mulberry tree in the end rather than a walnut tree <pause dur="short"/> no cos walnut trees are supposed to be really <pause dur="short"/> there is something about them that's quite toxic <pause dur="short"/> like rhododendrons</u>
<u n="60" who="S0283">okay</u>
<u n="61" who="S0282">well I don't know</u>
<u n="62" who="S0283">well we could we could put the <pause dur="short"/> almond tree down there with the apple tree and mulberry tree and the fig tree</u>
<u n="63" who="S0282">mm <pause dur="short"/> we could</u>
<u n="64" who="S0283">but erm but the apple tree's not done well down there</u>
<u n="65" who="S0282">no but I think that's <trunc>some</trunc> that's cos the deer ate <pause dur="short"/> its growing tips</u>
<u n="66" who="S0283">for anyone who's listening this isn't our own domestic deer this is a deer that walked in from the forest <pause dur="short"/> from the woods</u>
<u n="67" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what what think people think we've got a pet deer?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0283">well if there's <unclear/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0282" trans="overlap">have we got a pet deer?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0283">the deer ate the apple tree</u>
<u n="71" who="S0282">it's a passing deer</u>
<u n="72" who="S0283">yes <pause dur="short"/> it's a deer</u>
<u n="73" who="S0282">it's a itinerary itinerant deer</u>
<u n="74" who="S0283">yes <pause dur="short"/> anyway okay so yeah so so we're gonna put the bulbs in we also need to <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> I think dig up <pause dur="short"/> loads of rhododendron <pause dur="short"/> er up by the soft fruit <pause dur="short"/> I want to do a lot of weeding as well <pause dur="short"/> I think we need to get <trunc>re</trunc> get all the fern up</u>
<u n="75" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0283">erm and I'd like to thin out a lot of the weeds in the beds as well</u>
<u n="77" who="S0282">the weeds in the beds?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0283">at the back and at the front</u>
<u n="79" who="S0282">oh right okay is there a lot of weeds?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0283">yes</u>
<u n="81" who="S0282">oh no we need to tackles the trees though cos that sycamore is back <pause dur="short"/> by the rhubarb <pause dur="short"/> there's a stump right by the little engine room</u>
<u n="82" who="S0283" trans="overlap">when did you do that?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0282">and then I think I sprayed it so it's looking really black and twisted and horrible but it is never less persisting in growing lots and lots of little <pause dur="short"/> treelets off the big stump</u>
<u n="84" who="S0283">okay well we can kill those bastards</u>
<u n="85" who="S0282">and also I need to get up more trees <pause dur="short"/> because erm <pause dur="short"/> I said to the Woodland Trust that we would <pause dur="short"/> remove lots of saplings and I would take along about I said I'd take along about thirty <pause dur="short"/> oaks which I think we've got more or less <pause dur="short"/> thirty oaks but also various other things such as sweet chestnuts and beeches and <pause dur="short"/> erm what's the other thing?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0283">when's that on the second of December?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0282">er thirteenth of December something around there</u>
<u n="88" who="S0283">okay</u>
<u n="89" who="S0282">there's a planting of the <trunc>mil</trunc> of the centenary wood</u>
<u n="90" who="S0283" trans="overlap">and who is going to be actually doing the planting?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0282">I don't know there's a whole day where <pause dur="short"/> erm the woodland trust is looking for donations to buy trees to go in the centenary wood but there's a planting day so they said to turn up with my saplings then</u>
<u n="92" who="S0283">mm where is it?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0282"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0283">is there a wood in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0282">not yet but there will be <vocal desc="laugh"/> a wood in Epsom <pause dur="short"/> it's one of these new woods</u>
<u n="96" who="S0283">okay <pause dur="short"/> so what's there at the moment? just <pause dur="short"/> plain ground</u>
<u n="97" who="S0282">I don't know really I don't know what there is <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether it's sort of <pause dur="short"/> whether there's a wood <pause dur="short"/> or the beginnings of a wood there now that they're going to add to <pause dur="short"/> or whether somebody's donated them a piece of land or what really</u>
<u n="98" who="S0283" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I also would like to mow the lawn but I'm not sure that's gonna happen</u>
<u n="99" who="S0282">this week?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0282">well not if it's gonna rain like this</u>
<u n="102" who="S0283">no <pause dur="short"/> that's a bugger I would've liked to have done that</u>
<u n="103" who="S0282">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's about time really you might have to wait for a bit for that but that's not a long job is it?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0283">couple of hours three hours four hours</u>
<u n="105" who="S0282">mm <pause dur="short"/> half a day that's not too bad</u>
<u n="106" who="S0283">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I need to fix the trolley</u>
<u n="107" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0283">not happy about that</u>
<u n="109" who="S0282">well no that's a bit strange that its collapsed already</u>
<u n="110" who="S0283">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0282">when my dad bought a shed off the internet he bought a metal shed and the door was defective <pause dur="short"/> and it took about six months to get <pause dur="short"/> a door that fitted</u>
<u n="112" who="S0283">I've heard this story</u>
<u n="113" who="S0282">have you?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0283">yes I heard it in real time and I've heard it since a number of times as well</u>
<u n="115" who="S0282">but that's annoying because that's the kind of thing where</u>
<u n="116" who="S0283" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0282">you know you just keep on moaning and moaning and nobody takes any notice of you</u>
<u n="118" who="S0283">mm <pause dur="short"/> well erm it is just a question of fixing nuts <pause dur="short"/> so it should should be okay</u>
<u n="119" who="S0282">did you do anything to it to make it fall apart?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0283">what like using it?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well I thought</u>
<u n="122" who="S0283" trans="overlap">have you used it?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0282">yeah but I thought the log splitter was a bit heavier I thought that was really pushing it to its Nth degree that one</u>
<u n="124" who="S0283" trans="overlap">no it can deal with much more than that</u>
<u n="125" who="S0282">eh?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0283">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was it wasn't it wasn't the weight it was the twisting on the axle that did it <pause dur="short"/> it had self locking nut underneath the axle</u>
<u n="127" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0283">and basically if you if you move the erm <pause dur="short"/> pulley arm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0283">then it just unlocks the <trunc>un</trunc> the self-locking nut that's what happened <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="131" who="S0282">but then that's not a self-locking nut is it? it's</u>
<u n="132" who="S0283" trans="overlap">well exactly that's why I'm a bit cross</u>
<u n="133" who="S0282">it's the self</u>
<u n="134" who="S0283">it's an <trunc>un</trunc> it's a self-unlocking nut which isn't really what you want</u>
<u n="135" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0283">turned out I'm not happy</u>
<u n="137" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I can imagine it's not</u>
<u n="138" who="S0283">I'm not happy about that</u>
<u n="139" who="S0282">well no but this is is this the penalty of buying things off the internet? you can't actually see them before you buy them</u>
<u n="140" who="S0283">it would've done better with a cotter pin</u>
<u n="141" who="S0282">oh would it?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0283" trans="overlap">instead of a split pin <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0282">you don't even know what a cotter pin is do you?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0283">yes I do</u>
<u n="145" who="S0282">do you?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0283">yeah it's like a split pin</u>
<u n="147" who="S0282">and what's a split pin?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0283">it's a pin that's split <pause dur="short"/> and you put it through the hole and it expands outside of the hole you splay it and it holds things in place <pause dur="short"/> actually</u>
<u n="149" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> all this manly stuff you're learning</u>
<u n="150" who="S0283">don't taunt me in front of others <pause dur="short"/> because it's not fun it's not big it's not clever</u>
<u n="151" who="S0282" trans="overlap">well this is a new variable life you see you were an urban creature before and now you're a rural creature and you're learning about these cotter pin and split pins</u>
<u n="152" who="S0283" trans="overlap">I knew what cotter pins was before I</u>
<u n="153" who="S0282">bulbs</u>
<u n="154" who="S0283">moved out of London</u>
<u n="155" who="S0282">now know what a bulb is</u>
<u n="156" who="S0283" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> what is Kirsty Wark wearing?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0282">I know it's very strange isn't it it's a very savage colour</u>
<u n="158" who="S0283">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah so anyway okay so we've got all of that to do</u>
<u n="159" who="S0282">that's if it stops raining</u>
<u n="160" who="S0283">yeah and I also need to split logs and to get the chainsaw out as well</u>
<u n="161" who="S0282">you're not going to split logs when I'm not here are you?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0283">why not?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0282">because isn't it dangerous doesn't it need two people?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0283">no</u>
<u n="165" who="S0282">shouldn't I supervise you just in case there's an industrial accident?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0283">well you okay I won't <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="167" who="S0282" trans="overlap">what if I went out and I came home and the house was all quiet and dark and I couldn't find you and then I went down to the garage and there you were split in two by your log splitter and there'd be blood all over the garage</u>
<u n="168" who="S0283">is that likely to happen that I would get split in two?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="170" who="S0283">it's more likely that I'd lose a finger</u>
<u n="171" who="S0282">yeah but what would you do if you lost a finger</u>
<u n="172" who="S0283">well I'd look for it <pause dur="short"/> and then I'd probably phone the ambulance and say could you come and pick me up please? cos my wife has got the car <pause dur="short"/> and they'd take me to A and E</u>
<u n="173" who="S0282">would you have your mobile phone with you if you were log splitting in the garage?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0283">possibly possibly</u>
<u n="175" who="S0282">well you'd have to crawl back to the house wouldn't you to get your mobile phone</u>
<u n="176" who="S0283">I wouldn't have to crawl</u>
<u n="177" who="S0282">you might not make it</u>
<u n="178" who="S0283">I can walk without a finger</u>
<u n="179" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no but what if you had a catastrophic loss of blood?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0283"><vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="181" who="S0282">you could be fainting you could be light headed <pause dur="short"/> because you lost a finger what if you lost an arm or a hand or something?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0283" trans="overlap">I could <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="183" who="S0282" trans="overlap">there could be blood going everywhere</u>
<u n="184" who="S0283" trans="overlap">well okay well I won't do that tomorrow then I <unclear/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0282" trans="overlap">it might make your phone malfunction cos of all the blood</u>
<u n="186" who="S0283"><vocal desc="yawn"/> I won't do that tomorrow then I'll wait until Wednesday and you can you can be around watching me use the chainsaw and the log splitter</u>
<u n="187" who="S0282">mm <pause dur="short"/> that would really be exciting</u>
<u n="188" who="S0283">and what are you going to do? you're so drunk for anyone who's listening she's drunk <pause dur="short"/> and what are you going to do while I'm doing that?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> what in London tomorrow?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0283">no</u>
<u n="191" who="S0282">on Wednesday?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0282">oh who's that? <pause dur="short"/> emmanuel <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> prime minister of France?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0283">I've never heard of him</u>
<u n="195" who="S0282" trans="overlap">that <pause dur="short"/> no that he looks most unlikely <pause dur="short"/> he's not French has he got a French face? no <pause dur="short"/> and she's still wearing that top</u>
<u n="196" who="S0283">can you talk into the recorder please?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0282">sorry <pause dur="short"/> okay erm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0283">what are you?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0282" trans="overlap">on Wednesday?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0283">yeah <pause dur="short"/> while I'm doing all of that manly stuff I suppose you could do some weeding</u>
<u n="201" who="S0282">I don't know well we're waiting for the <pause dur="short"/> bloke from the phone company aren't we?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0283">are we?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0282">yep <pause dur="short"/> I think that post at the end of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s drive is a phone post don't you?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0283"><trunc>yeah</trunc> well yes is there any <pause dur="short"/> what's coming off it? where's our electricity come from?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0282">it comes from a post across the road <pause dur="short"/> er comes over the drive it comes over that gate</u>
<u n="206" who="S0283">right</u>
<u n="207" who="S0282">and it comes back to the house but but the post it comes from is over the other side of the road so I think the post outside <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> which where he's got his <anon type="place"/> cottage sign on it I think that's a phone post</u>
<u n="208" who="S0283" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="209" who="S0282">so I think I'm gonna say to the phone engineers they've got to come off that post and come to the back of the house where the electricity comes in</u>
<u n="210" who="S0283">okay</u>
<u n="211" who="S0282">and then that means they can come through the wall there by the bathroom</u>
<u n="212" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0282">and then there's a minimum amount of wiring inside the house</u>
<u n="214" who="S0283">okay <pause dur="short"/> they must have drilled</u>
<u n="215" who="S0282" trans="overlap">does that make sense?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0283">through the radiator</u>
<u n="217" who="S0282">through the radiator? no that would be that would be <pause dur="short"/> that would be very serious wouldn't it? no I think they need to come in actually I think they need to come in higher I think they need to come in <pause dur="short"/> towards the top of the of the room by the eaves rather than at the bottom because we don't want a wire going overhead that's snagging on things we want to go as high as possible don't we? so that it avoids</u>
<u n="218" who="S0283" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="219" who="S0282">erm <pause dur="short"/> any kind of snagging from beneath</u>
<u n="220" who="S0283">yeah it's the <pause dur="short"/> space between <pause dur="short"/> is there a jam above the door to the <pause dur="short"/> attic? <pause dur="short"/> could it go above the door to the attic?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0282">I don't think it could go that way <pause dur="short"/> I think it would come in</u>
<u n="222" who="S0283">above the bathroom?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0282">between the window and the bathroom door <pause dur="short"/> and then run a wire across the top of the bathroom door</u>
<u n="224" who="S0283">avoiding the radiator</u>
<u n="225" who="S0282">well it would be up higher than the radiator</u>
<u n="226" who="S0283">yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> whatever <pause dur="short"/> whatever</u>
<u n="227" who="S0282">if I can persuade him to do that but I think he's got to put in a master BT switch of something</u>
<u n="228" who="S0283">okay well <pause dur="short"/> I hope he knows what he's doing</u>
<u n="229" who="S0282">he will do but we've got to persuade him to do what we want rather than taking the easy route into the house really</u>
<u n="230" who="S0283" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> which is what they'll want to do</u>
<u n="231" who="S0282">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but then <pause dur="short"/> apparently it being Talktalk they use telephone lines rather than cables</u>
<u n="232" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0282">or they're quite happy to use phone lines and in fact it's not even Talktalk that's coming it's BT open reach that's coming</u>
<u n="234" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0282">so theoretically they've got authority to use the phone lines and things it might be he's got a better connection than we've got <pause dur="short"/> in the end</u>
<u n="236" who="S0283">we've got fibre optic he's got copper wire</u>
<u n="237" who="S0282">is that worse?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0283">yes</u>
<u n="239" who="S0282">no they're saying BT open reach were using erm <pause dur="short"/> were using er fibre optic now</u>
<u n="240" who="S0283">okay but the <pause dur="short"/> cable from a <pause dur="short"/> er telegraph pole isn't fibre optic</u>
<u n="241" who="S0282">isn't it?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0283">no <pause dur="short"/> copper wire</u>
<u n="243" who="S0282">and what does that mean?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0283">it means that it's not as fast as fibre optic <pause dur="short"/> it's probably fast enough for his purposes <pause dur="short"/> but it's not superfast</u>
<u n="245" who="S0282">isn't it?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0283" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="247" who="S0282">well we've got superfast</u>
<u n="248" who="S0283">we've got extraordinarily fast</u>
<u n="249" who="S0282">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thinks that he's <pause dur="short"/> that he's got faster</u>
<u n="250" who="S0283">erm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="yawn"/> with Sky <pause dur="short"/> has he not get a best service than us? a better service than us?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0283" trans="overlap">I don't <pause dur="short"/> not necessarily no</u>
<u n="253" who="S0282">why not? <pause dur="short"/> he thinks he's got a better service than us</u>
<u n="254" who="S0283">I'm sure he does but I'm not sure that he does <pause dur="short"/> his comes off a satellite not off <pause dur="short"/> off a cable</u>
<u n="255" who="S0282">is that better or worse?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0283">I don't know I don't know I don't know</u>
<u n="257" who="S0282" trans="overlap">he thinks it's better</u>
<u n="258" who="S0283">fine <pause dur="short"/> if you get I mean I I've got no problem with ours is perfectly fine <pause dur="short"/> there's not a problem with it at all</u>
<u n="259" who="S0282">there is a problem on a Friday sometimes <pause dur="short"/> I can't get online if you've got online before me</u>
<u n="260" who="S0283">no</u>
<u n="261" who="S0282">that's true it is true</u>
<u n="262" who="S0283" trans="overlap">that's nothing to do with</u>
<u n="263" who="S0282">if I have a problem and I can't get online it's on a Friday when you're here</u>
<u n="264" who="S0283">it's nothing to do with that</u>
<u n="265" who="S0282">well</u>
<u n="266" who="S0283">it really is nothing to do with that</u>
<u n="267" who="S0282">something happens</u>
<u n="268" who="S0283">mm <pause dur="short"/> anyway <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="269" who="S0282">erm <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> so we have to hope on <pause dur="short"/> that he actually turns up on Wednesday they did actually that letter I had said <trunc>if</trunc>if you don't make a new appointment we'll cancel the contract altogether so I thought he he</u>
<u n="270" who="S0283">okay <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="271" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but there's not enough time to organise a Freesat or the alternatives to <pause dur="short"/> to what he wants I mean if he was to have a new phone line he would have to have a new BT master switch anyway wouldn't he?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0283">er well can I just they're turning up on Wednesday <pause dur="short"/> I thought <pause dur="short"/> have we got a piece of paper that says they're turning up on Wednesday?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no there's no piece of paper saying they'll turn up on Wednesday when they didn't turn up on the first <pause dur="short"/> I phoned them up and said where are you? I was expecting you they said no no no it's on the eighth <pause dur="short"/> and then after they told me it was the eighth I then had a phone I then had a letter from them saying <pause dur="short"/> erm you weren't there for your appointment on the twenty-fourth <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> we need you to make another appointment unless you make another appointment we will cancel everything <pause dur="short"/> but I had already had that phone conversation saying they were coming on the eighth so <pause dur="short"/> unless there's some cross wiring internally</u>
<u n="274" who="S0283">right <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> well if they turn up on Wednesday they turn up on Wednesday</u>
<u n="275" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="276" who="S0283">he can have his own phone if he wants his own phone he can have his own <pause dur="short"/> tV if he wants his own TV and his own broadband if he wants it <pause dur="short"/> if he wants to pay twice for everything</u>
<u n="277" who="S0282">well he would have to have his own phone wouldn't he? he wants his they want they're own phone so they'd need to pay for their own phone <pause dur="short"/> the fact that then <pause dur="short"/> they are paying <pause dur="short"/> for extras that they don't need is unfortunate and if he had his own phone surely it would be a bit cheaper <pause dur="short"/> would it not be a bit cheaper?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0283">how do you mean?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0282">if you just had</u>
<u n="280" who="S0283" trans="overlap">can you talk into the thing please</u>
<u n="281" who="S0282">sorry if you just had a phone</u>
<u n="282" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0282" trans="overlap">rather then if he had broadband and television</u>
<u n="284" who="S0283" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> of course it would be cheaper <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0282">but does he get his <trunc>ch</trunc> his free calls to France? <pause dur="short"/> only because he's got the bigger package?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0283">no <pause dur="short"/> no you get that off your phone package no he's decided to get the TV package and he's decided to get the erm <pause dur="short"/> broadband because someone sold it to him <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't need either of them it's a waste of money</u>
<u n="287" who="S0282">there's nothing we can do about that now is there?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0283">no because it's his contract</u>
<u n="289" who="S0282">I suppose over time <pause dur="short"/> perhaps over time we can persuade him that he's <pause dur="short"/> bought more than he needs</u>
<u n="290" who="S0283" trans="overlap">he will always say he will always say that he's locked into a contract <pause dur="short"/> he's just an obstinate old git and he's not gonna stop <pause dur="short"/> he's he knows I had I told him what to do he's did something different he's done it deliberately</u>
<u n="291" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="292" who="S0283">so you know</u>
<u n="293" who="S0282">has it does it has it done it because he thinks he knows better than you?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0283">I have no idea no he's done it because he thinks he knows best <pause dur="short"/> he's done it I don't know why <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what's in his head</u>
<u n="295" who="S0282">I think he also thinks that unless he has a contract with them he can't keep his email address <pause dur="short"/> which as I which I can't blame him for because I thought well actually if we swapped we wouldn't keep our email address either</u>
<u n="296" who="S0283">erm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0282">but you can keep your email address</u>
<u n="298" who="S0283">you can keep your email address you don't need a television contract to keep your email address</u>
<u n="299" who="S0282">no that's true <pause dur="short"/> perhaps he thinks he's getting particularly good value</u>
<u n="300" who="S0283">well <pause dur="short"/> it <pause dur="short"/> depends</u>
<u n="301" who="S0282" trans="overlap">will he get better broadband?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0283" trans="overlap">if you thinks if you think if you think</u>
<u n="303" who="S0282" trans="overlap">will get better broadband here than he's had before?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0283">I don't well he would get better broadband than he's had before because he's got shit broadband before but it it's not good value for money to pay for something that you don't need <pause dur="short"/> it's not good value for money to pay for something that has already been paid for <pause dur="short"/> but is better than what you're paying for</u>
<u n="305" who="S0282">no but he'll he'll be thinking well if I'm on the same circuit as them they'll be able to see my emails or something</u>
<u n="306" who="S0283">but he's not thinking that at all he's just thinking this is what I want <pause dur="short"/> the the same way as he's thinking he thinks that he's setting up his own house in our house</u>
<u n="307" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="308" who="S0283">which is why he's brought his entire house with him</u>
<u n="309" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes</u>
<u n="310" who="S0283">so actually he's not he hasn't actually worked out that he's not living in his own house any more <pause dur="short"/> you know I wouldn't be surprised to <trunc>c</trunc> when they come back from France if he told us that he's organised <pause dur="short"/> insurance for us <pause dur="long"/> and he's signed us up with a new deal for electricity and gas <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0282">yes well <pause dur="short"/> we'll have to try and explain to him that we think that we owe SSE thousands of pounds and that's the reason why we can't swap</u>
<u n="312" who="S0283">yes well I think we do owe them thousands of pounds</u>
<u n="313" who="S0282">but that doesn't explain why they haven't stopped billing us since they read the meter</u>
<u n="314" who="S0283" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> they said they were gonna bill us in October <pause dur="short"/> so we're waiting for the bill <pause dur="short"/> I've said this to you several times</u>
<u n="315" who="S0282">I know but if they thought that we owed them several thousand pounds why would they wait until October to bill us?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0283" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know they've been peculiar and bizarre all the way through and they're still being peculiar and bizarre</u>
<u n="317" who="S0282">is there any chance at all <pause dur="short"/> that we've misunderstood the meter</u>
<u n="318" who="S0283">yes there is a chance</u>
<u n="319" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and we're actually thousands of pounds in advance because the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s paid</u>
<u n="320" who="S0283" trans="overlap">well well we're not thousands of pounds <pause dur="short"/> we're not thousands of no <pause dur="short"/> er the meter</u>
<u n="321" who="S0282" trans="overlap">perhaps <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> paid so much that they</u>
<u n="322" who="S0283" trans="overlap">no the meter was read <pause dur="short"/> the meter was read when they left <pause dur="short"/> so it's nothing to do with them <pause dur="short"/> is it? we we gave them a meter reading when we arrived here <pause dur="short"/> and the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s gave them a meter reading <pause dur="short"/> before they left here</u>
<u n="323" who="S0282">but we've had</u>
<u n="324" who="S0283" trans="overlap">so it is possible that I've misread it and it is possible that <pause dur="short"/> er we don't owe them money but we're not thousands of pounds in advance because we haven't given them thousands of pounds</u>
<u n="325" who="S0282">no no no but erm <pause dur="short"/> they've <pause dur="short"/> they have actually read the meter twice now and that hasn't</u>
<u n="326" who="S0283" trans="overlap">yes I understand that</u>
<u n="327" who="S0282">resulted in the bill</u>
<u n="328" who="S0283">I understand that <pause dur="short"/> I understand that I don't know what they're not doing <pause dur="short"/> but there's not a human being involved is there? cos it goes into computers <pause dur="short"/> and computers don't decide things they just do <pause dur="short"/> what they're programmed to do</u>
<u n="329" who="S0282">but if somebody went no but the person who came round to read the meter was a human being</u>
<u n="330" who="S0283">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0282">and they put it in their little machine and they took it away and theoretically then the machine <pause dur="short"/> at the other end should generate a bill</u>
<u n="332" who="S0283" trans="overlap">should generate a bill <pause dur="short"/> yes it should</u>
<u n="333" who="S0282">and the fact that is hasn't <pause dur="short"/> would surely indicate that we don't owe them money <pause dur="short"/> cos that's now happened twice</u>
<u n="334" who="S0283" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> well you can say that but it doesn't indicate any such thing <pause dur="short"/> it just <pause dur="short"/> I don't I don't know why they haven't billed us <unclear/> well <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why they didn't bill us three months ago when they should've done I don't understand but I don't think it's because they owe us thousands of pounds</u>
<u n="335" who="S0282">did you phone up?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0283">no</u>
<u n="337" who="S0282">I thought you phoned up?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0283">no</u>
<u n="339" who="S0282">really? I thought you phoned up and and said why you haven't you billed us?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0283">no <pause dur="short"/> I looked online <pause dur="short"/> to see whether or not they had billed us and they hadn't billed us <pause dur="short"/> so erm <pause dur="short"/> I <pause dur="short"/> checked and it said when it <pause dur="short"/> it said that they were going to bill us in August and then they didn't and now it says they're going to bill us in October so I presume they will <pause dur="short"/> and it may be that they bill us for thousands and thousands of pounds in which case we have to work out what to do about it</u>
<u n="341" who="S0282">well we have to throw ourselves on their mercy</u>
<u n="342" who="S0283">yep <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> not good</u>
<u n="343" who="S0282">well no bit worrying isn't it?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0283">yes <pause dur="short"/> it is worrying <pause dur="short"/> what are you doing now?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0282">making lists</u>
<u n="346" who="S0283">what are you making lists you can't make a list we're doing a tape recording at the moment</u>
<u n="347" who="S0282">no because you have to say on on the form that you send in what you've been talking about</u>
<u n="348" who="S0283">okay <pause dur="short"/> what have we been talking about?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0282">bulbs gardening IT connections <pause dur="short"/> gas bills <pause dur="short"/> this is scintillating</u>
<u n="350" who="S0283">I know the person who's listening to this must be thoroughly excited by by this conversation</u>
<u n="351" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to me is it going to be a machine that listens or a human being? <pause dur="short"/> and I thought oh I don't know</u>
<u n="352" who="S0283">I'd imagine it's a human being</u>
<u n="353" who="S0282">is there machines that do that sort of thing yet? I don't know</u>
<u n="354" who="S0283">well but if if the</u>
<u n="355" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I wouldn't of thought so</u>
<u n="356" who="S0283">if they're listening for <pause dur="short"/> grammar and accent and <pause dur="short"/> syntax and idiom and colloquials then a machine's not really gonna pick that up <unclear/> is it?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0282">no <pause dur="short"/> I guess not <pause dur="short"/> I can't read this</u>
<u n="358" who="S0283">there's about twenty-seven and a half minutes about a minute ago</u>
<u n="359" who="S0282">was it?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0283">yeah so it's twenty-nine fifteen</u>
<u n="361" who="S0282">oh that's half an hour then</u>
<u n="362" who="S0283">or is it twenty-eight <trunc>f</trunc>fifteen? <pause dur="short"/> no it's twenty-eight fifteen</u>
<u n="363" who="S0282">it has to be in segments of</u>
<u n="364" who="S0283">okay it's twenty-eight and a half minutes so far</u>
<u n="365" who="S0282">does that mean that we stop at thirty?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0283">well we're stop slightly beyond thirty and then they'll <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and then that'll be more than thirty so</u>
<u n="367" who="S0282">well no cos it goes in <trunc>incre</trunc> I have to round it up or round it down depending to the nearest</u>
<u n="368" who="S0283" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay well let's do another minute or so and then it'll be over thirty minutes</u>
<u n="369" who="S0282">right okay I don't know if they're anticipating getting tapes of people talking about how long they had to speak for <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0283"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's a bit</u>
<u n="371" who="S0282">that would be very boring</u>
<u n="372" who="S0283">well if everyone's just talking about how long they have to talk for then that's very very boring indeed</u>
<u n="373" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0283">so okay okay well listen tomorrow we er I mean I will probably be in the house tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> erm doing stuff but then we'll go out and do garden stuff on Wednesday</u>
<u n="375" who="S0282">what are you going to do tomorrow?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0283" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> well I told you I've got all sorts of <pause dur="short"/> sorting out and filing and stuff to do <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> so I'll do that tomorrow and then Wednesday and Friday we'll go out in the garden I guess</u>
<u n="377" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="378" who="S0283">and we'll do logs <pause dur="short"/> splitting and sawing of logs</u>
<u n="379" who="S0282">but you mustn't do that without me</u>
<u n="380" who="S0283">no we'll do that on Wednesday <pause dur="short"/> we'll do that Wednesday <pause dur="short"/> what are you writing now?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0282">gardening</u>
<u n="382" who="S0283" trans="overlap">splitting and</u>
<u n="383" who="S0282">gardening accidents</u>
<u n="384" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0283">oh yes you you</u>
<u n="386" who="S0282" trans="overlap">you must take your phone to the garage with you if you do log splitting</u>
<u n="387" who="S0283">yes you were also talking about</u>
<u n="388" who="S0282" trans="overlap">in case you</u>
<u n="389" who="S0283">whether I would had to limp up the road if I chop my finger off <pause dur="short"/> which I thought was slightly bizarre cos I I <unclear/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0282" trans="overlap">or whether you pass out</u>
<u n="391" who="S0283">walk on my hands and knees</u>
<u n="392" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="393" who="S0283">but anyway <pause dur="short"/> so so that's that okay we'll do that erm I'll do inside stuff tomorrow we'll do outside stuff Wednesday <pause dur="short"/> thursday we're eating Friday <pause dur="short"/> whatever <pause dur="short"/> saturday work out what to do</u>
<u n="394" who="S0282" trans="overlap">that's all we're doing on that's all we're doing on Thursday is it eating?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0283">yes <vocal desc="yawn"/> and er <pause dur="short"/> and then <unclear/></u>
<u n="396" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="397" who="S0283">so <pause dur="short"/> so that is our scintillating week <pause dur="short"/> so shall we stop it now?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0282">yes press there</u>
<u n="399" who="S0283">okay</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
