<text id="SNAS">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:41:10</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-10</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0487 S0488</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>university halls in london, my sisters bedroom</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>drugs , food, sex, internet, friends.</topics>
		<activity>Sisters nattering about everything</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0487">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>9_unknown</edqual>
				<occupation>Undergraduate</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Hindi -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0488">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation></occupation>
				<socgrade>unknown</socgrade>
				<nssec>unknown</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Hindi -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0488">but like I used to go on it and like it's like basically forums for people like talking about drugs and being like <unclear>actually</unclear> the my amphetamine complex and this</u>
<u n="2" who="S0487">yeah like actually no one's ever died from drugs</u>
<u n="3" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">yeah no one's <trunc>e</trunc> it's all the <pause dur="short"/> the thing is like with the stories about <pause dur="short"/> people dying from ecstasy I always just think that's so stupid but now it's like that that is actually <unclear/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">I never used to <unclear>I mean it's stupid though</unclear></u>
<u n="5" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">mm <pause dur="short"/> I just thought like oh I bet they took like five or like</u>
<u n="6" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it's everyone like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> no it's just a trigger it's like you have a heart problem you don't know about and it happens to be mixed with something that's like stronger on your heart and you've also drunk before and <pause dur="short"/> it's really <unclear>scary</unclear></u>
<u n="9" who="S0488" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">quite a lot of the ecstasy deaths are like</u>
<u n="10" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">rat poison</u>
<u n="11" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">actually a bad a pill</u>
<u n="12" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">really?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">I literally can't see myself taking drugs ever again</u>
<u n="15" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">like you know you took</u>
<u n="16" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">coke yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">I think that's just cos like it is peer pressure like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was doing it and she like kept mentioning it and then</u>
<u n="18" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">what like have a line have a line?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">no</u>
<u n="20" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">it was like</u>
<u n="22" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">she made you do it didn't she? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="23" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">just kept mentioning it like oh I've got two grams of coke wow so like</u>
<u n="24" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">really?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">and then er she was like oh do you want some? and I took I didn't <trunc>wa</trunc> well the thing is I didn't say like no I'm not doing it I was just like oh not now and then <pause dur="short"/> she asked like a couple of more times and I was like oh fuck it but I literally wanted to kill myself the next day</u>
<u n="26" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">yeah you had the freak out didn't you?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0487">I don't know how you drink though</u>
<u n="29" who="S0488">what even cos it's bad for my psoriasis?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0487">no just in my head we have a really similar reaction to drugs and like for me we erm alcohol is just as bad like it makes me feel really depressed</u>
<u n="31" who="S0488">it it I feel I dunno it used to it really used to like awfully depressed</u>
<u n="32" who="S0487">mm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0488">mm <pause dur="short"/> but then not being able to like interact with people when I went out started being <pause dur="short"/> really depressing too</u>
<u n="34" who="S0487">do you not find not going out is fine?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0488">yeah but like on my birthday</u>
<u n="36" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0488">like if I didn't drink that day and it's like a picnic and everyone's just wanting to get drunk</u>
<u n="38" who="S0487">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0488">it would have just been me like wanting to go home early</u>
<u n="40" who="S0487">home early?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0488">no early like</u>
<u n="42" who="S0487"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> early</u>
<u n="43" who="S0488" trans="overlap">no it would have been me like enjoying it for a bit and then everyone getting drunk and then</u>
<u n="44" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">yeah but I always think that but then it's like I forget as soon as I drink I'm not happy so it's like I may as well be home</u>
<u n="45" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">but I think <pause dur="short"/> I've like discovered the secret which is like you can't stop drinking once <trunc>y</trunc>you drink</u>
<u n="46" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">as in</u>
<u n="47" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">the moment you stop you're doomed like you have to like basically you have to keep yourself you have to either be getting the same amount of drunk or drunker the moment you <trunc>st</trunc> er like stop you start being undrunk</u>
<u n="48" who="S0487" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">and then it's then you start cos yeah when I like come down from drinking</u>
<u n="50" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="51" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">I start <trunc>i</trunc>if I leave it for like an hour erm then I can't anymore like I can't go back into the phase cos I suddenly feel awful</u>
<u n="52" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">it's like you have to keep like poisoning yourself</u>
<u n="54" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">and then until you fall asleep</u>
<u n="55" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">yeah yeah so like</u>
<u n="56" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">yeah but then</u>
<u n="57" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">and I get this thing like <trunc>wha</trunc> if I stop drinking for like an hour like on my birthday like three in the morning</u>
<u n="58" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">I just stop for a bit too long and then suddenly I like can't <trunc>ha</trunc> put anything else <trunc>li</trunc> in me like I'm just like</u>
<u n="60" who="S0487" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="61" who="S0488" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">oh that's awful but I know some people could like <trunc>g</trunc>go to sleep for a bit and then like wake up and start drinking</u>
<u n="62" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">or like do something else and then</u>
<u n="64" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">even the word like drinking <pause dur="short"/> fills me with disgust</u>
<u n="65" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">but I think for me it's like <pause dur="short"/> like with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we've been having like dinner and glasses of wine</u>
<u n="66" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">it's like I'm not like oh I'm so like I'm doing it for her but like her reaction when I was like oh I'm drinking now it's like they actually want to have dinner with you whereas when you're not</u>
<u n="68" who="S0487" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">no but</u>
<u n="69" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">you like they they it's like a chore</u>
<u n="70" who="S0487">mm <pause dur="short"/> I definitely feel it like <pause dur="short"/> even with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sometimes he's like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm sorry but I do really wish you drunk cos like I'd love a glass of wine <trunc>li</trunc>like right now and I know he feels like I'm like a bit of a drag <unclear>in that sense</unclear></u>
<u n="71" who="S0488">mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0487">cos like whenever <pause dur="short"/> we meet up in the evening I just wanna like drink tea and he's like always wants to take something</u>
<u n="73" who="S0488">but that's what I mean it's like <pause dur="short"/> I think also because I know that I really don't wanna take drugs</u>
<u n="74" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0488">but the thing is like</u>
<u n="76" who="S0487" trans="overlap">well <unclear/> compromise</u>
<u n="77" who="S0488">and <pause dur="short"/> and then my psoriasis was like bad anyway in Australia and I wasn't drinking <pause dur="short"/> and then it was like well this is just ridiculous</u>
<u n="78" who="S0487">yeah but like I think if you enjoy it</u>
<u n="79" who="S0488">also like apart from India like every culture does have a drinking culture</u>
<u n="80" who="S0487">mm <pause dur="short"/> er yeah <pause dur="short"/> like obviously <pause dur="short"/> if you enjoy it I think it's good erm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0488">but you know er the other thing I think it is culturally is like if you <pause dur="short"/> I was thinking if like if you're like the whole working thing</u>
<u n="82" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0488">if you don't get that much time with people say if I only have like two hours like to meet someone</u>
<u n="84" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0488">if you have two hours and you have a drink you get like to a deeper level a lot quicker in terms of like a friendlier level</u>
<u n="86" who="S0487" trans="overlap">but isn't that like a horrible thing? it's like we're so overworked we have to like take this poison so we can like feel like we connect on a deep level when actually we're like dumbing ourselves down I just and like I don't know I just think there's no good in it cos like sometimes I'm like oh yeah drinking like join in but then like as soon as you remember like look at white most white middle aged people like their faces their noses their skin their blood it's like from drinking that's why they're so like bloated and like desensitised</u>
<u n="87" who="S0488">I don't think it is from drinking I think it's from</u>
<u n="88" who="S0487" trans="overlap">er</u>
<u n="89" who="S0488"><trunc>in</trunc> eating too much</u>
<u n="90" who="S0487">every time you eat you every time you drink your brain cells die you get stupider <pause dur="short"/> that's what drinking does</u>
<u n="91" who="S0488">is that true?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0487">yeah every time you drink er it drinking is like very mild brain damage every time you drink you your brain cells</u>
<u n="93" who="S0488" trans="overlap">even like a glass of wine?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0487">yeah like obviously like a glass of red wine like people say it's good for you for some there are some benefits for your blood and stuff <pause dur="short"/> but mentally drinking the <trunc>rea</trunc> it slows your reaction because it's like very mild brain damage</u>
<u n="95" who="S0488">the thing is I'm like the worst type of drinker cos I don't really drink but when I drink I like binge drink and they say that that's the worst type cos if you're someone who just like likes a glass of wine it's actually fine because you're not doing it to get drunk but I don't really particularly want like one glass of wine</u>
<u n="96" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0488">it's like either I'm drinking or I'm not</u>
<u n="98" who="S0487">I just feel horrible when I'm drinking and like the only time I feel <unclear/> is when I'm drinking makes me feel really bloated and like big</u>
<u n="99" who="S0488">it does make you feel like really like chubby and like <pause dur="short"/> it makes my skin feel really like dry and awful</u>
<u n="100" who="S0487">it makes me feel awful in every way</u>
<u n="101" who="S0488">you you know like if you're taking drugs your eyes go like big and you feel like</u>
<u n="102" who="S0487">yeah you're like <trunc>bloat</trunc></u>
<u n="103" who="S0488" trans="overlap">you go like pixie</u>
<u n="104" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah you feel like yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0488">but when you're drinking it's like the opposite you like become like piggy and you're like oh</u>
<u n="106" who="S0487">yeah and you become like such a like big white human like bit fatty fat fat <pause dur="short"/> I hate it and also I just don't get the social thing like as soon as there's a bit of alcohol in me I'll be like laughing and stuff but my head will be as paranoid as when I smoked weed <pause dur="short"/> just like</u>
<u n="107" who="S0488" trans="overlap">mm see I <trunc>w</trunc> I used to be like that but I'm not anymore <pause dur="short"/> the the one thing I found my hallucinating is so much worse when I drink and the next day like this weekend's been awful cos I drank on Friday quite a lot</u>
<u n="108" who="S0487" trans="overlap">with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0488">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0487">you shouldn't do it</u>
<u n="111" who="S0488">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0487">the it's such bullshit that we are in a society it's like oh but you're a drag if you don't it's like well then the society can fuck off and you'll <unclear/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0488" trans="overlap">yeah but the thing is like</u>
<u n="114" who="S0487">you develop yourself in a</u>
<u n="115" who="S0488" trans="overlap">I completely understand and I'm like I don't care that you don't drink obviously</u>
<u n="116" who="S0487">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> so thank you</u>
<u n="117" who="S0488">I'm not gonna judge you <vocal desc="laugh"/> no but <pause dur="short"/> when I didn't drink apart from certain friends like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0487">how is she?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0488" trans="overlap">I'd like meet up with a friend for a bit and we like sit and er you can tell like I could feel that they weren't having a good time a lot of the time</u>
<u n="120" who="S0487" trans="overlap">but that's why I don't</u>
<u n="121" who="S0488" trans="overlap">unless it's like in the day and it's obviously a time for a cup of tea but like you feel like a drag and you are a drag to everyone and it was just not fun for me cos I was like I always felt like I'd have to like leave</u>
<u n="122" who="S0487">mm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0488">I would have to be like make an excuse cos I just felt like I was like it was a shit atmosphere and if it was one to one</u>
<u n="124" who="S0487">that's how I feel</u>
<u n="125" who="S0488" trans="overlap">then they wouldn't wanna have a beer and then it's like then they do and you're drinking water</u>
<u n="126" who="S0487" trans="overlap">and then they like resent it</u>
<u n="127" who="S0488">and they <trunc>y</trunc>you can you can tell they're a bit like on edge</u>
<u n="128" who="S0487">yeah and they feel judged but like <pause dur="short"/> at the end of the day <pause dur="short"/> like our society is fucked in those ways it's like such Babylon and it's like yeah it means like a life of sitting inside and waiting till you meet those people who actually don't care and probably don't drink either but I just think like <pause dur="short"/> like I get that feeling so much with people</u>
<u n="129" who="S0488">yeah and it's like</u>
<u n="130" who="S0487">so like hence not going out much</u>
<u n="131" who="S0488" trans="overlap">and you get loads of questions like oh what do you wanna do now? or like</u>
<u n="132" who="S0487">yeah I know it's like</u>
<u n="133" who="S0488" trans="overlap">or like like on Friday night</u>
<u n="134" who="S0487" trans="overlap">oh do you mind if I have that joint? and you're like it's fine</u>
<u n="135" who="S0488">yeah like on Friday night</u>
<u n="136" who="S0487" trans="overlap">and they're like oh</u>
<u n="137" who="S0488" trans="overlap">if I met up with if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had Friday evening if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had come round and we hadn't drink we probably would have like <pause dur="short"/> had a cup of tea and like some food</u>
<u n="138" who="S0487">yeah but what and that's so <unclear/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0488" trans="overlap">but instead we'd like started drinking straight away and like <pause dur="short"/> just like blurting everything out whereas like they're just like blurting loads of talk and then like crying and I think it's just like cos our society is quite emotionless like the trains like everyone is staring it's like you need that to like get out your emotions and like start again</u>
<u n="140" who="S0487">but do you not think like? it's all very well saying all these like things like it's good for but it's like look at the physics the science it kills your brain cells it makes you slow it slows reactions it makes you less intelligent and desensitised and there is no way that can be a good thing</u>
<u n="141" who="S0488">I think at the <trunc>mo</trunc></u>
<u n="142" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yes in the moment you might feel good but how can you defend it? how can you defend it? I just don't get it <pause dur="short"/> we're so desensitised to it</u>
<u n="143" who="S0488">but I think it depends because <pause dur="short"/> like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying his like great aunt she like drank a like cup of port every day a little cup if you're like someone who's like it's like <pause dur="short"/> you know just like it's like almost like a hot chocolate in the evening that's different</u>
<u n="144" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0488">to like a binge every week a binge every week is still worse</u>
<u n="146" who="S0487">no I don't it's different if it's like a hot chocolate in the evening drink</u>
<u n="147" who="S0488">like a hot toddy</u>
<u n="148" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah but I think mum mum's like drinks it habitually like with dinner but she's like mad like we went out it's like it was like five do you remember in Chelsea? we're having like hummus and she can't <trunc>s</trunc> like not blurt out that she needs a wine and then order one it's like</u>
<u n="149" who="S0488" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0487">I just think it's</u>
<u n="151" who="S0488">but it's like a <trunc>mi</trunc>middle class and wine is really bad <pause dur="short"/> like I remember at school they just told us all this stuff like oh like how much is too much and I remember like I swear dad and mum would have like a bottle of wine each a night</u>
<u n="152" who="S0487">they did</u>
<u n="153" who="S0488">sometimes like and they'd always have a lot of wine with dinner and always</u>
<u n="154" who="S0487" trans="overlap">and look at them now they're like fat</u>
<u n="155" who="S0488"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but you could be healthy and do that</u>
<u n="156" who="S0487">I don't think you can for very long <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> you can't it's poison drink there's no two ways about it that's why if you drink too much you throw up just like if you eat too much <unclear/> you throw up</u>
<u n="157" who="S0488">but if you eat too much pasta you throw up</u>
<u n="158" who="S0487">yeah but it is a poison</u>
<u n="159" who="S0488">animals get animals like eat like fermented fruit and get drunk <pause dur="short"/> or like it's not completely crazy</u>
<u n="160" who="S0487">no I think like if you live on a farm and make dandelion wine as like a ritual in the summer you can do it like very occasionally <pause dur="short"/> like I don't think that's wrong I just think the way it's normalised in like social it's so pressurised and it's like there's nothing weird about drinking in our society at all like <vocal desc="sigh"/> I dunno it's just I dunno it's just people just everyone ignores what it really is to the point that like if you say it you're seen as mad</u>
<u n="161" who="S0488">why you don't drink I know</u>
<u n="162" who="S0487" trans="overlap">but it's a poison you can't even deny that maybe one glass of wine with dinner like red wine for like your system but like <pause dur="short"/> it's not about the health benefit it's about intaking something because you think life's more fun with it that's killing your  body</u>
<u n="163" who="S0488">but the thing is for me it is kind of like <pause dur="short"/> whilst I'm in the system like if I lived in India I</u>
<u n="164" who="S0487" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0488" trans="overlap">or somewhere or even like here and I wasn't like being as social I I <trunc>wou</trunc> I'm not like someone who needs a drink</u>
<u n="166" who="S0487">mm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0488">like I wouldn't go to the supermarket and buy a bottle of wine for myself for like my house <pause dur="short"/> but while it's a thing I wanna be able to like see my friends on their terms which is</u>
<u n="168" who="S0487">yeah but you're putting at the end of the day you have to keep this body and this mind for the rest of your life like it's delusion it's just not truth food is different obviously you shouldn't be like a chocolate biscuit head yeah but and like I know tea is like not like extremely pure but</u>
<u n="169" who="S0488" trans="overlap">but the thing is I don't</u>
<u n="170" who="S0487" trans="overlap">it's delusion it's not reality</u>
<u n="171" who="S0488" trans="overlap">but do you to me like a processed like burger or like loads of processed biscuits it's like kind of the same body abuse for like <trunc>m</trunc>momentary pleasures like drinking loads of like beer</u>
<u n="172" who="S0487">really?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0488">maybe worse like beer is like</u>
<u n="174" who="S0487" trans="overlap">I don't at all</u>
<u n="175" who="S0488" trans="overlap">oh well a lot more of like <pause dur="short"/> beer's a much more natural process or like wine <pause dur="short"/> that they've been making forever and like <pause dur="short"/> er like it's horrible like processed fats and like palm oil which is all like biscuits and stuff that's in biscuits that's why it's even though I was thinking like oh alcohol is so bad for psoriasis now I'm like <pause dur="short"/> there are loads of things that are inflammatory like oil erm vegetable oils which are really unnatural like palm oil and stuff which is in all processed food and you know how when I started my psoriasis diet it like went away and then as soon as I started eating like gluten free biscuits</u>
<u n="176" who="S0487">it came back</u>
<u n="177" who="S0488">it came back like even though those were gluten free and dairy free</u>
<u n="178" who="S0487">yeah but it's different like but it's not just body abuse it's not like it's mostly not about body abuse it's about also just running away from reality</u>
<u n="179" who="S0488">but what about like it's okay that's like yeah maybe</u>
<u n="180" who="S0487" trans="overlap">I know like the feeling of enhancing reality it's like it's not enhancing</u>
<u n="181" who="S0488" trans="overlap">okay but maybe that's binge drinking which is different but I think like having like a cider or like <pause dur="short"/> a glass of wine with your mate at dinner is kind of different to like</u>
<u n="182" who="S0487">yeah I just think it's like a collective thing in our society it's just like running away and like <pause dur="short"/> I just don't like the way it's normalised and it's like <pause dur="short"/> it's such a rite of passage it's like oh you're over eighteen you have to drink all the time why don't you drink a glass of wine with dinner? oh people who don't drink are boring oh like</u>
<u n="183" who="S0488">yeah like</u>
<u n="184" who="S0487" trans="overlap">it</u>
<u n="185" who="S0488" trans="overlap">dad was like oh you know AA Gill the food writer? I've heard he's really boring he like he doesn't even drink and and I was like and dad was like erm erm but other things too and I was like</u>
<u n="186" who="S0487">yeah and it's like er also <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's just</u>
<u n="187" who="S0488" trans="overlap">but the thing is like I didn't used to like it at all like I used to hate it I used to hate that feeling but like you know the feeling when like your muscles go a bit relaxed and like you feel really relaxed after a drink?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0487" trans="overlap">you just you feel stupid</u>
<u n="189" who="S0488">I think some are worse though I find white wine's the most like head confusion to me <pause dur="short"/> like white wine's probably the worst</u>
<u n="190" who="S0487">like obviously chocolate biscuits stuff that's not good either but I think drinking's like a serious evil and it has been like</u>
<u n="191" who="S0488">but what do you think about like places like Russia where like they drink cos it's cold? it's like in the culture but it's not necessarily always bad</u>
<u n="192" who="S0487">yeah I think that is different but then it's like Russia like life expectancy is really low there is a lot of violence a lot of abuse it's very dangerous right because they have alcoholics everywhere</u>
<u n="193" who="S0488" trans="overlap">yeah but so is India and they don't drink</u>
<u n="194" who="S0487">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm not saying okay places that don't drink don't have their own evils</u>
<u n="195" who="S0488">that tastes like</u>
<u n="196" who="S0487">what?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0488">chemical</u>
<u n="198" who="S0487">obviously I'm not saying oh if people don't drink there's no evils I just think that it it's an evil that you can easily eradicate and that's normalising our society <pause dur="short"/> like yeah Russians drink I don't like judge people for drinking I just think like</u>
<u n="199" who="S0488">but do you think the same with drugs?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0488">and weed?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0488">I hate weed now I'm like I just think it's like the worst I think weed is also the worst thing like weed is like a really slow you're like it's not like you smoke and like with a pill I think it's like people who smoke weed they don't really notice it cos it's like a <trunc>s</trunc> a slow descent</u>
<u n="204" who="S0487">that's what alcohol is for me alcohol and weed are like the same I think like really natural really natural like <trunc>h</trunc> erm like African I dunno if people grow like African weed or something like it's really natural and they just have that I think it's like I still don't think it's good practice but I like can understand that I do get that some people like</u>
<u n="205" who="S0488">I'm just checking the time it's it's our thing's at nine isn't it? our show?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0488">it's not really eight is it?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0487">yeah it's like eight in the morning</u>
<u n="209" who="S0488">erm I don't know like I just feel like for me the way I felt the way I just I really didn't like feeling like a drag it was not fun and I know</u>
<u n="210" who="S0487" trans="overlap">I know but do you not think that's like giving in to people's evils?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0488">yeah but the thing is it's like if I was <trunc>con</trunc> if I was someone who could like like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when she doesn't drink she's still like really smiley and chatty but literally that's just not in my nature like I can't</u>
<u n="212" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah you're like</u>
<u n="213" who="S0488">I just can't keep up I I can't be be interested</u>
<u n="214" who="S0487" trans="overlap">I know but that's cos people are boring when they drink</u>
<u n="215" who="S0488" trans="overlap">then I just end up going to bed</u>
<u n="216" who="S0487">do you not think people are just <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I don't like judge people for drinking I don't it's I just like it know exactly what you mean <trunc>peo</trunc> I feel so like a drag even with like some of my best friends <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <trunc>l</trunc>like is the only one who doesn't drink and er she feels the same way as me like a hundred percent erm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0488">but it's like you feel like a drag because you are a drag because</u>
<u n="218" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0488">to them you like I I know when I'm not drinking and everyone's drinking I am a drag cos I know like so many times I went out with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mates and I'm like <trunc>w</trunc> saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like oh can we go? cos it's just so boring and now that I drink it's not like that it's like I can stay cos I'm having fun</u>
<u n="220" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0488" trans="overlap">and then I feel like you're just standing on the corner like watching everyone and waiting for them to like to get tired and get bored and they're not cos they're drinking</u>
<u n="222" who="S0487" trans="overlap">I know yeah but it's just</u>
<u n="223" who="S0488" trans="overlap">and then they come over and speak to you and like slur their words and expect you to like get on this deep conversation because you're not drinking you have all your barriers so you're not gonna talk about like all this really deep stuff straight away</u>
<u n="224" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah but it's not deep it's just mindless that's the thing people who drink delude themselves into thinking like oh it gives you like this deep thing it's like it's not deep it's you being an idiot you don't even remember what you said the <trunc>ni</trunc> the</u>
<u n="225" who="S0488" trans="overlap">not necessarily like say with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like <pause dur="short"/> the other night we didn't we weren't like mindlessly drunk we were just like a bit drunk <pause dur="short"/> so like when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came in and we all basically had a chat about loads of stuff and then like we <trunc>star</trunc> me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had a really deep chat about the funeral and stuff and it's like</u>
<u n="226" who="S0487">like I obviously</u>
<u n="227" who="S0488" trans="overlap">me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> could speak to speak about that but we'd take er ages to open up but it wouldn't just be like an hour in</u>
<u n="228" who="S0487">like I I understand like I just think it's really sad and I really I just think it's sad that it's literally it is every</u>
<u n="229" who="S0488">are you making <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a card?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0487">no</u>
<u n="231" who="S0488">are you making a card? <unclear/> shall we make one for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as well?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0487">yeah but I only have one pair of scissors</u>
<u n="233" who="S0488">okay</u>
<u n="234" who="S0487">erm I just find it like <pause dur="short"/> it's such a slippery slope and it's like yeah sometimes I guess but that's not how our society is with drinking it's literally every social event with adults</u>
<u n="235" who="S0488">yeah have you heard <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s new song for <unclear/> for any old excuse?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0487">no</u>
<u n="237" who="S0488">it's like erm <shift new="singing"/> Jason's passed his GCSEs let's get fucked up <shift new="normal"/> erm <shift new="singing"/> Joel's sister's <shift new="normal"/> erm <shift new="singing"/> having her sixteenth birthday let's get fucked up for any old excuse de dum de de <shift new="normal"/> and then it's all about like how in England you just any thing like my cousin's best friend's got a job let's get drunk</u>
<u n="238" who="S0487">yeah it is it's any old excuse <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> it is any old excuse <pause dur="short"/> it's just boring</u>
<u n="239" who="S0488">it is but that's the thing it's</u>
<u n="240" who="S0487" trans="overlap">it's boring that people make you</u>
<u n="241" who="S0488" trans="overlap">it's boring cos you don't and <trunc>a</trunc></u>
<u n="242" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah but people make out that you're boring because you don't drink it's not it's like I don't know</u>
<u n="243" who="S0488" trans="overlap">it's <trunc>peo</trunc> like society is boring <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0487">but society is boring</u>
<u n="245" who="S0488">no I do believe you but</u>
<u n="246" who="S0487">society is so boring you can't have a conversation with people the way that god made them just normal</u>
<u n="247" who="S0488">but do you think it's also like?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0487" trans="overlap">cos that's people have got too desensitised and too thick and</u>
<u n="249" who="S0488" trans="overlap">no and I think it is that but then also it's a it's like genuinely from your age to my age I like if I had a drink I would suddenly feel like awful and like literally like I wanted to kill myself like I'd start getting really dark thoughts and I don't get it as bad now like I don't get dark thoughts from the drink I feel like chatty and happy</u>
<u n="250" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah but maybe it's like society's pressure's like got to you</u>
<u n="251" who="S0488">no I think it's like also the whole thing is like drinking like exaggerates emotions like I'm not saying that you're only not drinking because you're like in a phase I'm just saying like</u>
<u n="252" who="S0487">I don't think I am in a phase <pause dur="short"/> like I think I definitely think living in India has like affected the way I think about it and obviously I'm not saying their society is perfect in any way</u>
<u n="253" who="S0488">maybe you need</u>
<u n="254" who="S0487" trans="overlap">far from it</u>
<u n="255" who="S0488" trans="overlap">to get drunk <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0487">no I don't that's like what drinking people say <pause dur="short"/> I don't need to poison my body I don't need to act like an idiot I don't need to like spend money on a poison that tastes like sugar because I'm too depressed in my life that I can't live the way that god made me just normal with my normal mind</u>
<u n="257" who="S0488">no that is true</u>
<u n="258" who="S0487">that's like the thing of our society that's like how people think <pause dur="short"/> you know? it's like twenty-four seven <pause dur="short"/> I just find it so sad that you can't just meet up with your friends and like have water and like I don't know why it's like we're all trying to run from this thing called reality we can't just</u>
<u n="259" who="S0488">but the thing is I just found like <pause dur="short"/> you know like when I always like remembered like the gigs I went to when with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and stuff and it was so fun</u>
<u n="260" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0488">and I always thought like oh I was just young and then like so for a few years I've been <trunc>li</trunc> oh my god life's really shit and disappointing and I feel felt like every event was actually just quite boring</u>
<u n="262" who="S0487">do you remember that you were drunk?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0488">yeah and then I remembered like well yeah we used to get drunk and like not really drunk but like have like two</u>
<u n="264" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0488">and then like since I started drinking like I've gone out and had fun whereas like all the time like like last year when I stayed in <anon type="place"/> like I was really adamant that I wasn't drinking I'd like go out and go to <trunc>th</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gig and it would just be like <trunc>y</trunc> it's just something you need it's like a social lubricant that you need if everyone's doing it</u>
<u n="266" who="S0487">in this yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0488">and it's like basically</u>
<u n="268" who="S0487" trans="overlap">this society</u>
<u n="269" who="S0488" trans="overlap">the the thought is other people like they won't <trunc>o</trunc>open up as well to you because you're not drinking</u>
<u n="270" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0488" trans="overlap">but even at erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s cousin <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> recently</u>
<u n="272" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0488"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum was like oh you don't want a drink do you? and I was <trunc>sa</trunc> oh no I'm drinking now and she was like oh my god that's amazing and like so nice to me and like brought over champagne and was like cheers and like kept topping me up and like then like gave me half a bottle just like to have <trunc>f</trunc>for myself</u>
<u n="274" who="S0487"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah she's like</u>
<u n="275" who="S0488" trans="overlap">and everyone was like plying me with alcohol and like loving me and I it was then you feel like everyone loves you and as much as like of course it's their <unclear>fault</unclear> if I was there and I was like not I would probably just be sitting down like not getting into it and not getting involved</u>
<u n="276" who="S0487">yeah but then like</u>
<u n="277" who="S0488">it's <unclear>more fun</unclear></u>
<u n="278" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah that's like the name of the game for our society</u>
<u n="279" who="S0488">it's the name of the game and like</u>
<u n="280" who="S0487" trans="overlap">that's the name of the game with all societies like take part in the masses even if you deep down know it's wrong or like be a the outsider and deal with like a more difficult life</u>
<u n="281" who="S0488">yeah and that's the same with like</u>
<u n="282" who="S0487" trans="overlap">what are you gonna choose?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0488" trans="overlap">being a vegetarian <pause dur="short"/> it's like or even being a vegan it's like if you wanna have those values you will also have to realise you're gonna be er the one at the table</u>
<u n="284" who="S0487">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's yeah it's true</u>
<u n="285" who="S0488">do you have another piece of paper like that?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0488">down there</u>
<u n="288" who="S0487">no it's true I don't know I just think and like weed alcohol drugs it's just such a trap of like the adult world and it's like so desensitised <pause dur="short"/> people are so in denial about it <pause dur="short"/> and I don't like it <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know? it's like I yeah even with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who's like my best friend I feel like definitely he thinks I'm quite boring in some ways because I don't drink</u>
<u n="289" who="S0488" trans="overlap">yeah and then I always feel like it's like</u>
<u n="290" who="S0487" trans="overlap">but it's like</u>
<u n="291" who="S0488" trans="overlap">a chore for like for them to see you because you don't drink</u>
<u n="292" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah it's like they're it's like oh and a night of sacrifice and it's like</u>
<u n="293" who="S0488" trans="overlap">yeah I feel like they sacrifice</u>
<u n="294" who="S0487" trans="overlap">I'm gonna see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> okay that's one night that's not gonna be like fun or wild</u>
<u n="295" who="S0488">that's the thing it's literally feels like a sacrifice to them and I just I was just really sick of that cos I felt like people were like dropping in to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and like you're like</u>
<u n="296" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah like the baby</u>
<u n="297" who="S0488" trans="overlap">the child that they come and baby and it's just like I just didn't wanna be that person like I I'm not saying that you shouldn't be that person I'm just <trunc>sayi</trunc></u>
<u n="298" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah but what is that person?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0488">no I'm not</u>
<u n="300" who="S0487">they are those people?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0488" trans="overlap">I I know I'm not saying like it like I agree at all <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0487"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="303" who="S0488" trans="overlap">I'm just saying like that's why I stopped because I didn't enjoy that</u>
<u n="304" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0488">and it's like I feel like now like people actually like will want me to come to a thing or like <trunc>co</trunc>come to a dinner party whereas before it's like oh great <unclear/> the the boring non drinker</u>
<u n="306" who="S0487"><trunc>ye</trunc>yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0488">like it's awful it really is awful</u>
<u n="308" who="S0487">I dunno I just think you're like the drinkers are the ones it's like we'll see who's laughing when they're all like red nosed alcoholics with big</u>
<u n="309" who="S0488"><vocal desc="yawn"/> but I don't think</u>
<u n="310" who="S0487" trans="overlap">bulging bellies</u>
<u n="311" who="S0488" trans="overlap">I'll be like that I'm not</u>
<u n="312" who="S0487"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="313" who="S0488">I'm not that into it</u>
<u n="314" who="S0487">yeah I <trunc>kn</trunc> no I know <trunc>tha</trunc> I can see like the different shades of grey but I can definitely see the different shades of grey I just think <vocal desc="sigh"/> it's just</u>
<u n="315" who="S0488">oh can I use that?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0487">I just really like being <pause dur="long"/> I dunno</u>
<u n="317" who="S0488">what does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0487"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> likes <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0488">what shall I cut out for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? <pause dur="long"/> a pumpkin?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0487"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> likes funny things and like food <trunc>a</trunc> <pause dur="long"/> but I don't know</u>
<u n="321" who="S0488">but I think what</u>
<u n="322" who="S0487" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0488" trans="overlap">you what a good thing to do is like join <pause dur="short"/> I dunno say like a cycling club or something like there are social things that are like more daytime and are</u>
<u n="324" who="S0487" trans="overlap">but I'm not like looking for social things now I'm quite I've got I dunno I'm used to like not doing social things I don't care <pause dur="short"/> at the end of the day</u>
<u n="325" who="S0488">but I just think social life is so important I wish I had like made more effort to do more social things <pause dur="short"/> like not that I haven't</u>
<u n="326" who="S0487" trans="overlap">yeah but I don't</u>
<u n="327" who="S0488">but I'm just saying like I think that's the thing that you most remember out of life is like things with other people</u>
<u n="328" who="S0487">yeah but that doesn't have to be the way society spells it out <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing yeah obviously</u>
<u n="329" who="S0488" trans="overlap">that's why I really really hope that cos you know the like er a really high member of the police force said the other day it was on the radio that erm he'd much rather the high <trunc>s</trunc> like the drunk high street on a Friday night was full of ecstasy users than drunk people</u>
<u n="330" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0488" trans="overlap">I was like I really hope that like drugs don't become like drink cos there's one thing for it to be like this with drinking imagine if it was like this with drugs as well? it would be so awful</u>
<u n="332" who="S0487">yeah but that's not that controversial so obviously he'd rather we're like hugging and like feeling depressed than like fighting and throwing up</u>
<u n="333" who="S0488">mm yeah but <pause dur="short"/> I personally think that drugs have more <pause dur="short"/> risk like I think drinking can turn you violent and stuff but I do genuinely think <trunc>drink</trunc> drugs are more risky with mental health problems</u>
<u n="334" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0488">like one time on acid can send you mad but I don't think one time drinking <pause dur="short"/> like drinking is like yeah for a long time you could turn violent or like turn mad or whatever or dependent but I don't think it's gonna happen after like one beer</u>
<u n="336" who="S0487">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> unless you're like mega mad no it's not but you could say the same about weed</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="337" who="S0488">yeah weed could send you made after one</u>
<u n="338" who="S0487">no</u>
<u n="339" who="S0488">yeah weed can give you like psychosis</u>
<u n="340" who="S0487">after one?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0488">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0487">really?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0488">well okay maybe not but like</u>
<u n="344" who="S0487"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0488">I don't wanna cut out pictures of cake on this cos then she'll be like where's my cake?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0487">no I know they're all cake there's nothing else for me to cut it's really annoying <pause dur="short"/> the pumpkins are good what about prawns?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0488"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> don't really like to drink do they?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0487">mm I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does</u>
<u n="349" who="S0488">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does</u>
<u n="350" who="S0487">I hate it I think it's an ill of our society</u>
<u n="351" who="S0488">see I don't think it's an ill</u>
<u n="352" who="S0487">you don't think it's an ill of our <trunc>socie</trunc> can I use your scissors?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0488"><vocal desc="yawn"/> yeah I did but now I don't er</u>
<u n="354" who="S0487">no <pause dur="short"/> it's not religion that's the <unclear/> of the masses it's drinking <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0488">oh I'm getting really sleepy now</u>
<u n="356" who="S0487">I'm really happy I've been really <trunc>unsl</trunc> not sleepy since I've been back</u>
<u n="357" who="S0488">you're happy?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0487">yeah I've not</u>
<u n="359" who="S0488" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> when you're too sleepy</u>
<u n="360" who="S0487">like last night I got home from work at one and I went to bed and I woke up at like nine</u>
<u n="361" who="S0488">oh no I've I'm getting up early like I went yeah I went to bed at one last night and got up at like eight thirty this morning so that was good you know when you're like get you get like seven or eight hours but you don't overdo it</u>
<u n="362" who="S0487">and you just don't need more and it's like I actually wouldn't be able to go back to bed</u>
<u n="363" who="S0488" trans="overlap">like India was erm and like yeah India is where we slept loads</u>
<u n="364" who="S0487">yeah it was so hot</u>
<u n="365" who="S0488">and but you know when also like there's not that much you wanna do so you just end up sleeping?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm so excited about my year out</u>
<u n="367" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">really?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">yeah I'm just so excited now it's gonna be great</u>
<u n="369" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">do you know where you you wanna go?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">we only have one place to go unless I do Urdu</u>
<u n="371" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">where's that?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">Urdu is Lucknow and Hindi is Jaipur but I think like</u>
<u n="373" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">Jaipur is it?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0487" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">if we're gonna do <trunc>Hi</trunc> Jaipur</u>
<u n="375" who="S0488" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">can I have the scissors? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">yeah and <unclear/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> but I wouldn't wanna go to</u>
<u n="378" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">like really?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">India and a year abroad would be my idea of hell</u>
<u n="380" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">really? that's so surprising</u>
<u n="381" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">I'd go to like Japan on a year abroad or like</u>
<u n="382" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">no you can do so much man I can do so much there so <trunc>ye</trunc> I can you can like <unclear>meet a tailor</unclear></u>
<u n="383" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">yeah but you're in India</u>
<u n="384" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">no I got</u>
<u n="385" who="S0488" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> hate it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">no I think I can <unclear/> get into it not easily but if you like get your head around it and you feel good physically I do <pause dur="short"/> you feel like life</u>
<u n="387" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">I think when you're in a hot place <trunc>th</trunc> you feel a lot healthier</u>
<u n="388" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">definitely</u>
<u n="389" who="S0488" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">not too hot</u>
<u n="390" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">I'm so excited <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">can I use the scissors?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">yeah can you just cut the <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">is it for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">yeah cos we made loads together</u>
<u n="395" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">did he like doing it?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">yeah he really likes doing it</u>
<u n="397" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">ah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">it was really fun <pause dur="short"/> we made a really cool one together</u>
<u n="399" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">have you got it?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="401" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">can I have the scissors?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">hang on <pause dur="long"/> I mean this those</u>
<u n="403" who="S0488" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">oh yes</u>
<u n="404" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">the <unclear/></u>
<u n="405" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">okay</u>
<u n="406" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">I need water I'm dying</u>
<u n="407" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">like it this tap here is a bit weird this bathroom one for water <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">can you pass me the scissors?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">don't you wanna make one like that for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? <pause dur="long"/> I'm kind of nervous about seeing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> no I think it will be fine there'll be other people there</u>
<u n="411" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">yeah but you're like it's like you don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> always freezes me out and it's really mean and like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s like got this like secret hate against me</u>
<u n="412" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">see I think they probably me more than you</u>
<u n="413" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">yeah they do</u>
<u n="414" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">no I'm just saying cos I don't get it as bad</u>
<u n="415" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">yeah but you don't have history with them</u>
<u n="416" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">that's true er <pause dur="short"/> erm I'm just gonna get some water shall I take the plates in or is it better to leave them here until you wash them up?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">er <pause dur="short"/> leave them <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0487" whoConfidence="low">sounds like there's a party in one of the other rooms on your floor</u>
<u n="419" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">in my flat? or the floor?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0487" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">yeah in the flat</u>
<u n="421" who="S0488" whoConfidence="low">oh</u>
<u n="422" who="S0487">erm I forgot I need to call <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about something I'll be really quick</u>
<u n="423" who="S0488">sure you will</u>
<u n="424" who="S0487">sorry</u>
<u n="425" who="S0488">such a <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0487">yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0488">I'm joking <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="428" who="S0487" trans="overlap">well I won't call if you have a problem but</u>
<u n="429" who="S0488"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm joking</u>
<u n="430" who="S0487">okay</u>
<u n="431" who="S0488">so moody sometimes</u>
<event desc="sound of phone"/>
<u n="432" who="S0488"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can you pass me my book?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0487"><unclear/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0488">yeah thanks</u>
<u n="435" who="S0487">er? <foreign lang="und"/></u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
