<text id="SNCG">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:13:41</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-25</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0618 S0619</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Campervan journey from Tarnow to Białka Tatrzańska, Poland – part 1.</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Party, buying/building/renting a home, racism, relationships, not drinking, the stay in Białka Tatrzańska, sleep patterns, friendship issues, health.</topics>
		<activity>Two friends talking about various topics (see 9 above) while driving in a campervan from Tarnow to Białka Tatrzańska, Poland – part 1.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0618">
				<exactage>42</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge/Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months on and off</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>unemployed/ Some part-time private TEFL teacher/ Semi-retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0619">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury, Lancashire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Nort West: Lancs, Greater Manchester</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>nearly 4 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher of English as a foreign Language</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0618">is the counter moving?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0619">yep the counter is moving</u>
<u n="3" who="S0618">hooray</u>
<u n="4" who="S0619"><unclear/> before</u>
<u n="5" who="S0618">now Simon doesn't say turn here but I'm gonna turn here anyway cos you know <unclear>better</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> and left again yeah?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0619">yeah I think if we just go back to <unclear/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> she looks happy don't she? <pause dur="short"/> morning</u>
<u n="8" who="S0619" trans="overlap">she looks thrilled with the joys of <unclear/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she was she was just giving way to me and looking grumpy about it well don't give way to me then anyway</u>
<u n="10" who="S0619">right</u>
<u n="11" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0619">here we go and if we turn right we're all good back on track</u>
<u n="13" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="14" who="S0619">so it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> okay <trunc>s</trunc> this sign says turn right</u>
<u n="16" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0619">yeah turn right <unclear>and then</unclear></u>
<u n="19" who="S0618" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="20" who="S0619">motorway's down there somewhere erm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh hold on my door isn't closed properly I wondered what that noise was</u>
<event desc="sound of door slamming"/>
<u n="22" who="S0618">oops <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's better</u>
<u n="23" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh oh</u>
<u n="24" who="S0618">right don't drive into the bus okay and relax</u>
<u n="25" who="S0619"><unclear/> and relax</u>
<u n="26" who="S0618">right so we're there groovy so we're going</u>
<u n="27" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0618">this way this road is the seventy-three isn't it? I know exactly where I am</u>
<u n="29" who="S0619">okay</u>
<u n="30" who="S0618">that's cool <pause dur="short"/> so good anyway where were we? erm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I'm gonna tell you about Saturday night <unclear/> and the nutters</u>
<u n="32" who="S0618">oh lovely</u>
<u n="33" who="S0619"><unclear/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0618">okay cos it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday today</u>
<u n="35" who="S0619" trans="overlap">today yes</u>
<u n="36" who="S0618">okay so how was the party?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0619">really nice</u>
<u n="38" who="S0618">oh good</u>
<u n="39" who="S0619">really Polish <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0618">good</u>
<u n="41" who="S0619">you know <pause dur="short"/> definitions of party are different in different countries</u>
<u n="42" who="S0618">this is true mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0619" trans="overlap">erm you know and it was just really nice erm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0618">what do you mean by nice?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0619">well you know lots of people all together</u>
<u n="46" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0619">chatting and drinking it was just really nice and his friends were really nice and there was music and and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had made loads of food</u>
<u n="48" who="S0618">Polish music? or?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0619">no <pause dur="short"/> just English more or less loads of indie stuff like Kasabian</u>
<u n="50" who="S0618" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="51" who="S0619">erm cos I went to the flat and I thought it was just <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s flat you know</u>
<u n="52" who="S0618">ah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0619" trans="overlap">erm and I was like cos I know that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s job has something to do with interior design and I was like this is you know it's a bit old-fashioned and they'd <trunc>ha</trunc>had like erm a cupboard full of teacups and stuff and I thought this just doesn't seem right</u>
<u n="54" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="55" who="S0619">erm <pause dur="short"/> er oh you know it was very nice with lots of people there but just sort of a bit dated a bit old-fashioned and I thought oh well maybe <trunc>s</trunc> you know someone's gave them loads of furniture and then at about ten o'clock <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum came home er and was sort of tidying around everybody er</u>
<u n="56" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> as mums do yep</u>
<u n="57" who="S0619" trans="overlap">as mums do and I didn't realise that they lived with her</u>
<u n="58" who="S0618">ah right</u>
<u n="59" who="S0619">yeah still er and I suppose you know they're saving for their own house</u>
<u n="60" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0619">but I don't know if you agree with me that if I was married or if I was in a <trunc>r</trunc> er relationship I would rather blow the money on rent every week</u>
<u n="62" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> live in a shoebox</u>
<u n="63" who="S0619">er</u>
<u n="64" who="S0618" trans="overlap">or a garage or a shed</u>
<u n="65" who="S0619">than live with my parents</u>
<u n="66" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0619">with my</u>
<u n="68" who="S0618">I agree</u>
<u n="69" who="S0619" trans="overlap">you know with my partner I think you know it's awful blowing all that money when you're trying to save for a house but <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0618">yeah <unclear>I think</unclear></u>
<u n="71" who="S0619">I <unclear>couldn't've</unclear> been married and live at home</u>
<u n="72" who="S0618">it seems a little bit different here and in Germany in that people tend to build their own house</u>
<u n="73" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0618">erm or buy a house you know pretty much outright they don't bother with mortgages</u>
<u n="75" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0618">and in the meantime they rent or more likely in Poland yeah they live with their parents</u>
<u n="77" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0618">I've got German friends that erm actually I haven't got any German friends who live with their parents now they all rent but then rents are fairly cheap and the market is makes it very easy for</u>
<u n="79" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="80" who="S0618">for people to rent and there are <trunc>l</trunc>lots and lots of legal protections which maybe don't exist in the rental market in Poland I don't know</u>
<u n="81" who="S0619">mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't <trunc>kn</trunc></u>
<u n="82" who="S0618">a lot of folks live at home er you know even single folks in Poland seem to live at home in their</u>
<u n="83" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0618">thirties forties</u>
<u n="85" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0619"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> lives <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> lives at home from Monday to Thursday with his mum and she <trunc>m</trunc> you know makes all his meals for him and all of this stuff</u>
<u n="88" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah how old's he? he's gotta be <unclear/> forty</u>
<u n="89" who="S0619" trans="overlap">thirty-two</u>
<u n="90" who="S0618">is that? oh is he really that young?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0618">god yeah okay</u>
<u n="93" who="S0619">er and then he does have his own place but it's in <anon type="place"/> which is like I dunno <trunc>f</trunc>forty minutes drive</u>
<u n="94" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0619">so he can <unclear>only be</unclear> there at the weekends erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="96" who="S0618">yeah I suppose it's just a you know a cultural difference</u>
<u n="97" who="S0619">cultural difference yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0619">if you live on your own I think it's okay but I mean if you're single I think it's okay but if you're married I just <unclear>don't think</unclear></u>
<u n="100" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="101" who="S0619">I remember saying to a student last year a little boy in conversation club how many people live in your house? and he was like nine people <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like er what? who? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="103" who="S0619">and it's you know him and his brother and his mum and dad and their mum and dad and his cousins and his auntie and uncle</u>
<u n="104" who="S0618">wow</u>
<u n="105" who="S0619">you know and er I imagine it's a very big house but</u>
<u n="106" who="S0618">mm that's a bit like Ireland maybe a couple of generations ago</u>
<u n="107" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0618">and Scotland actually I don't know about England probably not</u>
<u n="109" who="S0619">mm I don't think the houses are big enough</u>
<u n="110" who="S0618">no but even in I'm thinking about erm my father-in-law who's eighty-three grew up in Scotland and <unclear>then</unclear> about ninety-seven of them living in a two up two down</u>
<u n="111" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0618">erm and likewise with my mother-in-law who's eighty-eight something like that eighty-seven eighty-eight erm she lived in <anon type="place"/> and there were a million of them as well so I dunno and is that? <vocal desc="misc"/> yeah dunno I was just trying to relate it to religion potentially where you have loads of children cos you don't have contraception but erm I dunno</u>
<u n="113" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0618">I suppose that's not so applicable these days</u>
<u n="115" who="S0619">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I think it's just a way to save money here <unclear/> sort of thing and</u>
<u n="116" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0619">you know they're very family oriented more than in England</u>
<u n="118" who="S0618">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="119" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I always feel weird saying that like you know in England people don't care about their family</u>
<u n="120" who="S0618"><unclear/> it's different</u>
<u n="121" who="S0619">but it's just a different relationship isn't it?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0618">yes</u>
<u n="123" who="S0619">a stronger relationship</u>
<u n="124" who="S0618">I never hugged my family I didn't realise that's what people did</u>
<u n="125" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0618">and then <pause dur="short"/> I suppose really it is being married and hugging all the in-laws and think why don't I hug my own family?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0618">and then I started hugging them which I think they were a bit shocked by <vocal desc="laugh"/> initially but</u>
<u n="129" who="S0619">ah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0618">they seem to have warmed up to it so now they just sort of expect a hug and they get one yeah <pause dur="short"/> being overtaken by a big lorry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0619">how embarrassing</u>
<u n="132" who="S0618">I know I let him overtake cos it takes me a while to get up to speed <pause dur="short"/> I suppose I'm a bit wary of the sound quality as well we might need to</u>
<u n="133" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah that's true</u>
<u n="134" who="S0618">speak up a bit for our recording <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0619">isn't it strange building a motorway but with only two lanes?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I remember when the A14 was built in <anon type="place"/> although back in the day it was the A45 and that gets to three lanes in bits but is mostly two lanes and that's the main route from the docks erm at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0618">right through to erm going up to <anon type="place"/> way and joins the A1 or along to join the M6 and then on to Scotland <pause dur="short"/> so it was a major motorway</u>
<u n="139" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear>and only</unclear> two lanes</u>
<u n="140" who="S0618">a major yeah huge and it was two lanes and I remember my dad telling me cos I was a kid when it was built but my dad told me that there were all of these studies at the time about erm the volume of traffic and what was anticipated in the coming decades and they didn't really have a clue so</u>
<u n="141" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm yeah they must've just</u>
<u n="142" who="S0618">yeah they do more works on it now but er</u>
<u n="143" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0618">put three lanes in at some of the peak places</u>
<u n="145" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> er loads of the motorways around <anon type="place"/> are all fifty miles an hour limit</u>
<u n="146" who="S0618">wow</u>
<u n="147" who="S0619">to cos it gets really really congested erm <pause dur="short"/> so it makes the <trunc>f</trunc> the flow of the traffic better</u>
<u n="148" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0619"><unclear>I suppose</unclear> cos people aren't you know being silly people aren't braking or whatever or <unclear/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0619">and there's loads of speed cameras <unclear>every like two hundred miles</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> stupid</u>
<u n="152" who="S0618">oh god yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0619">so you've really gotta take your time</u>
<u n="154" who="S0618"><unclear/> you were telling me about your party erm</u>
<u n="155" who="S0619">I was yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0619"><unclear/> distracted by this <unclear/> er so met erm a couple of friends of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s that she'd met on her CELTA one's from <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> and</u>
<u n="158" who="S0618">ah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0619">his girlfriend is Romanian and they met on the CELTA course</u>
<u n="160" who="S0618">ah lovely</u>
<u n="161" who="S0619" trans="overlap">erm nice yeah and they both live in <anon type="place"/> now teaching er she hates it and wants to move to the sunshine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0618">I can understand that <unclear>bit</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0619" trans="overlap">er and he kind of likes it</u>
<u n="164" who="S0618">ah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0619">erm but they're talking about moving <trunc>sh</trunc> cos she lived in Portugal before she <unclear>moved</unclear> here</u>
<u n="166" who="S0618">wow</u>
<u n="167" who="S0619">and she wants to go back to Portugal</u>
<u n="168" who="S0618">god what a difference Portugal or <anon type="place"/> wow</u>
<u n="169" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I know Portugal to Poland</u>
<u n="170" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0619">it's like <trunc>ex</trunc> complete extremes isn't it? so</u>
<u n="172" who="S0618">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="173" who="S0619" trans="overlap">erm so that was nice they were nice</u>
<u n="174" who="S0618">which is nice <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0619">which is nice <unclear/> running out of words today we've got two and two and a half hours of this er</u>
<u n="176" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0618">yes talk words <unclear/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0619">er and then my student <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was there</u>
<u n="179" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0619">did I tell you this story? I shall tell you again for the benefit of our listeners cos it's funny er you've met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the really big one he's my student</u>
<u n="181" who="S0618"><anon type="place"/>? or <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no here <pause dur="short"/> er he came bowling with us</u>
<u n="183" who="S0618">oh yes</u>
<u n="184" who="S0619">big guy</u>
<u n="185" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0619">quiet speaks English with like a posh accent</u>
<u n="187" who="S0618" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="188" who="S0619">that he's got from I don't know where</u>
<u n="189" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0619">erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was his native speaker teacher last year</u>
<u n="191" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0619">erm and <pause dur="short"/> he er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oh I've been in the prison because he has been a prison officer for twelve years</u>
<u n="193" who="S0618">oh wow</u>
<u n="194" who="S0619">er and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thought he meant I've been in prison for twelve years</u>
<u n="195" who="S0618">I'm ah right</u>
<u n="196" who="S0619" trans="overlap">and he thought <pause dur="short"/> and he thought he had this student in his class he was learning English to get him on the straight and narrow</u>
<u n="197" who="S0618" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0619">after twelve years in prison</u>
<u n="199" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh that's funny</u>
<u n="200" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I was like twelve years in prison? you it's like I dunno killing someone you'd get something like twelve years <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0619">erm you know he's so quiet and he doesn't really say much and he's quite shy erm</u>
<u n="203" who="S0618">that's funny <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0619" trans="overlap">you know and he just thought he was <unclear/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0618" trans="overlap">so a little bit lost in translation there wasn't it?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah so I really took the piss out of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at this party <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0618">ah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0619">er it was funny you know he's just so sort of gentle</u>
<u n="209" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I dunno how he would work in a prison he bakes cakes</u>
<u n="211" who="S0618">ah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0619">and ballroom dances and is a master beekeeper</u>
<u n="213" who="S0618">oh wow that's cool</u>
<u n="214" who="S0619" trans="overlap">erm and he has all of these hobbies and he's you know he's single and he's just</u>
<u n="215" who="S0618">gay?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0619">no I don't think so</u>
<u n="217" who="S0618" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="218" who="S0619">I don't think so I don't know and just really sort of sweet er erm and <pause dur="short"/> he</u>
<u n="219" who="S0618">and not a murderer</u>
<u n="220" who="S0619">and not a murderer</u>
<u n="221" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0619">so that's a good that's a good <unclear>thing</unclear></u>
<u n="223" who="S0618" trans="overlap">which is nice</u>
<u n="224" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0619">yeah so he was there and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> from the office was there</u>
<u n="226" who="S0618">uhu</u>
<u n="227" who="S0619">er and then yeah other assorted friends <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s brother was there who is the twin of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they look</u>
<u n="228" who="S0618" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="229" who="S0619">so identical there's five years between them four years between them</u>
<u n="230" who="S0618" trans="overlap">goodness</u>
<u n="231" who="S0619">erm identical er</u>
<u n="232" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> younger or older?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0619">er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is the older one</u>
<u n="234" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="235" who="S0619">his brother's twenty-four like me er and he lives in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0618">oh my god</u>
<u n="237" who="S0619" trans="overlap">the arse end of nowhere</u>
<u n="238" who="S0618">yeah <anon type="place"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0619">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0618" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="241" who="S0619">erm and</u>
<u n="242" who="S0618">so he did come back for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s birthday?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0619" trans="overlap">he'd come back for <unclear/> for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s birthday with er <trunc>th</trunc>three of his friends his girlfriend and another married couple that they they must've you know gone to school together and decided oh we'll go to England to seek our fortune so we were talking <trunc>t</trunc> I was talking to them and you know what's the differences? do you like living in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="244" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0619">oh I like living in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="247" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0618">well the beer's <unclear>good and</unclear> cheap so</u>
<u n="249" who="S0619">yep you know and what's the difference between Polish young people and English young people? they didn't have a lot of positive things to say</u>
<u n="250" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0619">er <pause dur="short"/> and then one of them starting going oh there's too many Muslims in <anon type="place"/> and I was like</u>
<u n="252" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh for fuck's sake</u>
<u n="253" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I was like I am not talking to you any more</u>
<u n="254" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0619">goodbye and I just like it really got to me because I was thinking the Muslims who live in <anon type="place"/> are British</u>
<u n="256" who="S0618">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0619" trans="overlap">British people with British passports I was like</u>
<u n="258" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0619">you're the immigrant</u>
<u n="260" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0619">you're the person who shouldn't be there if no one er you know if someone's not supposed to be there it's you <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0618">how did they respond to that?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I didn't say that I just went <unclear/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh you maybe should've done for god's sake</u>
<u n="265" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I know and one of them was like</u>
<u n="266" who="S0618" trans="overlap">there seems to be so much <unclear/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0619">what do you think about it? all of these people in England? and I was like but they're <trunc>Eng</trunc> they're English <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0618">jeez even if they're not English what's the problem?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah I don't know where they get this racism from</u>
<u n="270" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I think <unclear>it's</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0619"><unclear>where they</unclear></u>
<u n="272" who="S0618" trans="overlap">it's all based on fear this whole austerity story to my mind is a complete fabrication to divide and conquer it's to set humanity against humanity</u>
<u n="273" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0618">so Cameron and pals go along fleecing people of all their money and power and all the rest of it and meanwhile poor people are fighting poor people it's all bollocks</u>
<u n="275" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0618">but anyway they've obviously swallowed a story so</u>
<u n="277" who="S0619">yeah but they're told you know in the news that these people are bad and they hate them</u>
<u n="278" who="S0618">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0619">even though especially Polish people in Poland have never met anyone who's not white</u>
<u n="280" who="S0618">I know</u>
<u n="281" who="S0619">it just it blows my socks off</u>
<u n="282" who="S0618">yeah or maybe never met someone who's not Christian or <unclear/> or</u>
<u n="283" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear>not no religion</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0619">erm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0618">I know I think if people form their opinions of other people on how they actually find other people through their own direct experience</u>
<u n="287" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear>I know</unclear></u>
<u n="288" who="S0618">then in my experience of human beings is that we all want to love and be loved we all want the best for our family</u>
<u n="289" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0618">we all want to have enough of everything and we generally do</u>
<u n="291" who="S0619">yep</u>
<u n="292" who="S0618">you know I worked at charitable organisations where people are living in extreme poverty and so it does exist it does exist in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="294" who="S0618">in <anon type="place"/> well it exists everywhere but you know it's not really a case of <unclear>in</unclear> giving to one part of a population who you divide according to religion or skin colour or whatever you're depriving other people you're not it's bollocks</u>
<u n="295" who="S0619">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0618">so anyway anyway I'm preaching to the converted with you I know <vocal desc="laugh"/> so</u>
<u n="297" who="S0619">I just thought it was <pause dur="short"/> it's just a strange thing to say <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0619">this you know this man who and they must have pretty miserable lives in England you know they work long hours in a meat factory</u>
<u n="300" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0619">and I just think you know I know that you don't want to be there and you know want to come and live <trunc>li</trunc> you know live in Poland with your family and with your friends and you are only doing it for the money but er I was talking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about this yesterday I think this this Polish thing about erm the future and saving for the future and</u>
<u n="302" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0619">the things that you're gonna do in the future even if it means that you're fucking miserable while you're doing it</u>
<u n="304" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah I know <vocal desc="laugh"/> but not for a decade or two I know</u>
<u n="305" who="S0619" trans="overlap">and it's <unclear>like</unclear> why?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0619">like what's the point?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0618">I know</u>
<u n="309" who="S0619">I'd rather be I'd rather <vocal desc="sigh"/> sort of anticipate having a disappointing future if what I'm doing at the moment is <pause dur="short"/> is making me happy</u>
<u n="310" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0619">I dunno</u>
<u n="312" who="S0618">I don't know I think I've changed a lot erm end of the nineties my mum got a terminal cancer diagnosis and being around her and watching how she lived her life really influenced me I think and I live very much</u>
<u n="313" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0618">in the moment now</u>
<u n="315" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0618">then when my partner got terminal cancer diagnosis you know just kind of reinforces that when everybody you love is been you know given a death sentence</u>
<u n="317" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0618">well we've all got a death sentence from the moment we're born really</u>
<u n="319" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0618">but if if</u>
<u n="321" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> time yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0618">you know if you know it's gonna be kind of sooner rather than later then</u>
<u n="323" who="S0619">yeah mm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0618">I do think it changes how you perceive reality and your priorities <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0619">I had erm a question from my students we were talking ambitions and bucket lists and dreams and this kind of thing and the first question was is life boring?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0618">oh</u>
<u n="327" who="S0619">er and I think it's er <trunc>g</trunc> <trunc>th</trunc>there's two answers obviously which are yes and no in some ways</u>
<u n="328" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm no there's a third one but anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0619" trans="overlap">okay oh well to say</u>
<u n="330" who="S0618" trans="overlap">just being awkward</u>
<u n="331" who="S0619">yeah well tell me in a minute and I think in some ways it is you know you're waking up at the same time eating the same breakfasts and going to work er or if you're a student you're going to school every day and it can be very boring erm and at the same time of course it's not boring there's so many exciting things for you to do er and you can make life interesting and you can meet new people and laugh at jokes and tell stories and all of these things make life interesting</u>
<u n="332" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0619">so I don't know what's your third?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that life is neither boring nor not boring life in and of itself just is</u>
<u n="335" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0618">and it's only a human perception</u>
<u n="337" who="S0619">it's not really answering the question <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0618">well it is and I think it's a really important answer to the question it's like you know technically speaking</u>
<u n="339" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0618">there is no good or and there is no evil there are only perceptions of how you feel about certain events so</u>
<u n="341" who="S0619">yeah <unclear>or</unclear></u>
<u n="342" who="S0618">really if you take humans and er our own subjective perceptions out of the equation it neither is or isn't <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know it's not good or evil it's not boring or not boring it's just it is as it is but yeah I've been bored lately and I think now I've recognised that I'm taking steps to remedy that</u>
<u n="343" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0618">and I I do think we have as humans this built-in kind of indicator I mean we have this whole rainbow of emotions this whole spectrum but it all boils down to does it feel good? or not? <vocal desc="laugh"/> and you've struck upon this before and if it doesn't well what needs to change?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0618">and if it does then great do more of that and so yeah boredom is just one aspect of that</u>
<u n="347" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="348" who="S0618">doesn't feel so great <pause dur="short"/> so yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0619">yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0618">so how was yesterday? do you want to talk about <anon type="place"/>? or not?</u>
<u n="351" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0618">no?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0619">no I do but I might cry</u>
<u n="354" who="S0618">oh okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0619">er</u>
<u n="356" who="S0618">would you rather not cry while being recorded? or?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0619">I'm not bothered <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="358" who="S0618">okay fair enough</u>
<u n="359" who="S0619">er I just sort of <trunc>s</trunc> you know said <pause dur="short"/> it's all or nothing thank you</u>
<u n="360" who="S0618"><unclear>you're welcome</unclear></u>
<u n="361" who="S0619">erm <pause dur="short"/> which is you know it's a thing this relationship or it's nothing <unclear>you know er</unclear> you can't keep phoning me every night er to tell me about your day like that's gonna have to stop</u>
<u n="362" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0619">er so he said nothing</u>
<u n="364" who="S0618">he said nothing? he didn't have a view? or <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no no his answer was er in the question all or nothing he chose nothing</u>
<u n="366" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh in the question he chose nothing</u>
<u n="367" who="S0619">he didn't sort of sit in <trunc>s</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> in silence for the rest of the <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh okay <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="369" who="S0619">I'm gonna take a vow of silence until you leave</u>
<u n="370" who="S0618" trans="overlap">just talk amongst yourself <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="373" who="S0619">er so</u>
<u n="374" who="S0618" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="375" who="S0619">but</u>
<u n="376" who="S0618">well I suppose if</u>
<u n="377" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I think it's the better outcome it's the er saddest right now but</u>
<u n="378" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0619">next week it'll feel even better</u>
<u n="380" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no that's cool I think it's good to have you know to know where you're at really</u>
<u n="381" who="S0619">well yeah exactly now I know where I stand and I can</u>
<u n="382" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0619">make my choices and make my decisions er</u>
<u n="384" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0619">based on that so it's good it's good good</u>
<u n="386" who="S0618">good <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm kind of relieved in a way from a selfish viewpoint I mean you know your relationship or not with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is none of my business but I don't like the guy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="387" who="S0619">yeah I</u>
<u n="388" who="S0618" trans="overlap">and I didn't say that to you in so many words before you went to <anon type="place"/> cos I I don't know that you'd be</u>
<u n="389" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0618">swayed by my view anyway I don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said the same thing but</u>
<u n="392" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no I don't like the guy</u>
<u n="393" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="394" who="S0618">he's <unclear>more</unclear> er I dunno there's a vibe that just doesn't sit right with me</u>
<u n="395" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0618">so <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but no so interesting oh crumbs so</u>
<u n="397" who="S0619">no no it's fine now like</u>
<u n="398" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0619">it is what it is</u>
<u n="400" who="S0618">yeah exactly it is what it is and I suppose <pause dur="short"/> with anything that <pause dur="short"/> comes to an end there's a you know process to go through so</u>
<u n="401" who="S0619">oh absolutely</u>
<u n="402" who="S0618">but we're just gonna have a good day today</u>
<u n="403" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="404" who="S0618">you're gonna be surrounded by friends and people who love you and who are supportive of you and</u>
<u n="405" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="406" who="S0618">we're gonna ski and we're gonna have nice food and</u>
<u n="407" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yes are you skiing today?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0618">go to the spa <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah I think the idea is to get there about two or half past or something</u>
<u n="409" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0618">and erm you're gonna go off with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0618">and have some lunch with a woman at her house</u>
<u n="413" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="414" who="S0618">that involves things that have been killed</u>
<u n="415" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0618">and I've bought myself a one person portion curry out of the freezer</u>
<u n="417" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="418" who="S0618">so I'll <unclear>cook</unclear> up my veggie option where we're staying and then we'll meet up again and go skiing I dunno about five or something</u>
<u n="419" who="S0619">uhu oh I don't know how I feel about skiing in the dark</u>
<u n="420" who="S0618">oh well I presume they'll put some lights on</u>
<u n="421" who="S0619">no</u>
<u n="422" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0619">it's not gonna be pitch black</u>
<u n="424" who="S0618">we're not gonna need a head torch we'll be alright you know</u>
<u n="425" who="S0619">I might not ski today</u>
<u n="426" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="427" who="S0619">and just come and sit and read my book</u>
<u n="428" who="S0618">yeah do you feel like you need any time alone to process the events of yesterday?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0619">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> no I just don't fancy skiing</u>
<u n="430" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="431" who="S0619">because</u>
<u n="432" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0619">it's raining <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0618">it is raining and you've been lunging down</u>
<u n="435" who="S0619" trans="overlap">and I've been lunging</u>
<u n="436" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear>you've been half freezing</unclear></u>
<u n="437" who="S0619">and I just think er it's probably not a good decision er <pause dur="short"/> today</u>
<u n="438" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0619">er and if I can get wi-fi somewhere I can try and send these reports on my phone <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="440" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0619">er <pause dur="short"/> give that a go</u>
<u n="442" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0619">and then tomorrow I'll be fresh</u>
<u n="444" who="S0618">I have to admit the most attractive thing all of this for me is the spa <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0619">I am so excited</u>
<u n="446" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I love a spa I love I</u>
<u n="447" who="S0619" trans="overlap">have you brought your cossie?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0618">I bloody hope so I think it was the first thing in the case <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="449" who="S0619">it was the first thing in my case but then I repacked and then <unclear>I don't</unclear></u>
<u n="450" who="S0618" trans="overlap">ah okay</u>
<u n="451" who="S0619">I <trunc>sus</trunc> if it's not in there I am gonna</u>
<u n="452" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah go naked</u>
<u n="453" who="S0619"><unclear/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I <unclear>went</unclear> to a place one time with my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she forgot to bring her cossie and we were all gutted so between us we managed to sort of find some big pants</u>
<u n="455" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0618">that were black and like a big erm vest thing that sort of goes under a blouse and</u>
<u n="457" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0618">she just kind of managed to bluff it which was good and kept her towel on a lot but</u>
<u n="459" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0618">yeah it was bluffable it was good</u>
<u n="461" who="S0619"><unclear/></u>
<u n="462" who="S0618" trans="overlap">and I thought as well I know being off the booze I've never been to a spa and not <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="463" who="S0619" trans="overlap">not been drank in yeah Prosecco</u>
<u n="464" who="S0618">yeah exactly so yeah that was and er while I was in Lidl I nearly lifted a a couple of bottles of bubbles but anyway we will cope it'll be a new experience <pause dur="short"/> spa with no alcohol</u>
<u n="465" who="S0619" trans="overlap">and I'm totally up for February as well</u>
<u n="466" who="S0618">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0619">for sure er if not</u>
<u n="468" who="S0618" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="469" who="S0619">forever</u>
<u n="470" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0619">I really don't think it's for me</u>
<u n="472" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0619">er and you know at the party they were all like don't do it don't extend it and I just thought why? it's nothing to do with you</u>
<u n="474" who="S0618">exactly</u>
<u n="475" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0618">why do people need for you to have some alcohol?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah it's like you said it says more about the other person I think</u>
<u n="478" who="S0618" trans="overlap">it does <pause dur="short"/> yeah I've got</u>
<u n="479" who="S0619" trans="overlap">it's like going you're really boring if you're sober so you need to drink er cos you're not interesting enough</u>
<u n="480" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah thanks mate</u>
<u n="481" who="S0619" trans="overlap">or it's saying erm I need you to drink to sort of erm</u>
<u n="482" who="S0618" trans="overlap">feel better about my drinking</u>
<u n="483" who="S0619">yeah to sort of</u>
<u n="484" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0619">what's the word? not validate it or you know say that it's okay</u>
<u n="486" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0619">but if someone's not drinking I think there's some you know something quite erm <unclear/> er some <pause dur="short"/> erm what's the word? fucking hell er you know you're a bit more sort of moral or you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="489" who="S0619">there's even if you don't show this <unclear>erm and</unclear> it's not coming across in your eyes you know people</u>
<u n="490" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0619">will always think</u>
<u n="492" who="S0618">there are some experiments could be done here <unclear>maybe</unclear> we could have some fun with this</u>
<u n="493" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0618">well we could try different reasons for not drinking</u>
<u n="495" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="496" who="S0618">and see</u>
<u n="497" who="S0619">see which is more or less offensive</u>
<u n="498" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah what's more acceptable</u>
<u n="499" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I think saying dry January is very acceptable</u>
<u n="500" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0619">cos people know it and it's a thing that people do</u>
<u n="502" who="S0618">yeah and sober October</u>
<u n="503" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0618">people do <pause dur="short"/> but to say oh no you know I'm just not drinking cos I choose not to doesn't seem to be acceptable <unclear/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="506" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="508" who="S0618">so I wonder if I'm part of a twelve-step programme</u>
<u n="509" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="510" who="S0618" trans="overlap">whether people there people will immediately back off and not push the issue</u>
<u n="511" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0618">won't spike your drink and will offer you lots of juice</u>
<u n="513" who="S0619" trans="overlap">help and support yeah</u>
<u n="514" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="516" who="S0618">so <unclear/></u>
<u n="517" who="S0619">well I started drinking wine at eight in the morning <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I decided I best stop</u>
<u n="518" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="519" who="S0619">I'm okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="520" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0619">but it all er you know things like oh for health or for weight</u>
<u n="522" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0619">people don't like that</u>
<u n="524" who="S0618">no not at all</u>
<u n="525" who="S0619">erm for money people don't like that I tried to use the money on Friday and they were like but it's a party it's free <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like oh right so</u>
<u n="526" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="527" who="S0619">I only drink if I don't have to pay for it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what about it's against my religious principles? do you think that would be <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="529" who="S0619" trans="overlap">well what religion?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0618">I I don't know</u>
<u n="531" who="S0619" trans="overlap">it it would have to be Muslim I guess</u>
<u n="532" who="S0618" trans="overlap">Muslim hey you would and that's</u>
<u n="533" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="534" who="S0618">yeah try that in Poland <pause dur="short"/> I'm sorry</u>
<u n="535" who="S0619" trans="overlap">sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0618">but as a Muslim woman</u>
<u n="537" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="538" who="S0618">that's magnificent I think we should try that</u>
<u n="539" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think I'd have to sort of er <vocal desc="laugh"/> adapt to a few other <trunc>th</trunc>things <vocal desc="laugh"/> otherwise they might think I'm lying</u>
<u n="540" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0619">I don't know</u>
<u n="542" who="S0618">oh dear</u>
<u n="543" who="S0619">I'd have to stop eating bacon I don't eat that much bacon anyway <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="544" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="545" who="S0619"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="546" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0619"><unclear/> yeah it's a good experiment I think</u>
<u n="548" who="S0618">what is all that noise going on there?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0619">something's rattling oh it might be bits of ice cube or <unclear/></u>
<u n="550" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah I was kind of hoping it was all the snow coming off the roof cos it's been on there for a month like</u>
<u n="551" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah cos I saw like ice flying off someone's car before</u>
<u n="552" who="S0618">yeah let's hope icicles don't fly through somebody's windscreen</u>
<u n="553" who="S0619">yeah <unclear>it's like</unclear></u>
<u n="554" who="S0618">so whoops sorry</u>
<u n="555" who="S0619">the Final Destination films that is a weird noise though isn't it?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> sounds a bit liquidy anyway hope it's okay won't panic</u>
<u n="557" who="S0619"><vocal desc="yawn"/> <unclear/> miserable <unclear/> day</u>
<u n="558" who="S0618">I was just thinking you were just oh on the wavelength there</u>
<u n="559" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="560" who="S0618">I was just thinking exactly that I mean again oh actually talking about boring or not boring or good or evil this is where I got the idea and it's I worked in a booze shop <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm for a while</u>
<u n="561" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="562" who="S0618">and people'd come in and go oh isn't it an awful day? <pause dur="short"/> and I want to say the day in of itself is neither awful nor not awful it all depends on your perception</u>
<u n="563" who="S0619">it's like the happiest day of someone's life</u>
<u n="564" who="S0618" trans="overlap">so what's pissed on your brain this morning? <pause dur="short"/> yeah exactly so</u>
<u n="565" who="S0619">someone's just got married they're having the best day</u>
<u n="566" who="S0618"><unclear/> it's just a topic of conversation really isn't it?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yes it is</u>
<u n="568" who="S0618">it's a topic of conversation <unclear/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0619" trans="overlap">it's a filler when you're not sure <unclear>what else to say</unclear></u>
<u n="570" who="S0618">yeah but then why do we choose something that's gonna bring something less than positive into the other person's energy stream you know?</u>
<u n="571" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0618">why are we saying oh isn't it all really shit? oh isn't it great? oh this rain's horrible isn't it? or <unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="573" who="S0619" trans="overlap">but I also say it er when the weather's nice you know I don't always you know only choose to do it <unclear/></u>
<u n="574" who="S0618" trans="overlap">you don't go oh isn't it hot? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no I always go I love blue skies blue sky's great er <pause dur="short"/> so I do cover all of the weather <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="576" who="S0618">oh okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0619">I'm not sort of <trunc>weath</trunc></u>
<u n="578" who="S0618">you're not weatherist</u>
<u n="579" who="S0619" trans="overlap">weatherist</u>
<u n="580" who="S0618">weatherist</u>
<u n="581" who="S0619" trans="overlap">weatherist</u>
<u n="582" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0619">I acknowledge all types of weather <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="584" who="S0618">well done <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0618">the full diversity the full spectrum</u>
<u n="587" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> anyway waved goodbye to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> won't see her cos she's flown Wednesday</u>
<u n="588" who="S0618">so she's been over for a week but</u>
<u n="589" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="590" who="S0618">you've hardly met really that's amazing I suppose they stayed in</u>
<u n="591" who="S0619">they were in <anon type="place"/> for a night yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0618">and they stayed in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="593" who="S0619">they didn't stay</u>
<u n="594" who="S0618">oh</u>
<u n="595" who="S0619">but I didn't see them at all that <unclear>well I</unclear> I saw them in in the morning they went to <anon type="place"/> and it was when I was at the party and I got back at one I think so they were back and in bed and er so just sort of seen them around breakfast time and they're eating well their breakfast time which is ten thirty which is my second breakfast time</u>
<u n="596" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="597" who="S0618">yeah after you've been to the gym and come home starving</u>
<u n="598" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="599" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've brought some spirulina with me and a food blender</u>
<u n="600" who="S0619">oh good for you</u>
<u n="601" who="S0618" trans="overlap">so we can have smoothies in the morning</u>
<u n="602" who="S0619">smoothie time</u>
<u n="603" who="S0618">yay</u>
<u n="604" who="S0619">good for you</u>
<u n="605" who="S0618">yeah it's quite handy coming in the van we would've been a bit stuffed had we got a bus</u>
<u n="606" who="S0619">I know and also the duvet <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="607" who="S0618">I know the bus with a double duvet</u>
<u n="608" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="609" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="610" who="S0619">yeah well I've brought a duvet a pillow and two blankets so that should be <unclear/></u>
<u n="611" who="S0618" trans="overlap">me too <pause dur="short"/> I meant to ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> how cold it is at this place</u>
<u n="612" who="S0619">I think there'll be heating</u>
<u n="613" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="614" who="S0619">from what she's said which I <trunc>th</trunc> I don't know how true this is it's a type of I think they're called pensions pensions <unclear/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh yeah like a guest house type thing?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I think so but it's a part of a convent</u>
<u n="617" who="S0618">ah</u>
<u n="618" who="S0619">or it's run by nuns and either way it's nun related</u>
<u n="619" who="S0618">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="620" who="S0619">cos her auntie is a nun</u>
<u n="621" who="S0618">nun related accommodation I like this okay</u>
<u n="622" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah <unclear/> erm and <pause dur="short"/> so they provide food for you er as they do in other types of pensions</u>
<u n="623" who="S0618" trans="overlap">ah hence the chicken for lunch</u>
<u n="624" who="S0619">hence the chicken</u>
<u n="625" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="626" who="S0619">erm so they provide food but they also have cooking facilities</u>
<u n="627" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="628" who="S0619">I don't know whether ordinarily you would be allowed to use them</u>
<u n="629" who="S0618" trans="overlap">well I asked <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she said yes you can</u>
<u n="630" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="631" who="S0618">so erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="632" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0618">I've got curry for one and then I've got erm soup for four that we can have another time</u>
<u n="634" who="S0619">oh good</u>
<u n="635" who="S0618">so</u>
<u n="636" who="S0619">sounds nice</u>
<u n="637" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah so <unclear/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0618" trans="overlap">on no it's broccoli oh shit we're all gonna be sleeping in one room and farting oh god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="640" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> in the same room <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="641" who="S0618">we may not wake up anyway <unclear/> okay</u>
<u n="642" who="S0619">erm yeah anyway what day is it? it's Monday</u>
<u n="643" who="S0618">Monday yeah</u>
<u n="644" who="S0619" trans="overlap">so no medication since don't know</u>
<u n="645" who="S0618">just before the party?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0619">I didn't think I had it or did I?</u>
<u n="647" who="S0618">I thought you told me you had a little snifter before the party so you could breathe and <unclear/></u>
<u n="648" who="S0619" trans="overlap">maybe I was maybe I was thinking about it</u>
<u n="649" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="650" who="S0619">but I don't think I did you know</u>
<u n="651" who="S0618">no good for you</u>
<u n="652" who="S0619">I don't think I did I've just been hammering this other prescribed thing</u>
<u n="653" who="S0618">uhu</u>
<u n="654" who="S0619">erm</u>
<u n="655" who="S0618">is that the nasal flush thing?</u>
<u n="656" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no no no this is it's like a steroid thing from the doctors that I've had for a while</u>
<u n="657" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0619">but it <trunc>d</trunc> it's not it's it it's one of those things where you don't <trunc>f</trunc> sense the relief as much as with this thing that I'm addicted to</u>
<u n="659" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="660" who="S0619">there is no sense of relief but it's you know more long term or long lasting or it's doing it sort of behind the scenes so it's not a quick release</u>
<u n="661" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="662" who="S0619">er</u>
<u n="663" who="S0618">so once it's taken a week or so to get in your system will you feel more relief?</u>
<u n="664" who="S0619" trans="overlap">hopefully yeah</u>
<u n="665" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="666" who="S0619">er and with this flush thing <pause dur="short"/> it's not <trunc>r</trunc> it's not quite right what I wanted is a thing which you just really spray this stream of water up one nostril and then the water comes out of the other</u>
<u n="667" who="S0618">oh lovely</u>
<u n="668" who="S0619">er and it's with it it takes all of the insides of your nose <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="669" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="670" who="S0619">erm it really clears you out but what I've got isn't that but it's not bad <pause dur="short"/> er but I'm definitely gonna take the medication tonight and tomorrow night just because I don't wanna be keeping people awake and I'm</u>
<u n="671" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh I forgot my earplugs okay</u>
<u n="672" who="S0619">really erm struggling with sleep</u>
<u n="673" who="S0618">are you?</u>
<u n="674" who="S0619">erm yeah I was up at half four and I don't think I went back to sleep then cos my alarm went off at half seven I was just tossing and turning</u>
<u n="675" who="S0618">there is a school of thought that suggests that humans only really need four to six hours in any one block</u>
<u n="676" who="S0619">yeah but I you know I know my body and I know that I need eight hours</u>
<u n="677" who="S0618">mm do you need it in one block?</u>
<u n="678" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="679" who="S0618">oh okay</u>
<u n="680" who="S0619">and that's for sort of optimum me during the week when I'm working it just drops to about seven</u>
<u n="681" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="682" who="S0619">and</u>
<u n="683" who="S0618">my optimum where I feel fantastic is five or six you know from midnight</u>
<u n="684" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="685" who="S0618">and then another hour or two from about five in the evening</u>
<u n="686" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="687" who="S0618">and I feel fabulous on that but at the moment I don't have enough to do and to keep me amused and entertained within the day</u>
<u n="688" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="689" who="S0618">to warrant so many waking hours so I'm indulging in sleep reality which from having fantastic dreams I've been really enjoying so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="690" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="691" who="S0618">I'm not gonna change at the moment I imagine when I'm farming I will slip back into a four to six hours and then an hour or two in the evening</u>
<u n="692" who="S0619">I can't nap I can't sleep during the day er <pause dur="short"/> I've never been able to on buses on trains on flights</u>
<u n="693" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="694" who="S0619">it's torture <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="695" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0619">in many ways like my dad can fall asleep within three minutes like</u>
<u n="697" who="S0618" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="698" who="S0619">on the sofa when he gets home from work</u>
<u n="699" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="700" who="S0619">I can't do that</u>
<u n="701" who="S0618">I can <pause dur="short"/> love it</u>
<u n="702" who="S0619">mm my mum's the same as me she just <pause dur="short"/> you know <unclear/> awake in the morning</u>
<u n="703" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="704" who="S0619">you know that's it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="705" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="706" who="S0619">no</u>
<u n="707" who="S0618">I became an accomplished napper when I first got my mortgage</u>
<u n="708" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="709" who="S0618">which is probably about fifteen years ago now and couldn't afford it as nobody could with mortgages back in the day and so I worked seven days a week and sometimes fifteen hours a day</u>
<u n="710" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0618">but there was a gap where I finished work at three in the afternoon and started again seven in the evening so I had to drive home which was about half an hour and then I'd have something to eat and then I would nap and then I'd get up and wash and then go to work in the evening till eleven or midnight or whatever and that nap between jobs was just so important</u>
<u n="712" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="713" who="S0618">it really was crucial to not killing myself driving and getting enough <pause dur="short"/> with hindsight I suppose I look back and <vocal desc="sigh"/> I think what a nut job working so bloody hard why did I do that? that was just crazy but hey you know done is done and that's the person I was back then so</u>
<u n="714" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0618">I don't regret it it just was as it was</u>
<u n="716" who="S0619">yeah erm you know I don't think I will ever be that person I don't have that <pause dur="short"/> characteristic or whatever er er er er to work hard or to work really long hours</u>
<u n="717" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="718" who="S0619">or to do more than is absolutely necessary</u>
<u n="719" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="720" who="S0619">I think we've talked about this before</u>
<u n="721" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0619">yeah but <pause dur="short"/> it's not for me and I think that's something that you get from your parents and their attitude to work which is my dad does the bare minimum <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="723" who="S0618">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="724" who="S0619">and my mum does so much that she you know drives herself mad</u>
<u n="725" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="726" who="S0619">and makes herself quite unwell so</u>
<u n="727" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah it's not good</u>
<u n="728" who="S0619">so I've sort of learnt from both of them I guess <pause dur="long"/> <shift new="singing"/> do do do do do <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="729" who="S0618">I know I had to turn Simon down erm because he was playing some music but I suppose now we're on the motorway I could</u>
<u n="730" who="S0619">no just <unclear/></u>
<u n="731" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="732" who="S0619"><unclear/> we'll get there at half one cos that's <unclear>really soon</unclear> that can't be right</u>
<u n="733" who="S0618">yeah well if we do we'll find a coffee shop</u>
<u n="734" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="735" who="S0618">erm I don't think we'll be soon because once we get on the seven which is south</u>
<u n="736" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <unclear/> slow right down</u>
<u n="737" who="S0618">yeah I'm presuming it's gonna have snow on it as well I'm amazed this road is clear</u>
<u n="738" who="S0619">I think they come out they come out er early</u>
<u n="739" who="S0618">wow really must do it's amazing</u>
<u n="740" who="S0619">but it is warming up you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="741" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah we're three point five degrees plus which is very <unclear/> we were minus half a degree when we were leaving <anon type="place"/> so</u>
<u n="742" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah we were</u>
<u n="743" who="S0618">it's warmer here</u>
<u n="744" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yep <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> it sounds really nice though from what people have said and loads of people are going to <anon type="place"/> this week</u>
<u n="745" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="746" who="S0619">it's gonna be rammed</u>
<u n="747" who="S0618">it really is I suppose it's gonna be full of school teachers</u>
<u n="748" who="S0619">true yeah kids</u>
<u n="749" who="S0618">oh no oh shit I forgot about that yeah oh no they're not allowed in the spa though are they?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0619">I think there's an adult only section</u>
<u n="751" who="S0618">that'll do rightly</u>
<u n="752" who="S0619"><unclear/> <unclear>that though</unclear> said to the school er sorry I am away until Wednesday <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="753" who="S0618">good for you I'm on holiday <pause dur="short"/> yeah what a work ethic huh?</u>
<u n="754" who="S0619">yep <pause dur="short"/> I did some work last week just writing these reports for other teachers so I've only got three to do at the moment take more than twenty minutes</u>
<u n="755" who="S0618">right</u>
<u n="756" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> I've never been to <anon type="place"/> have you?</u>
<u n="757" who="S0618"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="758" who="S0619"><anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh it's like a <unclear/></u>
<u n="759" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh shopping centre</u>
<u n="760" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="761" who="S0618">I think I've had a wee there</u>
<u n="762" who="S0619">ah nice</u>
<u n="763" who="S0618">I've I've weed most of the A4</u>
<u n="764" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="765" who="S0618">I must say services are vastly more abundant in south eastern Poland than they are in Northern Ireland</u>
<u n="766" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="767" who="S0618">when I first moved there <vocal desc="sigh"/> oh god two thousand and seven two thousand and eight something like that two thousand and six? no two thousand and seven erm <pause dur="short"/> there were no service stations there was nowhere to stop for a wee <vocal desc="laugh"/> so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="768" who="S0619">really?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0618">so I was driving all over the country trying to find a Tesco that was open and had a toilet</u>
<u n="770" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="771" who="S0618">erm ended up weeing in ditches a lot trying not to get my nice suits too dirty my shiny shoes too muddy <pause dur="short"/> so yeah car's a bit slow caught me by surprise erm</u>
<u n="772" who="S0619">very odd</u>
<u n="773" who="S0618">yeah then you move here and you've got these gorgeous motorways</u>
<u n="774" who="S0619">yep</u>
<u n="775" who="S0618">and er an abundance of services it's fantastic <pause dur="short"/> more please Poland well done</u>
<u n="776" who="S0619">I like service stations don't go enough</u>
<u n="777" who="S0618">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="778" who="S0619">maybe once a year</u>
<u n="779" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="780" who="S0619">the best one is in the Scottish borders</u>
<u n="781" who="S0618">I know it</u>
<u n="782" who="S0619">is it the one with the fish pond outside?</u>
<u n="783" who="S0618">yes</u>
<u n="784" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="785" who="S0618">which was frozen when I was there and it's got</u>
<u n="786" who="S0619" trans="overlap">that's everyone's favourite services in England</u>
<u n="787" who="S0618" trans="overlap">like <pause dur="short"/> five star Michelin grade food is that the one?</u>
<u n="788" who="S0619">oh I don't know I've never had the food</u>
<u n="789" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="790" who="S0619">I always stopped for a coffee when I was at uni</u>
<u n="791" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> really luxurious</u>
<u n="792" who="S0619">I definite there's definitely one it's the only one I can think of erm with a fish pond</u>
<u n="793" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="794" who="S0619">must be the same</u>
<u n="795" who="S0618">must be the same one yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's funny <pause dur="short"/> yeah if I erm do the ferry boat from Northern Ireland to <anon type="place"/> in Scotland and drive down to England and do the reverse back I'm usually ready for some cheap diesel and a wee by the time I reach there so and it's nice just to park the van up and walk about as well</u>
<u n="796" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="797" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="798" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah there's lots</u>
<u n="799" who="S0618">nice bit</u>
<u n="800" who="S0619">of nice places yeah <pause dur="long"/> oh <vocal desc="yawn"/> I'm trying to think what other news I have <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="801" who="S0618">well there's quite a lot of news actually I think not seeing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is a big bit of news</u>
<u n="802" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="803" who="S0618">that's a big change in your life</u>
<u n="804" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="805" who="S0618">yeah oh yeah February you were saying you wouldn't mind coming back to this spa place in February</u>
<u n="806" who="S0619">was I?</u>
<u n="807" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="808" who="S0618">what were you saying about February?</u>
<u n="809" who="S0619">I don't know</u>
<u n="810" who="S0618">oh</u>
<u n="811" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="812" who="S0618">oh I don't know oh</u>
<u n="813" who="S0619" trans="overlap">erm February February</u>
<u n="814" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="815" who="S0619">I can't remember I've said so much <vocal desc="laugh"/> er I think er you know having this is really good cos you you just have to say it you just have to say whatever is in your mind</u>
<u n="816" who="S0618">it's good</u>
<u n="817" who="S0619">I think it is really</u>
<u n="818" who="S0618">therapy</u>
<u n="819" who="S0619">it is it's really er <unclear/> people talk a lot but they don't talk maybe enough I don't know</u>
<u n="820" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="821" who="S0619">I'm quite a sort of <pause dur="short"/> quiet person if I can stay quiet I er I will</u>
<u n="822" who="S0618">my three week sore throat has disappeared since we've been talking</u>
<u n="823" who="S0619">yeah? good</u>
<u n="824" who="S0618">yeah and I <trunc>kn</trunc> you know I know from past experience any throat blockage is something that's going unsaid so</u>
<u n="825" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="826" who="S0618">yeah it's good</u>
<u n="827" who="S0619">yeah I've been coughing a lot at night and I think it's because <pause dur="short"/> there was things that I needed to get out</u>
<u n="828" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="829" who="S0619"><unclear/> so</u>
<u n="830" who="S0618">is it a productive cough?</u>
<u n="831" who="S0619">no well it's it's hopefully it'll stop now <vocal desc="laugh"/> seeing as I've said what's needed to be said and it's</u>
<u n="832" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="833" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="834" who="S0618">stop the music I'm trying to sort that out <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how to <trunc>s</trunc> keep Simon sat nav on but er stop the music coming from my Iphone <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'll just turn it down</u>
<u n="835" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="836" who="S0619">kind of nice</u>
<u n="837" who="S0618">well I know it's it's erm <pause dur="short"/> it's er <unclear>jesus christ</unclear></u>
<u n="838" who="S0619" trans="overlap">jeez</u>
<u n="839" who="S0618">I know this is Polish overtaking <pause dur="short"/> I hope you haven't been too freaked out by my driving in the UK I like to leave loads of room and pull out in loads of time and pull back and just have big distances between me and other vehicles</u>
<u n="840" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="841" who="S0618">but that's not the culture here you pull out at the last minute and as soon as you've overtaken you're expected to pull in again <pause dur="short"/> could be a little bit <vocal desc="misc"/> at times <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> ah no</u>
<u n="842" who="S0619">so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s away</u>
<u n="843" who="S0618">yeah I meant to send her a message this morning</u>
<u n="844" who="S0619">yeah I <trunc>d</trunc> well we were just mid-conversation er when I left the house <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I've not actually said</u>
<u n="845" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="846" who="S0619">what I wanted to say but I was just telling her about yesterday and she was <pause dur="short"/> being very nice and supportive</u>
<u n="847" who="S0618">yeah she's a nice and supportive friend isn't she?</u>
<u n="848" who="S0619" trans="overlap">she is lovely friend</u>
<u n="849" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="850" who="S0619">sometimes I find her difficult to talk to I think we're both quite maybe quite quiet I don't know</u>
<u n="851" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> me three</u>
<u n="852" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="853" who="S0618">yeah I suppose <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is the talkative one out of the all of us</u>
<u n="854" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah she is</u>
<u n="855" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="856" who="S0619"><unclear>but yeah</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="857" who="S0618" trans="overlap">actually I find you really talkative as well <unclear/></u>
<u n="858" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I find you really talkative</u>
<u n="859" who="S0618">do you? oh my god</u>
<u n="860" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="861" who="S0618">I would say that you are more talkative than me in our groups would you say that I'm more talkative than you in our groups?</u>
<u n="862" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah for sure</u>
<u n="863" who="S0618">oh my god</u>
<u n="864" who="S0619">oh what? in the in the Whatsapp groups? or in real life?</u>
<u n="865" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh er no I mean in life like</u>
<u n="866" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="867" who="S0618">if we're together I mean on Whatsapp <trunc>y</trunc>yeah I'm quite talkative in that</u>
<u n="868" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah and I don't really use it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="869" who="S0618">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="870" who="S0619">just read</u>
<u n="871" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="872" who="S0619">erm</u>
<u n="873" who="S0618">you're a lurker</u>
<u n="874" who="S0619">I am a lurker yes</u>
<u n="875" who="S0618">that's okay</u>
<u n="876" who="S0619">er in real life yeah I think</u>
<u n="877" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> real life</u>
<u n="878" who="S0619">you're more talkative than I am</u>
<u n="879" who="S0618">as opposed to made up life</u>
<u n="880" who="S0619">virtual yeah virtual reality</u>
<u n="881" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="882" who="S0619">erm yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s always got something to say I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is quite quiet quite quiet</u>
<u n="883" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="884" who="S0619"><unclear/></u>
<u n="885" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s quiet</u>
<u n="886" who="S0619"><trunc>y</trunc>yeah</u>
<u n="887" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="888" who="S0619">well I <vocal desc="laugh"/> would be if I was fifteen <unclear/></u>
<u n="889" who="S0618">well and had <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for a mother who talks a lot</u>
<u n="890" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="891" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="892" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="893" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="894" who="S0619">it's funny isn't it? how <pause dur="short"/> the way that you see yourself is is different to how other people see you</u>
<u n="895" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="896" who="S0619">and it's not it's not a sort of a negative thing a lot of the time it can be quite interesting when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said I was attention-seeking and self-destructive</u>
<u n="897" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="898" who="S0619">I thought about that for about well I still think about it <unclear/></u>
<u n="899" who="S0618">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="900" who="S0619" trans="overlap">am I? am I though? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="901" who="S0618">do I detect a little mirror <vocal desc="laugh"/> reflecting back at him there?</u>
<u n="902" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah and I thought goodness</u>
<u n="903" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="904" who="S0619">I just don't think I'm either of those things <unclear>but</unclear></u>
<u n="905" who="S0618">if I had to say does who does that apply to all the more? you or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="906" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="907" who="S0618">I would say <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> by a country mile</u>
<u n="908" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="909" who="S0618">I think he's seeing in you what is more apparent in himself</u>
<u n="910" who="S0619">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I sort of you know it we were drunk and we were arguing</u>
<u n="911" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="912" who="S0619">er I mean I wasn't arguing I wasn't saying anything at all he we just sort of shouting at me <vocal desc="laugh"/> er</u>
<u n="913" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay so he was arguing</u>
<u n="914" who="S0619">so he was arguing I sat and just sort of stared at the wall <vocal desc="laugh"/> er and then <pause dur="short"/> someone was like right <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> out of there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="915" who="S0618">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="916" who="S0619">out <unclear/> er <pause dur="short"/> yeah and I was really upset and I really thought about it all over Christmas this was in December and I spent all of Christmas thinking <pause dur="short"/> how am I self-destructive? I just don't think I am</u>
<u n="917" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I suppose if somebody says something like that to you that is really quite a striking comment</u>
<u n="918" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0618">then yeah you owe it yourself to look at that</u>
<u n="920" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="921" who="S0618">and turn it over in your mind running through your emotions</u>
<u n="922" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="923" who="S0618">and if it doesn't resonate with you as truth then reject it</u>
<u n="924" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="925" who="S0618">cos your truth is the only one that matters somebody else's is their subjective idea of you it's not real</u>
<u n="926" who="S0619">true yes</u>
<u n="927" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so bollocks <vocal desc="laugh"/> fuck off <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="928" who="S0619" trans="overlap">bollocks to that</u>
<u n="929" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="930" who="S0619" trans="overlap">you know attention-seeking possibly but self-destructive I don't think so</u>
<u n="931" who="S0618" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> I perceive <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to be attention-seeking self-destructive I don't know about I don't really feel I know him well enough</u>
<u n="932" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="933" who="S0618">but I would say he's attention-seeking</u>
<u n="934" who="S0619">it's sort of the way that he acts and you know the way he presents himself to the world</u>
<u n="935" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="936" who="S0619">says I want people to notice me</u>
<u n="937" who="S0618">yeah and to like me</u>
<u n="938" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="939" who="S0618" trans="overlap">well we all like to be liked but yeah</u>
<u n="940" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="941" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>interesting</unclear></u>
<u n="942" who="S0619"><unclear/> so we must be turning south</u>
<u n="943" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> we will this is so weird this next bit of road because on the map it looks like you head west to <anon type="place"/> you get to <anon type="place"/> and oh hang on my road's disappearing and do I need to move over? I think I do</u>
<u n="944" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="945" who="S0618">and I need to indicate that way yes erm so yeah it looks like you drive west to <anon type="place"/> and then when you get there you turn left and then head south towards <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> but you'll see it just looks like we end up driving towards built-up <anon type="place"/> and every time I think am I going the right way?</u>
<u n="946" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="947" who="S0618">and I am because we're on the seven and then you're on the seven till pretty much <anon type="place"/> where the hippies live so yeah</u>
<u n="948" who="S0619">I see</u>
<u n="949" who="S0618">but you'll see what I mean <pause dur="short"/> and I do think this is much quicker than going <anon type="place"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="950" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="951" who="S0618">just cos you've got this much motorway and actually the motorway is surprisingly clear I wonder had we headed south and then west if we would have encountered a lot more snow bad weather</u>
<u n="952" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="953" who="S0618">so</u>
<u n="954" who="S0619">yep</u>
<u n="955" who="S0618">anyway who knows?</u>
<u n="956" who="S0619">who knows? anyway <unclear/></u>
<u n="957" who="S0618" trans="overlap">jeez I'm trying to keep this windscreen clean <pause dur="short"/> can you actually see? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="958" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> no no <trunc>ch</trunc> sound <unclear/></u>
<u n="959" who="S0618" trans="overlap">it was funny having <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the passenger seat on the way back from our little jolly <vocal desc="laugh"/> the other day</u>
<u n="960" who="S0619" trans="overlap">she was funny</u>
<u n="961" who="S0618">pronouncing place names er oh my god and er most place names seem to have so many syllables</u>
<u n="962" who="S0619"><unclear/></u>
<u n="963" who="S0618">ah doesn't really does it?</u>
<u n="964" who="S0619">ah everyone's going to <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="965" who="S0618">they are did you wonder where all of the school teachers in Poland were? well they're here I think there are traffic lights up here that's what that is</u>
<u n="966" who="S0619">oh</u>
<u n="967" who="S0618">so the ones on the left had to stop to let us all go</u>
<u n="968" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="969" who="S0618">yeah there we are look</u>
<u n="970" who="S0619">erm er I had a message from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="971" who="S0618">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="972" who="S0619"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in <anon type="place"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="973" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="974" who="S0619">last week</u>
<u n="975" who="S0618">and?</u>
<u n="976" who="S0619">and he said oh are you free at the weekend just just gone and I said</u>
<u n="977" who="S0618">no</u>
<u n="978" who="S0619">er no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="979" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="980" who="S0619">well you know I was but I sort of said no</u>
<u n="981" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="982" who="S0619">erm and then I said I'll be free next weekend cos he's not on winter break yet</u>
<u n="983" who="S0618">as in the one that's coming?</u>
<u n="984" who="S0619">yep</u>
<u n="985" who="S0618">oh cool</u>
<u n="986" who="S0619">er</u>
<u n="987" who="S0618" trans="overlap">he's got a winter break?</u>
<u n="988" who="S0619">it's <trunc>s</trunc>staggered we're in a different erm</u>
<u n="989" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> ah</u>
<u n="990" who="S0619">we're in</u>
<u n="991" who="S0618" trans="overlap">a different time zone</u>
<u n="992" who="S0619"><anon type="place"/> and he's in the other one <unclear/></u>
<u n="993" who="S0618">he's still in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="994" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no it's different we're</u>
<u n="995" who="S0618">ah</u>
<u n="996" who="S0619">not in <anon type="place"/> but we're in something else</u>
<u n="997" who="S0618">oh <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="998" who="S0619">er we're in the <anon type="place"/> one and he's in the <anon type="place"/> one</u>
<u n="999" who="S0618">oh okay</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0619">and they have different they stagger the holidays through the country so that not everyone <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1001" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah not everyone is driving to <anon type="place"/> at the same time <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1002" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> at the same time <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1003" who="S0618">a whole country</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0619">yeah erm</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0618"><anon type="place"/> I suppose is gonna be <unclear/></u>
<u n="1006" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0618">they they'd all go to <anon type="place"/> though wouldn't they? cos it's closer</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0619">possibly yeah</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0618">I need a wee</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0619">so do I <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1011" who="S0618">oh okay find somewhere I think we can probably do coffee break at some point if you're up for that?</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0618">cos we've got yeah it's not even half past twelve yet and we're already heading south</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0618">oh mind you time of arrival half past one so ah bloody red light <unclear/> so let's envisage green lights from here on in</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0618">so it's all green green for go yeah</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> green for go <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0618">where were we? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1020" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah so I said</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0619">I'll be free next weekend if you want to come for a coffee because I'm not drinking and he said oh I've got no money anyway so that'll be nice and I said I might go to the to the ethnography</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0618">oh the ethnographic museum</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0619" trans="overlap">ethnography</u>
<u n="1025" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1026" who="S0619">yeah I don't know how to say this word</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> museum</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0619" trans="overlap">ethnographic museum for the Egyptian</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0619">exhibition and er gypsy caravans in the garden if you would like to join us</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0618">cool</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0619">you see how you feel</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0618" trans="overlap">cool <pause dur="short"/> on Saturday I'm going to <anon type="place"/> to have lunch with one of my CELTA friends</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0619">oh nice</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0618"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1036" who="S0619">nice</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0618"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm so yeah</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0619">oh so maybe Sunday or maybe <unclear>do without you</unclear> whatever you decide</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah yeah maybe Sunday</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0619">maybe Sunday <unclear/> that</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0618" trans="overlap">at least he's being upfront about not having any money</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0618">so take a flask then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1044" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0618">but yeah</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0619" trans="overlap">or</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0618">it's difficult actually cos you're gonna wanna stop at some point to warm up</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0618">mm anyway <unclear/></u>
<u n="1050" who="S0619">or</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0618">green light</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0619" trans="overlap">we could go to <anon type="place"/> if you fancy it</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0618">yeah no it'd be nice</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear>it's safe there</unclear></u>
<u n="1055" who="S0618">I don't mind a trip on Sunday I'd love to catch up with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well I really like him he's a lovely guy</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah I've not seen him for ages</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I quite like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when he's sober and not being depressive on drugs so</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah well we could go to</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0619"><anon type="place"/> on Sunday <vocal desc="laugh"/> can't get away er there's a nice coffee place</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0618">yeah?</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0619">called <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1063" who="S0618"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1065" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what? as in grundy undies <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> er I think it's someone's name</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0618">oh okay</u>
<u n="1068" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1069" who="S0618">there's a Polish man's name that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's hilarious</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0619">I dunno whose name it is <unclear/></u>
<u n="1073" who="S0618" trans="overlap">what's your baby boy called? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oh lovely</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no a surname I think not a first name</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0618">oh okay <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's any better <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1076" who="S0619"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1077" who="S0618">we're the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> family</u>
<u n="1078" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1079" who="S0618">what's the English equivalent? skidmark?</u>
<u n="1080" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1081" who="S0618">oh dear</u>
<u n="1082" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1083" who="S0618">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> so yeah that'd be good</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0619">mm yeah we'll see how we feel <unclear>anyway</unclear></u>
<u n="1085" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0619"><unclear>still trying</unclear> to decide and I need to do a bit of work at the weekend only on Saturday <unclear/></u>
<u n="1087" who="S0618" trans="overlap">really? oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> everybody's back to</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear>elephant</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1089" who="S0618">oh yeah everybody's back to working so hard now and I'm gonna be so bored next week I'm gonna go somewhere I might go to <anon type="place"/> for a couple of nights</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0619">oh nice</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0618">yeah I'm gonna have to do something cos you're all gonna be off working really hard again and I'm just gonna get bored if I now car you're going to let me in I know I'm slow going uphill but I'm coming out anyway thank you erm yeah</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0619"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> can't believe <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been to</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0618">the UAE</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0619">UAE</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0619">is that is</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0618"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1098" who="S0619">er it's own country? or is that just the collective term for the area?</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0618">oh my god that's a really good question as far as I'm aware it's</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0619" trans="overlap">cos I said to</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0618">a country</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0619">ah</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0618">but now you mention it that's put a question mark in my mind</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0619" trans="overlap">cos I thought <pause dur="short"/> er United Arab Emirates was the whole shebang</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0618">no I'm sure they've got a football team</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0619">ah okay mm <unclear>what</unclear> a strange place to go must be expensive well I dunno I've never been well I don't know where it is</u>
<u n="1107" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1108" who="S0619">it's you know near Dubai and the rest of them</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0618">yeah that part of the world really does not appeal to me</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0619">does it not?</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0618">no the whole sort of Jerusalem Bethlehem thing does and then</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0618">sort of Georgia and around there the poorer nations do</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah I'd like to Israel</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0618" trans="overlap">but yeah I've been to Israel it's pretty cool but this whole affluence thing that's</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0618">I dunno it's just like how man fucks nature basically you know building this well building buildings in the middle of the desert</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0618">it just seems so artificial</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0618">and so abhorrent</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0619">erm</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0618">okay speed camera what was the speed limit? <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0619">seventy</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0618">speed of the car in front that's pointing the other way anyway erm</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0619">what was I gonna say? I know loads of people who live in Dubai loads of friends er teachers and er people who work for Emirates Airlines</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0619">er and I know my cousin lives in <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> erm with his friend er and my auntie and uncle went to visit him</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0619">and it just sounds the most ridiculous place er it's like you know you talk about culture shock but this is something else</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0619">erm and the amount of money and how expensive things are they were taking him like <vocal desc="laugh"/> Uncle Ben's rice cos otherwise if you buy it there it's like ten pounds a packet <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1133" who="S0618">what? jeez</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1135" who="S0618" trans="overlap">okay it's not on the bucket list <unclear/></u>
<u n="1136" who="S0619">er you know and I've taught kids from Saudi Arabia kids from Dubai kids from all of that area and the girls are great but the boys are just awful</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0618">arrogant arses?</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0619" trans="overlap">they er they are ten years old and they think they own the world</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0618">oh god</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0619">because they've not been told otherwise</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0618">yeah not been taught manners</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0619">yeah er and someone I know <pause dur="short"/> told me a story about er a maid er a a an English woman who went to work in Dubai as like a maid and er look after the kids like an au pair erm and <pause dur="short"/> on the first day the boy sat on his bed and went dress me</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1144" who="S0619">and</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0618">what?</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0619">er and he went well <trunc>i</trunc>it's part of your job you have to dress me and she went and she said well I'm just gonna go downstairs either you get dressed yourself or you go to school without any clothes on <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1147" who="S0618">fair enough</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0619">er so</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0618">wow</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0619">and then from there he learnt to dress himself</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0618">very good yeah no <pause dur="short"/> I had a friend whose husband worked in <anon type="place"/> and lived there and it sounds like the worth or value that other people give you based on your bank balance</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0618">and your parents' economic affluence</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0618">and I find that also abhorrent</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0618">it's not a culture I want to engage with on that level</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0619">no</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0618">oh jesus are you pulling out? you can stay there and you can pull out ah</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0619">ah</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0618">ah <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1163" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1164" who="S0618">stuck <pause dur="short"/> can now move along thank you isn't this beautiful?</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0619">absolutely stunning</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0618" trans="overlap">woo this is one of my favourite bits when you come over this hill actually I'd forgotten about that actually</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0619">it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="1168" who="S0618">bugger all snow though hey?</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0619">it's all melted</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0618">yeah <unclear/> said skiing conditions were perfect</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0619">oh good</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0618">not too much snow not too ice well yeah not too icy just perfect so looking forward to that</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0619">oh good good good</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0618"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1175" who="S0619" trans="overlap">I thought it'd take hours and hours</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0618">no I've done this trip a few times visiting hippies and it erm I can get to <anon type="place"/> in a little over a couple of hours</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0618">then I'm just up the mountain and round <unclear/></u>
<u n="1179" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0618">yeah a little bit off the beaten track after that are you cold?</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0619">no I'm not</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0618">okay</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0619">I'm just just right</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0618">might just divert that onto the tootsies cos my <trunc>f</trunc> I've got <unclear>no foot</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1185" who="S0619">oh no</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0618"><unclear>I think</unclear> a little bit cold</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0619"><shift new="singing"/> do do do do do do do my leg's gonna really hurt tomorrow <shift new="normal"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> at the time I was like this is really gonna cane in the morning</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0619"><unclear/> I've had some spirulina and I've had some protein and</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0618">good</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0619">had to put some <pause dur="short"/> chia seeds this morning</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0618">lovely</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0619" trans="overlap">in my <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> in my millet porridge <unclear/></u>
<u n="1194" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh that is disgusting I can't believe you're mixing all of that with millet millet to me is like erm</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0619">it's like mashed potato</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0618">yeah you can make millet mash if you <vocal desc="laugh"/> make it really wet that you obviously are erm but otherwise it's just like fluffy grains like couscous</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0618"><unclear/> vegetables stir fry veg or something mix it all in it's lovely</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah it's really wet</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you're funny</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well er once you put some cranberries in it and some peanut butter and some honey it just</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's all fine</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0619">could be anything</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0619">you know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1206" who="S0618">fair enough <pause dur="short"/> fair enough</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0619"><vocal desc="sigh"/> and I was seeing if it's like nutritionally better than erm <pause dur="short"/> oats but er <vocal desc="sigh"/> it's all much of a muchness I think</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0619">if you get into that wheaty territory</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0618">am I meant to be giving way to that? oh it's a person at a bus stop it's not a person at a pedestrian crossing <pause dur="short"/> yeah what did I have? I had chia seeds and I had bananas and I had <vocal desc="misc"/> goji berries and cacao powder and spirulina</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1212" who="S0618">and I finished off my soya milk just cos I didn't wanna leave it in the fridge</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0618">I think that's the road you take to go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1215" who="S0619">uhu <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="1216" who="S0618">yeah it is fifty-two erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah and it was delicious and I thought get the goji berries and the cacao down but I'm still not bleeding</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0618">so if I'm pregnant and it it's the immaculate conception you'll believe me won't you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1219" who="S0619">absolutely <unclear/></u>
<u n="1220" who="S0618">I don't think the tabloid press <unclear>would but</unclear></u>
<u n="1221" who="S0619"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="1222" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0619">but no I'm expecting it to occur</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0618">I know I could</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0619" trans="overlap">imminently</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0618">spontaneously combust any moment</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0619">imminently</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear>of course</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's all well no because <pause dur="short"/> it should be another week but I just don't think it's going to be</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0618">ah no I think I'm a couple of days overdue <pause dur="short"/> ah <vocal desc="yawn"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1231" who="S0619"><shift new="singing"/> do do do do do do <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1232" who="S0618">so what do we say here? looks like anticipated arrival time one thirty we've got another seventy-five kilometres so <pause dur="short"/> I think I'll try and stop at one of these I think there's an Orlen one of these massive petrol stations that's not a services but that's got a little café in it</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0619">okay</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0618">so I'll pull over there get some diesel and then we can get a nice cuppa in there if you fancy it?</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0619">yes please <pause dur="short"/> just need the toilet <unclear>more</unclear></u>
<u n="1236" who="S0618">yeah I need a wee</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0619">I mean it's not desperate</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0619" trans="overlap">just always bloody happens</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0618">I know I mean there's one in the van but I just try not to use it cos then I've got to empty it</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0618">er usually comes a point in the spring where I start using it but</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0619">mm <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="1244" who="S0618" trans="overlap">winter I'm not</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1246" who="S0618">not usually in the van that much</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0619"><vocal desc="yawn"/> erm what was I gonna say? er er er er er I've just been drinking so much water the past few weeks I think cos I'm exercising more and just thirsty</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0619">in litres a day</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0618"><unclear>it's er</unclear> good</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0619" trans="overlap">between three and four I think</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0618">that's perfect yeah</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0619"><unclear/> good enough for me and feeling thirsty as well</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0619">I think your body adapts</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0618">it does yeah</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0619">and the more you drink it expects that every day</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0619">whereas <pause dur="short"/> you know lots of people don't drink anything er and they don't seem to feel thirsty</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I've noticed that <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0618">she drinks coffee but never water she never needs a wee <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1263" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1264" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1265" who="S0619">I know in some ways it's completely stupid cos I'm having loads of wees in the night but</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0619">it's a small price to pay <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1268" who="S0618"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1269" who="S0619">I was super bloated the other night I took a picture and sent it to my friend I could've been having a baby you know I was so bloated it looked outrageous</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0618" trans="overlap">what did you eat <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0619"><unclear/> no neither I'd made some pork</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0619">with er mash potatoes and sweetcorn</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0618">proper mash?</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0618">that you did from potatoes?</u>
<u n="1277" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1278" who="S0618">to get rather than a bag of Smash or something</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0619">no actual actual potato</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0618" trans="overlap">actual spuds?</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0619">actual human potato</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0618"><unclear/> milk and butter with them?</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0619">er did I? I put butter oh no not only milk cos I didn't have any butter but I drink loads of milk</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0619">and don't have any bloatiness</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0618">well</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0619">but I think maybe I ate too quickly or something</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0618">yeah perhaps</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0619">don't know</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0618">I suppose pork'll take a while to digest</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0619">yeah maybe it's the <trunc>f</trunc> I dunno the fat and the pork I don't know</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0618">did you read that stuff about vegan bodybuilders?</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> there's a lot and there's</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0619">interesting</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0618">there's some British boxer guy who wins load of stuff world champion blah de blah David someone or other he's vegan</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0619">uhu</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0618">erm yeah there are quite a lot it's thought that erm <pause dur="short"/> your body gets more energy like oh a speed camera pure energy the closer your food is to er sunshine so like</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0619" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0618">raw vegetables are meant to be the best</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah I</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> alkaline and just yeah close to sunshine</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0619">I've read or I watched the videos er of this person on Youtube who is on a raw <trunc>f</trunc> plant-based sort of vegan diet er and her body there's not a scrap of fat on it</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0619">and she has so much energy but I just <trunc>ins</trunc> I don't know</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0618">but you're living in Poland</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0618">I think not a scrap of fat would be a real problem</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0619">uhu yeah she lives in Australia this girl</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0619">so she's <unclear/></u>
<u n="1312" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah my friend in Australia <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's raw vegan and bursting with energy</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0618">and I ate pretty much raw when I was there apart from a few meals but then it was the height of summer and forty degrees</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0618">but it I felt fantastic on it you know</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0618">juicing every morning erm a lot <unclear>you know</unclear> just a lot of raw food but it's <unclear/> for so much more accessible there as well cos you can get</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0618">raw vegan cafes</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0619"><vocal desc="cough"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0618">erm yeah</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0619">erm</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0618">oh jesus I thought that van was going into that car then</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0618">oh that was tight anyway <pause dur="short"/> yeah and then I got back to the UK in January and tried to carry on with the raw stuff and just couldn't do it</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0618"><unclear>I was</unclear> bloody freezing and so I got very <vocal desc="laugh"/> quickly into soups and stews and curries again</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0619">yep</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0619">I'm due a soup</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0618">well there's broccoli in the back</u>
<u n="1333" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1334" who="S0619">right now</u>
<u n="1335" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1336" who="S0619">erm</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0618">well it's frozen at the moment</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1339" who="S0618"><unclear/> you might have to wait <unclear>erm cooking up yeah</unclear> it's like a big block of green ice</u>
<u n="1340" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1341" who="S0619">oh that's funny</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0619">erm what was I gonna say? don't know I love er being on holiday and eating so much fish</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0619">just eat fish every day all day every day and fresh fresh fish and fresh vegetables</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0618">if you ever go to Northern Ireland and County Down and the east coast let me know and I'll give you directions to where you can it's like erm it's actually in <anon type="place"/> where George Best the footballer lived there for a time</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0618">and I think his family still do but anyway it's a place where the boats come in and it's a factory where they then sort of skin all of the fish and chop all the bits out and package them up put them on ice for shipping to supermarket shipping abroad whatever but they don't mind anybody just wandering into the warehouse or to the factory</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh just take things</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1350" who="S0618">and just sort of pointing at what you want and <unclear>then</unclear> you can have a bit of whatever they happen to be chopping up and you won't get fresher because it's all been</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0618">caught right there that morning</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0619"><unclear>delish</unclear></u>
<u n="1354" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I did eat fish when I lived there and I didn't before I lived in that part of the world and I think that's part of it it seems so honest</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0618">in a way and you know supporting your local community and they weren't taking the piss and being unsustainable</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0618">erm it's just like <unclear>a small concern</unclear> and then since I've left there I've stopped eating it again</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0618">and I won't have it in restaurants <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> but again you know er yeah <unclear/> Argentina I ended up living near the sea or near a fishing community I probably would eat it again</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0619">I'm excited for summer and I'm excited for September and the possibilities er <pause dur="short"/> and sunshine</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0618">yay</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0619" trans="overlap">and the ocean</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0618">I keep thinking you know I might just fuck off to Tenerife for a week in February</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0619">mm <pause dur="short"/> do it</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0618" trans="overlap">because I can I know</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0619">that was my plan for winter break or that's what I was thinking of doing anyway</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah I was always checking flights <unclear/></u>
<u n="1370" who="S0618">you can do Tenerife south from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1371" who="S0619">yeah that's what I was looking <unclear/></u>
<u n="1372" who="S0618" trans="overlap">it's really cheap it was like I dunno fifty quid return</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0618">last time I looked yeah I might just have a look at that and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the friend I have trips with now and again he found this incredibly cheap <trunc>c</trunc>car company on Tenerife erm and you need to organise your own insurance cos they do rip you off a bit there if they can but you can do that online for like twenty quid or something for a week and then I think we hired a car for forty quid for the week</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0618">and other places were wanting <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>f</trunc> like twenty-five quid a day or something ridiculous</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1378" who="S0618">worked out really well and fuel was very cheap so <unclear>cover all</unclear> of the island and me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> seem to like the same things I did notice that he was walking a lot less but then he had a heart attack about a fortnight after he got back so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1379" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0618">I don't think he was very well at the time he's had a couple of stints now and <pause dur="short"/> he's walking and cycling a lot more again</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0619">oh good</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0618">why are you all pulling in in front of me and making me brake? because you were all turning okay <pause dur="long"/> yeah <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> so what does this say?</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0619">sixty-six minutes to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1384" who="S0618">to <anon type="place"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so we are bright and early</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0619">god it's beautiful</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0618">isn't it? you can see why I want to live here</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0619">yeah for sure for sure for sure</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> or let me rephrase that you can see why I'm going to live here</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0619">yeah yes</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="long"/> hang on I've just thought actually let me just stop that er about an hour and thirteen I must stop that and start a new one</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
