<text id="SNCL">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:16:04</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-09</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0336 S0337</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>At home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>driving, cars, commuting, saving</topics>
		<activity>Cooking dinner</activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0336">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Wegberg</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Germany</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>none</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Peterborough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>17 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>German -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0337">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Peterborough</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>none</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Peterborough</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0336">I erm have pretty much decided that I'm not gonna to drive to work any more</u>
<u n="2" who="S0337">any more any more</u>
<u n="3" who="S0336">any more any more</u>
<u n="4" who="S0337">okay</u>
<u n="5" who="S0336">erm my car isn't reliable in the slightest and I'm just not enjoying it at all like <pause dur="short"/> aside from the like the congestion traffic et cetera et cetera like obviously with it getting darker now for the whole hour I'm driving home I'm just <pause dur="short"/> I'm squinting and I'm starting in like into headlights and it's just not <pause dur="short"/> very nice and I I get to work in the morning and I'm exhausted because I've had to concentrate so hard for the last hour just to get myself to work I'm exhausted by the time I start and when I get home I'm exhausted because <pause dur="short"/> I've done a whole day's work and then I've had to drive home for an hour <pause dur="short"/> so I'm getting home and it's it's not even seven o'clock and I'm absolutely shattered whereas like <pause dur="short"/> even though the train is a little bit more of a faff <pause dur="short"/> but when I get to work on on the mornings I get the train even though I've left probably for work about forty minutes earlier than I would be car I'm <trunc>actuall</trunc> I've got more energy by the time I get to work and then</u>
<u n="6" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0336">coming home like I've got plenty of energy when I get home to do stuff</u>
<u n="8" who="S0337">okay if that's what you wanna do that's what you'll do</u>
<u n="9" who="S0336">and the way I see it like that</u>
<u n="10" who="S0337" trans="overlap">you need if you need to take the car you can take it</u>
<u n="11" who="S0336">well the way I see is that like <pause dur="short"/> erm this way I'm getting incidental exercise so I don't have to feel so bad about like not getting to the gym and stuff erm <pause dur="short"/> but er that kind of brings me to my car <pause dur="short"/> I wanna get rid</u>
<u n="12" who="S0337">okay</u>
<u n="13" who="S0336">I don't see the point of holding onto it obviously I've said I wanna take you out in it tonight to listen to it you know when you just I know it's about to cost me more money? it is about to cost me more money I was I was kind of surprised that they were even willing to offer me like six or seven hundred quid for it because it's done so many miles and it's so old and it is battered <pause dur="short"/> but I'm surprised it's even worth that at the moment <pause dur="short"/> my concern is actually if I let it get to a state where it needs more work again not only is it gonna cost me money but actually the value of the car isn't gonna warrant me paying it <pause dur="short"/> if the car's worth six hundred quid now I don't wanna keep spending two or three hundred pound at a time to fix it cos that's <trunc>jus</trunc> ridiculous</u>
<u n="14" who="S0337">it's not actually <unclear/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0336" trans="overlap">I'm never gonna get that money back <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> which brings me onto <pause dur="short"/> something we were talking about yesterday in that <pause dur="short"/> erm I wondered whether <pause dur="short"/> you perhaps would like to buy a new car <pause dur="short"/> using my car as part exchange <pause dur="short"/> and then sell your car and just pocket the money <pause dur="short"/> because you said to me basically yesterday that getting cars on finance it that would be the money you would put into savings for if you wanted to go away with your friends et cetera et cetera well <pause dur="short"/> if you if you use the money that you got for your car and put it into a savings account</u>
<u n="16" who="S0337">so I just straight sell my car now <pause dur="short"/> basically?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0336">I mean it's just an idea I'm not saying that that's I'm not saying I'm not you're not I'm just kind of putting it out there as a suggestion that we could use my car as part exchange and actually get a little bit of money off and then whatever you make on your car you can just keep as savings for you to do whatever you want with</u>
<u n="18" who="S0337">okay <pause dur="short"/> let me try and work this out right we use both cars as a <pause dur="short"/> deposit for one car</u>
<u n="19" who="S0336">well we could do that</u>
<u n="20" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0336">if you wanted</u>
<u n="22" who="S0337">well yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0336">but that means you'd have no cash though so it would <trunc>kind</trunc> almost defy the</u>
<u n="24" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah maybe</u>
<u n="25" who="S0336" trans="overlap">the point of it</u>
<u n="26" who="S0337">yeah or maybe sell my car and then use some of that as deposit</u>
<u n="27" who="S0336">yeah well what I was <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="28" who="S0337" trans="overlap">I might see about if my parents want a new car</u>
<u n="29" who="S0336">well what was <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="30" who="S0337" trans="overlap"><unclear>combine</unclear> those off them</u>
<u n="31" who="S0336">what I was thinking is what you might be able to do is you know that fifteen hundred pounds you've got that's kind of stashed aside at the moment? <pause dur="short"/> you could use that plus my car as a deposit and then put that money back in there <pause dur="short"/> when you sell your car do you know what I mean? so you'd have like you'd have over two grand as a deposit which means hopefully that would bring your monthly repayments down like a little bit</u>
<u n="32" who="S0337">and then I sell my car as soon as possible</u>
<u n="33" who="S0336">and then you sell your car as soon as possible <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0337">about to obviously pay for <pause dur="short"/> my MOT aren't I?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0336">yeah but I actually see that as a positive cos <pause dur="short"/> if</u>
<u n="36" who="S0337" trans="overlap">what freshly MOT'd?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0336">yeah it's but it's a selling point saying you know it's not gonna need a service or MOT for another year like that's a really big selling point <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and you know like you probably will actually get more for your car with it being serviced and MOT'd cos people kind of trust it a little bit more <pause dur="long"/> so I don't see it as a bad thing that it's about to go in for service and MOT</u>
<u n="38" who="S0337">if it passes</u>
<u n="39" who="S0336">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0337"><unclear/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0336">erm <pause dur="short"/> but yeah annoyingly there's a little bit of a <pause dur="short"/> been a little bit of a ticker on it because my tax is due at the end of this month and the tax is like ninety quid for six months which isn't the be all and end all <pause dur="short"/> but it's something to bear in mind erm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0337">I'll talk to <pause dur="short"/> I'll <trunc>s</trunc> I'll talk to my parents and see what they advise</u>
<u n="43" who="S0336">well I haven't done any sums or anything this is just like me thinking off the top of my head I need to get rid of my car <pause dur="short"/> put it that way <pause dur="short"/> I'd quite like the seven hundred quid however that comes do you know what mean? <pause dur="long"/> is this okay with bruises <unclear>or not</unclear>? <pause dur="long"/> can we watch a film tonight?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0337">no <unclear/> the other night <pause dur="short"/> you had me watching Soap Awards</u>
<u n="45" who="S0336">it wasn't the Soap Awards it was the Pride of Britain you idiot</u>
<u n="46" who="S0337">similar</u>
<u n="47" who="S0336">and we didn't even end up watching all of that you went and played League</u>
<u n="48" who="S0337">yeah it's <pause dur="short"/> bit more grilling <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0336">I don't think we need any <pause dur="short"/> it's not okay that's not making that make much difference I don't think <pause dur="long"/> erm they're gonna be on for at least another half an hour but how long do you think they'll take?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0337">I dunno five or ten minutes on the grill</u>
<u n="51" who="S0336">and what about the <unclear>furniture</unclear> and stuff? <pause dur="short"/> forget it? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="52" who="S0337">did you get broccoli?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0336">I'm sure I bought broccoli on at the weekend <pause dur="long"/> okay</u>
<u n="54" who="S0337">got carrots</u>
<u n="55" who="S0336">they're off as well aren't they?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0337">no I they're alright</u>
<u n="57" who="S0336">I don't I don't even like carrots that much</u>
<u n="58" who="S0337">don't you?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0336">no <pause dur="short"/> but yeah go for it I think we'll</u>
<u n="60" who="S0337" trans="overlap">got peas don't we have that frozen veg still?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0336">maybe <pause dur="long"/> I don't mind carrots in stuff I just don't really <pause dur="short"/> and I'll eat them if they're on my plate but <pause dur="long"/> yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0337">want that?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0336">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says all her friends have been a bit shit recently</u>
<u n="64" who="S0337">really? does she wanna come round?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0336">well</u>
<u n="66" who="S0337" trans="overlap">not now but</u>
<u n="67" who="S0336">she basically said that was been she's obviously trying to ask her girls like her best friends erm to arrange like er drinks before she goes and like they basically all said they could only do Thursday next week and now they've all all but bailed and she's just like I don't think they understand I'm like moving away like they don't seem to give a shit <pause dur="short"/> and apparently she had a bit of a cry today about that</u>
<u n="68" who="S0337">yeah well <pause dur="short"/> so she should</u>
<u n="69" who="S0336">it is shit</u>
<u n="70" who="S0337">yeah well she's entitled to not so she should</u>
<u n="71" who="S0336">no</u>
<u n="72" who="S0337" trans="overlap">she's entitled to</u>
<u n="73" who="S0336">I'm a bit annoyed I don't know if her friends are like fully kind of comprehending the fact that like this is a really big move for her and it would be good to have some support</u>
<u n="74" who="S0337">I think that all the time</u>
<u n="75" who="S0336">mm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0337">why's it yellow by the way? <pause dur="short"/> it's still hard</u>
<u n="77" who="S0336">probably cos it's been in that in that drawer it's</u>
<u n="78" who="S0337" trans="overlap">in that bag</u>
<u n="79" who="S0336">it would be fine if it wasn't it's not even the tenth yet is it?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0337">no</u>
<u n="81" who="S0336">the tenth's tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm not putting stuff in there any more erm yeah I felt a bit sorry for her they're not very nice</u>
<u n="82" who="S0337">we've got a big fridge</u>
<u n="83" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0337" trans="overlap">we'll use the fridge erm yeah that's a bit shit if she wants to pop over she should pop over</u>
<u n="85" who="S0336" trans="overlap">I think she's like quite happy to do a takeaway next week which would be good</u>
<u n="86" who="S0337">yeah I said I'm not going out at work</u>
<u n="87" who="S0336">she said she hasn't actually spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about it cos he doesn't plan that far in advance</u>
<u n="88" who="S0337">oh</u>
<u n="89" who="S0336">so she just assumes she</u>
<u n="90" who="S0337" trans="overlap">what day is it Friday?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0337">mm <pause dur="long"/> guess neighbours across the road <pause dur="short"/> they've not moved in but I presume they're moving in next week now</u>
<u n="93" who="S0336">I think I saw them the other <trunc>ni</trunc> er</u>
<u n="94" who="S0337" trans="overlap">the other week</u>
<u n="95" who="S0336" trans="overlap">they were around yesterday</u>
<u n="96" who="S0337">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0336">I don't know what to do about <unclear/> tomorrow all I can do is like <pause dur="short"/> keep an eye on my phone and ring you as soon as they ring me</u>
<u n="98" who="S0337">oh are they calling you? they've got your number then?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0336" trans="overlap">they've got my mobile number</u>
<u n="100" who="S0337" trans="overlap">your mobile that's fine so long as they've got that erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s not in tomorrow didn't have my one on one my one on one? one to one</u>
<u n="101" who="S0336">what one to one was it gonna be? just the catch up?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0337">no it's like</u>
<u n="103" who="S0336">your six months then</u>
<u n="104" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0336" trans="overlap">that's that's happening nearly a year in</u>
<u n="106" who="S0337">well I had one yeah I dunno now <pause dur="short"/> they er I need a <trunc>per</trunc></u>
<u n="107" who="S0336" trans="overlap">have you thought about what erm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0337" trans="overlap">I need a personal development plan</u>
<u n="109" who="S0336">okay</u>
<u n="110" who="S0337">a PDP</u>
<u n="111" who="S0336">have you thought about like what you wanna talk to him about and what you wanna ask and stuff?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0337">no he's not in on Monday he's not in tomorrow Monday I'm not in on Tuesday <pause dur="short"/> so it's Wednesday and I'm not in on Thursday at least we've done my Wednesdays probably gonna happen Wednesday <pause dur="short"/> if it doesn't happen Wednesday then he's late</u>
<u n="113" who="S0336">but you need to have a serious think about what you wanna talk to him about</u>
<u n="114" who="S0337">I know</u>
<u n="115" who="S0336">I don't want you to go in there and be like yeah it's all fine <pause dur="short"/> it's it's kind of not like there's stuff you wanna ask him</u>
<u n="116" who="S0337">what?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0336">more money</u>
<u n="118" who="S0337">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0336">what do you have to do for more money and actually it shouldn't even be that you should kind of go in there saying actually I was made permanent it wasn't I was made permanent and it wasn't even discussed with me like I think in the last year like I've grown from strength to strength I I'm now in charge of like one of our largest customers you know they're really happy with the work that I'm doing for them on a on a day to day basis</u>
<u n="120" who="S0337" trans="overlap">can't say that</u>
<u n="121" who="S0336">like I I think</u>
<u n="122" who="S0337">cos obviously there are issues there but</u>
<u n="123" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0337">there's always gonna be issues</u>
<u n="125" who="S0336">I think and just sort of say you know I think it do deserve more money and that and the conversation was kind of skipped over by just announcing that I'd been made permanent without kind of talking to me about it I was little bit disappointed like obviously I'm happy to be made permanent but</u>
<u n="126" who="S0337">yeah I've <trunc>al</trunc></u>
<u n="127" who="S0336" trans="overlap">it's <trunc>actua</trunc></u>
<u n="128" who="S0337" trans="overlap">I've kind of said this to him</u>
<u n="129" who="S0336">it's such a big thing and for them to just be like oh by the way now you're permanent and that that be it that's quite disappointing <pause dur="short"/> you have to really like in your one to one</u>
<u n="130" who="S0337" trans="overlap">yeah I know but</u>
<u n="131" who="S0336" trans="overlap">you should be allowed to fight your corner</u>
<u n="132" who="S0337">when you look at the <trunc>ra</trunc> <vocal desc="sigh"/> I'm not I'm key standard rate and everyone in the office and they're not gonna go just giving two grand more than that now it just doesn't happen it might have been in the past with some people in the</u>
<u n="133" who="S0336" trans="overlap">yeah no I appreciate that but that's such a defeatist attitude to have to say oh nobody else in the office is being paid more so why would I ask for more?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0337" trans="overlap">it's not defeatist</u>
<u n="135" who="S0336">it is</u>
<u n="136" who="S0337">it's realist</u>
<u n="137" who="S0336">you have to ask if you don't ask you don't get</u>
<u n="138" who="S0337">I know <pause dur="short"/> oh there's peppers in there</u>
<u n="139" who="S0336">and even if he turns around and says oh I can't offer you more at this point you say right okay well I wanna know that if I do X Y and Z I will get more money cos otherwise there's no incentive <pause dur="short"/> and they know that they can't say right this is what this is how we think you've fared over the last year your goals for the next twelve months are this and expect you to do it for no extra money that's not how it works <pause dur="long"/> yes? fighting face <pause dur="long"/> but yeah all the</u>
<u n="140" who="S0337" trans="overlap">oops</u>
<u n="141" who="S0336">all the personal development stuff is obviously important for you as well <pause dur="short"/> you can ask about all of that kind of thing <pause dur="long"/> do you think he'll pick up on the fact that you're late quite a lot?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0337">I'm not like late all the time <pause dur="short"/> I'm cutting it fine</u>
<u n="143" who="S0336"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0337">all the time <pause dur="short"/> I wasn't late this morning <pause dur="short"/> I was late yesterday I wasn't I haven't been late the rest of the week</u>
<u n="145" who="S0336">okay</u>
<u n="146" who="S0337">I just cut it fine</u>
<u n="147" who="S0336">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0337">I cut it fine</u>
<u n="149" who="S0336" trans="overlap">well that that</u>
<u n="150" who="S0337" trans="overlap">when I lived</u>
<u n="151" who="S0336">I almost feel like that looks just as bad as being late though like you walking into the office at one minute to nine when other people have been sat at their desk for fifteen minutes</u>
<u n="152" who="S0337">I'm not getting paid enough to come in <vocal desc="laugh"/> there's different ways of playing it</u>
<u n="153" who="S0336" trans="overlap">you know what I'm saying though</u>
<u n="154" who="S0337">I know I know shall I leave this for a bit yeah?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0336">yeah they've probably got another twenty twenty-five minutes</u>
<u n="156" who="S0337">well we're gonna do it like that</u>
<u n="157" who="S0336">two are probably gonna do it like that</u>
<u n="158" who="S0337">shall we just put a rack on top of</u>
<u n="159" who="S0336" trans="overlap">just put some tin foil on <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0337">erm <pause dur="long"/> well they'll just go in here won't they? er is it like that?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0336">well what'll probably happen is that the fat will drip down and it won't just catch in that one <trunc>li</trunc> neat little thing it'll run around the whole thing</u>
<u n="162" who="S0337">this sucks</u>
<u n="163" who="S0336">so that's slightly redundant</u>
<u n="164" who="S0337">well let's not waste that <pause dur="short"/> no we'll be we're not gonna use that clearly <pause dur="short"/> we're not wasting it and chucking it out obviously</u>
<u n="165" who="S0336">okay <pause dur="short"/> but it needs to be at least that long</u>
<u n="166" who="S0337" trans="overlap">a whole strip that's retarded <pause dur="short"/> just <trunc>f</trunc> just for those two little things</u>
<u n="167" who="S0336">we're about to <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0337">oh have we used this already? <pause dur="short"/> what did we use it for?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0336">well it didn't come with a lot I don't think did it?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0337" trans="overlap">five metres</u>
<u n="171" who="S0336">oh</u>
<u n="172" who="S0337">how have we used five metres already?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0336">all those ribs of course</u>
<u n="174" who="S0337">oh yeah all those ribs yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0336">never mind that'll have to do <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0337">yeah I dunno <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
