<text id="SNDW">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:38:53</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-02-07</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0607 S0644</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In the car travelling through California on holiday (Redwoods area)</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Friends, wider family circle</topics>
		<activity>Friends, wider family circle</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0607">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Pembury, England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern/ 'BBC' English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Battle</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 month</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Translator/Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Italian -- level unspecified; French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0644">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English/British</nat>
				<birthplace>Enfield, UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London/ South-East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>36 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Office worker (temp)</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Brazilian Portuguese -- basic</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0644">oh there's a little river there as well <pause dur="short"/> look</u>
<u n="2" who="S0607">so cute I like the woods type thing do you?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah I do <pause dur="short"/> see <unclear/> if it had been snowing or raining it would it would also have been quite nice this</u>
<u n="4" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0644">I wouldn't have <unclear>minded</unclear> that but the fact that it is it's spring like innit? and it's beautiful and those deers those little deers</u>
<u n="6" who="S0607" trans="overlap">ah so cute <pause dur="short"/> but sorry you were just saying something and then I was like stop</u>
<u n="7" who="S0644">that's okay I think all I was saying is it comes down to this I think it's <pause dur="short"/> probably is better educationally <trunc>prob</trunc> er cos there's no distraction and it's all very simple and that but I think you miss out on too much fun</u>
<u n="8" who="S0607">yeah actually that was like <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> really not necessarily the most fun it probably was the most fun part of my life and it was all about those boys</u>
<u n="9" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> slut</u>
<u n="10" who="S0607">I mean it was just like <pause dur="short"/> it was so great</u>
<u n="11" who="S0644">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was just fun weren't it?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0607">did you used to go to house parties?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0644">yeah erm now I think of it I suppose they weren't really parties they were just everyone sitting around like there wasn't there wasn't always music and that but sitting around and having a drink and yeah somebody being sick somewhere</u>
<u n="14" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0644">yeah they were good <pause dur="short"/> they were good <pause dur="short"/> or other parties do you know what? we used to go clubs from quite early they were like special kids' clubs</u>
<u n="16" who="S0607">oh really?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0644">yeah like if you had to be under <trunc>six</trunc> it was up to sixteen and stuff but they were really good <pause dur="short"/> there was one in <anon type="place"/> we used to go to like one there was once a month there was one in <anon type="place"/> and everyone used to go on a Saturday night and it was just brilliant</u>
<u n="18" who="S0607">isn't that brilliant? so hang what kind of thing erm was it how was it organised?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0644">well there was one in <anon type="place"/> that was called <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="20" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0644">and it was just really cool everyone was about <trunc>f</trunc> we were about fourteen I suppose you could be thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen</u>
<u n="22" who="S0607" trans="overlap">so it was for that age group? who was starting to get <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0607">erm it was for that age group</u>
<u n="25" who="S0644">yeah the oldest people were probably about sixteen seventeen</u>
<u n="26" who="S0607" trans="overlap">that's so good</u>
<u n="27" who="S0644">it was</u>
<u n="28" who="S0607">I always used to think that whenever anything was put on for that age range it was far too nerdy for any of us to go</u>
<u n="29" who="S0644" trans="overlap">a bit sad <pause dur="short"/> yeah no these were like actual like proper good they were probably better than some of the ones I've been to recently actually</u>
<u n="30" who="S0607" trans="overlap">that's brilliant</u>
<u n="31" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0607" trans="overlap">and at and at what time what sort of time like what what time did you go home?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0644">it probably finished about eleven</u>
<u n="34" who="S0607">that's so great</u>
<u n="35" who="S0644">yeah it was it was really good</u>
<u n="36" who="S0607">and probably your mum and dad could feel like it was ace as well</u>
<u n="37" who="S0644" trans="overlap">funny I don't remember getting I don't remember all we used to just seem to be able to go <pause dur="short"/> it's funny that</u>
<u n="38" who="S0607" trans="overlap">who <pause dur="short"/> who is it organised by? do you remember?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0644">erm I remember the little club where it is it's like a a community hall type thing that in the town and it was just an organised you know like you'd have a club night?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0644">it was just that sort of thing it was really good but there was this one in <anon type="place"/> that was on I think almost every Saturday night almost every Saturday night Friday nights was indie night and I wasn't into indie at the time</u>
<u n="42" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0644">Saturday nights was reggae nights and that was good cos it had all like the <pause dur="short"/> up startings of drum and base and startings of hard-core well hard-core had already started but the commercial hard-core like The Prodigy and all that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="44" who="S0607" trans="overlap">oh I love The Prodigy</u>
<u n="45" who="S0644">and it was just brilliant it was so exciting you could get drink in there like everyone was pissed they were on</u>
<u n="46" who="S0607" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0644">yeah you could get you could get booze in there somehow I think you had to be <trunc>eight</trunc> it was for eighteens but they had <trunc>s</trunc> I think you could be sixteen to twenty-one or something like that</u>
<u n="48" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0644">sixteen to twenty-one but it we were all about fourteen fifteen</u>
<u n="50" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0644">and they'd let us in and I dunno how we got away with it actually but they were just really good nights</u>
<u n="52" who="S0607" trans="overlap">ah that's so great did you have to get a cab home?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0644">erm sometimes we used to stay at my house a bit for that and we used to stay at my friend my other friend's so I got away with quite a lot really when I think about it so sometimes my mum would pick us up sometimes we got a cab</u>
<u n="54" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0644">yeah sometimes we got a cab back</u>
<u n="56" who="S0607">I went through a stage where I was like between the age of fourteen and sixteen it was a constant battle against my dad to be allowed to do things</u>
<u n="57" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0607">and it was mainly these house parties cos there were luckily there were a couple of parents <pause dur="short"/> said get on with it who would have these parties so one was this girl called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> whose mum was divorced from her dad er cos she had this big house in the middle of nowhere in the countryside</u>
<u n="59" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0607">and she would just let her have a massive party and erm <pause dur="short"/> er they're but then so she would just not supervise really she would be there somewhere but you never really saw her</u>
<u n="61" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0607">you might see her at the beginning erm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> she was never there and and that the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> party ones were brilliant because it's <trunc>re</trunc> by the way I think this is really naughty and very erm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0644" trans="overlap">irresponsible</u>
<u n="64" who="S0607">not right but <trunc>sh</trunc> my mum and dad used to ring whoever's parents were having this party and asked if</u>
<u n="65" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0607">are they gonna be supervised?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0644">and they'd go yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0607" trans="overlap">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s mum would say yes but she was never there</u>
<u n="69" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0607">she was never there <pause dur="short"/> we just did whatever we wanted</u>
<u n="71" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="72" who="S0607" trans="overlap">so I'm lucky I didn't have teenage pregnancy or something</u>
<u n="73" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="74" who="S0607">because basically we all slept in the same rooms I remember <pause dur="short"/> erm this is getting a bit like I can't tell you this now</u>
<u n="75" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0607">but nothing you know really untoward happened</u>
<u n="77" who="S0644" trans="overlap">really untoward</u>
<u n="78" who="S0607">erm but and then there was another there was a guy whose parents used to let him have a party</u>
<u n="79" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0607">but they were honest so my dad would call up in fact my dad knew him</u>
<u n="81" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0607">cos he was their lawyer and he would say is it erm supervised? and they would say no</u>
<u n="83" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0607">and in fact</u>
<u n="85" who="S0644"><unclear/> let them get on with it</u>
<u n="86" who="S0607">that bloke's mother said to my mum if I were you I wouldn't let her come</u>
<u n="87" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0607">so <pause dur="short"/> have I put it on too warm now? or is it nice?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0644" trans="overlap">it is a bit shall I put it back on?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0607" trans="overlap">is it toasty?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0644">put it back on it's alright <unclear/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0607">I think I went too far the other way</u>
<u n="93" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0607">yeah and I was like bloody thanks a lot I couldn't believe it I was totally doomed then</u>
<u n="95" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="96" who="S0607">so when it was that guy's house I was I start cos I made such a stink about it with my dad like the it was constant rows about these parties so at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s I was able to go but of course they only had one like twice a year</u>
<u n="97" who="S0644">mm mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0607">and then this other guy he had them quite a lot so then my dad went for a compromise I was allowed to go but of course no way was I allowed to stay over</u>
<u n="99" who="S0644" trans="overlap">stay the night</u>
<u n="100" who="S0607">but that meant my dad had to come and get me and then he would like decide on the time</u>
<u n="101" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0607">it was so mortifying</u>
<u n="103" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0607">be like my dad's here to get me</u>
<u n="105" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0607">and of course dad doesn't wanna stay up till like two</u>
<u n="107" who="S0644">no</u>
<u n="108" who="S0607">so he would probably come and get me at</u>
<u n="109" who="S0644" trans="overlap">no ten twelve</u>
<u n="110" who="S0607">maybe like twelve</u>
<u n="111" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0607">or in fact maybe even a bit earlier and that was just so <trunc>embar</trunc> nothing</u>
<u n="113" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0607">it meant that nothing could really get going for me do you know what I mean? cos it was like</u>
<u n="115" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0607">it all had an end time</u>
<u n="117" who="S0644">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0607">whereas at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house</u>
<u n="119" who="S0644" trans="overlap">what age was that?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0607">well that was probably between fourteen and sixteen but cos I remember one time I remember that when I hit seventeen I was suddenly just allowed to do it all <pause dur="short"/> when I was seventeen I was suddenly allowed</u>
<u n="121" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0607">to go clubbing and everything whereas before I had been clubbing but it wasn't allowed <unclear/> very difficult to to to wangle it</u>
<u n="123" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0607">erm but then it was wonderful</u>
<u n="125" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0607">thank you dad for letting me go one year before the legal age</u>
<u n="127" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0607">erm and then we really did also though I was I was one of the youngest in my year so you can't so I was probably</u>
<u n="129" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0607">probably <trunc>s</trunc> so I was <unclear/></u>
<u n="131" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><unclear/> eighteen when you were just seventeen</u>
<u n="132" who="S0607">when I yeah so erm but at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house though there was no such limitation so you would just stay up <trunc>l</trunc> mainly stay up till dawn</u>
<u n="133" who="S0644">brilliant</u>
<u n="134" who="S0607">and erm and and then all the interesting stuff starts to happen all these conversations that you have like there would always be some boy who you hadn't spoken to before and you'd suddenly be sat on the farm gate</u>
<u n="135" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0607">at dawn chatting so really deep about something</u>
<u n="137" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0607">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0644">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we had a few of <trunc>tho</trunc> it was more <pause dur="short"/> they weren't so much parties they were at people's houses where the parents either weren't there or had gone out and</u>
<u n="140" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0644"><trunc>s</trunc> and I do remember a couple of those I remember once there was me and another girl and we were staying at this other girl's house and her house was so horrible it was really dirty and disgusting</u>
<u n="142" who="S0607" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="143" who="S0644">and er she wasn't from it was all a bit wrong all of it like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she didn't come from a very good start and all the rest of it and erm once we were staying there and her mum came home with this bloke and I could remember he was called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0607"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0644">and he was just hideous</u>
<u n="146" who="S0607">oh no</u>
<u n="147" who="S0644" trans="overlap">and she said erm and she'd just picked him up I dunno they'd been out all been out somewhere we'd got home about eleven and then her mum come home even later like sometimes the mum would come home sometimes she wouldn't sort of thing like</u>
<u n="148" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0644">we could just go and stay there whenever and it didn't really matter <pause dur="short"/> she'd come home and though you could tell they'd both be pissed and we were all like these fifteen nearly sixteen year old girls still sitting there and her and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and she said I hope everyone's feeling very open-minded tonight because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gonna stay here and we were just like what I couldn't believe it like I imagine</u>
<u n="150" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0644">imagine if your mum came home and did that</u>
<u n="152" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0644">said that in front of you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was nothing to shout about <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0644">you know what I mean? and I just thought oh right yeah and you couldn't say no you were staying at their house but</u>
<u n="156" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0644">I just thought how bizarre</u>
<u n="158" who="S0607">actually erm I would like to go home <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0644" trans="overlap">that that goes on <pause dur="short"/> now</u>
<u n="160" who="S0607">look at that one</u>
<u n="161" who="S0644">is that a redwood there?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0607">we we can't see how tall they they're getting</u>
<u n="163" who="S0644">let's have some <pause dur="short"/> look at this</u>
<u n="164" who="S0607">we're not at the tallest bit</u>
<u n="165" who="S0644">is this the redwood forest?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0607">I think we're <trunc>start</trunc> it's starting <pause dur="short"/> it's not fully in but it's <pause dur="short"/> oh that's fantastic</u>
<u n="167" who="S0644">trees are beautiful <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna hug a tree today</u>
<u n="168" who="S0607">yeah <pause dur="long"/> I think we've like erm <pause dur="short"/> started to forget the topics</u>
<u n="169" who="S0644">yeah we're getting distracted <pause dur="short"/> but it started what we was talking about basically is the difference between going to a school where there's boys and and all the things that follows on from that like the going out</u>
<u n="170" who="S0607" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0644">and the fun and parties and all of that sort of thing</u>
<u n="172" who="S0607">but no I mean like our topics I'm trying to think now what</u>
<u n="173" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="174" who="S0607">I'm actually starting to feel like we're just now getting into normal every day conversation and we've forgotten</u>
<u n="175" who="S0644">I don't mind</u>
<u n="176" who="S0607">things that I'm sure there was something things that I really wanted to tell you but I can't remember what they are now <pause dur="short"/> everything is a whole topic and now I'm like but what is? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0644">well</u>
<u n="178" who="S0607">we haven't finished covering the theory of everything though have we?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0644">the theory of everything will never end <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> the theory of everything will never end <pause dur="short"/> there were loads of things before coming away that I wanted to talk but now don't seem important like work</u>
<u n="180" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0644">how much I disliked that job</u>
<u n="182" who="S0607">now it's all just <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0607">yeah you were gonna tell me about that job</u>
<u n="185" who="S0644">oh I know what I'll tell you about the it was more like it was start where it ended yesterday</u>
<u n="186" who="S0607">was it because you didn't finish telling me about the thing</u>
<u n="187" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I'm determined to tell you <pause dur="short"/> the project?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0607">yeah because I realised at one point yesterday I was like so hang on I still don't know about the project <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0644">well it's not really urgent and we there were far bigger fish to fry cos we came across that lovely scenery and all that stuff so it's fun like</u>
<u n="190" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0644">it's not a <unclear/> it's just something that I wanted to eventually tell you about because it's it sort of leads onto making loads and loads and loads of money</u>
<u n="192" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0644"><vocal desc="sigh"/> so I'll try and be as quick as possible I know I said that yesterday and wished I hadn't done it</u>
<u n="194" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0644">but <pause dur="short"/> it was so <pause dur="short"/> that's how my idea came about it was from a place of genuinely trying to do something good</u>
<u n="196" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0644">which I thought was good erm but also cos I thought he's gonna make loads of money because like Zumba erm <pause dur="short"/> it's a new thing</u>
<u n="198" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0644">it's not really new but it is a new thing if you market it as a new thing and sell it as a new thing and I had I had everything done for it so basically what happened then was I spent</u>
<u n="200" who="S0607" trans="overlap">are are you gonna tell me <pause dur="short"/> a bit about how it would work? cos I'm curious to imagine</u>
<u n="201" who="S0644">well it's so simple it's so so so so simple so <pause dur="short"/> I wrote a manual on it because you had to write a manual for part of this bloody course erm <pause dur="short"/> exercises right you know squats?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="203" who="S0644">squats but holding onto the baby so you squat and then you lift up the baby and that's your shoulder press and then you twist</u>
<u n="204" who="S0607">no</u>
<u n="205" who="S0644">either standing or not standing basically I got a girl to do this once I got a girl to do a class with her baby</u>
<u n="206" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0644">and demonstrate so I could demonstrate and it was and she was properly in a sweat <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> exercise class</u>
<u n="208" who="S0607" trans="overlap">I bet that was really helpful cos you can then really see what <unclear/> could actually do</u>
<u n="209" who="S0644" trans="overlap">well it was it was so so so so good I think it was so good and I think it's the sort of thing that girls when you've had a baby they wanna get into shape but they don't wanna go to a gym and they it would have been a sociable thing it would have been a</u>
<u n="210" who="S0607" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0644">there were so many good things to it <pause dur="short"/> so and I thought and I kept thinking well why hasn't someone else done this then? like</u>
<u n="212" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0644">it's such a good idea and then I went on Youtube <pause dur="short"/> and loads of people have done it</u>
<u n="214" who="S0607" trans="overlap">was there a <unclear/>? <pause dur="short"/> were there any bits where she was laying down?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0644">yeah sit-ups crunches erm planks so many things you can do with a baby and they're more importantly they're things that you need to be able to do if you've got a baby you need to have be able to have good erm coordination and good core strength and good balance and</u>
<u n="216" who="S0607" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="217" who="S0644">good you know what I mean? like there's all these things that to</u>
<u n="218" who="S0607">and also</u>
<u n="219" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="220" who="S0607" trans="overlap">is there some bits where the baby is just laid there?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0644">yeah but</u>
<u n="222" who="S0607">but I was thinking <pause dur="short"/> part of</u>
<u n="223" who="S0644" trans="overlap">when you do a press-up <unclear/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0607" trans="overlap"><unclear/> is genius because you can just bring the baby</u>
<u n="225" who="S0644">that's it</u>
<u n="226" who="S0607">do you know what I mean? why should she not <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0644" trans="overlap">but it's actually a bonding thing for babies you see because</u>
<u n="228" who="S0607" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="229" who="S0644">you're <trunc>u</trunc> they like being picked up and held and moved and carried and sort of</u>
<u n="230" who="S0607" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0644">lifted and they like all that and <pause dur="short"/> it was work it was really work but most importantly it is what people fail to realise or seem to have <unclear/> realised is that it starts <pause dur="short"/> from the word go babies learning behaviour babies learning what's the thing to do so it's no good saying well when they're five I'm gonna start going to class I mean you can do it like that but</u>
<u n="232" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0644" trans="overlap">babies as young as two there's a problem with obesity is babies as young as two cos they're not moving enough they're not doing this and in this exercise you can see the baby was kicking and like all doing the things that they should do</u>
<u n="234" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0644">like moving and it was such a genius genius idea and when I would tell people about it they'd all go oh yeah that's a really good idea I'd do that I dunno if they were just being polite</u>
<u n="236" who="S0607" trans="overlap">and what did that girl think? the one who did it? the one</u>
<u n="237" who="S0644" trans="overlap">she thought it was a really good workout <pause dur="short"/> she she was sweating you could see she was out of breath</u>
<u n="238" who="S0607" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0644">and sweating and but the baby liked it the baby would like oh not that I'm gonna send it to you cos I'm sure you <unclear/> but you would see if I showed it to you</u>
<u n="240" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0644">anyway so <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> finds out I thought well look this is an idea and I thought if I don't do it I'll never know I'll never it's all very well isn't it talking about I've got this brilliant idea and I'm gonna do this and it's gonna if you don't actually do anything about it you'll never know</u>
<u n="242" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0644">so I thought to myself <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> that's what I'll do so I know I'd also realise from this point you're never gonna make a lot of money doing fitness stuff unless</u>
<u n="244" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0644">unless you come up with something original</u>
<u n="246" who="S0607" trans="overlap">a brand or something</u>
<u n="247" who="S0644">or come up with some or unless you were just happy doing all the classes and all the rest of it and</u>
<u n="248" who="S0607" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="249" who="S0644">anyway <pause dur="short"/> so erm <pause dur="short"/> in short what you have to do there's a company called reps it's called Register of Exercise Professionals and if you are a fitness instructor you have to belong to them and in order to belong to them you've gotta have insurance you've gotta have qualifications it's like Corgi registered you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0607" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0644">like if you're an electrician electrician</u>
<u n="252" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="253" who="S0644">it's like being Corgi registered that says you are legit erm</u>
<u n="254" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0644">you've got all the necessary things and you're fit to work in that industry</u>
<u n="256" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0644">it's basically another money spinning thing really erm so I phoned them up and I said look so if I have an idea of a course how do I go about it? and I said oh yeah yeah yeah we do all that <pause dur="short"/> in order to get your course endorsed which is what they call it you've gotta <pause dur="short"/> do this you know you've gotta do all</u>
<u n="258" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0644">follow this procedure you've gotta follow all this information so and it was not a straightforward thing you had to do a course to show that you're able to teach so a very like a basic teach your class <pause dur="short"/> so what</u>
<u n="260" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0644">what you do is you you get the idea and you develop it into a course and then the idea</u>
<u n="262" who="S0607" trans="overlap">do you have to pay for all of this?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0644">yeah through the nose and the idea would be that I've got this idea you're a fitness instructor you come on my course pay me the money then you're allowed to go and teach my course</u>
<u n="264" who="S0607">oh I see yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0644" trans="overlap">that's how that's how Zumba worked</u>
<u n="266" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0644" trans="overlap">that's how they made all their money cos they've got the Zumba <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> franchise or or brand you come and do the course then you can go and teach it</u>
<u n="268" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0644">and that's how you make your money <pause dur="short"/> so for example like you can pay a hundred and fifty pounds to do a day course up to a <trunc>hund</trunc> about a hundred and fifty pounds to do a day course more sometimes but I thought</u>
<u n="270" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0644">a hundred and fifty was quite a good amount now if you get six people on your course obviously you've gotta pay your taxes and all the rest of it and your room hire where you're gonna teach</u>
<u n="272" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0644">but six people hang on what is that?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0607">sorry I'm just <unclear>going</unclear> to unzip this thing <pause dur="short"/> seems to be shut no matter what I do</u>
<u n="275" who="S0644">that's a grand a day</u>
<u n="276" who="S0607">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and that's for when that's for when you're teaching them how to teach it</u>
<u n="277" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0607">oh sorry</u>
<u n="279" who="S0644">so like you know if you go on a creative <trunc>cour</trunc> creative writing course you pay your money</u>
<u n="280" who="S0607">but is it like an and is it like erm they can't teach your thing without you teaching them? like is there like erm</u>
<u n="281" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah a qualification</u>
<u n="282" who="S0607">but is it also a erm what d'you call it? a erm approved course? so that you have to have a but have you got like not copyright but do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah totally</u>
<u n="284" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0644">so like for me if I wanted to be able to teach spin <pause dur="short"/> in order to teach the spin class you have to go to a place where they are erm authorised you it belongs to that company basically and unless you've got the company approved course you you can't teach it</u>
<u n="286" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0644">erm so yeah that was the idea so I looked into it I <trunc>st</trunc> I wrote this manual and I took a job that was really rubbish money so that I could leave early in the day and have a day off a week erm <pause dur="short"/> to carry on doing <trunc>thi</trunc> cos there was no time you know what I mean? it's like anything else</u>
<u n="288" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0644">so I was writing this manual as it so happened <pause dur="short"/> I had January off last year because my dad had to have an operation on his leg</u>
<u n="290" who="S0607">oh yeah I remember</u>
<u n="291" who="S0644">do you remember? so I was off for a month looking after him and I'd do that in the evenings or in the day or whatever and do you want me to steer?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/> sorry</u>
<u n="293" who="S0644">I can steer I don't mind</u>
<u n="294" who="S0607">that's so bad isn't it? I've done I've finished now doing it now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0644">carry on <pause dur="short"/> hold your stop</u>
<u n="296" who="S0607" trans="overlap">it's alright it's alright <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0644">it's not really bad</u>
<u n="298" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0644">people do eat don't they as they're going along? <pause dur="short"/> oh look <pause dur="short"/> oh wow</u>
<u n="300" who="S0607">where's the drive-through coffee place? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0644">yeah I am getting a bit like jittery</u>
<u n="302" who="S0607">yeah lightheaded and you know</u>
<u n="303" who="S0644">I could just do with a fix <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0607">I didn't know that we would have this I I don't I know that sounds daft but I just</u>
<u n="305" who="S0644" trans="overlap">what the woods?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0607">I didn't know that we would have this road <pause dur="short"/> I think I I haven't been able to understand how it all is but now I think we are officially in</u>
<u n="307" who="S0644">redwood territory</u>
<u n="308" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so you had January off <pause dur="short"/> to</u>
<u n="309" who="S0644" trans="overlap">and it <trunc>lit</trunc> it literally took about at least <trunc>ma</trunc> that's when I got most of the work done but I did so much research like there was a <pause dur="short"/> there was a woman called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I can't remember what her name is and she'd recently done this research she was from <anon type="place"/> so I was gonna say I went to <anon type="place"/> can I come and meet you to discuss your research and use it in my manual to prove that women should do exercise with babies?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0644">cos that's gonna go in my favour and all the rest of it blah blah blah blah blah blah blah <pause dur="short"/> so I did loads of work on it now I had checked before with these people I said I've got this idea can I do it? they yeah yeah that sounds fine all it means all it is you've gotta do this you've gotta do this you've gotta do this a course in that write this manual a course in this</u>
<u n="312" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0644">so I do had to do loads of courses on one of these courses I met this woman erm and she was really nice I really liked her <pause dur="short"/> and erm actually I'm not even gonna bother with that cos it's all just negative rubbish</u>
<u n="314" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0644">the bottom line is I did loads of work I went on two courses</u>
<u n="316" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0644">ah that's it I had to do a course another course in erm <pause dur="short"/> exercise for pregnancy in postnatal women</u>
<u n="318" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0644">especially cos if you're doing any <trunc>cou</trunc> some without getting like too into it you can imagine how much work went into it</u>
<u n="320" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0644">it took about a year longer really I took days off I got this girl to come and film the thing I had to get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> my friend to film it</u>
<u n="322" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0644">I had to pay him to do that I had to ask the people that I used to work for doing personal training if I could have that room to do the filming in I had to do so much work then it got to this point <pause dur="short"/> erm where I was working through it's like a checklist and it says have you done this? have you done this? have you done this? have you done this? have you done this? have you done this? get to this point and it says explain why it's inappropriate to use babies as weights erm as part of a exercise thing and I thought well that's that's the entire gist of my</u>
<u n="324" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0644">thing so what do you mean? erm now I'd already seen another bit in the same fucking manual</u>
<u n="326" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0644">that says you can <trunc>b</trunc> exercise that involves babies and children can be done as long as you've done their prerequisite course which I've just been on</u>
<u n="328" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0644">so you can do it or what? so</u>
<u n="330" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0644">I called up this woman and this was when I realised that people don't know what the fuck they're doing <unclear/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0644">so I called up this woman I said hello erm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0607" trans="overlap">I can just imagine I can just imagine</u>
<u n="335" who="S0644">this was in August right? which was just after everything else that had gone wrong that year not a very good year and I'd been working on it and working on it and working on it and doing all these horrible jobs that I hated thinking well pretty soon</u>
<u n="336" who="S0607" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="337" who="S0644">I'll be teaching this course and I'm gonna make about</u>
<u n="338" who="S0607" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="339" who="S0644">a thousand pounds a per day</u>
<u n="340" who="S0607">for this yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0644">so I got it and I this I phoned up this woman I said hello I just I've been working on this and I said I've just come across this bit that says you can't use babies for a weight and she said <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah not a good idea <vocal desc="gasp"/> <pause dur="short"/> and I said have you done any exercise yourself? I said have you got any history in exercise yourself? she went all quiet</u>
<u n="342" who="S0607"><trunc>ha</trunc><trunc>ha</trunc>has anybody thought about the fact that you know you're constantly picking up babies?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0644">well this is it right I'm not being funny <pause dur="short"/> even a person without any exercise or particular interest in exercise as you you are <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0644">has just said that it's it's what it's called functional exercise</u>
<u n="346" who="S0607" trans="overlap">exercise</u>
<u n="347" who="S0644">yeah it's what is called functional exercise so it's the opposite of you know men go to the gym and they just work on that muscle cos they want that muscle so they'll do all these exercises just to build up this particular muscle</u>
<u n="348" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0644">cos they wanna look like a certain way <pause dur="short"/> functional exercises are doing things cos you need to do them</u>
<u n="350" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0644">and they're the best exercises so</u>
<u n="352" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0644">when we were all cave people we were all getting exactly the right kind of exercise by running away from dinosaurs climbing up trees swimming</u>
<u n="354" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0644">erm in all the things that you needed to be able to do you've got just</u>
<u n="356" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0644">cos you <trunc>nee</trunc> cos it was functional</u>
<u n="358" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0644">in your everyday life</u>
<u n="360" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0644">so that's <unclear/> exercise so if you are carrying a baby round lifting a baby up putting a baby down carrying shopping going up the stairs you need to do stuff that emulates those moves you <unclear/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0644">so it's all exercise it's just you don't call it exercise but this was</u>
<u n="364" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="365" who="S0644">this was calling it exercise and was gonna be a new craze like <unclear/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0644">anyway <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> I knew it was a good idea but this these people were were <unclear/> so</u>
<u n="368" who="S0607" trans="overlap">so what happened then on that conversation? so it was like oh</u>
<u n="369" who="S0644">well no she said yeah not a very good idea and I thought you know you can't lose your temper because you might need these people to be nice to you somehow</u>
<u n="370" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0644">you know what I mean? you can't say what you're really thinking but I did say to her I said well what cos I felt like saying what do you mean not a good idea? you're doing it all day long and you've got a baby</u>
<u n="372" who="S0607" trans="overlap">cos</u>
<u n="373" who="S0644">what do you mean it's not a good idea?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0607" trans="overlap"><unclear/> is it the same phone number that you'd called in the beginning?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0607">when you said I'm thinking about doing this and they said these are all the things you've gotta do?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0644">well this is it right what I've realised this has been a a fantastic exercise in the <pause dur="short"/> in the lesson of just how <pause dur="short"/> what a load of bollocks it all really is</u>
<u n="378" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0644">so you think you're talking to people that know what they're talking about they don't they don't know what they're talking about</u>
<u n="380" who="S0607" trans="overlap">also it's the fact that no matter what you're doing you call the thing up</u>
<u n="381" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="382" who="S0607">in any situation</u>
<u n="383" who="S0644" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="384" who="S0607">so maybe some research for this trip</u>
<u n="385" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="386" who="S0607">you call the thing up and you go is it gonna be okay to do this that and the other? and they go yeah all you've gotta do is this</u>
<u n="387" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="388" who="S0607">then it doesn't work</u>
<u n="389" who="S0644" trans="overlap">it's wrong</u>
<u n="390" who="S0607">it all goes to shit you call up and the</u>
<u n="391" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0607">other person that you speak to on that day</u>
<u n="393" who="S0644" trans="overlap">is all they've left</u>
<u n="394" who="S0607">says well of course you can't do that</u>
<u n="395" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0607">and then you say</u>
<u n="397" who="S0644">that I</u>
<u n="398" who="S0607">that last time I spoke to you</u>
<u n="399" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="400" who="S0607">and now this is something that I can't get used to and I still haven't managed to remember to do it cos you always get the name of the first person so you can go Clive Anderson said</u>
<u n="401" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="402" who="S0607">but I never do but my dad's really good at that he'll <unclear/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0607">and also makes them shit themselves</u>
<u n="405" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="406" who="S0607">cos my dad'll say can I have your name please?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0644" trans="overlap">cos then you're culpable aren't you?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0644">then you're culpable for it</u>
<u n="410" who="S0607">otherwise you're just some moron on the end of the phone going but I rang up a week ago and someone said</u>
<u n="411" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0607">but the other thing</u>
<u n="413" who="S0644" trans="overlap">this is it</u>
<u n="414" who="S0607">for all these things everything where you have to ring up and find out should we be ringing twice just to check?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0644">well</u>
<u n="416" who="S0607"><vocal desc="gasp"/> sorry like the hire car right</u>
<u n="417" who="S0644">right</u>
<u n="418" who="S0607">I called up and said <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> for this car not the original booking I called up and said erm <pause dur="short"/> I said hang on what was it?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0644" trans="overlap">do we need an international <unclear>permit</unclear>?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0607">I said</u>
<u n="423" who="S0644" trans="overlap">cos so far no one gives a monkey's</u>
<u n="424" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I said <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah it hadn't mentioned additional driver anywhere and in the original booking additional driver had been free but it had been sold as like special offer free additional driver</u>
<u n="425" who="S0644">oh right</u>
<u n="426" who="S0607">so with this one nobody had mentioned it and I rang up and said it doesn't mention additional driving <unclear/> cos I hate this erm secret charges thing and he said yeah additional driver is like eight dollars a day extra unless you're a <trunc>mem</trunc> and then he went quiet and then he went unless you're a member of the AA and then it's free and I was like oh so then I got off the phone and I was thinking well I was gonna become a member of the AA anyway and I was gonna do it in March</u>
<u n="427" who="S0644">right</u>
<u n="428" who="S0607">when I'm back erm <pause dur="short"/> because I wanna get rid of my German er roadside assistance and I wanna get my English one back</u>
<u n="429" who="S0644">oh right</u>
<u n="430" who="S0607">so then I spent twenty minutes on the AA website trying to build my own coverage cos erm they they've got their standard ones and then they've got build your own erm and it I was doing really well I was like oh it's only gonna be this much it's brilliant and we'll get free extra driver in America and</u>
<u n="431" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="432" who="S0607">and I even worked out so so anal I even worked out how much more it was gonna cost me to <trunc>cu</trunc> to be a member of the AA a month earlier than I wanted to be</u>
<u n="433" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="434" who="S0607">it was like six pounds</u>
<u n="435" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="436" who="S0607">I could have charged you three do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="438" who="S0607">erm <pause dur="short"/> so anyway then I thought oh cos I'm so used to being <unclear>pissed</unclear> over</u>
<u n="439" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="440" who="S0607">I I just I thought oh what is it okay that I'm the <trunc>me</trunc> AA member or does she have to be AA member?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0607">so I called again right and I said just to check</u>
<u n="443" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0607">erm with this AA membership</u>
<u n="445" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0607">is it okay if I'm the member and I'm the initial driver and will will my friend still be free? and he went oh there's no need to worry about that because in California additional drivers are free anyway</u>
<u n="447" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0607">thank you very much goodbye</u>
<u n="449" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0607">and then I just sat there and went mum</u>
<u n="451" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0607">she was like what now? what now? I was like I just spent forty minutes</u>
<u n="453" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0607">researching the AA and I bloody called back and and and then</u>
<u n="455" who="S0644" trans="overlap">this is what I'm saying the left hand does not know what the right hand is doing it's partly because everything is so complicated now</u>
<u n="456" who="S0607">well you feel like saying to the bloke thank you very much for your help can I also speak to any colleague</u>
<u n="457" who="S0644">yeah anyone</u>
<u n="458" who="S0607" trans="overlap">just to ask them the same question? <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> driver anyway in California all the time and free drop it off somewhere else</u>
<u n="459" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0607">in California which is why overall the car hire is cheaper not just because we have less days but because we were taking it over the state line</u>
<u n="461" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="462" who="S0607">so then we were having a drop off fee and erm an additional driver fee which doesn't apply in California so anyway so it's totally the same <pause dur="short"/> so you call up and this woman goes</u>
<u n="463" who="S0644" trans="overlap">it's total bollocks</u>
<u n="464" who="S0607">not a good idea so what happened then?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0644">it is total well this is what I'm saying like people don't so</u>
<u n="466" who="S0607"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did you feel like did you feel murderous?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0644">yeah but I thought at this <trunc>poi</trunc> well I thought well no no no I thought like you don't understand I've been in touch with your</u>
<u n="468" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0644">consultants for a year I've done this course I've done that course I've bought this I've put in that because you're consultant it's so funny though what's happened since then because</u>
<u n="470" who="S0607">just drink this water</u>
<u n="471" who="S0644">cut a long story short no I can't cut a long story short at all</u>
<u n="472" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0644">erm <pause dur="short"/> what happened was I said well look can you check this with you? so she replied back and said cos of insurance purposes cos we're not allowed to insure something that's that's you know what health and safety is and anything to do with babies is apparently too risky I said look well look I said in you're the official guide to endorsement and it was called that The Complete Guide to Endorsement there's a a paragraph erm that says you can do this</u>
<u n="474" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0644">so I said look in your guide it says this so can you check that against the insurers please? so I had to wait about two weeks and I kept on and on and on and <pause dur="short"/> you know when you've gotta be polite? that was the worst bit</u>
<u n="476" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0644">because I thought I don't wanna totally lose my rag in case</u>
<u n="478" who="S0607" trans="overlap">and then burn your bridges and everything</u>
<u n="479" who="S0644" trans="overlap">well in case it does have a bearing as it turns out I could have done cos it's all a Mickey <trunc>Mou</trunc> a total Mickey Mouse organisation and no one knows what they're doing <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> so in eventually come back with a erm I showed you that was the email it come back and said sorry and we sorry that you've had to do this erm <pause dur="short"/> but if you have any more ideas in the future please let us know</u>
<u n="480" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> do you know that's the one I sent you didn't I?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0607">yes</u>
<u n="483" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I think</u>
<u n="484" who="S0607">yes and your emails were really good</u>
<u n="485" who="S0644">well I</u>
<u n="486" who="S0607" trans="overlap">did it take you ages to write those? because</u>
<u n="487" who="S0644">not really cos <trunc>er</trunc> <trunc>d</trunc>do you know that was the one good thing that I really enjoyed I do really like having the opportunity to articulate a when you feel really strongly about something and especially when you know you're fucking right</u>
<u n="488" who="S0607">what's this?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0644" trans="overlap">to give somebody a what for</u>
<u n="490" who="S0607">slide ahead</u>
<u n="491" who="S0644" trans="overlap">slide ahead</u>
<u n="492" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0644">go on</u>
<u n="494" who="S0607">it said earlier slide area and I thought it just meant some rocks might fall and now it's saying slide ahead <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0644">that means slide ahead though</u>
<u n="496" who="S0607">doesn't it just mean</u>
<u n="497" who="S0644" trans="overlap">a slide ahead</u>
<u n="498" who="S0607">it it's a <pause dur="short"/> downhill or?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh maybe it's yeah a gradient <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="501" who="S0644">see I bet loads of people have just gone <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0644">and straight off now if you went off there where would you end up?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="505" who="S0644">right down there yeah there's no there's no <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="506" who="S0607">there's no coming back from there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="507" who="S0644">oh it's a little lake <unclear/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0607" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0644">yeah it's a little lake</u>
<u n="510" who="S0607">I have been sort of looking out to see if erm <pause dur="short"/> to see if there's like a place where you can where there's a walk trail even though I knew that I don't think I could do it until I've had a coffee and something to eat</u>
<u n="511" who="S0644">there's a tent down there and a little</u>
<u n="512" who="S0607">ah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0644">look it's like a little camping site it all looks abandoned though</u>
<u n="514" who="S0607">oh it's not a Starbucks then?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I was gonna pull in</u>
<u n="517" who="S0644">yeah it looks a little bit derelict</u>
<u n="518" who="S0607">does it?</u>
<u n="519" who="S0644" trans="overlap">see I'd be too scared to stay out here</u>
<u n="520" who="S0607" trans="overlap">oh look at here <pause dur="short"/> yeah and</u>
<u n="521" who="S0644" trans="overlap">no actually no I would for one day</u>
<u n="522" who="S0607">well we were in that place last night with the erm oh look look at that little one</u>
<u n="523" who="S0644"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0607"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="525" who="S0644"><vocal desc="sneeze"/> oh look at that river beautiful <pause dur="short"/> oh look <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0607">is it blue again?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="528" who="S0607">yeah we were there last night like basically in the town and I still was dreaming that there were two men outside the window</u>
<u n="529" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="530" who="S0607">do you know what I did?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0644">were they nice?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0607">no</u>
<u n="533" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="534" who="S0607">they were gonna do bad things</u>
<u n="535" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0607">I started to think those windows are really not brilliant windows like they're not</u>
<u n="537" who="S0644" trans="overlap">what those mosquito ones?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0607">the ones where you just well it was the mosquito net that made me decide it was okay</u>
<u n="539" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="540" who="S0607">cos the windows themselves I thought they can just go <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="542" who="S0607">but I thought oh but there's a mosquito net</u>
<u n="543" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="544" who="S0607">like as if that would stop someone I guess but</u>
<u n="545" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="546" who="S0607">erm <pause dur="short"/> but I've got this erm personal alarm that I've never actually had at hand when needed</u>
<u n="547" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="548" who="S0607">it was really okay visit world famous drive through tree</u>
<u n="549" who="S0644">ah</u>
<u n="550" who="S0607">where?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0644">well it's gonna be coming up</u>
<u n="552" who="S0607">why why does it say that and then not give you any information?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0644" trans="overlap">it's gonna be coming up <pause dur="short"/> it's gotta be en route</u>
<u n="554" who="S0607"><unclear>editing</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah so I've got this er alarm which you're supposed to carry around you know like when you're accidentally in the middle of the dark area on your own</u>
<u n="555" who="S0644" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="556" who="S0607">but you haven't brought it with you</u>
<u n="557" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="558" who="S0607">erm <pause dur="short"/> so I <trunc>p</trunc> basically put it up <unclear/></u>
<u n="559" who="S0644" trans="overlap">drive through tree's coming up <pause dur="short"/> world famous drive through tree</u>
<u n="560" who="S0607" trans="overlap">do you think they're gonna make us pay to go through it?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0644">no <pause dur="short"/> it's a free tree</u>
<u n="562" who="S0607" trans="overlap">I can't bear it</u>
<u n="563" who="S0644">it's coming up <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="564" who="S0607" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="565" who="S0644">oh what if there's there might even be like a coffee place</u>
<u n="566" who="S0607">a visitor's centre</u>
<u n="567" who="S0644">yeah there is <pause dur="short"/> drive through drive through <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="568" who="S0607">drive through <unclear>tree</unclear> quarter of a mile do I have to go up here then?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0644">yeah oh round?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0607">oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>I was gonna</unclear> go up there</u>
<u n="571" who="S0644">into their house</u>
<u n="572" who="S0607">okay so let's just be clear we need to come back to here and go up there to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="573" who="S0644">on the one 0 one <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0607"><shift new="singing"/> driving down the one 0 one <shift new="normal"/> man I should have really brought that song with us even though it's a bit like contrived</u>
<u n="575" who="S0644" trans="overlap">hey I don't know if it is</u>
<u n="576" who="S0607"><shift new="singing"/> California <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="578" who="S0607"><shift new="singing"/> California <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="579" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0607"><shift new="singing"/> here we come <unclear>home</unclear> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="581" who="S0644" trans="overlap">do every rose his its thorn</u>
<u n="582" who="S0607"><shift new="singing"/> every rose has its thorn <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah</u>
<u n="584" who="S0607"><shift new="singing"/> just like every light has its dawn <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="585" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="place"/> caf and grill oh oh <anon type="place"/> caf and grill</u>
<u n="586" who="S0607">where?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0644">straight down</u>
<u n="588" who="S0607">it's cos the sun's blinding me now now are we driving through the tree first and then having a caf and grill?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I think have a coffee</u>
<u n="590" who="S0607">and then do it</u>
<u n="591" who="S0644">then do it cos I think everything'll be better after after that take out dining or take out it's there it's there it's there and it's perfect</u>
<u n="592" who="S0607" trans="overlap">where shall I park?</u>
<u n="593" who="S0644">er in the back in the back</u>
<u n="594" who="S0607">yeah but there's no one else parked you don't know what to do</u>
<u n="595" who="S0644">I think you should park erm</u>
<u n="596" who="S0607">I like totally maybe here</u>
<u n="597" who="S0644" trans="overlap">here there's a space look there there's <unclear/> spaces</u>
<u n="598" who="S0607" trans="overlap">oh oh</u>
<u n="599" who="S0644">they're here</u>
<u n="600" who="S0607">okay hang on</u>
<u n="601" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="602" who="S0607">actually <pause dur="long"/> well I I I'll just say to them like I parked there is that like okay?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><unclear/> gimme a ticket man</u>
<u n="604" who="S0607">cos like I wasn't sure</u>
<u n="605" who="S0644" trans="overlap">ah man</u>
<u n="606" who="S0607">then we'll come out and like you see what I've done is I've made it so there's no space for anyone on this side so I'll just quickly do a bit better cos I hate it when people do that</u>
<u n="607" who="S0644">there's actually another one just there</u>
<u n="608" who="S0607">what another grill?</u>
<u n="609" who="S0644">yeah restaurant there</u>
<u n="610" who="S0607" trans="overlap">oh do you want?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0644">I'm gonna look at them both</u>
<u n="612" who="S0607" trans="overlap">is there a menu to check?</u>
<u n="613" who="S0644">erm <pause dur="long"/> go to that one cos it's easier to park then we'll walk down</u>
<u n="614" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah okay</u>
<u n="615" who="S0644">ah this is this is</u>
<u n="616" who="S0607" trans="overlap">on the right <unclear/></u>
<u n="617" who="S0644">really <unclear/></u>
<u n="618" who="S0607">it is but it's also a bit like mm mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="619" who="S0644">I'd have just driven there</u>
<u n="620" who="S0607">I hope that they like provide things that aren't just totally deep fried</u>
<u n="621" who="S0644">what here? <pause dur="short"/> are you gonna eat something? I suppose it is lunchtime isn't it?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0607">I've gotta have some lunch I'm starving</u>
<u n="623" who="S0644">are ya?</u>
<u n="624" who="S0607">this one looks even weirder</u>
<u n="625" who="S0644">I like weird places <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> anywhere</u>
<u n="626" who="S0607" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah I just</u>
<u n="627" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="628" who="S0607">I think it's a bit like where's all that space? it's cos there's too much space I'm like where's the parking? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="629" who="S0644">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think it's there</u>
<u n="630" who="S0607">just park anywhere oh it's Sunday I wonder if it's even open?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0644">I think it's closed actually</u>
<u n="632" who="S0607">imagine they're both closed damn it in bloody what's-its-face we should have picked up loads of shit</u>
<u n="633" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I bet they are <pause dur="short"/> I bet they're shut <pause dur="short"/> open no I think it's been shut a long time <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="634" who="S0607">is it worth do you wanna quickly check?</u>
<u n="635" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><unclear/> tell you <unclear/> the next one <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="636" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
