<text id="SNG4">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:06:56</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-11</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0255 S0257 S0258</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's house</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Television programmes, knitting &amp; crocheting, family, books versus eBooks, films, books.</topics>
		<activity>Talking at Book Club</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising, requesting, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0255">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Boston, Lincs</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Boston/London/Peterborough</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>account manager - sales</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0257">
				<exactage>45</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Peterborough</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Anglia</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>45</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Head of admin and HR</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_1</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>German -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0258">
				<exactage>31</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Essex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Essex</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>7</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Accountant</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="2" who="S0257">do you watch The Secret Life of Dogs?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="4" who="S0257">have you been?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0255">yeah I've been watching that</u>
<u n="6" who="S0258">no I should watch that</u>
<u n="7" who="S0257">I I should be recording or set it to come on but I tend to just sort of catch it part way in</u>
<u n="8" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0257">and the first one I saw they were talking about overweight dogs</u>
<u n="10" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0257">and they er invited owners into <unclear/> laboratory conditions and said just prepare your dog's food</u>
<u n="13" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="14" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="15" who="S0257">and this was all dry food and over eighty percent of owners weighed out too much or or they served up too much food</u>
<u n="16" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0257">only about two out of twenty used a <vocal desc="misc"/> a <trunc>w</trunc> er a scale or</u>
<u n="18" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="20" who="S0257">or a receptacle that <trunc>w</trunc> to to measure it out it's like when we feed <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I've got an old Tupperware bowl and I know that about that far down from the top</u>
<u n="21" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="22" who="S0257">is the right</u>
<u n="23" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="24" who="S0257">weight for her</u>
<u n="25" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="26" who="S0257">but over eighty percent overfed and some of them you could see them they would sort of put some in look at it and go</u>
<u n="27" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0257">oh put a bit more in</u>
<u n="29" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0257">and they what they do is they set up cameras in people's homes erm or or the environment the dog is in and sometimes it's about behaviours this time it was just about obese dogs</u>
<u n="31" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0257">as I said and er there was this little I think it was a King Charles spaniel or something quite little and he was a barrel</u>
<u n="33" who="S0258"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh</u>
<u n="34" who="S0257">and she said they are very careful they weigh his food out and he'll walk away from it in the evenings very often but what they didn't what the lady didn't realise her elderly mother lives with them</u>
<u n="35" who="S0258">oh no</u>
<u n="36" who="S0257">and she would sit in the living room with a tray</u>
<u n="37" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0257">and the family would sit in the in the kitchen or on the dining room so the dog <vocal desc="laugh"/> would go into the living room and just sit like that so mum old dear would every single time would feed the dog</u>
<u n="39" who="S0258">oh no</u>
<u n="40" who="S0257">and er they they run a pub</u>
<u n="41" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0257">so in the evenings the dog would be down in the pub as well and they <vocal desc="laugh"/> put cameras up there and the bar staff erm were lovely to this to the <trunc>d</trunc> little dog and all the customers were but they were sort of using the dog as entertainment</u>
<u n="43" who="S0258">oh no</u>
<u n="44" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0257">throwing pork scratchings</u>
<u n="46" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0257">and they were sliding them along the floor and the dog was hurtling along so it's er</u>
<u n="48" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0257">they said it's actually getting some exercise</u>
<u n="50" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="51" who="S0257">so it's better than just feeding it so it's getting some exercise</u>
<u n="52" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0257">but it would go through two packets of pork scratchings a night</u>
<u n="54" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0258">oh no</u>
<u n="56" who="S0257">and then eventually cos it kept looking at it's dinner going mm that's not pork scratchings <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="58" who="S0257">but eventually it would come back to it and it would eat all that on top of everything else</u>
<u n="59" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0257">and the poor woman was absolutely horrified</u>
<u n="61" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0257">that er everybody else was feeding this dog</u>
<u n="63" who="S0258">I think dogs are like that aren't they? cos they'll just eat whatever's in front of em won't they? or I always I don't really know that much about dogs but say you like</u>
<u n="64" who="S0257">some breeds</u>
<u n="65" who="S0258">some breeds will</u>
<u n="66" who="S0257">will will eat <trunc>everyth</trunc> er is it Labradors? or? er are known for doing that</u>
<u n="67" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0257">our dog she tends to she's got she's got OCD as well it doesn't matter how full her bowl is</u>
<u n="71" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0257">it's like you cut it in half she will eat half of it</u>
<u n="73" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0257">but she'll eat half of it down to the bottom of the bowl and it's</u>
<u n="75" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0257">it's like a solid wall of food and then the other half the bowl is full</u>
<u n="77" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0257">and she she never eats more and she rarely eats less it's half the bowl you can see she's</u>
<u n="79" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0257">measured it out she's gone right that's it and then she'll go back to the rest of it later but later could be four or five hours later even</u>
<u n="81" who="S0258">oh see my <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="82" who="S0257">but there's nobody else in the house that will eat it she knows that</u>
<u n="83" who="S0258">oh yeah so she knows it's safe</u>
<u n="84" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="85" who="S0257">but the cat will go and have a little look</u>
<u n="86" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0257">but the cat and the dog share the same water bowl</u>
<u n="88" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0257">but the the the biscuits are too big for our cat to eat</u>
<u n="90" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0257">so yeah she's never <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has never gone hungry she's got no reason to to worry and and just eat it all really quickly</u>
<u n="92" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah that it might be eaten</u>
<u n="93" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0258">see my mother-in-law's dog won't eat in front of you like if you put her food out you have to go out the room</u>
<u n="95" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="96" who="S0258">she'll only eat or she'll take it and she'll go in the corner and she'll eat herself dogs are weird</u>
<u n="97" who="S0255">strange</u>
<u n="98" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0258">dogs are strange <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0257"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will get a mouthful of biscuits and our we've got a kitchen diner <trunc>m</trunc> the kitchen part of it where all the work units are</u>
<u n="102" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="103" who="S0257">it's got a erm er a washable floor but where the dining room part is it's it's carpet</u>
<u n="104" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0257">so she'll she'll her food is on the</u>
<u n="106" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="107" who="S0257">on the hard surface so she'll go and get a mouthful carry it over to the carpet put it all down on the carpet and then pick it up off there</u>
<u n="108" who="S0258">oh</u>
<u n="109" who="S0257">and I don't know why I don't know why she does it</u>
<u n="110" who="S0255" trans="overlap">strange mm</u>
<u n="111" who="S0257">there's no rhyme or reason unless she just doesn't like standing on that floor</u>
<u n="112" who="S0255">could be mm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0258">oh animals</u>
<u n="114" who="S0255">have you seen any any of the erm Super Senses of animals? <pause dur="short"/> that's erm</u>
<u n="115" who="S0258">no</u>
<u n="116" who="S0257">no</u>
<u n="117" who="S0258">what's that about?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0255">it's erm they they do a sense each time so the first one was on <trunc>s</trunc>sight</u>
<u n="119" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0255">erm and er it was really interesting they started showing how how we see things cos light bounces off it</u>
<u n="121" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0255">and obviously if it's a prism or the rainbow</u>
<u n="124" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0255">you can see all the different colours</u>
<u n="126" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0255">and how different animals use different layers of the spectrum of the colours to actually enable them to hunt and and survive</u>
<u n="128" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0255">erm and it went right through to infrared where where er a snake erm which was some sort of bat-eating snake it was called or something erm but it used to be in the caves with the bats and it actually used infrared</u>
<u n="130" who="S0258">ah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0255">so it could see the heat</u>
<u n="132" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="133" who="S0255">with the with the animals</u>
<u n="134" who="S0258">that's amazing</u>
<u n="135" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0255">and the other end of the spectrum was the erm <vocal desc="misc"/> er <trunc>l</trunc>like ultraviolet</u>
<u n="137" who="S0258">uhu</u>
<u n="138" who="S0255">that sort of and and it was showing the the animals that used that and</u>
<u n="139" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0255">and how <trunc>l</trunc> showing it it was like flies with all the millions of eyes and how they can see</u>
<u n="141" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0255">in slow motion and how this is why you can never sort of <trunc>hi</trunc>hit a fly with it or</u>
<u n="143" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0255">all that sort of stuff</u>
<u n="146" who="S0257">cos don't dogs just see in shades of grey?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0258">I have heard that er yeah actually</u>
<u n="148" who="S0257">they don't see colour</u>
<u n="149" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0258">yeah they only see black and white yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0255">mm I think I've heard that as well</u>
<u n="152" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="153" who="S0257">erm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0255">oh no it was really interesting</u>
<u n="155" who="S0257">why is it with cats you can put a piece of cheese down in front of them or a bit of ham or something</u>
<u n="156" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="157" who="S0257">and and they don't see it but they can spot a a bird or a mouse?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0257">I I don't know if they're just terribly short-sighted</u>
<u n="160" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0258">I remember when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was born that I couldn't believe that babies can't see colour can they? for quite a long time and</u>
<u n="162" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0258">it's not that long is it? maybe six weeks or something or</u>
<u n="164" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0258">I was like really? he can only see black and white? it was just</u>
<u n="167" who="S0255">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0258">amazing</u>
<u n="169" who="S0255">and er the second one of the senses was on erm <trunc>s</trunc> hearing</u>
<u n="170" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0255">but I haven't watched that yet it's on the planner but it's really interesting and then there's there's a third one which I don't know whether it'll be on smell or touch</u>
<u n="172" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="173" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0258">I'll have to what channel's that on?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0257"><unclear>I was just gonna ask that</unclear></u>
<u n="176" who="S0255">erm I don't know</u>
<u n="177" who="S0258"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'll find it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0255">mm you know sort of I think it's maybe er BBC two or something like that</u>
<u n="179" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0255">mm sort of <trunc>sen</trunc> <trunc>se</trunc> their <trunc>se</trunc> their secret senses or Super Senses or something like that but yeah if you google it you'll find it</u>
<u n="181" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="182" who="S0255"><unclear/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0258">oh yeah I'll have to it'll probably be on Iplayer</u>
<u n="184" who="S0255" trans="overlap">it is really interesting</u>
<u n="185" who="S0258">yeah it does sound it</u>
<u n="186" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0258">the sort of thing I'd quite like</u>
<u n="188" who="S0257">I do like a bit of BBC</u>
<u n="189" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0257">I keep saying these days I really don't think we get anything out of satellite</u>
<u n="191" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="192" who="S0257"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gets all the sports</u>
<u n="193" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0257">but we don't watch movies</u>
<u n="195" who="S0258">oh</u>
<u n="196" who="S0257">er we between us we've got hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of DVDs</u>
<u n="197" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0257">we don't watch <trunc>w</trunc>we often don't even watch the television it's on just for background really</u>
<u n="199" who="S0258">we're the same I mean especially the films like I think erm I dunno it's like there never seems to be anything but you know like on the Box Office there's always loads of good films isn't there?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0258">but there's never anything actually on the on the actual ones</u>
<u n="202" who="S0257">no</u>
<u n="203" who="S0258">we watch erm cos we've got Amazon Prime I think it was Lovefilm but now it's just called Amazon Prime Instant</u>
<u n="204" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0258">that's quite good actually cos it's got all of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s shows on it and quite a few bits on there but I haven't really got the attention span to watch films these days cos I'm always thinking of like a hundred things at once</u>
<u n="206" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0258">like thinking of things I've got to do <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0257">I can't just sit and watch TV</u>
<u n="210" who="S0258">mm I can't</u>
<u n="211" who="S0257">if I do I fall asleep</u>
<u n="212" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0257">at at seven o'clock in the evening eight o'clock in the evening</u>
<u n="214" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="215" who="S0257">whereas if I'm doing something cos I do tea cosies and</u>
<u n="216" who="S0258">oh yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0257">I've started doing I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s put a few pictures up and and er to be honest it was her that gave me the idea little snuggly blankets</u>
<u n="218" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="219" who="S0257">if you knit or crochet a blanket and attached to the middle of it is a little toy</u>
<u n="220" who="S0258">yes I saw those actually in</u>
<u n="221" who="S0257">so I've I've started doing those</u>
<u n="222" who="S0258">ah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0257">and I can do one in an evening</u>
<u n="224" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0257">if I set my mind to it</u>
<u n="227" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0257">but I can't just watch television</u>
<u n="229" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0257">my mind's like you say my mind wanders</u>
<u n="231" who="S0258">I can't concentrate</u>
<u n="232" who="S0257">I fall asleep and if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says to me come on let's watch a DVD</u>
<u n="233" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0257">you choose and I'll say what's the point I'll be asleep in ten minutes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0257">you <trunc>choo</trunc> you may as well</u>
<u n="237" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0257">watch something that you wanna see through to the end</u>
<u n="239" who="S0258">oh I'm the same it frustrates <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos he's like can you not just watch a film with me?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0258">and I'm like well no cos I just get all I'll just go and do so and so</u>
<u n="242" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0258">or I'll do this or I'll do that at the same time and <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0255">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> always falls asleep and it's not even in a film it's just in a normal TV programme</u>
<u n="245" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0258">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0255">he just falls asleep</u>
<u n="248" who="S0258">there's something about the TV isn't there?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="250" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0258">being on the sofa and being all cosy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="252" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="253" who="S0258">er what was I gonna say? oh a lady at work she's quite into knitting and crocheting she brought in erm <vocal desc="misc"/> like a little pattern book she got with a magazine of all Christmas stuff and</u>
<u n="254" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="255" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="256" who="S0258">so she's gonna make a few bits stockings and I think there was a snowman doorstop and cos I love I'm all over anything like that</u>
<u n="257" who="S0257" trans="overlap">oh nice</u>
<u n="258" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0258">anything kind of decorating the house</u>
<u n="261" who="S0257">you should learn <unclear/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0258">I would like to I would like to cos my mum always used to be able to knit and crochet but I don't think I've got the patience or the kind of I dunno like is it the coordination almost? or <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="263" who="S0255">mm dexterity</u>
<u n="264" who="S0257">if you crochet though you can do it literally in five minutes</u>
<u n="265" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah dexterity that's the word yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0257">I've just got a big erm like a a jute bag</u>
<u n="267" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0257">and I just keep my whatever I'm working on at the moment</u>
<u n="269" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0257">in there and you can keep the wool in there so you literally just</u>
<u n="271" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0257">working with what what you can hold in your hand</u>
<u n="273" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0257">and if you need to put it away put it down you just put it back in the bag and it's it's all in there you don't have to</u>
<u n="275" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="276" who="S0257">you know make any clear any er any area or anything or <unclear/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0258">I've heard it's very therapeutic and like people say it's</u>
<u n="278" who="S0257" trans="overlap">and it's very trendy these days</u>
<u n="279" who="S0258">do you know? I know so many people who are into knitting now</u>
<u n="280" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="281" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0258">there's a knitting club</u>
<u n="283" who="S0257">I started up I've started up a knit and natter club at work</u>
<u n="284" who="S0255">have you?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0258">I was just about to say a knitting club yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0257">Thursday lunchtimes erm and and it was a case of a couple of people wanted to know one of them was my daughter I think we started three four weeks ago and I just showed them on the first one how to do basic stitches and how to do a granny square</u>
<u n="287" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0257">and everybody wants to <trunc>m</trunc> be making blankets</u>
<u n="289" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0257">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s birthday's November and she was determined she was gonna make this like a double bed size blanket</u>
<u n="292" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="293" who="S0257">so she worked out she needed two hundred and eighty-four squares and she'd got to about seventy</u>
<u n="294" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0258">wow</u>
<u n="296" who="S0257">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> goes to band rehearsal every week once a week so now I'll go to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="297" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="298" who="S0257">or she'll come to mine we try and work it on a Wednesday so we can watch Great British Bake Off as well</u>
<u n="299" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0257">and she says to me mum I'm not even twenty and I'm turning into an old lady <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0258">oh and it's quite popular now though</u>
<u n="303" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0258">I think it's got a revival like baking as well though like cos the Bake Off I think</u>
<u n="305" who="S0255">mm oh yeah did you watch it last night?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0258">yeah it was good</u>
<u n="308" who="S0255">mm I was out last night when I got in and I watched it when I got in</u>
<u n="309" who="S0258">they amaze me some of the stuff they do though</u>
<u n="310" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0258">it's like</u>
<u n="312" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="313" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0258">cos I I can make cakes but they never look pretty <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="316" who="S0258">and the way that they just</u>
<u n="317" who="S0257">it's of the scale isn't it?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0258">just nail yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="320" who="S0258">but that erm <vocal desc="misc"/> I know you didn't watch it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but the Swedish Scandinavian cake did you watch it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0255">no I watched it</u>
<u n="322" who="S0258">oh you did watch it? sorry oh I thought you said you didn't watch it</u>
<u n="323" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah that's no I watched it after I got in</u>
<u n="324" who="S0258">oh sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0257"><unclear/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0255">mm oh yeah I couldn't wait till today</u>
<u n="327" who="S0258">yeah yeah yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0255">princess cake yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0257"><unclear/> cake</u>
<u n="330" who="S0258">oh that looked amazing didn't it?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0258">I was like oh</u>
<u n="333" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0258">that looks really good</u>
<u n="335" who="S0257">but when you see some of the fantastic results they all have had</u>
<u n="336" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0257">and then when they did that princess cake only two of them turned out didn't they?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="339" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0257">and the others</u>
<u n="341" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0257">looked a right</u>
<u n="343" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0257">hash</u>
<u n="345" who="S0255">mm yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0257">probably a lot better than mine would've turned out</u>
<u n="347" who="S0258"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0257">but still and you <trunc>thi</trunc></u>
<u n="349" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0257">and it it just makes you appreciate the fact that they are erm amateurs</u>
<u n="351" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0257">they're only doing it cos they love doing it</u>
<u n="353" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0255">that's what that erm Nancy said didn't she? she said with something like that</u>
<u n="355" who="S0258">I like her</u>
<u n="356" who="S0255">she said it's if you've got the basics if you've got the skills</u>
<u n="357" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="358" who="S0255">and you can just do them</u>
<u n="359" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0255">and that's what she was saying oh you need to <trunc>d</trunc> for the different types of sponge and different things</u>
<u n="361" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="362" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="363" who="S0255">she knows what you need to do for that and she knows when you need to prove it and how long and <trunc>w</trunc> and if you've got those skills</u>
<u n="364" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0255">which so she's a really good solid baker</u>
<u n="366" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0255">with a bit of flair as well</u>
<u n="368" who="S0258">I think she's good</u>
<u n="369" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="371" who="S0258">I I think she might</u>
<u n="372" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah I like her</u>
<u n="373" who="S0258">I think she might I like her</u>
<u n="374" who="S0255">I think she might</u>
<u n="375" who="S0258">but that girl the little baby</u>
<u n="376" who="S0255">Martha</u>
<u n="377" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="379" who="S0255">oh oh I love her</u>
<u n="380" who="S0258">I know she's oh my god</u>
<u n="381" who="S0257">she's doing her A levels</u>
<u n="382" who="S0258">doing her A levels</u>
<u n="383" who="S0255">mm yeah she took two exams the following week and she's like going well I'm <trunc>d</trunc> I haven't practised that it's like a technical thing and then she did it really well didn't she?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0258">she's amazing</u>
<u n="385" who="S0257"><unclear/> see her last week though she</u>
<u n="386" who="S0255">oh</u>
<u n="387" who="S0257">one something that she did didn't turn out very well at all and she got and and er I like the fact that the judges are no less harsh on her just because she's seventeen</u>
<u n="388" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="389" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah she's young yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0257">and the others but she was actually crying</u>
<u n="392" who="S0255">I know she was outside in tears and she was saying I know it's silly but I'm not but and they've just said it's not very good and <trunc>w</trunc> you know</u>
<u n="393" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="394" who="S0255">and then the next one the next thing she did in the next round was just amazing again wasn't it?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0255">and you think well yeah bless her</u>
<u n="397" who="S0258">she's definitely</u>
<u n="398" who="S0255" trans="overlap">can you pass the sauce?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0258">oh yeah of course</u>
<u n="400" who="S0255">thanks mm</u>
<u n="401" who="S0258">she's definitely like a natural talent isn't she like?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0255" trans="overlap">she's only oh yeah yeah but when she started doing all the different things with the erm <vocal desc="misc"/> one of the things she did was obviously skiing <unclear/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="404" who="S0255">so er she must've had that</u>
<u n="405" who="S0258">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0255">the right life you know growing up with the</u>
<u n="407" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="408" who="S0258" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0255">with skiing and this and that and the other when she did all that and it's sort of like oh well I've had this with the chalet thingy and</u>
<u n="410" who="S0257" trans="overlap">biscuit chalet <unclear/> wasn't it? the showstopper</u>
<u n="411" who="S0255">mm yeah yeah some of the stuff she does</u>
<u n="412" who="S0257">and it always er amazes me when perhaps it mm perhaps it's wrong of me to say so but when big hairy fellas</u>
<u n="413" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0257">produce these</u>
<u n="415" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0257">such delicate pieces of work</u>
<u n="417" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="418" who="S0258">it's amazing that one that was always a pencil behind his ear with <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="419" who="S0257">the <trunc>buil</trunc> er is he a carpenter or something?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0258">yeah something like that yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0257" trans="overlap">yeah he's always got a pencil <unclear/> his ear</u>
<u n="422" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0258">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think Norman seems to be a favourite doesn't he? the the oh the erm Scottish guy</u>
<u n="424" who="S0257" trans="overlap">I think he went out last week</u>
<u n="425" who="S0255">Norman?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0258">oh did he?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0255">yeah Norman went last week</u>
<u n="428" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="429" who="S0258">oh I think of another name</u>
<u n="430" who="S0257">there's Luis</u>
<u n="431" who="S0255">there's Luis who is the old guy who's very technical does amazing</u>
<u n="432" who="S0258" trans="overlap">Luis Luis that's it not Norman</u>
<u n="433" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0257">he's got real OCD hasn't he?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="436" who="S0257">as well I think he said</u>
<u n="437" who="S0255">has he?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0257">yeah yeah so</u>
<u n="439" who="S0255">oh</u>
<u n="440" who="S0257">everything has to be</u>
<u n="441" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="442" who="S0257">his his design for the er what did he call it? the tower no <trunc>s</trunc> the the <trunc>s</trunc>something on the tower <trunc>o</trunc></u>
<u n="443" who="S0255">the the tower on the no the</u>
<u n="444" who="S0257" trans="overlap">on the hill or</u>
<u n="445" who="S0255">cave on erm castle on the rock oh ah yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0257" trans="overlap">something like that</u>
<u n="447" who="S0255">er the one that did yeah I know the one you mean</u>
<u n="448" who="S0257">with all the caramel</u>
<u n="449" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="450" who="S0257">when he showed them his design it was almost like er a erm <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0255">technical drawing mm</u>
<u n="452" who="S0257">a technical yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0257">a technical drawing</u>
<u n="455" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="456" who="S0257">so precise</u>
<u n="457" who="S0258">oh I have to admit those erm <vocal desc="misc"/> the technical <trunc>chal</trunc> the one with the caramel</u>
<u n="458" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="460" who="S0258">those cakes looked amazing didn't they?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="462" who="S0258">all those layers oh you could so just looked so good</u>
<u n="463" who="S0257">I've always wanted to do a it's <unclear/> torte isn't it?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="466" who="S0258">I think that's what it's called yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0257" trans="overlap">cos I had er a cookery book and it was one of the main pictures in it you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0258">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="470" who="S0257">you get a big page and I've always fancied doing that and thought no I can't make caramel</u>
<u n="471" who="S0258"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0257">mm but I'm er I'm sure you know if you set your mind to it <unclear/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0255">it's getting it the right temperature isn't it?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="476" who="S0255">and then working it and using it then</u>
<u n="477" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="478" who="S0258">yeah I wouldn't even know where to start on anything like that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="480" who="S0258">I'd like to though maybe I'll like make a croque-en-bouche for next book club or something?</u>
<u n="481" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="482" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0258"><unclear/> I'll be like what did you bring?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0258"><unclear/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0255">that was erm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0258">this</u>
<u n="489" who="S0257"><unclear>us just</unclear> turning up with sausage rolls and brownies</u>
<u n="490" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0258">I'm struggling with a croque-en-bouche</u>
<u n="492" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/> croque-en-bouche</u>
<u n="493" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0255">that was erm Australian Masterchef wasn't it? they always used to do</u>
<u n="495" who="S0258">oh did they? was it?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0255">when er towards the end <trunc>w</trunc>when they had the the last few they had to just do this showstopper</u>
<u n="497" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0255">and they used to bring somebody in they'd go right and then they'd er and it almost always was a croque-en-bouche</u>
<u n="499" who="S0258" trans="overlap">en-bouche <vocal desc="misc"/> oh</u>
<u n="500" who="S0255">and they'd all go oh</u>
<u n="501" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0258"><unclear/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0255">and spinning all the sugar</u>
<u n="504" who="S0257">I watched that on one occasion</u>
<u n="505" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="506" who="S0257">and they were I think they were shucking oysters is it shucking? it is isn't it? when you open an oyster you <trunc>shu</trunc> you use a shuck</u>
<u n="507" who="S0255" trans="overlap">don't know</u>
<u n="508" who="S0258">mm don't like oysters</u>
<u n="509" who="S0257">and you shuck it er oysters and they had king big king prawns and it was they had erm professionals that literally spend all day doing this and then record holders for how many er they can do in a certain amount of time and they were just <unclear/> they were literally picking up a prawn</u>
<u n="510" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="511" who="S0257">once they'd picked from the point of pricking it <vocal desc="misc"/> pricking it up? picking it up getting it to the hand it was half stripped</u>
<u n="512" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="513" who="S0257">and it was just this movement like this</u>
<u n="514" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0257">er you know what it's like when you try and peel a prawn yourself?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0257">it's so fiddly</u>
<u n="518" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0257">and they were just <vocal desc="misc"/> with them and the contestants' faces were like masks of horror</u>
<u n="520" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0257">thinking oh I I can't do that that quickly</u>
<u n="522" who="S0255">mm <pause dur="short"/> I watched one one series of that a few years ago the Australian one</u>
<u n="523" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="524" who="S0255">just cos er I happened to be flicking through and it was the first one as a coincidence when I started watching it</u>
<u n="525" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0255">and I watched that series but apart from that erm one the other time I've gone in I've not been interested in it cos I think er it's it's very much like with the <trunc>B</trunc>British Bake Off you get to know the people and you like them</u>
<u n="527" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="528" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0258">it's the characters yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0255">mm same with America's Next Top Model and all those sort of things if you start watching any any of those things</u>
<u n="532" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="533" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0255">you need to watch them sort of from the <trunc>begin</trunc>beginning</u>
<u n="535" who="S0258">oh definitely yeah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="537" who="S0258">yeah no I've kind of given up with Next Top Model cos I did start watching it</u>
<u n="538" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="539" who="S0258">and now I've just thought oh I think</u>
<u n="540" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="541" who="S0258">it's been going for so long now</u>
<u n="542" who="S0255">I haven't watched it for years</u>
<u n="543" who="S0257">don't think I've ever watched it</u>
<u n="544" who="S0255">but this year it's men and women in it</u>
<u n="545" who="S0258" trans="overlap">oh just as well yeah that's why</u>
<u n="546" who="S0257">oh really?</u>
<u n="547" who="S0255">mm and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s watching it and also the the one that's eliminated they're out the house but they go along to the photo shoot and they have a photo taken each time as well</u>
<u n="548" who="S0258">oh okay</u>
<u n="549" who="S0255">and then social media all these photos are put up and er at the end social media have a vote to put one person back in</u>
<u n="550" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0257">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0258"><unclear/> a little bit</u>
<u n="553" who="S0255">whether it's for the final or mm</u>
<u n="554" who="S0258">oh that's good</u>
<u n="555" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0258">cos that sort of cos the format is a bit old now isn't it?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0255">mm the thing I enjoy most about that is the er is the photographs when they do the photo shoot</u>
<u n="558" who="S0258">yeah and we see em at the end yeah</u>
<u n="559" who="S0255">and do that so here's the when they're actually taking the photographs</u>
<u n="560" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="561" who="S0255">and then this is the photo that they've</u>
<u n="562" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="563" who="S0255">they've got from it erm I just cos for me I think it's cause and effect I like</u>
<u n="564" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="565" who="S0255">you see something happening and that's what the result is</u>
<u n="566" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="567" who="S0255">and that's the bit I enjoy and I can just literally just watch that bit out of any of them and be quite happy just to watch that</u>
<u n="568" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="569" who="S0257">and are they into touching up the photos and airbrushing that sort of thing?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0255">no well no I don't no they don't they just it's just as they are isn't it?</u>
<u n="571" who="S0258">yeah I think it's as they are I quite like when you see like these girls who obviously they're really skinny and tall but I just look at them like you're not actually that pretty</u>
<u n="572" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="573" who="S0258">and then you they photograph</u>
<u n="574" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="575" who="S0258">and the way they do em and they just look</u>
<u n="576" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0258">a hundred dollar a hundred million dollars</u>
<u n="578" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0258">and the way they can just</u>
<u n="580" who="S0257" trans="overlap">sensational</u>
<u n="581" who="S0258">yeah it's quite interesting</u>
<u n="582" who="S0255">well a lot of it is is how you stand and</u>
<u n="583" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="584" who="S0255">and like elongating parts and</u>
<u n="585" who="S0258">how you can hold yourself and yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0255">reflecting the light off your face</u>
<u n="587" who="S0258">there is more to it</u>
<u n="588" who="S0255">she says turning her light to the <trunc>fa</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="589" who="S0258">the face to the light yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0255">the face to the light above her</u>
<u n="591" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0255">yeah mm no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> likes it she she really likes watching it</u>
<u n="593" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="594" who="S0255">but at the beginning the first couple of them she'll be saying she'll be going she certainly needs a makeover what are they gonna do with her? are they gonna make it <unclear>elf and pixie</unclear> face</u>
<u n="595" who="S0258" trans="overlap">oh yeah I like that one though when they cut their hair</u>
<u n="596" who="S0255">and do this yeah</u>
<u n="597" who="S0258">in that episode when they cut all their hair that's always there was er <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="598" who="S0255">mm there's always the ones that are crying and</u>
<u n="599" who="S0258">yeah there's always one</u>
<u n="600" who="S0255">you're cutting off my hair</u>
<u n="601" who="S0258">you can't cut off my hair I'm so ugly now</u>
<u n="602" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like</u>
<u n="603" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="604" who="S0255">no you really aren't</u>
<u n="605" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="607" who="S0258">no I do like it</u>
<u n="608" who="S0255">mm ah</u>
<u n="609" who="S0258">proper trashy TV <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="610" who="S0255">oh yeah yeah not quite Jeremy Kyle but</u>
<u n="611" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="612" who="S0258">oh no</u>
<u n="613" who="S0255">mother-in-law watches that</u>
<u n="614" who="S0258">oh does she?</u>
<u n="615" who="S0255">mm look at this look at this she's a lovely girl such a lovely girl look at her and look at that <trunc>ma</trunc> he's gone and done this and he's done that <vocal desc="misc"/> poor little girl she goes</u>
<u n="616" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="617" who="S0258">ah do you know it does make me angry watching that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="618" who="S0255">mm remember <trunc>f</trunc> a year or so back</u>
<u n="619" who="S0258">oh</u>
<u n="620" who="S0255">when something was all over Facebook there were <anon type="place"/> people from <anon type="place"/> on it weren't they? that</u>
<u n="621" who="S0258">oh really?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0255">oh my god this girl's on it and I went to school with her and she</u>
<u n="623" who="S0258">oh no</u>
<u n="624" who="S0255">I don't know what they were on for but</u>
<u n="625" who="S0257">my <trunc>ne</trunc></u>
<u n="626" who="S0258">oh no</u>
<u n="627" who="S0257">she was my next door neighbour she now lives in Canada</u>
<u n="628" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="629" who="S0257">her and her friend were flown out to America on erm</u>
<u n="630" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="631" who="S0257">don't think it was <trunc>Opr</trunc> oh it erm not Oprah Winfrey what was the what was the woman's name? <pause dur="short"/> erm <trunc>ano</trunc>another erm host</u>
<u n="632" who="S0258">Ricki Lake?</u>
<u n="633" who="S0255" trans="overlap">Ellen DeGeneres?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0258">no</u>
<u n="635" who="S0257">no</u>
<u n="636" who="S0255">oh not Ricki Lake?</u>
<u n="637" who="S0257">no of of the same sort of Oprah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="639" who="S0258">oh erm</u>
<u n="640" who="S0255">erm Jeremy Kyle all those sort of things I can see her face now I can't remember but it was I'm British but I love or or I want to fall in love with an American man</u>
<u n="641" who="S0255">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="642" who="S0257">or something really corny like that</u>
<u n="643" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="644" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="645" who="S0257">erm and er er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her friend were were it was an all expenses paid trip I don't know how they got chosen</u>
<u n="646" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="647" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="648" who="S0257">it was before I knew them and they got er got flown out there they were on this show and it was it was so cringeworthy these American guys were coming on and they'd maybe only be there in a pair of jeans they were</u>
<u n="649" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="650" who="S0257">and they'd they'd carry a rose or something and declare their undying love</u>
<u n="651" who="S0258">oh god</u>
<u n="652" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="653" who="S0257">but it's on TV</u>
<u n="654" who="S0258"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="655" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="656" who="S0257">and it's the first time you've clapped eyes on em and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friend <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s quite I mean she's outgoing</u>
<u n="657" who="S0255">oh excuse me</u>
<u n="658" who="S0257">but she's not very sort of high five and woo woo</u>
<u n="659" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="660" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="661" who="S0257">and her friend kept turning to her and going like this for a fist pump <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="662" who="S0255">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="663" who="S0257">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like mm can't really leave her hanging hey</u>
<u n="664" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="665" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="666" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="667" who="S0255">mm so did they ever meet <trunc>Am</trunc>American guys and?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0257">well it was a bit like erm <pause dur="short"/> blind Date</u>
<u n="669" who="S0255">oh right</u>
<u n="670" who="S0258">oh right</u>
<u n="671" who="S0257"><unclear/> that show anyway</u>
<u n="672" who="S0255">mm mm</u>
<u n="673" who="S0258">I used to love that when that used to be on</u>
<u n="674" who="S0255" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="675" who="S0257">Blind Date? yeah</u>
<u n="676" who="S0258"><shift new="singing"/> do do do do do do <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="677" who="S0255">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="678" who="S0257">bit of Cilla</u>
<u n="679" who="S0258"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="680" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="681" who="S0257">you knew it was Saturday night then didn't you?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0258"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="683" who="S0255">what's your name and where do you come from?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0258"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="685" who="S0257">see that's that's that was</u>
<u n="686" who="S0255">proper telly</u>
<u n="687" who="S0257">prime time TV</u>
<u n="688" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="689" who="S0257">Saturday night</u>
<u n="690" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="691" who="S0258">not not like X Factor</u>
<u n="692" who="S0257"><unclear/> get now</u>
<u n="693" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="694" who="S0258">yeah I don't even know what's on I actually only had X Factor on yesterday cos it was just on in the background <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like oh you only put it on cos Simon Cowell's back I was like well</u>
<u n="695" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="696" who="S0258">I didn't even realise he was back until I turned it on</u>
<u n="697" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="698" who="S0258">but there isn't really erm I don't think people watch Saturday TV night TV now</u>
<u n="699" who="S0255">no no</u>
<u n="700" who="S0258">but all the good shows like Gladiators and You Bet and stuff that's not on any more obviously</u>
<u n="701" who="S0257">oh god they were brilliant weren't they?</u>
<u n="702" who="S0255">Summertime Specials that's what I grew up with on the Saturday night</u>
<u n="703" who="S0257" trans="overlap">you could almost set your set your watch by the</u>
<u n="704" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="705" who="S0257">whatever was on TV couldn't you?</u>
<u n="706" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="707" who="S0257">it was like a erm a ritual <unclear/> you'd watch this</u>
<u n="708" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="709" who="S0257">then you watch er you know</u>
<u n="710" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="711" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="712" who="S0258">you'd watch er wrestling on Saturday afternoon</u>
<u n="713" who="S0255" trans="overlap">It's a It's a Knockout yeah</u>
<u n="714" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="715" who="S0255">four o'clock used to be the wrestling</u>
<u n="716" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="717" who="S0257"><unclear/></u>
<u n="718" who="S0255">yeah and my nana who was well she still is she's ninety something now and she's a little tiny bird-like er absolutely immaculate with how she dresses and everything and she'd be sat there and she used to just get go on get at em <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="719" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="720" who="S0255">ah don't <vocal desc="misc"/> and all that</u>
<u n="721" who="S0257" trans="overlap">you had er you had all nana's at the side didn't you?</u>
<u n="722" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="723" who="S0257">with their hats on and their coat and handbags and</u>
<u n="724" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah I know and we used to be looking going</u>
<u n="725" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="726" who="S0257">and they would</u>
<u n="727" who="S0258"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="728" who="S0255">it's nana</u>
<u n="729" who="S0257">try and keep try and hit the er the wrestler</u>
<u n="730" who="S0255">yeah oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0257">cos the because there'd always be a baddie and a goodie</u>
<u n="732" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="733" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="734" who="S0257">and they'd be trying to hit them</u>
<u n="735" who="S0255">mm well when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was growing up he got into that erm WWE</u>
<u n="736" who="S0258">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="737" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="738" who="S0255">or it was WWF then but yeah the wrestling and he used to be all into them and watching em all the time so for his birthday when he must've been about nine I <trunc>s</trunc> I bought tickets and I took him to <anon type="place"/> to go and watch one of the live wrestling show things and I like yeah WWE wrestling and <trunc>th</trunc>this person was on and that person was on</u>
<u n="739" who="S0258">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="740" who="S0255">and I sat there thinking yeah I'm being a good mummy here and I'm bringing them er bringing him and we sat quite near the front and we're looking and he was all excited and then all these half-naked men started coming out and I thought actually</u>
<u n="741" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="742" who="S0255">you're not it's it's not that <trunc>ba</trunc> like I hadn't even really thought cos you're watching it on the telly</u>
<u n="743" who="S0258">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="744" who="S0255">and they're all got the makeup paint stuff on</u>
<u n="745" who="S0258"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="746" who="S0257">I wonder if he wants to come back next week?</u>
<u n="747" who="S0258"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="748" who="S0255">well exactly yeah it was like I was like mm actually yeah this is actually alright <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh and he loved it</u>
<u n="749" who="S0258">ah this guy at work who's in his mid-twenties he's really into wrestling</u>
<u n="750" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="751" who="S0258">he like collects all he's single bless him</u>
<u n="752" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="753" who="S0258">but he'd make someone a lovely sort of boyfriend but he collects all the belts and he people will say to you know it's not real and he says don't talk to me about it</u>
<u n="754" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="755" who="S0258">cos I think he wants to believe <unclear/></u>
<u n="756" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="757" who="S0257"><unclear/> not <trunc>s</trunc> <unclear/> staged</u>
<u n="758" who="S0258">yeah he's such a lovely person bless him</u>
<u n="759" who="S0255">ah mm</u>
<u n="760" who="S0258">yeah bit off the wall</u>
<u n="761" who="S0255">I won't introduce him to my daughter</u>
<u n="762" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="763" who="S0255">cos he sounds a bit too lovely</u>
<u n="764" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="765" who="S0255">bit too special</u>
<u n="766" who="S0258" trans="overlap">is she on the lookout?</u>
<u n="767" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="768" who="S0258">is she?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0255">well</u>
<u n="770" who="S0258">oh okay</u>
<u n="771" who="S0255">yeah I mean she's</u>
<u n="772" who="S0257">are you on the lookout for her?</u>
<u n="773" who="S0255">well <trunc>n</trunc>no</u>
<u n="774" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="775" who="S0255">I'm well no I <trunc>d</trunc> I'm not into pimping her out or anything no she's</u>
<u n="776" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="777" who="S0255">she's</u>
<u n="778" who="S0257">matchmaking I thought you were gonna say</u>
<u n="779" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah matchmaking's the word</u>
<u n="780" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="781" who="S0255">er yeah er I mean</u>
<u n="782" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="783" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="784" who="S0255">she <vocal desc="laugh"/> she yeah she'd <trunc>l</trunc> she'd love to be a part of a couple</u>
<u n="785" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="786" who="S0255">love to settle down she's had offers but she's not interested she said it's gotta be the right person</u>
<u n="787" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="788" who="S0255">erm she doesn't wanna play around mess around she wants to be have a serious relationship with someone and she says it may not work and if it doesn't then hopefully I'll have another serious relationship with somebody else but I'm not gonna see somebody who just wants fun cos I know I don't want that</u>
<u n="789" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="790" who="S0255">so yeah</u>
<u n="791" who="S0257">that's the right way to be isn't it? you don't lower your standards for somebody else</u>
<u n="792" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="793" who="S0258">exactly</u>
<u n="794" who="S0255">no no exactly exactly and <trunc>sh</trunc>and she says er you know she's really busy she's got obviously the skating she's got the Rainbow group she runs and</u>
<u n="795" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="796" who="S0255">et cetera and goes out with her friends and does stuff so she's busy she says you know</u>
<u n="797" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="798" who="S0255">I don't quite know when I'd fit one in</u>
<u n="799" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="800" who="S0255">I said well that's great</u>
<u n="801" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="802" who="S0255">cos that's how it should be cos then that's</u>
<u n="803" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="804" who="S0255">when you do meet somebody but they then fit in around you</u>
<u n="805" who="S0258">when you least expect it</u>
<u n="806" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="807" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="808" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="809" who="S0257">when you're not on the lookout when you're not</u>
<u n="810" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="811" who="S0258">that's when you always meet someone</u>
<u n="812" who="S0257" trans="overlap"><trunc>al</trunc>almost searching for <unclear/> yeah you just</u>
<u n="813" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="814" who="S0258">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="815" who="S0255">but she's said that said before you know she said oh she said I'm not that bothered and sometimes she goes I would quite like to be but <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then she says</u>
<u n="816" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="817" who="S0255">but I know it's not gonna happen I'm gonna end up this lonely old spinster</u>
<u n="818" who="S0258">oh bless her</u>
<u n="819" who="S0255">and I I'll have lots of cats and dogs</u>
<u n="820" who="S0257">ah</u>
<u n="821" who="S0258"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="822" who="S0255">and I'll smell of cat and dog wee</u>
<u n="823" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="824" who="S0257">oh so she'll be a crazy old spinster? <unclear/></u>
<u n="825" who="S0255">oh yeah yeah she said and eventually I'll die and they'll just eat me but it'll be fine</u>
<u n="826" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="827" who="S0255">and I'm like <vocal desc="laugh"/> where's this coming from?</u>
<u n="828" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="829" who="S0258">she's only a baby yet isn't she?</u>
<u n="830" who="S0255">oh she yeah she's twenty-three twenty-four</u>
<u n="831" who="S0258"><vocal desc="misc"/> ah twenty-four</u>
<u n="832" who="S0255">twenty-three? twenty-four in a in a few weeks yeah yeah twenty-four oh god how's how's my daughter twenty-four?</u>
<u n="833" who="S0258">I do know</u>
<u n="834" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="835" who="S0258">I do know somebody who's just turned twenty-five a guy at work</u>
<u n="836" who="S0255">oh do you?</u>
<u n="837" who="S0258">yeah he's very <trunc>n</trunc> he's a bit timid though</u>
<u n="838" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="839" who="S0258">would she like a timid guy? or would you think she'd prefer somebody a bit more confident?</u>
<u n="840" who="S0255" trans="overlap">er I think she needs</u>
<u n="841" who="S0258">he's not the wrestling guy someone else just so you know</u>
<u n="842" who="S0255">no just another one</u>
<u n="843" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="844" who="S0258">it's not the wrestling guy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="845" who="S0257">not the weird one</u>
<u n="846" who="S0255">not the weird wrestling one</u>
<u n="847" who="S0257">and what and what is weird about him?</u>
<u n="848" who="S0258"><vocal desc="misc"/> erm well he lives on his own</u>
<u n="849" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="850" who="S0258">he used to share a house with his brother but his brother's moved out now and I would probably say he's a little bit set in his ways</u>
<u n="851" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="852" who="S0258">cos he's lived on his own for quite a while and he's he's quite tidy and he just he probably doesn't go out that much maybe</u>
<u n="853" who="S0257">but that must mean that he's got</u>
<u n="854" who="S0255"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s not tidy I don't know how that would work? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="855" who="S0258" trans="overlap">but I dunno if he's looking for <trunc>s</trunc> the right person to</u>
<u n="856" who="S0255" trans="overlap">would he would he tidy up after her? <vocal desc="laugh"/> she might like that</u>
<u n="857" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="858" who="S0258">I don't know if he's looking for the <trunc>ri</trunc> he needs the right person to bring him out of his shell a little bit you know?</u>
<u n="859" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="860" who="S0255">yeah mm</u>
<u n="861" who="S0258">there's potential there</u>
<u n="862" who="S0255">yeah it's funny cos she's quite chatty and bright but er she's actually really quite shy</u>
<u n="863" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="864" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="865" who="S0255">she had she says it's funny because you know normally when people start to get interested in each other there's a bit of a <vocal desc="gasp"/> does he like me? doesn't he? oh he said that what does that mean?</u>
<u n="866" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="867" who="S0255">oh well I'll say so and so and I'll text <trunc>messa</trunc> and she said it's that excitement bubbling she absolutely hates that it terrifies her</u>
<u n="868" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="869" who="S0258">does it?</u>
<u n="870" who="S0255">er well not even not so much terrifies she just doesn't enjoy it</u>
<u n="871" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="872" who="S0255">she said I just we start a bit like this she said and and I just wanna say to them look is something gonna happen? is it going somewhere?</u>
<u n="873" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="874" who="S0255">cos if it is that's great let's just get on you know</u>
<u n="875" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="876" who="S0255">and go out and see what happens</u>
<u n="877" who="S0257">if not <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="878" who="S0255">or if not er er cos er I don't like this</u>
<u n="879" who="S0257"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="880" who="S0255">and or I do you just wanna be a friend? and so she's sort of almost like feels <trunc>li</trunc> and she has to hold back</u>
<u n="881" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="882" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="883" who="S0255">and she sort of goes mm I really really gets in a tizzy about it bless her but oh I'm sure it'll happen I'm I'm sure it'll happen</u>
<u n="884" who="S0257">I would hate to be a teenager early twenties and setting out on the</u>
<u n="885" who="S0255">mm yeah</u>
<u n="886" who="S0257">journey to find a a life partner</u>
<u n="887" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="888" who="S0258">it's all different now though it's like everyone does online don't they?</u>
<u n="889" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="890" who="S0257">that's how I met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> though online</u>
<u n="891" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="892" who="S0258">yeah but even like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at work the one he was he met his girlfriend <trunc>sh</trunc> when he was twenty-one and she was twenty-three online and I was really surprised by that</u>
<u n="893" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="894" who="S0258">cos I always thought that I know people my age use</u>
<u n="895" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="896" who="S0258">online dating but I didn't think someone in their early twenties would</u>
<u n="897" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no yeah they do</u>
<u n="898" who="S0258">cos I thought surely they're using the <trunc>s</trunc>the same old meeting in the bars and stuff</u>
<u n="899" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="900" who="S0258">but no</u>
<u n="901" who="S0255">no no</u>
<u n="902" who="S0257">no</u>
<u n="903" who="S0258">it's across the board now it's everyone isn't it?</u>
<u n="904" who="S0257" trans="overlap">it is absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="905" who="S0255">mm mm</u>
<u n="906" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="907" who="S0257">and I think it's partly because some people are er nervous about meeting somebody they don't know and being with <trunc>s</trunc> er being in the same room or going on a date</u>
<u n="908" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="909" who="S0257">with somebody they don't know whereas <trunc>on</trunc>online you can get to know people well you</u>
<u n="910" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah email and phone and</u>
<u n="911" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="912" who="S0257">if you've got if you haven't got a weirdo on the other end</u>
<u n="913" who="S0258">yeah that's the thing you have to filter <unclear/></u>
<u n="914" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="915" who="S0257" trans="overlap"><unclear/> you can get to know somebody before you actually meet them</u>
<u n="916" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="917" who="S0257">and at least know things about them and about their character sense of humour and that sort of thing and their interests</u>
<u n="918" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="919" who="S0258">but even if you were searching like you can filter down people they always say what they're looking for don't they?</u>
<u n="920" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="921" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="922" who="S0258">so there's none of that kind of like if</u>
<u n="923" who="S0257"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="924" who="S0258">if you want children</u>
<u n="925" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="926" who="S0258">you want someone who wants children and someone that</u>
<u n="927" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="928" who="S0258">specifically says I don't want children you're like okay</u>
<u n="929" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="930" who="S0258">I I don't want him you know you can</u>
<u n="931" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="932" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="933" who="S0258">get you know get to the right person <unclear/></u>
<u n="934" who="S0255" trans="overlap">just like that that advert where the guy's sat there with a camel next to him</u>
<u n="935" who="S0257">camel <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="936" who="S0255">on this dating website you er you you like long walks on the beach and in the sand or something on this website you'd be a match</u>
<u n="937" who="S0257">and they're both the same age <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="938" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="939" who="S0255">and they're yeah it's like mm yeah</u>
<u n="940" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="941" who="S0255">it's funny</u>
<u n="942" who="S0257">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="943" who="S0255">but I think with thing like Tinder now which I mean I'm</u>
<u n="944" who="S0258">oh yeah</u>
<u n="945" who="S0255">I'm not on but I think that just shows you who's in the same area doesn't it? and you can start chatting or stuff</u>
<u n="946" who="S0258">I think that's more for</u>
<u n="947" who="S0255">young</u>
<u n="948" who="S0258">hooking up like <unclear/></u>
<u n="949" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="950" who="S0255">yeah that's no and that's what I was gonna <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="951" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="952" who="S0255">I was gonna say that though because</u>
<u n="953" who="S0257" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s daughter went on didn't she</u>
<u n="954" who="S0255">yeah mm</u>
<u n="955" who="S0257">get an alert or something?</u>
<u n="956" who="S0258"><unclear>oh yeah she's mm</unclear></u>
<u n="957" who="S0255">yeah she got an alert that she'd gone on that er just</u>
<u n="958" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="959" who="S0255">I was just think er cos of that my one of my oh what is it? <trunc>some</trunc>somebody vaguely in the family's daughter they sent a a snapshot on Facebook and said look this is er you know only on Tinder or whatever and somebody had gone oh hi how are you? I'm okay how are you? and he said shall we play Pearl Harbour? and she went what's that? I lay back and I'm Japan and you come in and blow me or something <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="960" who="S0257"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="961" who="S0258"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="962" who="S0257">oh my god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="963" who="S0255">and it's just like she went oh my god <unclear/> sent it to the LAD's Bible and <trunc>w</trunc>wait to see if I can get famous</u>
<u n="964" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="965" who="S0257">no</u>
<u n="966" who="S0258">oh my god</u>
<u n="967" who="S0255" trans="overlap">and it's like <unclear/> say so it'll say Tinder</u>
<u n="968" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="969" who="S0255">although the idea is oh well you can see who is er yeah it is</u>
<u n="970" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="971" who="S0255">basically just a</u>
<u n="972" who="S0258"><unclear/> makes me a bit uncomfortable though</u>
<u n="973" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="974" who="S0258">knowing that people can see exactly where you are</u>
<u n="975" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="976" who="S0255">you can switch your location services off they can't</u>
<u n="977" who="S0258">oh oh can you? <unclear/></u>
<u n="978" who="S0255">well not on Tinder</u>
<u n="979" who="S0258">not on Tinder <unclear/></u>
<u n="980" who="S0255">I don't know on Tinder the whole point of Tinder is I think is that</u>
<u n="981" who="S0258">yeah you can yeah</u>
<u n="982" who="S0255">yeah it's who's there but</u>
<u n="983" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="984" who="S0255">no no I mean generally it's like when everything's posted on Facebook now and it says where you are when you post it so</u>
<u n="985" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="986" who="S0258">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="987" who="S0255">but you can switch that off as well can't you?</u>
<u n="988" who="S0258" trans="overlap">you can turn it off yeah</u>
<u n="989" who="S0257" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="990" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="991" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="992" who="S0255">I think it's just a lot of people don't know what you can and can't do and</u>
<u n="993" who="S0258">no</u>
<u n="994" who="S0255">they don't know what's happening when you've got thing like this Facebook Messenger now have you seen that now?</u>
<u n="995" who="S0258">oh yes</u>
<u n="996" who="S0255">if you've got Iphone's</u>
<u n="997" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="998" who="S0255">you have to have the Messenger it's the only way you can see messages and if you've got that it then gets access to everything</u>
<u n="999" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0257" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0255">erm and there's all the and I keep reading different bits and thinking well but you can't get off it if you want to do Messenger</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0257">no</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0255">and the whole thing I liked on Facebook was you had Messenger and you could be if you're on the PC you could be chatting to people or you're chatting on your phone to people</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0255">at the same time as being on Facebook</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0255">but now it has to go into this different app and if this other app's taking all this sort of stuff and you keep going in trying to change the settings and you think well actually it sounds like they're being a bit naughty</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0258" trans="overlap">it's a little bit strange isn't it? yeah</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0257">cos there have been times where you know you might be a <trunc>g</trunc>might be a game or something that looks interesting or er or</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0257">some kind of app within Facebook and you think oh yeah I'll have a look at that</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0257">and then it says to do this you need to allow</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0258">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1016" who="S0257">access all of your information blah and <unclear/></u>
<u n="1017" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah and allow it to post on your behalf</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0255">and I'm like</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0258"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1021" who="S0255">what?</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0257">er no thank you</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0258">yeah they always say that don't they?</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0255">yeah and I go no</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0255">so I no I don't don't go on any of those</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0257">er talking of posting on your behalf have you heard about erm it's I think it's er you can set up your er Twitter account</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0257">and you can sort of preprogramme messages or tweets</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0258">yes</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0257">so that if you die</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0258">huh oh</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0257">it will continue to to post tweets in your name in the style that you write</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0258">oh</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0257">I know</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0258"><unclear/> that's a bit</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0255">is that so people don't know you're dead? or does it say by the way I died this is what I think</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0257" trans="overlap">but you but you can yeah you you can set messages</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0255">wow</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0257">so that it I'm I'm not sure how exactly how it works</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0258" trans="overlap">if I have died then like maybe like I'm gonna say if I have passed away then I'd</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0258">oh I dunno that's uncomfortable isn't it?</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0257">isn't it?</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0258">creepy as well</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0258">really strange</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0257">and I was reading about a lady it was mm not kind of linked I suppose reading about a lady today who is one of seven hundred and fifty people just seven hundred and fifty people</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0257">shortlisted for a one-way trip to Mars</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0258">oh <trunc>oka</trunc></u>
<u n="1057" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1058" who="S0258">one way?</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0257">so it was on the BBC website yeah it would be to colonise Mars</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0257">and erm <vocal desc="misc"/> she's got a one in thirty-five chance so what does that mean? two hundred people? or twenty people they're gonna send? I can't work it out now</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0258">how it's it takes a long time to get there though doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0257">it's about five years</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0258">oh is it <trunc>f</trunc>? oh so I thought it was longer than that</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0257" trans="overlap">yeah yeah so five year</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0258" trans="overlap">oh can you imagine five years?</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0257">so they'll go</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0257">and stay there but not come back</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0255">and then not not be able to come back</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0257">and I'm er because it it was written</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0258">oh</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0257"><trunc>i</trunc>it was written by her but also her husband</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0257">because it said how how does it feel</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0257">er when your wife is is down on a list for a one-way trip to Mars?</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0258">is she leaving him behind?</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0257">and he he said to begin with er they're American and he said to begin with he erm looked on it as her deserting him leaving him</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0257"><trunc>wanti</trunc>wanting to leave him not really</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0257">er you know wanting to be with him at all why else would she do this? and then he said he's come to accept the fact that she wants to do it for humanity</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0258" trans="overlap">humanity yeah</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0257">and blah blah blah and he's so proud of her and he'll always be rather than being her her being Mrs and then his name he will always be</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0257">Mr</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0258">to her yeah</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0257">and her name</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0258">because that's how he wants to be remembered if she should get so the husband of this wonderful woman</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0258" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0257">that's er but yeah one er one in thirty-five that's <unclear>really</unclear></u>
<u n="1098" who="S0258" trans="overlap">is she is she an astronaut then? or is she just an ordinary?</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0257">no no she's er er it's this is it it's erm there were I think there were <trunc>tw</trunc> was it twenty thousand erm requests</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0258">wow</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0257">or twenty thousand applications and it's been shortlisted and shortlisted and shortlisted but it's all just you know Joe Public</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0258">oh that's mad isn't it? like</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0258">I suppose are they gonna be like you know having children out there? are they gonna be expected to populate? or?</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0257">I don't know</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0255">well if they're setting up a colony yeah they're gonna have to be</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0258">it's like a TV show <unclear>I'm sure there's</unclear> lots of TV shows</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0257" trans="overlap">so why wouldn't they be looking for couples? yeah</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0255">well yeah</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0257">you'd think they'd be looking for couples then wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0255">yeah although with a couple you might get one person that really wants to and the other one says they'll go and actually then they'll either drop out part way through</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0255">change their mind halfway there or not be wholeheartedly into it</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0257">yeah yeah it just seemed really bizarre</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0257">I think to to go through a <trunc>pr</trunc> the process of applications</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0257">er who who would ever think that in our lifetime we'd be thinking about <trunc>col</trunc>colonising Mars?</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0258">five years though blooming eck</u>
<u n="1123" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1124" who="S0258">you know I can't even</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0255">I wonder if you'll be able to do Words with Friends out there?</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1128" who="S0255"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1129" who="S0258">just a five-year journey I just can't even fathom</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0255">imagine getting there check-in Facebook Mars</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1132" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1133" who="S0257">set up new place</u>
<u n="1134" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1135" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0258">dunno I can't</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0258">it's just insane isn't it?</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0257">but would how long would it take for it to</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0257">travel back though? to actually</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0257">oh oh that was five years ago <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1144" who="S0255">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0258">that's mad isn't it?</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0258">crazy</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0257">but then again erm <trunc>m</trunc>man first walked walked in the on the moon in nineteen sixty-nine and we've got the space station haven't we?</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0258">mm mm</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0257">so what? forty years after that? when <trunc>d</trunc>when did the space station go up?</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0255">don't know <unclear/> don't look at me like I know</u>
<u n="1154" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1155" who="S0255">I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1156" who="S0258">come on you know</u>
<u n="1157" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1158" who="S0258">your area of expertise</u>
<u n="1159" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1160" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0257">it can't have been more than about forty fifty years after that can it? was it two thousand and nine two thousand and nineteen something like that? forty fifty years I'm gonna hazard a <trunc>gue</trunc></u>
<u n="1162" who="S0255">I don't know</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0257">two thousand and nineteen we're in two thousand and fourteen</u>
<u n="1164" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1165" who="S0255">I can look up I'll find out this is er an interesting fact we need to know</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0257" trans="overlap">but you know you thinking of from now forty forty years' time</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah what's gonna be? yeah</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0257">what advances are there going to be?</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0258">I've been reading well so the guy at work <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying that there's a lot of talk them erm <vocal desc="misc"/> moon landing to all be a myth now and like a conspiracy theory just to do with the cold war and</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0257" trans="overlap">there's always been yeah</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0258">cos no one's done it since have they? like actually walked on the moon</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0257">no no but then er it's you know when it's done once</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0258">I know yeah well true</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0257" trans="overlap">er the first ones get the glory don't they?</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0258">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0257">been there done that I suppose but yeah there was a lot of theories about</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0255" trans="overlap">well it's not the space shuttle is it? it's the satellite we're talking about not it's alright I'm <unclear/> put the wrong thing in</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0257">the space erm</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0255">satellite</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0257"><vocal desc="misc"/> no not satellite is it?</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0255">not shuttle?</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0257">it's erm</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0255">did you say shuttle? no</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0257">no</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0255">station</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0257">station that's the word</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0255">that's the word <trunc>sta</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc><trunc>s</trunc>space station</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0257">space station</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0255">yeah it's that one <unclear>taken</unclear> nineteen ninety-eight</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0258" trans="overlap">that telescope actually is <unclear/></u>
<u n="1191" who="S0257"><vocal desc="gasp"/> so less less than thirty years</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0255" trans="overlap">twentieth of November nineteen nineteen ninety-eight</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0258">so is there people who've been living there like <trunc>perm</trunc> <trunc>per</trunc>? I dunno</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0257" trans="overlap">no they stay there for a while and rotate cos er</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0255" trans="overlap">I think people take them up and they swap</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0258">oh there was a guy actually I remember maybe about a year ago there was this interview was he coming back or something?</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0257">cos they were watching the World Cup live up there weren't they?</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0255">were they?</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0255">was that when they were saying about send pictures in of you watching the World Cup to see who's watching it in the strangest place? I know one of the commentators said that</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0257" trans="overlap">I <trunc>t</trunc> <trunc>ca</trunc> I don't remember but I I remember seeing live</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0258">that's insane isn't it?</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0257">or or recorded</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0257">erm footage</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0257">of er I can't remember was he German? or Russian? or? er and it was his team was playing</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0257">and there were two or three of them <trunc>s</trunc>sitting <vocal desc="laugh"/> or floating there</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0255">ah</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0257">went woo when they score</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0255">yeah cos we actually had the erm we were down at the lake again and we had the fire big we've got a</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0255">it's a washing machine drum on bricks</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0258"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1220" who="S0255">which is er it's a big fire we have</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0257">brilliant</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0255">we had that and then we had a table and we got the <trunc>sat</trunc> the Sky <trunc>d</trunc>dish in the caravan so had that all coming through and onto the TV and we were all sat there all in the dark with this big fire going</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0257">amazing</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0258" trans="overlap">oh that sounds lovely</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0255">and the telly with the World Cup not that I was interested in the World Cup</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1227" who="S0255">but it was just the fact that we were watching in the middle of a field</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0255">round a fire <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1230" who="S0258">sounds lovely</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0257">it does certainly does</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0255">did we ought to talk about the book?</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we keep coming round <unclear/></u>
<u n="1235" who="S0258">do you know? we've done it again haven't we?</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0258">it <trunc>al</trunc>it always happens doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0257">where is it even?</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0258">I have it here</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1241" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0258">so what did you think?</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0257">I really really liked it</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0258" trans="overlap">shall I get my notebook?</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0257">I really liked the main character but I liked her friend what was her friend called? Mrs</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0258">Mrs Smiling</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0255">Mrs Smiling</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0257">that's it and I loved the way she was always referred to as Mrs Smiling there was only one or two occasions where the main character referred to her by name</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0257">and erm the the the oddball family</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0258">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0257">I thought was fab</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0258"><unclear/> I really liked it because if you read any of those kind of Thomas Hardy type you know books where they are kind of all set in the countryside</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0258">but this is like the real countryside and in a way</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0257">all the interbreeding and <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1259" who="S0258">all the interbreeding and stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/> there is a film actually with erm Kate Beckinsale</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0258">but</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0257">and when I hadn't realised cos I've heard of it but I hadn't realised you've got Christmas at Cold Comfort Farm er was it Return to Cold Comfort Farm?</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yes <unclear>the other ones</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah Conference is it? Conference at Cold Comfort Farm</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0257">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1266" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0257">so I might fish out some of them at some point and er and have a read and I've I meant to say earlier actually my <trunc>m</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> my sister was telling me on <trunc>Sun</trunc> er one of my sisters was telling me on Sunday she'd been to <anon type="place"/> library and said <vocal desc="misc"/> have you still got that book? I can't remember what it's what it's called but it's a bit like a looky-likey and the librarian said</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0258"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1269" who="S0257">I've never heard it described as that but I know exactly what you mean</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0257">and er and it's er a book that you can say so if you like erm Stella Gibbons</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0258" trans="overlap">Gibbons yeah</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0257">you can look up Stella Gibbons in the book and it'll say these authors also write in the same style</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0258"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0255">oh oh that's really good</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0257">so if you like</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0258" trans="overlap">that's good yeah</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0257" trans="overlap">yeah if you like her I don't know what it's called though she just described it as a looky-likey</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0255">it's a looky-likey book</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1281" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1282" who="S0257">so if er if you've</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0257">if you just like the the kind of the the way the <trunc>s</trunc>the way the story is is written</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm oh that is good</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0257">then you might like this author this author and this author</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0255">mm but I just rely on Amazon for that</u>
<u n="1289" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1290" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0257">yeah I do</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0255">Amazon recommends</u>
<u n="1293" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1294" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0258">what would you do without Amazon?</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0255">it knows the ones I've had so yeah good old Amazon</u>
<u n="1297" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1298" who="S0258">yeah what would you do without it?</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1301" who="S0258">oh I bought this years ago actually</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0255"><unclear/> because I I read it last year I think I I don't know if I was going to <trunc>Sar</trunc> when I was going to Sardinia or if that was the year before or <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="1303" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0255">but I know at some point I know I was saying about some reading books and you er you just rattled off two or three</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0255">and that was one of the ones that you said to me and I actually read it then</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0255">and when you said last <trunc>ti</trunc> last book club oh has anyone read that? and we were like no no no and it was even when I actually went to try and download it it kept saying you've already bought it</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0255">I'm going no I haven't and I thought it was messing around</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0255">kept saying you've already purchased this when I looked and saw it was over a year ago I realised oh I'd read it</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0255">and I do that so often I read books</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0255">and then I totally forget I've read them</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0258">oh really?</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0255">and I can get em and I start reading it and I start think this is a bit familiar</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0258"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1321" who="S0255">this is this is actually very familiar <trunc>d</trunc>do I do I think I've read this?</u>
<u n="1322" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1323" who="S0257">that's the only thing I've erm I don't like about my Kindle</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0257">cos when you when you're reading a book book</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0257">the first thing you do is you see the title</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0257">and and then you crack it open to where you need to be but with your Kindle you just switch it on it goes straight to that page</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0257">and I'm every time I read something on a Kindle I can't remember what it's called</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0255">mm can't remember what book you're reading</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0257" trans="overlap">I don't know what it's called cos I I only it's only when we're in book club that we say this is the title of it</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0257">and then you download it</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0257">and you don't see the title again normally after that</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0258">do you know I have to admit I really do miss reading proper books erm cos I took erm I let <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have three pound a week pocket money and he can usually get like a kid's book but he got one for four pound this week but we went into WH Smith and you know when you walk past like all the bestsellers?</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0258">that's where I used to always</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0258">look for books but I don't even like you know I just walk straight past it now and I did think</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0258">oh I did look at one and thought oh it looks nice</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0258">I'll look at that on Amazon later but</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0258">I you know that feeling of actually having books</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0255">cos I used to go to charity shops</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0258" trans="overlap">oh yeah I love going to charity shops yeah</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0255" trans="overlap">I used to go and rummage through charity shops or boot fairs or something and just go along</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0257">Tesco's is fab</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0258">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0257"><unclear/> on at the right time because they they're selling books for diabetes</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0258">the offers yeah</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0257">so fifty P for a paperback</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0257"><trunc>p</trunc>pound of a hardback</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0255">well I think that but I know I wouldn't actually want to read a book again because the odd time we've had a book with book club that we've only been able to get in er in an actual book copy I've really <trunc>n</trunc> er not liked having to carry a book with me so when I</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0258">that's the only thing</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0255">when I'm waiting somewhere and I'd flick it on my phone maybe and read four or five pages while I'm in the queue somewhere</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0255">I can't do that if I've actually got a book to you er</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0255">cos you don't get the book out and stand and</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0258">that's the thing yeah</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0255">that sort of stuff so yeah I must admit I that's the only only thing I don't like now and that's why I don't I always read</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0257" trans="overlap">the convenience</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0255">I know cos I've got the app on the <trunc>Kind</trunc> on the Apple Ipad</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0255">so I'll just have that with me all the time and read that erm</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0258">I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gets mad at me cos he's always like oh you should just why don't you use your Kindle? but that app is so good</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0258">cos I read often read on my phone or my Ipad whatever</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0255">yeah yeah I do</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0258">whatever I can really</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0255">well I said my Kindle I've got a Kindle from when I had it originally and I take that on holiday so if I'm on the beach</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah it's perfect isn't it?</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0255">that's or by the pool or something like that</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0255">I've got that</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0258">it's perfect</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0255">because I know then I don't mind if that gets a bit of sand on it or a bit of whatever</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0255">it's not my Ipad</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0258">exactly</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0255">and you can actually get erm the internet on that as well now can't you? on the Kindle</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0258" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0257" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0255"><trunc>w</trunc>well you can could anyway but mine was sort of a test thing of it when they were testing it</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0257">and was it you that said when you got your your Kindle you you actually got it because you were fed up with having a laptop in bed? and you found the <trunc>K</trunc></u>
<u n="1407" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0257">er somebody said to me they'd got a erm one of the Kindle's with internet access because their laptop was too cumbersome in bed</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0257">so they bought the Kindle</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0257">to use for the internet</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0257">not for not for reading books</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0257">just because of its erm of the of the convenience of its size and everything</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0258">I was really resistant to have a Kindle like when they first came out</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah oh I was</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0258" trans="overlap">I thought oh I wouldn't want that</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0255">that's what I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> all the time</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah oh why would I want that?</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0258">but then my sister got one and she kept raving about it so then I sort of looked at hers and thought oh that would be handy</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0258">and then you don't look back then do you?</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0257">I'd never even looked at one in the shop I cos I</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0257">being er a book lover</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0257">I love books</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0255">not anything else but I had when I first got a Blackberry it came with a few books on it er Sherlock Holmes</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0257">and a bit of Shakespeare and something and so I I just started reading them</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0257">and then hadn't even mentioned a Kindle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hadn't mentioned a Kindle and he just bought me one out the blue for Christmas</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0257">and I kind of said to him that's really kind but I don't know if I'll use it really</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0257">and he's never touched it because he loves books so much but I would take them like if if we when we go to Dublin I'll read on the plane</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0257">you you're hardly up there for fifty minutes</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0257">so you just pull it out read a couple of pages and</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0257">and tuck it away but I wouldn't do that with a book because I'd be afraid of damaging it or <unclear/></u>
<u n="1454" who="S0255">what? reading it on a plane?</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0257">well just trying to shove it in a case or</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0255" trans="overlap">or just shove it oh yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0258">oh yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0257">you know having a big enough handbag or something for it and</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0257">and spoiling it</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0258">see I love the choice</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0258">cos I think there's nothing worse than if you say I used to if you're going on holiday I'll buy like five or six books</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0258">I'll be really excited about this is what I'm gonna read on holiday but if you get a rubbish one I'll be like oh don't wanna read that</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0257" trans="overlap">yeah I don't wanna read <unclear/></u>
<u n="1469" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0258">I'll leave that here</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0258">and then I'll be like oh I'll read the next one but obviously when you're carrying like five hundred books around with you</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1474" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0258">you don't really have that problem <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1476" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0255">no that's it</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0257">no</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0255">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got me my Kindle erm <trunc>w</trunc> it was when we started going out to that chalet in France for skiing</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0255">and he'd be out there for so long and I'd be flying backwards and forwards and he got me it for Christmas and he said I know you don't want one he said but <trunc>m</trunc> I just thought even if you just read it literally when you're on the plane</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0255">er up and down and then er just use it like that and I started using it and that was it that's</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0255">so the only books I've read since is one that I read to try and help me with my maths which is er for like about teenage lads to help them with their maths and stuff and I thought oh yeah and it's really good or primary school lads erm but apart from that er it's only been when book club it's</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0255">we can't get it on</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0255">what <trunc>d</trunc> and I'm like what do you mean we can't get it on Kindle? and sometimes I go to buy a book on on there on Amazon and it'll say not available for Kindle click to say yes you want the publisher to say you want it on Kindle and I'm almost like for <trunc>K</trunc> and I won't buy it</u>
<u n="1492" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1493" who="S0255">but er I then just go yes and go on and find another book I won't actually get the hard copy of that to read it</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah I'm the same</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0257">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0255">even if I want to read the book because I think</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0257">out of principle?</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0255">er well no it's it's not that it's just</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0258">convenience?</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0255">I'm so conditioned now that I read on my Ipad</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0255">I read on my Ipad and on my Iphone I don't I don't read books</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0255">and it's not anything against books</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0257">and are you happy paying the prices? Kindle prices</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0255">yeah cos usually they're cheaper than</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0258">a lot cheaper</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0255">the hard back anyway</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0255">or free or yeah but I mean I'll just buy it anyway if I wanted it</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0255">it wouldn't matter to me how much it was</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0257">I do like that there are so many free ones or so cheap even if you pay ninety-nine P</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0255">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0257">for something</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0258">yeah they are really cheap I did see today when I was in WH Smith just erm in the window Kate you liked Kate Mosse didn't you?</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0258">the one who did erm</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0255">yes Labyrinth</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0258">Labyrinth her new one is out</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0255">is it?</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0258">called The Taxidermist's Daughter</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0255">oh right</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0258">and it said oh half price eight pound fifty I thought eight pound fifty?</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0255">eight pound fifty?</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0257" trans="overlap">eight pound fifty?</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1531" who="S0257"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1532" who="S0258">thought well it won't be that on the Kindle</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0257">but my treat is to erm to go to Waterstones</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0258">oh</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0257"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I'll go there</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0257">and we'll spend an hour</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0257">walking around</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0258">yes of course</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<event desc="0257 leaves"/>
<u n="1543" who="S0255">but I must admit I mean for me a brand new book er particularly like a real hardback book</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0255">it's almost like when you open when you used to have jars of coffee</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0255">before machines you used to open that and you'd break the foil and you'd get that smell</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah smell yeah</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0255">and to me that new book when you open it</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0255">and it's like totally new and uncreased and you almost don't want to fold it back</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0255">to keep it open so I do I do miss books but I know I'd never read them again now in the same way because</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0255">er I've as I say I've been conditioned into doing this</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0258" trans="overlap">we've moved on <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1557" who="S0255">yeah well exactly yeah</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0258">that's it we have haven't we?</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0258">but erm I have started cos I've got so many books in there but I was saying to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that if I hadn't bought the Kindle cos I've had the Kindle probably about as long as you maybe like three years four years if not longer</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0258">imagine how many books we would have</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0258">if we didn't have the Kindle</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0258">I was saying I'd probably have about another two hundred books where would I have put them? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1567" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0258">erm but my mother-in-law always used to for my birthday she'd like spend like say fifty pound on new books for me on Amazon</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0258">and like no one can buy you books any more can they?</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0258">that's the only thing like you can't get books as presents</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0255">no er cos I wanted to buy somebody a gift voucher for the Kindle</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0255">as such to buy a book but you can't you can buy an Amazon voucher</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0258">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0255">but that isn't the same as buying a book</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0258">exactly yeah</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0255">or book voucher there's erm an app or a website I saw that you can go in and choose the book and they then send the card through to the person or something through to the person</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0255">and that person then buys the book for the Kindle</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0255">but I thought I don't necessarily want to choose the book for the person and</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah exactly yeah you just want like a Kindle <trunc>vou</trunc></u>
<u n="1585" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0258">er yeah I'm surprised they don't do that</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0255" trans="overlap">I'm sure that they'll I'm sure they will yeah</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0258">I'm sure they will yeah</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0255">we just need to say to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she needs to feed it into the suggestion box</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah we do <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah we do</u>
<u n="1591" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1592" who="S0255">cos you you should er I mean they might even do it for this year it's probably one of these things that they've thought about and they'll do</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0255">so you can actually buy a Kindle gift voucher rather than just an Amazon gift voucher</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah exactly yeah exactly</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0255">yeah which'd be which'd be good</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0258">oh definitely yeah what am I reading? oh I finished that Little Lies that one <unclear/> yeah that was really good</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0255" trans="overlap">oh yeah oh I downloaded that</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0255">but I'm halfway through the Roy Grace one</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0258">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0255">and then <unclear/> cos obviously cos I'd read that before I was sort of <trunc>s</trunc> got that I got that skimmed a bit with that one</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0255">as well so I've been doing that and then yeah I got the Little Lies one I just there's so many things at the minute that I want to read it's erm <trunc>s</trunc> and and there there's people I've found now with people that I like the books of I've read through the whole series</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0255">and then I'm reading the new ones as they're just released</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0255">and I'm waiting like I'm waiting for Karin Slaughter and I'm waiting for so and so and I'm waiting for so and so and it's almost like hurry up and write them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1609" who="S0258" trans="overlap">oh I really did like that Karin Slaughter book</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0258">I should read I should get the other one</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0255">you should yeah do cos that was the first one wasn't it? and you just</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0258"><unclear/> oh I should make a note yeah the first one</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0255" trans="overlap"><unclear/> have to look and then do</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0258">it was <trunc>rea</trunc> I really enjoyed that though</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0255">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0258"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1618" who="S0255">cos I I've read the whole lot cos I know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said she'd read them all but actually</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0255">there's like another set of them afterwards</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0255">and she hadn't read those</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0255">but no I I really like those</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0258">no that it was really really good</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0258">it's like sometimes there's there's so many books you forget about em don't you?</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0255">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0258">let me write it down actually this is like my little notebook</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0255" trans="overlap">book book <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1631" who="S0258">yeah well just everything just goes in here</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0255">mm Karin <trunc>Slau</trunc></u>
<u n="1633" who="S0258">even like marinate <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s chicken phone plumber</u>
<u n="1634" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1635" who="S0258">everything Karin Slaughter</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0255">I've got a whiteboard in the office at home and I</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0258" trans="overlap">oh have you? <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0255">and I just write everything on that</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0258">oh</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0255">particularly at the minute cos my brain isn't working at all with one thing and another and it's just</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0258">mine mine never has really</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0258">to be honest</u>
<u n="1644" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1645" who="S0258">I'm just really forgetful right <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> shall I do your score? cos I think no one's been doing em lately have they? like the proper book club the old you know</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no mm <vocal desc="misc"/> yes er well I'd give it seven out of ten</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0258">yep</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0255">yep</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0258">can I have a comment? the one one <trunc>li</trunc></u>
<u n="1650" who="S0255">er I'll do it when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> comes back</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0258">oh yeah sorry</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0255">cos and she'll</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0255">I haven't said about</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0258">of course yeah</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0255">what I thought about it yet I haven't even thought of a comment yet</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0258">no me neither</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0255">mm have to think of that <pause dur="short"/> I like that thing on the ball the martini shaken not stirred</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0258">oh yeah it's all movie quotes</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0255">is it all just quotes?</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0258" trans="overlap">it is yeah</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0255">I'll be back are you talking to me? show me the money I like those sort of things I've I've got quite a lot erm in outside I've got the outside barbeque</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0258">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0255">with the</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0255">like the hut thing over it</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0255">and I've got em all stuck on the the posts and the walls and things like that</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0258">oh lovely</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0255">and things like you are my sunshine or</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0255">friends are like stars you can't always see them but you know that they're there</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0255">and all those sort of nice ones</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0258">yeah that actually always bring er that's always a good topic of conversation</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0258">that movie quotes one cos there is one on there that we never I don't think I can't remember which one is it? where it says we all go a little mad sometimes what's that one? no one knows <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm sure if I googled it I'd find out</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0255">yeah oh er no I've heard that</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0255">we all go a little mad sometimes shall I google it for you?</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0258">yeah go on then yeah</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0255">that's the standard thing now isn't it? with anything</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0258">oh god</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0255">I just love it cos er it's</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0258"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> even knows what Google is google it <trunc>mu</trunc> ask Google mummy</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> what was it you said the other day when you were at mine something that he'd? something he was saying something or other about and er he sort of said well ask Google</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0258">oh</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0255">you put it on Facebook some er it you er you said something about oh I wonder what so and so or something is happening and he said ask Google mummy</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0258">oh yeah yeah he did yeah</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0255"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0258">I mean I think I yeah</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1695" who="S0258">he he does only cos there's a Youtube advert for Google Glass which is ask Google</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0258">and so cos he loves Youtube ask Google mummy <vocal desc="laugh"/> he is funny</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0255">Psycho</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0258">oh is it?</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0258">oh</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0255">yes</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0258"><unclear/> yeah cos that one cos there's quite a few movie quotes ones</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0258">cos that's like a hard kind of canvassy thing but I like that one cos it had ones that like ones that I they're not all really old-fashioned ones if you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0255">mm yeah</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0258">like it's got the Forrest Gump one and the Terminator one and</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0255">yeah you talking to me?</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0258">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1710" who="S0255">that's Rocky isn't it?</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0255">yeah just fun yeah so he says she goes a little mad sometimes we all go a little mad sometimes haven't you?</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0258">oh yeah that's at the end isn't it? is that?</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yes sometimes just one time can be enough thank you Norman</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0258">is that at the end? when he's like got his mum or he thinks he's his mum?</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0255" trans="overlap">I don't know I don't know</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0258">that's quite a good film actually</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0255">yeah that's the shower isn't it? <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1719" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah it's quite creepy</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0258">yeah cos was he dressing up as his mum? yeah that was it wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0255">I I can't remember er <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="1723" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0255">it's a long time since I saw it</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah it's a long time since I did</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0255">but he was in the motel wasn't he?</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0258">but erm yeah <trunc>t</trunc> Psycho he was dressing up as his mum and talking to or was he talking to himself like split personality that he'd cos she thinks his mum's up there but his mum not up there is that it? I'll have to watch it</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0257">I can't remember</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0258">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/> I</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0257">I know it was weird</u>
<u n="1731" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1732" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0258">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1734" who="S0255">it is weird</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0258">best way to describe it</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0258">I'll have to Youtube Youtube's got everything <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1738" who="S0257">wasn't his his his mum had died and she was still up there dead wasn't she?</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0258">that was it was that it?</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0257">and he was dressing up</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0258">dressing up that was it</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0257">in her clothes</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah clothes</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0257">to almost bring her back to life again</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0255">excellent</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0258">creepy</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0255">anyway back to the book</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0258">mm yes</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0255">so right yeah as as I say I read it <trunc>o</trunc>over a year ago when</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0257">yep</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0255"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> recommended it to me</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0255">erm and it's funny because it was only when you said this <trunc>ti</trunc> I read it and I enjoyed it</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0255">erm things like er the Flora whatever her name at some point through it she started to really annoy me cos I was thinking</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0255">if I was there I'd probably've <trunc>s</trunc>slapped her round the face and told her to get off and you know let me carry on <trunc>wi</trunc> er with my own life and</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0257">yeah no weird interbred line</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0255" trans="overlap">and it just yeah and and like at the end when matey flies in and then she goes off and they live happily ever after I suddenly thought it changed into a totally different book</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0255">because it was suddenly you didn't need the big cheesy grin at the end with them getting married and</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0255">living er happily ever after I loved the things like the names of the cows</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0258">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1769" who="S0255">was it? Feckless</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0258">Pointless</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0255"><trunc>P</trunc>Pointless</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0258">Aimless</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0257">Graceless</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0258">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1775" who="S0255">yeah er yeah so er I I loved all that sort of stuff but it was only when you said er recommending it for this time and said erm oh it's your favourite satire and all this sort of thing</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0255">and when I actually looked and I was trying to buy it and wondering why it wouldn't let me buy it again and I was seeing the things with the reviews and I thought actually cos I didn't read it at all as a satire book</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0258" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0255">and it was only when I looked and saw sort of started looking into it again and saw the character names Mrs Smiling who is the nice <trunc>re</trunc> and I suddenly thought and it was like this big penny dropped</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0255">and I totally missed all I just read it as a book without</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0255">and when I started going through it <trunc>l</trunc> thinking back to it I thought oh yes oh and that's why they were called oh right oh and Big Business the bull and you <trunc>kn</trunc></u>
<u n="1785" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0255">and all this sort of stuff and just and I I say I hadn't read it like that but I did really enjoy it I did did really enjoy it apart from the when she started to annoy me to a certain point and</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0257"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0255">things like when it was all being built up I think when it was gonna be was it for the wedding? some somebody's wedding they were organising in the house</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0255">and they were trying to do it without the old lady knowing</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0255">and it was all gonna be fine and then they got her down and then it was just you sort of thought well that was setting things up so much for a fall that actually</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1795" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0255">real life even <trunc>f</trunc>fantasy life they wouldn't have done that because that was just stupid so</u>
<u n="1797" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1798" who="S0255">things like that annoyed me but erm but yeah I suppose the quote cos I gave it seven out of ten</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0257">okay</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0255">erm and er I just great escapism</u>
<u n="1801" who="S0258">great <trunc>esc</trunc></u>
<u n="1802" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0258">oh I've written loads I'll fill it up as there's only us three</u>
<u n="1804" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1805" who="S0258">so <unclear/> okay shall I go next?</u>
<u n="1806" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0258">erm I give it nine out of ten I will say it's my favourite book cos I always think that it's like me and my sister's kind of sense of humour</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0258">like we find it <trunc>re</trunc> I always still find it really funny like whenever we go on trains we always say like don't forget to feed the parrot and like no one really gets it but</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0258">I just I think oh my sister read it when she was about fourteen and I think I must have read it I would've been <trunc>fif</trunc> about fifteen I think so we're <trunc>re</trunc> yeah it's like a really sort of <unclear/> old book</u>
<u n="1812" who="S0255" trans="overlap">impressionable age</u>
<u n="1813" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0258">yeah we just I find it really funny it's my sense of humour I guess <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1816" who="S0257">I found it very witty I've I I did like <trunc>charac</trunc> I liked all of the characters even the miserable old woman upstairs</u>
<u n="1817" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1818" who="S0257">even the the ones that you want to slap I think I thought there was all it was very quaint and painted the author had painted</u>
<u n="1819" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0257">really lovely pictures of of all the characters and really set the scenes and when they were decorating the farm for the wedding</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0257">you could picture what they were doing with all the flowers and erm just <trunc>r</trunc> created great images</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0257">I I thought but er I can't say it made me laugh out loud necessarily but I did sort of titter</u>
<u n="1825" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1826" who="S0257">at at several little bits and it did encourage me to look to see what other books the author had written on that same on the Cold Comfort theme so erm yes I'll be I'll looking out for them and getting them <trunc>on</trunc>once I work my way through <vocal desc="laugh"/> my backlist of of books to read that's those are on the list as well</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1828" who="S0258">I've got another one I could recommend you if you like this erm by Nancy Mitford called er Move Over Darling which is a bit sort of er nineteen thirties kind of satirey kind of one</u>
<u n="1829" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1830" who="S0258">but they're kind of cos erm the Mitford Sisters were really interesting cos I only realised when I I think I picked that up in a charity shop and I <trunc>re</trunc> I found it really funny and it was just about I haven't read it for ages but like English girl <trunc>ma</trunc>marries this French guy and they have this child and then they're gonna split up but then the child's trying to get em back together</u>
<u n="1831" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1832" who="S0258">but again it's quite witty but she was one of erm think her sister was like a Nazi wasn't she? or something they're all quite famous like I think all there was erm two or three and they're like quite well bred kind of post World War Two family</u>
<u n="1833" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1834" who="S0258">and one of them was an author one of em I think was very high up with Hitler like a British girl who ran off to Germany to join the Nazis and the other one's did various bits and bobs as well I think one of em was in the fascists or something like the British Union of Fascists but they're all really interesting anyway</u>
<u n="1835" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1836" who="S0258">so that's I think it's called Move Over Darling that's quite good is it Move Over Darling? or something it's got darling</u>
<u n="1837" who="S0257">yeah Move Over <trunc>Darl</trunc></u>
<u n="1838" who="S0258">is it called that? what's it got?</u>
<u n="1839" who="S0257"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1840" who="S0258">what's the what's the rating on Amazon? it might have a <trunc>r</trunc> I've told you this and it might have a really bad rating</u>
<u n="1841" who="S0257"><trunc>Christi</trunc>Christine Stovell?</u>
<u n="1842" who="S0258">no</u>
<u n="1843" who="S0257">oh</u>
<u n="1844" who="S0258">let me put in the author's name cos it might not be Move Over Darling it might be something darling</u>
<u n="1845" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1846" who="S0258">I'll know from when I see it</u>
<u n="1847" who="S0257">because Move Over Darling was a film with erm</u>
<u n="1848" who="S0258"><unclear/> that's it no sorry it's called The Blessing <vocal desc="laugh"/> something totally different</u>
<u n="1849" who="S0257">oh</u>
<u n="1850" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1851" who="S0258">The Blessing three ninety-five</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0257">oh I like the sound of Move Over Darling</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0255">I found one called The Darlings</u>
<u n="1854" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1855" who="S0257">Move Over Darling had Diana I was trying to say Dors was it Dors? Diana Dors Diana</u>
<u n="1856" who="S0258" trans="overlap">think it just says The Blessing is a hilarious tale of love and fidelity</u>
<u n="1857" who="S0257" trans="overlap">who was in Calamity Jane?</u>
<u n="1858" who="S0258">oh</u>
<u n="1859" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1860" who="S0255">Calamity Jane? <unclear/> all I can think is John Wayne <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1861" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0257">well that kind of era</u>
<u n="1863" who="S0255">Diana?</u>
<u n="1864" who="S0257">is it Diana?</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0258">anyway I quite that's quite a good book <unclear/></u>
<u n="1866" who="S0257">right what is it IMDb? IMBb? <unclear/> database IMDb er Calamity Jane I'll tell you who it was cos it's gonna bug me now all evening</u>
<u n="1867" who="S0255"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1868" who="S0257">Doris Day</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0255">oh Doris Day</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0257">yeah not <trunc>Di</trunc></u>
<u n="1871" who="S0255" trans="overlap">not Diana no</u>
<u n="1872" who="S0257">yeah Doris Day she was in Move Over Darling</u>
<u n="1873" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1874" who="S0257">er The Blessing?</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0258">yes</u>
<u n="1876" who="S0257">can't find it <pause dur="short"/> found a book of blessings</u>
<u n="1877" who="S0258">if you put in Nancy Mitford then it'll it'll come I <trunc>s</trunc> that's just how I search for it</u>
<u n="1878" who="S0257">erm I need to give a score don't I? I'm gonna give a score of eight out of ten please</u>
<u n="1879" who="S0258">lovely</u>
<u n="1880" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1881" who="S0258"><unclear/> what we should do?</u>
<u n="1882" who="S0257"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1883" who="S0258">we should do the next meeting <unclear/> shouldn't we?</u>
<u n="1884" who="S0255">we should</u>
<u n="1885" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1886" who="S0258"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1887" who="S0255">do you want to know about the next book?</u>
<u n="1888" who="S0258">oh yes yeah sorry let me just er</u>
<u n="1889" who="S0257">how are we choosing the next book?</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0255">well er <vocal desc="sigh"/> it's still off that list isn't it? so</u>
<u n="1891" who="S0258">do you wanna just choose any book <unclear/></u>
<u n="1892" who="S0257" trans="overlap">I don't have I don't have the list</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0258">no</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0255">oh well er but it was said on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said on Facebook did I have the list?</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0258">that's really stupid</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0255">but yeah</u>
<u n="1897" who="S0257">and you were honest?</u>
<u n="1898" who="S0255">I said I did</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0258">why didn't you lie?</u>
<u n="1900" who="S0255">cos she was gonna send me it if I didn't have it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1901" who="S0257">oh flip</u>
<u n="1902" who="S0258">can you not?</u>
<u n="1903" who="S0255">well</u>
<u n="1904" who="S0257"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1905" who="S0258">can you not just choose a book <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? cos I think I'd much rather read a book every book that you've chosen I've really enjoyed actually</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0255">yeah er yeah that's true erm in that case I'll <trunc>h</trunc>I'll hold I think what we need to do is maybe put a motion forward that we don't do the list because I mean for me it's alright having this list and and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wanting to read lots of other books that are like this and like that but then when it's her turn she can choose a book like that and we can read it</u>
<u n="1907" who="S0258">she chose a thriller though the irony of it is is</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0257" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1909" who="S0255" trans="overlap">she chose I Am Pilgrim didn't she?</u>
<u n="1910" who="S0258" trans="overlap">she chose I Am Pilgrim which was the best thriller of the best thrillers of the lot</u>
<u n="1911" who="S0255" trans="overlap">and that was one of the best books we've read yeah</u>
<u n="1912" who="S0257">when is his next book coming out? hasn't it gone to <trunc>pr</trunc>print?</u>
<u n="1913" who="S0255" trans="overlap">well no he's er he's got erm two three and four in his head ready but he's gonna do the screenplay for erm I Am Pilgrim</u>
<u n="1914" who="S0257">I Am Pilgrim</u>
<u n="1915" who="S0258" trans="overlap">oh that'll be a good film though</u>
<u n="1916" who="S0255" trans="overlap">so yeah but cos he is his background is writing screenplays isn't it?</u>
<u n="1917" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1918" who="S0255">action films</u>
<u n="1919" who="S0257">well as long as it's not Tom Cruise playing <unclear/></u>
<u n="1920" who="S0255">well no</u>
<u n="1921" who="S0258">I think it'd be better as a TV series</u>
<u n="1922" who="S0255">depends if Tom Cruise'll erm if he buys</u>
<u n="1923" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1924" who="S0255">the rights to the film then he'll be in it I'm sure</u>
<u n="1925" who="S0258">probably will</u>
<u n="1926" who="S0255">but it'll be I'm hoping he's gonna he'll get the other books going and get the next books coming out</u>
<u n="1927" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1928" who="S0255">but he said he wasn't gonna spend all the time writing the second one until he knew how the first one was received</u>
<u n="1929" who="S0258"><unclear>well that's got</unclear></u>
<u n="1930" who="S0255">and then everybody loved it so</u>
<u n="1931" who="S0257">yeah exactly so he needs to get his finger out and</u>
<u n="1932" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1933" who="S0257">get the next one out</u>
<u n="1934" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1935" who="S0258">I hope it's not too rushed if he does it as a film cos a lot happens doesn't it? they don't wanna miss any things out</u>
<u n="1936" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1937" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1938" who="S0258">it'd be better as a TV like a Homeland kinda</u>
<u n="1939" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah series</u>
<u n="1940" who="S0258">TV series wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="1941" who="S0255">yeah yeah I think so</u>
<u n="1942" who="S0258">yeah oh sorry <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1943" who="S0257">sorry</u>
<u n="1944" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1945" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1946" who="S0258">right shall we do our next date?</u>
<u n="1947" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1948" who="S0255">yes let's do the next date</u>
<u n="1949" who="S0258" trans="overlap">yeah let's do the date so</u>
<u n="1950" who="S0255">and then I think what we need to do is have a bit of a chat with everyone involved and say let's decide what we're doing for the books and stuff</u>
<u n="1951" who="S0257">or</u>
<u n="1952" who="S0258">it's got too complicated now as well because <trunc>c</trunc> you know how <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was asking who chose and everything?</u>
<u n="1953" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1954" who="S0258">I think no one's got a grip on what's actually happening</u>
<u n="1955" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="1956" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="1957" who="S0257">and I don't think that's any any person's fault anybody's fault at all</u>
<u n="1958" who="S0258">no no no not at all</u>
<u n="1959" who="S0257">we've just kind of lost our way a little bit</u>
<u n="1960" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1961" who="S0257">I think as well where we've had people drop out</u>
<u n="1962" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1963" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1964" who="S0255">people have come in so they've</u>
<u n="1965" who="S0257">the rota's got shorter because the number of people is er less</u>
<u n="1966" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah yeah this is it yeah</u>
<u n="1967" who="S0257">what if here's a suggestion what if you just choose a book</u>
<u n="1968" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1969" who="S0257">nominate a book</u>
<u n="1970" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1971" who="S0257">if you have one in mind that that you'd like to and then we say erm whilst we know we've got the list</u>
<u n="1972" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1973" who="S0257">we couldn't actually or or you couldn't find one that you would personally nominate</u>
<u n="1974" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1975" who="S0257">so if nobody has an <trunc>ob</trunc> any objection you'd like to nominate a different book if if anybody <trunc>ob</trunc></u>
<u n="1976" who="S0255" trans="overlap">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s yeah</u>
<u n="1977" who="S0258">yeah go on</u>
<u n="1978" who="S0257">if anybody objects strongly</u>
<u n="1979" who="S0255">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1980" who="S0257">then we can revisit the list</u>
<u n="1981" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="1982" who="S0258">yeah that's a good idea</u>
<u n="1983" who="S0255">yeah because I mean I've found one that I looked er cos I was <trunc>try</trunc> the thing is I started looking at all these different ones</u>
<u n="1984" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1985" who="S0255">and thought no no no no no and then I found one</u>
<u n="1986" who="S0257" trans="overlap">and if nothing really jumps out</u>
<u n="1987" who="S0255">well I found one that I thought I was actually chuckling reading it but it's meant to be one that people either laugh out loud and thinks really funny</u>
<u n="1988" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="1989" who="S0255">or don't get in the slightest so I thought well that could get a good discussion going</u>
<u n="1990" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="1991" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="1992" who="S0255">but erm no I think I'll er I'll have to have a think though cos I haven't got a <trunc>b</trunc> I don't wanna just</u>
<u n="1993" who="S0258" trans="overlap">well of course yeah yeah of course</u>
<u n="1994" who="S0255">choose one else it won't be a very good one</u>
<u n="1995" who="S0257">I mean lists as well it depends how they're compiled</u>
<u n="1996" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="1997" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="1998" who="S0257">doesn't it? if they're if they're <trunc>c</trunc> if it's compiled by sales then it just means a lot of people have bought it not necessarily a lot of people have really really liked it</u>
<u n="1999" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2000" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2001" who="S0255">but this list it's a hundred books to read before you die and it's been compiled by somebody so it's all the greats and the this and the that</u>
<u n="2002" who="S0257">but who who says it's great</u>
<u n="2003" who="S0255">well exactly yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2004" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="2005" who="S0257">this is an argument that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I have very often and er well you know</u>
<u n="2006" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="2007" who="S0257">you watch these top ten of this and top ten of that</u>
<u n="2008" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2009" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2010" who="S0257">and we'll be screaming at the TV saying well who chose not in my top ten <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2011" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2012" who="S0255">no exactly what about this? what about that?</u>
<u n="2013" who="S0257">who put that one in there? yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2014" who="S0255">mm yeah okay that's fine so let's do a date one two three four</u>
<u n="2015" who="S0258"><unclear/> the ninth</u>
<u n="2016" who="S0257">so you need to be after the</u>
<u n="2017" who="S0255" trans="overlap">well my operation's the thirteenth</u>
<u n="2018" who="S0257" trans="overlap">did you say the thirteenth?</u>
<u n="2019" who="S0258">okay</u>
<u n="2020" who="S0255">so it's whether to say to do it the I wouldn't be er that week I'm in hospital anyway but whether do it the week after that</u>
<u n="2021" who="S0257">I can't do Thursday the twenty-third</u>
<u n="2022" who="S0255">right</u>
<u n="2023" who="S0257">I could do Thursday the thirtieth</u>
<u n="2024" who="S0255">well <pause dur="short"/> can I do the ninth? let me just think no it's the second the ninth I'm just well I'm just thinking <trunc>w</trunc>we don't wanna leave it too long do we really?</u>
<u n="2025" who="S0257">I can't do the ninth</u>
<u n="2026" who="S0255">cos otherwise it's gonna drift again oh you can't do the ninth?</u>
<u n="2027" who="S0257">no</u>
<u n="2028" who="S0255">actually you're gonna get really busy with your parties now aren't you?</u>
<u n="2029" who="S0257">yeah that's what I'm I'm doing one in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="2030" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="2031" who="S0258">what if we do it on a Wednesday instead of a Thursday?</u>
<u n="2032" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2033" who="S0257">huh Great British Bake Off although I record it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2034" who="S0255">mm yeah mm mm mm</u>
<u n="2035" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2036" who="S0257">I'll sacrifice it for book club</u>
<u n="2037" who="S0258">it might be over by then</u>
<u n="2038" who="S0255">or a or a Tuesday or something we could always</u>
<u n="2039" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2040" who="S0255">that's something I think we maybe need to talk about as a group is erm Thursday's used to be cos</u>
<u n="2041" who="S0258"><unclear/> day</u>
<u n="2042" who="S0255"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to go out and do a pub quiz</u>
<u n="2043" who="S0257">and and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s chap</u>
<u n="2044" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah did snooker</u>
<u n="2045" who="S0257">was out bowling or something wasn't he?</u>
<u n="2046" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2047" who="S0257">erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has band rehearsal and they've just moved it from a Wednesday to a Tuesday I think</u>
<u n="2048" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="2049" who="S0258">I can't really do a Tuesday</u>
<u n="2050" who="S0255">okay</u>
<u n="2051" who="S0258">only cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has this exercise class that he does every week</u>
<u n="2052" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="2053" who="S0257">oh right</u>
<u n="2054" who="S0258">on a Tuesday you see but erm I could come up I just erm can come afterwards it just you know what it's like I'll just wait for him to come back then I'll go so I'd just be a bit late</u>
<u n="2055" who="S0255" trans="overlap">oh no no no <trunc>i</trunc>it wants to be on a night that we so I mean Thursday's are okay it's just when we can do it two three four <pause dur="short"/> so as I say it's either well the ninth or then er the twenty-third then it's gonna be the thirtieth</u>
<u n="2056" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="2057" who="S0255">but that's <trunc>qu</trunc>quite a while isn't it?</u>
<u n="2058" who="S0258">when when are you back <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? are you in hospital for a week?</u>
<u n="2059" who="S0255">I have the operation on the thirteenth</u>
<u n="2060" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2061" who="S0255">and and I <trunc>sh</trunc> I'll be in for about three days</u>
<u n="2062" who="S0258">yep</u>
<u n="2063" who="S0255">erm</u>
<u n="2064" who="S0257">mm be seven weeks</u>
<u n="2065" who="S0255">yeah I think it's about seven weeks or so before I can drive</u>
<u n="2066" who="S0258"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh</u>
<u n="2067" who="S0255">but I can always be picked up and taken somewhere</u>
<u n="2068" who="S0258">yeah of course</u>
<u n="2069" who="S0255">but obviously it's</u>
<u n="2070" who="S0257" trans="overlap">well I'm sailing right past your house if it's anywhere</u>
<u n="2071" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2072" who="S0257">er</u>
<u n="2073" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2074" who="S0257">you know this direction</u>
<u n="2075" who="S0255">yeah it it's just obviously the <trunc>f</trunc> I mean well the first week I'll be in hospital but it's like the the week after that it's whether I'd be er you know</u>
<u n="2076" who="S0258">we don't want yeah that's what I mean</u>
<u n="2077" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="2078" who="S0258">I don't want you to be under pressure</u>
<u n="2079" who="S0255">so <trunc>m</trunc>so maybe like the thirtieth <pause dur="short"/> is the thirtieth of October any good?</u>
<u n="2080" who="S0258">yeah I can do the thirtieth</u>
<u n="2081" who="S0257" trans="overlap">thirtieth's good for me</u>
<u n="2082" who="S0255">yeah?</u>
<u n="2083" who="S0258">well let's say the thirtieth</u>
<u n="2084" who="S0255">okay which I'm gonna write that down instead of erm</u>
<u n="2085" who="S0258">it's sort of it's got really strange with the choices do you <trunc>wan</trunc>do you <trunc>wan</trunc>?</u>
<u n="2086" who="S0255">yeah thanks</u>
<u n="2087" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="2088" who="S0258">with all the book choices now though hasn't it? because it's like you're choosing tonight but then on your night is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> choosing? I'm guessing or it's like you know what I mean? it's don't worry it's all got a bit topsy-turvy hasn't it?</u>
<u n="2089" who="S0257"><unclear/></u>
<u n="2090" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah I think I think it has and the thing is cos we</u>
<u n="2091" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2092" who="S0255">cos we've often hosted for other people anyway</u>
<u n="2093" who="S0258">that's it as well yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2094" who="S0255" trans="overlap">which has got it out of <trunc>syn</trunc> but that doesn't matter cos we've er so you don't always choose on the night that you're hosting</u>
<u n="2095" who="S0258">yeah exactly yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2096" who="S0255">but actually it's yeah it's got a bit out of sync but I can't remember what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said so I think it's I'm choosing that I think oh wasn't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> meant to be choosing next time?</u>
<u n="2097" who="S0258">maybe that's why cos I've definitely done three so I know I've I'm cos people have only had two</u>
<u n="2098" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah oh no I've done <trunc>t</trunc>I've done two yeah</u>
<u n="2099" who="S0258">yeah so</u>
<u n="2100" who="S0257" trans="overlap">yeah I've done two I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> excuse me I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said she's done three</u>
<u n="2101" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="2102" who="S0258"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? has she done three?</u>
<u n="2103" who="S0257"><vocal desc="cough"/> excuse me I can't remember if that's what she said</u>
<u n="2104" who="S0258" trans="overlap"><unclear>guided chair</unclear> Pilgrim</u>
<u n="2105" who="S0255">I don't know</u>
<u n="2106" who="S0258">no me neither</u>
<u n="2107" who="S0255">I'm gonna stop this</u>
<u n="2108" who="S0258">well we said book club at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house book to be</u>
<u n="2109" who="S0255">yeah to be confirmed</u>
<u n="2110" who="S0258">to be confirmed</u>
<u n="2111" who="S0257"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s chosen three <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says I've chosen twice hosted twice can't remember when I last chose but it was I Am Pilgrim</u>
<u n="2112" who="S0258">I think it's cos</u>
<u n="2113" who="S0257">and she and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s said it was a year ago cos it was a book club that she was in New New York</u>
<u n="2114" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah she was in New York wasn't she?</u>
<u n="2115" who="S0258">we had that rota didn't we?</u>
<u n="2116" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2117" who="S0258">and I think probably cos I've I bet it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> then it was me who've chosen three</u>
<u n="2118" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2119" who="S0258">and then I bet the next one was the one where it all</u>
<u n="2120" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="2121" who="S0258">you know like got changed and everything</u>
<u n="2122" who="S0257">cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on Tuesday even said how about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> chooses next and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the one after then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="2123" who="S0255">mm <pause dur="short"/> but then it's sort of like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hasn't come tonight</u>
<u n="2124" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2125" who="S0255">and you just sort of think I think</u>
<u n="2126" who="S0257">and she hasn't responded to that either</u>
<u n="2127" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no I think er er to me it's almost like <trunc>y</trunc> we need people that are coming er that can come and if people want to come and go</u>
<u n="2128" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2129" who="S0255">then they just go along with the books that we're doing</u>
<u n="2130" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2131" who="S0255">cos it'd be a shame it er it's been so good it'd be a shame if it did drift out I mean er</u>
<u n="2132" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2133" who="S0255">it's been over two years we've been doing it</u>
<u n="2134" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2135" who="S0257">yeah er I think</u>
<u n="2136" who="S0255">and it's you know I've made some really good friends with</u>
<u n="2137" who="S0258">exactly</u>
<u n="2138" who="S0255">with coming doing this but</u>
<u n="2139" who="S0258"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh I really don't want it to fizzle out</u>
<u n="2140" who="S0255">no</u>
<u n="2141" who="S0258">but I I do think that this new way of choosing books is to blame a little bit but I wasn't there for that one so I</u>
<u n="2142" who="S0255" trans="overlap">no I wasn't</u>
<u n="2143" who="S0258">I would've strongly opposed it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2144" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2145" who="S0258">cos I like choosing books that erm other <trunc>pe</trunc> you know cos I <unclear/> like</u>
<u n="2146" who="S0255" trans="overlap">yeah cos it's a book you've enjoyed and it <trunc>y</trunc>you</u>
<u n="2147" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2148" who="S0255">not that you think everybody else is going to necessarily enjoy it cos some people won't</u>
<u n="2149" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2150" who="S0255">but it it's a book that you know you think is a good book</u>
<u n="2151" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2152" who="S0255">rather than just picking a book out of the air you can look at reviews and you can look at this that and the other but</u>
<u n="2153" who="S0258">but even if we were <trunc>t</trunc> wanted to do something different you know like Richard and Judy do their like book club list?</u>
<u n="2154" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2155" who="S0258">even we could go through that</u>
<u n="2156" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2157" who="S0258">cos they're all a lot of those like The House at Riverton like those books like</u>
<u n="2158" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="2159" who="S0258">they're all on there aren't they?</u>
<u n="2160" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="2161" who="S0258">like all those kind of bestseller type books</u>
<u n="2162" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2163" who="S0258">if we wanted to do something that wasn't all classics</u>
<u n="2164" who="S0255">yeah and plus er yeah there must be some sort of book club recommends this</u>
<u n="2165" who="S0258">yeah book club recommendation</u>
<u n="2166" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2167" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="2168" who="S0258">cos a lot sometimes a lot of the Kindle books have the book book club notes at the back don't they? <unclear/> notes for book clubs</u>
<u n="2169" who="S0255">yeah that's right yeah and questions for book club is that is that something?</u>
<u n="2170" who="S0257"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="2171" who="S0258">I think they must be</u>
<u n="2172" who="S0257">discussion points</u>
<u n="2173" who="S0258">yeah discussion points and things</u>
<u n="2174" who="S0255">cos we used to all talk about it and then we used to er used to ask a question didn't we? like the person whose book it was'd ask a question</u>
<u n="2175" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2176" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="2177" who="S0255">about the book and everybody had</u>
<u n="2178" who="S0258">oh yeah yeah we used to do it properly yeah</u>
<u n="2179" who="S0255">yeah and we used to do a lot more structured like that and then I think it then got cos <trunc>w</trunc> obviously getting more and more friendly and chatting more and things going on</u>
<u n="2180" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2181" who="S0255">and <trunc>cha</trunc></u>
<u n="2182" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2183" who="S0255">which is great and it but it's almost like we think well we need to maybe have social times as well as</u>
<u n="2184" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2185" who="S0255">which we you know we have done we've done Christmas and we've had the anniversary and</u>
<u n="2186" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="2187" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2188" who="S0255">and that sort of stuff and</u>
<u n="2189" who="S0257">cheese and wine</u>
<u n="2190" who="S0255">cheese and wine</u>
<u n="2191" who="S0258">oh yeah</u>
<u n="2192" who="S0255">lots of cheese</u>
<u n="2193" who="S0257">mm</u>
<u n="2194" who="S0255">more cheese more cheese</u>
<u n="2195" who="S0258">mm</u>
<u n="2196" who="S0257">a beehive</u>
<u n="2197" who="S0255">beehive</u>
<u n="2198" who="S0258">that was good</u>
<u n="2199" who="S0255">yeah yeah so maybe</u>
<u n="2200" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2201" who="S0255">we need to be doing stuff like that and have the social side and then try and keep the book <trunc>cl</trunc> not not talking and chatting and stuff but</u>
<u n="2202" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2203" who="S0255">make sure we have a structured book club bit for it</u>
<u n="2204" who="S0257">yeah a <trunc>foc</trunc>a focused night</u>
<u n="2205" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="2206" who="S0258">cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s usually quite good at doing that but I think she's cos I don't know if it's cos she's busy but she seems to have like</u>
<u n="2207" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2208" who="S0258">stepped back a little bit from it</u>
<u n="2209" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="2210" who="S0258">now doesn't she?</u>
<u n="2211" who="S0257">yeah</u>
<u n="2212" who="S0255">yeah</u>
<u n="2213" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2214" who="S0255">yeah mm okay</u>
<u n="2215" who="S0258">yeah</u>
<u n="2216" who="S0255">mm</u>
<u n="2217" who="S0258"><trunc>brilli</trunc></u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
