<text id="SNJP">
	<header>
		<rec_length>2:32:07</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-26</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0190 S0192 S0227</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In an Indian restaurant in Rushden</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Weddings, extended family, invitations, seating arrangements, idyllic marriage, food, Italian food, spice, university, PhDs, working abroad, life experience, having children, recordings, pidgins &amp; creoles, grammar, linguistics, language, vocabulary, orthography, flat adverbs, French, shellfish, South Korean food, visiting Devon, grandparents, liver, disgusting foods, Hannibal TV show, birthdays, place names, compounds, Spanish &amp; language learning, travel,  countries visited, desserts, sickness, near-death experiences, saltwater crocodiles, landslides, death, health, anxiety, satellite navigation, annoying neighbors, parties, garden fires, ghosting, being full, recordings, restaurants, eating out, cooking VS washing up, frugality, waking up, shoes,</topics>
		<activity>A meal for my father's 55th birthday</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, announcing, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0190">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>St Neots. Cambs.</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>55</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Activity co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0192">
				<exactage>28</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bedford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>22</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>English Language Instructor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2>Spanish</l2>
				<fls>Korean -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0227">
				<exactage>54</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Crayford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>9</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>customer services agent</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- intermediate; Spanish -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0227">your group but I would have also your great uncle has offered his his band for free here <pause dur="short"/> I would have had them as well because the music that they played was completely targeted at the young <pause dur="short"/> and not for the other generations that were there so it was</u>
<u n="2" who="S0190" trans="overlap">it was club music</u>
<u n="3" who="S0227">it was it was a club <trunc>mu</trunc></u>
<u n="4" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="5" who="S0227">no it wasn't no erm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0192">so they had this lovely traditional wedding and then club music?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0227">it was a bit yeah erm but the the <trunc>s</trunc> the Georgian house the the meal you get <unclear>tentativeness</unclear> of the the service</u>
<u n="8" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0227">and you erm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0190">the gardens were fantastic</u>
<u n="11" who="S0192" trans="overlap">well that's the thing I think</u>
<u n="12" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes it was constant we were getting <trunc>fi</trunc> erm you had before the meal we got all <trunc>co</trunc> the the canapés oh there was there was sausages were there and every time your champagne glass was emptied it was recharged you know can I give you another drink? and and you you you get a erm you get a snapshot of how</u>
<u n="13" who="S0192" trans="overlap">well it's gonna be quite different if you come to mine then</u>
<u n="14" who="S0227" trans="overlap">the gentry live but it's you you cut it to your own cloth that how the gentry lived in the er in the nineteenth century and erm it was lovely though and it was a nice beautiful day the weather was lovely on that day</u>
<u n="15" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0227">and so everything was was perfect erm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0190">they were really really lucky</u>
<u n="18" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="19" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="20" who="S0190">it was the the Saturday before or the Saturday after? terrible</u>
<u n="21" who="S0192">I mean I guess for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I we would love something like that but that's never gonna happen we can't ever afford it no</u>
<u n="22" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's too if you no you</u>
<u n="23" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh sorry that's where I put I booked the same table</u>
<u n="24" who="S0227" trans="overlap">cut the <trunc>cu</trunc> you cut it to your cloth</u>
<u n="25" who="S0192">so I wouldn't yeah but I wouldn't want</u>
<u n="26" who="S0227" trans="overlap">we'll put</u>
<u n="27" who="S0192" trans="overlap">something in between</u>
<u n="28" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="29" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I'd rather either have one extreme or the other</u>
<u n="30" who="S0227">yeah but</u>
<u n="31" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I wouldn't rather be somewhere in the middle where I'm a bit like oh this isn't very tasteful or it's you know a bit cheapy</u>
<u n="32" who="S0227" trans="overlap">you you you can probably it's like it but you're so it's a very it it's a very expensive day it's you know</u>
<u n="33" who="S0190">it can be a very expensive day</u>
<u n="34" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah no that's what I mean it can be you don't it doesn't have to be you know</u>
<u n="35" who="S0192">well it's the cost of a the wedding <trunc>cere</trunc> well it's not <trunc>n</trunc> the wedding is the signing of a paper forty pounds</u>
<u n="36" who="S0227">yeah I mean you need a</u>
<u n="37" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s face</u>
<u n="38" who="S0227">you need</u>
<u n="39" who="S0190">no I just I'm just surprised that was</u>
<u n="40" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0190">I've never because I've always been involved in a wedding where it's been er a a ceremony and everything else but I just think mm forty pounds for just a piece of paper</u>
<u n="42" who="S0192">yeah and that's all we have to do for and that would have to be on a weekday</u>
<u n="43" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="44" who="S0192">it becomes two hundred pounds if it's the weekend</u>
<u n="45" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0190">does it really?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0192">yeah mm just to sign the piece of paper two hundred pounds just to sign a piece of paper</u>
<u n="48" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="49" who="S0190">do you not go through a ceremony or anything? it's literally just</u>
<u n="50" who="S0192">erm we have to say some vows</u>
<u n="51" who="S0190" trans="overlap">are you talking about a registry office?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh yeah there's vows</u>
<u n="53" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh right you still go and do the registry office wedding</u>
<u n="55" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah it it's not just yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0192" trans="overlap">if if if we we wouldn't get married we would <trunc>s</trunc> well that is getting married isn't it we <trunc>wou</trunc> sorry we would get married but we wouldn't have a wedding and then potentially a few years down the line <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I might have a wedding</u>
<u n="57" who="S0190" trans="overlap">a celebrate thing</u>
<u n="58" who="S0192">yeah and and do something yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0227" trans="overlap">you you can <trunc>re</trunc> <trunc>re</trunc> yes you could reenergise and that and blah blah blah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0192">but at the moment it's pragmatic there's not</u>
<u n="61" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="62" who="S0192">it's because we will need to for</u>
<u n="63" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah but you shouldn't <pause dur="short"/> you shouldn't do it because you feel obliged to do it you do it because you want to that's what you decide in the end you <trunc>ch</trunc> or even if you <trunc>ta</trunc> you have your like you say you just your ceremony and then later on you have your wedding blessed or something if you that's entirely up to you but you do it because you want to not because you think oh gosh the family like it to do this I mean I'm sure that that</u>
<u n="64" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="65" who="S0192" trans="overlap">knowing me what would you</u>
<u n="66" who="S0190" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s parents</u>
<u n="67" who="S0192">what would you say I should do?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0190">don't get married</u>
<u n="69" who="S0192">just don't get married?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0227">no but if he needs it for a job</u>
<u n="71" who="S0190" trans="overlap">if you have to for a job yeah definitely</u>
<u n="72" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0190">but I think the way you speak I don't think you particularly want to get married you don't feel that you need to your bond that you have together is strong enough a piece of paper is gonna make no difference to you either way</u>
<u n="74" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0190">so what's the point?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0227">so if it's if it's for a job then you</u>
<u n="77" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's just like you're getting another degree certificate or something <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0227">you you you you take you take the the bare minimum and that's it you can have a celebration you could <pause dur="short"/> erm keep it to a a a bare <trunc>mini</trunc> <trunc>minim</trunc> a a bare minimum erm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0192">you need</u>
<u n="80" who="S0227" trans="overlap">you have a slight dilemma because of how things have happened</u>
<u n="81" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I don't know who to invite is a problem</u>
<u n="82" who="S0227" trans="overlap">that's your dilemma</u>
<u n="83" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah it's a it's a really big dilemma because</u>
<u n="84" who="S0190">you can invite everybody</u>
<u n="85" who="S0227">well</u>
<u n="86" who="S0190">just exactly the same as as erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did there was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and and his wife there was er</u>
<u n="87" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's not</u>
<u n="88" who="S0190" trans="overlap">the two of us we had a photograph taken with them and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we had it taken I had one taken with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and what's her <trunc>f</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? so we all just did it for the day</u>
<u n="89" who="S0192">for a wedding I'd agree</u>
<u n="90" who="S0190" trans="overlap">that's it</u>
<u n="91" who="S0192">but if we're just signing a piece of paper it's a long way for people to come yeah so</u>
<u n="92" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh well for oh yes just for a piece of paper well it depends on whether you want to all go out for a meal</u>
<u n="93" who="S0192" trans="overlap">because we have to have witnesses don't we to do it?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0227" trans="overlap">if if</u>
<u n="95" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="96" who="S0227">if I mean if you want to <trunc>ce</trunc>celebrate it your your your your dilemma would be that <pause dur="short"/> who to invite and who not to invite <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0192">I've even told <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that I'm not sure I'd invite him now I know that sounds strange but if I invite <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> must invite her brothers</u>
<u n="98" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="99" who="S0192" trans="overlap">she has three brothers</u>
<u n="100" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="101" who="S0192">who all have wives who all have children</u>
<u n="102" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="103" who="S0192">they're not just gonna come all the brothers on their own that suddenly</u>
<u n="104" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="105" who="S0192">if I invite <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it opens it up to</u>
<u n="106" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well they're not gonna come in the week are they though are they really if it's in the week?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes the the the price escalates</u>
<u n="108" who="S0192">we were very tempted to just have a very very small selection of people let's say</u>
<u n="109" who="S0227" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0192">maybe her parents and then you guys and</u>
<u n="111" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="112" who="S0192">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0227">it's well don't if you if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> comes you must invite <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0192">yeah I know</u>
<u n="115" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I can't believe I'm saying that but</u>
<u n="116" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="117" who="S0227" trans="overlap">the but the my Libra scales must balance and there has to be balance</u>
<u n="118" who="S0192">how would you feel if I didn't invite you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0227">I would feel</u>
<u n="120" who="S0190" trans="overlap">if I didn't invite me? erm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0192">if I just said it was just mum and dad that was it?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0190">fine if that's what you want</u>
<u n="123" who="S0192">it's not necessarily what I want it's just</u>
<u n="124" who="S0227">there's there is a cost to this</u>
<u n="125" who="S0192">it's just easier isn't it?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0227">I I tell you a problem that I see here</u>
<u n="127" who="S0190" trans="overlap">you're I think you will you have more I mean I I go along I've always gone along with what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have always wanted erm it's it was quite difficult to have to be with her in the thing but life goes on and what have you</u>
<u n="128" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0190">erm <pause dur="short"/> the hardest part I think is is for you and to think that you what don't have your day spoilt by trying to juggle <pause dur="short"/> I won't have a problem I will do whatever you like I think you'll have more of a problem with your mother it will</u>
<u n="130" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I agree</u>
<u n="131" who="S0192">yeah no definitely</u>
<u n="132" who="S0190" trans="overlap">it will er upset <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I I don't myself and like I said with my scale of balances I I will never like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I can't like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> comes he must come</u>
<u n="134" who="S0192">yeah oh yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0227">are you with me? that I couldn't I could not sell I could try selling to you that you should invite <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I think</u>
<u n="136" who="S0192" trans="overlap">which is why for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I for simplicity's sake</u>
<u n="137" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="138" who="S0192">we were considering just her parents er my parents that's it no siblings</u>
<u n="139" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="140" who="S0192">no anyone else</u>
<u n="141" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="142" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well that's if you wanted it the other option is just to choose two sets of close friends and just do it completely on your own</u>
<u n="143" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah we could just do it with friends couldn't we?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0190" trans="overlap">and then just have a family get together on one side</u>
<u n="145" who="S0227" trans="overlap">the thing is that's I understand it's all of the postcards <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0190">and a family get together and you can either decide to make it with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s family and</u>
<u n="147" who="S0192">we could do that couldn't we?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0190" trans="overlap">with them and that way</u>
<u n="149" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we could travel around couldn't we?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0190" trans="overlap">nobody <trunc>nobod</trunc> that's right I mean you</u>
<u n="151" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I could I could go to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s family and we celebrate I could then come and stay with you guys with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and we celebrate and then I could stay with mum</u>
<u n="152" who="S0190" trans="overlap">and I think</u>
<u n="153" who="S0227">yeah right</u>
<u n="154" who="S0190" trans="overlap">that's right</u>
<u n="155" who="S0192">yeah we hadn't considered that</u>
<u n="156" who="S0227">no it's an option</u>
<u n="157" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that might be a good idea</u>
<u n="158" who="S0190">that way you don't have to have anybody and it you won't be sitting there all day worrying that people are gonna feel like</u>
<u n="159" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's not that I don't want</u>
<u n="160" who="S0227">no no</u>
<u n="161" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no no I know but but it</u>
<u n="162" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it starts escalating doesn't it? it starts building</u>
<u n="163" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well it it it</u>
<u n="164" who="S0227">it it becomes a <trunc>mon</trunc> it becomes well I can see <pause dur="short"/> this will this is a dilemma I see is that <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> mum is invited I'm invited whatever and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or not are you with me? but she's going to be thinking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> should be on this</u>
<u n="165" who="S0192">oh yeah definitely</u>
<u n="166" who="S0227">and this</u>
<u n="167" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0227" trans="overlap">this erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will definitely that's it that</u>
<u n="169" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and then I can't have four people and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s only got two so</u>
<u n="170" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> should be there by rights of passage he's your brother there's there's</u>
<u n="171" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but he was there when I proposed</u>
<u n="172" who="S0227">yes he has to be there when</u>
<u n="173" who="S0192" trans="overlap">isn't that enough?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0190" trans="overlap">but he's already had that one</u>
<u n="175" who="S0192">you know</u>
<u n="176" who="S0227" trans="overlap">he has to be there you may have to if you go down the line of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you may have to bite the bullet on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s side of her you may have to bite the bullet</u>
<u n="177" who="S0192">that's another like fifteen people</u>
<u n="178" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well yes <pause dur="short"/> but you may have to bite the bullet</u>
<u n="179" who="S0192">but it's a lot of it's it's a lot to ask of people to come all the way down there just to see us sign the paper</u>
<u n="180" who="S0227" trans="overlap">unless unless er unless</u>
<u n="181" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah but that's <trunc>wh</trunc> that's why I'm saying that it sounds to me you better if they came two special friends from either side or mutual friends whatever and just have that and then go out for a meal afterwards and just just enjoy a nice time</u>
<u n="182" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I'm leaning towards that idea yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0190">and then like I say you that way nobody's offended nobody's left out and nobody's more popular than anybody else</u>
<u n="184" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah and then everyone</u>
<u n="185" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's still</u>
<u n="186" who="S0192" trans="overlap">doesn't have to travel down to <anon type="place"/> either</u>
<u n="187" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I it's still</u>
<u n="188" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we can travel to those</u>
<u n="189" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0227">it's <pause dur="short"/> I think if as I said it's difficult your brother is your brother <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> shares your blood but he's not your brother</u>
<u n="191" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="192" who="S0227">but this is a big problem for mum <pause dur="short"/> I've already just actually discussed this with your brother <pause dur="short"/> and I've said that that if he is invited this must come from you not from her she cannot impose him on you if you say he's coming then that's fine but for her to say he's coming is not her decision to do that are you with me? I mean I think that's your dilemma</u>
<u n="193" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I just think cos don't want any child there so</u>
<u n="194" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="195" who="S0192">if it were to happen</u>
<u n="196" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="197" who="S0192">I mean when when one child is there all the attention is on the child always er</u>
<u n="198" who="S0227">it's a dilemma because <pause dur="short"/> erm the parents putting up makes <pause dur="short"/> problems further down the road with these this I mean it's like</u>
<u n="199" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean it does doesn't it?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0227">it's like erm <pause dur="short"/> if you have a child</u>
<u n="201" who="S0190" trans="overlap">it does but there's a way round it</u>
<u n="202" who="S0227" trans="overlap">if you have a child or your brother has a child <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> your mother has two choices we either see that child together or she sees him later than me because I will not have <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> seeing</u>
<u n="203" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="204" who="S0227" trans="overlap">my grandchild before I do are you with me? because that to me is wrong erm if <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0192" trans="overlap">don't worry I'm not gonna have a child <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0227"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and</u>
<u n="207" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I'm not gonna have one</u>
<u n="208" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have a child I will step back and let <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> go in right? because it's their grandchild I will take up the role as grandfather but there's a there's a <unclear/> erm there was <pause dur="short"/> there was a a moment where I wasn't sure if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was going to preside over a a role in the wedding and I went to the rehearsal just in case he didn't but the right was his not mine because I I've been offered and if he couldn't do it I would take his place but I wasn't gonna say no I</u>
<u n="209" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no of course</u>
<u n="210" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I'm here and took <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> into this cos</u>
<u n="211" who="S0192">you're ancillary characters</u>
<u n="212" who="S0227" trans="overlap">fortunately <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had changed <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did a <trunc>con</trunc> a <trunc>con</trunc> conversation in France four years earlier and said he wants me and not his dad on the top table well he was saying you can't do that because</u>
<u n="213" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and you agreed</u>
<u n="214" who="S0227" trans="overlap">he's your father we agreed that that was wrong and</u>
<u n="215" who="S0192" trans="overlap">was it awkward for you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at the wedding?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0190">no because in the end and it it helped that the actual caterer adjusted it because of the layout of the room and how many they were allowed to have and how they set the tables out they're supposed to have a the top table and then eight tables of ten ten tables eight tables of ten they changed it and extended the top table so in the long run we all sat on the top table so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sat one end and <trunc>m</trunc> and your dad and I sat the other end so nobody was more than anybody else</u>
<u n="217" who="S0227">it also helps that er me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> get on fine we I knew him a long time ago are you with me? and so there's no animosity or anything</u>
<u n="218" who="S0192">does he have any relation to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? cos it all seems to revolve around</u>
<u n="219" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="220" who="S0192" trans="overlap">this this children's home</u>
<u n="221" who="S0227" trans="overlap">er ask me who who erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know him?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="223" who="S0227">who is driving instructor was</u>
<u n="224" who="S0192">very strange</u>
<u n="225" who="S0227"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0192">mm very strange</u>
<u n="227" who="S0227">yes it's all</u>
<u n="228" who="S0190">and where's your <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0192">the way it's all</u>
<u n="230" who="S0227" trans="overlap">and it's very</u>
<u n="231" who="S0190">pardon?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="233" who="S0192">the children's home I find it really strange</u>
<u n="234" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="235" who="S0192">at least on</u>
<u n="236" who="S0190" trans="overlap">he's got all the erm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0192">this side of the family you weren't there mum worked there dad went there</u>
<u n="238" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0190">that's where I met your mum all those years ago</u>
<u n="240" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0227">I said that I only know these people because of that home without that home I would you wouldn't exist</u>
<u n="242" who="S0192">no no I know</u>
<u n="243" who="S0227">if I hadn't gone there you would not exist because I'd have been in London and gone stayed at Watford or whatever <pause dur="short"/> so yes</u>
<u n="244" who="S0190">there you go</u>
<u n="245" who="S0192">and again the problem is <pause dur="short"/> a lovely large wedding like that is really not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and my style it's not if if we had the money what I would really like to do is find a beautiful deserted island somewhere and have just us and invite all my family and friends and pay for them to come out and we'd hire a boat and do all this kind of stuff you know but you need to be a millionaire to do all these kind of things</u>
<u n="246" who="S0190" trans="overlap">mm of course you do</u>
<u n="247" who="S0192">so it's not practical</u>
<u n="248" who="S0227">the person you've got to manage <pause dur="short"/> the person's <trunc>man</trunc> expectations you've got to manage is your mother's</u>
<u n="249" who="S0192"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0190">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="251" who="S0192">to a certain degree</u>
<u n="252" who="S0227" trans="overlap">er no I'm not</u>
<u n="253" who="S0192" trans="overlap">to a certain degree</u>
<u n="254" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s the most important</u>
<u n="255" who="S0227">no yes actually</u>
<u n="256" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah actually <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is the most important</u>
<u n="257" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><trunc>ye</trunc> <trunc>ye</trunc> <trunc>ye</trunc> no I'm <trunc>se</trunc> without notwithstanding <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and that's my problem I worry that I <trunc>thi</trunc> I'm pretty sure <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has the same opinion as me but</u>
<u n="259" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="260" who="S0192">occasionally</u>
<u n="261" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="262" who="S0192">there are certain things where I I doubt myself and wonder and I try and talk to her about well of course I talk to her about it cos I don't wanna be leading the charge on something that she doesn't feel erm <pause dur="short"/> and if she's happy we're very open with each other we're very honest and we talk about everything and</u>
<u n="263" who="S0227" trans="overlap">what's her take on children?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0192">er same as me really we both discussed the fact that probably part of us would definitely like to have children it's such <pause dur="short"/> a big experience it's such a core part of life that how could we miss out on such an experience? especially with people like us who love to experience however <pause dur="short"/> there's too much that we have to do before then that potentially if we pretty much vaguely have up until forty planned out <pause dur="short"/> vaguely <pause dur="short"/> now after forty that's when I kind of think we could have children</u>
<u n="265" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="266" who="S0192">no not at all</u>
<u n="267" who="S0190"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0227">well well that</u>
<u n="269" who="S0192">and we've discussed we've said when we get to forty I think we'll have done everything we wanna do and we'll be in a good enough job and we'll be qualified enough to be able to give a child a good life but she may have hit the the menopause by then cos her family hit it quite young</u>
<u n="270" who="S0227">it's not</u>
<u n="271" who="S0192" trans="overlap">her mum hit it at forty</u>
<u n="272" who="S0227">it's not impossible</u>
<u n="273" who="S0192">so we've talked about erm adopting honestly adopting we thought if we if er between here and then we don't feel ready to have a child then maybe when we get to that point we'll adopt</u>
<u n="274" who="S0227">well though tasked with my with the erm the erm standard bearer of my genetic material <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0192">I'm sorry dad you say you don't put any pressure on me</u>
<u n="276" who="S0227">no no no</u>
<u n="277" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but you do you do</u>
<u n="278" who="S0227">I mean there's always the <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you've told me before you want <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to take my name</u>
<u n="280" who="S0227">yes although</u>
<u n="281" who="S0192" trans="overlap">because you keep saying well where would the mark in history be?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0227" trans="overlap">erm erm</u>
<u n="283" who="S0192" trans="overlap">he does put some pressure he does it kind of passively aggressively but you really do</u>
<u n="284" who="S0227" trans="overlap">but although your your brother might end up as being the the standard bearer</u>
<u n="285" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0227">I don't know I mean you may not have children to be honest there is a very good argument not to have them I mean and there's an argument to have them</u>
<u n="287" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0190">if if you both boys could land up having daughters and there still won't be one</u>
<u n="289" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0190">so what's the as though</u>
<u n="291" who="S0192">we'll pass on the genetic material but not the name</u>
<u n="292" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah but that's yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0227">oh yeah the well</u>
<u n="294" who="S0192">unless they don't change their name</u>
<u n="295" who="S0227">it's it's erm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0192">that's the thing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> might not even change her name</u>
<u n="297" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><event desc="unintelligible"/>?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0192">sorry say that again</u>
<u n="299" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0192">that's yes that was yours yes</u>
<u n="301" who="S0227">yes thank you</u>
<u n="302" who="S0192">thank you very much that looks interesting</u>
<u n="303" who="S0227">another one?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0190">for her think that</u>
<u n="305" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><event desc="unintelligible"/> yeah thank you very much</u>
<u n="306" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0192">thank you</u>
<u n="308" who="S0190" trans="overlap">thank you</u>
<u n="309" who="S0192">I told you I had egg looks a bit different</u>
<u n="310" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but it looks good <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would you like to? there's an awful</u>
<u n="312" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no no no go on you tuck in I need a tiny little bit on the plate</u>
<u n="313" who="S0192">are we all are we all gonna share?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0190">yeah no no you <trunc>t</trunc> you enjoy I I'm like you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I can't eat it so I won't be able to enjoy my main course</u>
<u n="315" who="S0192">it should be like a yoghurty creamed <pause dur="short"/> interesting it's like a <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> salad in an Indian</u>
<u n="316" who="S0227">do you want a er piece of chicken off this?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0190">no thank you you enjoy it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="318" who="S0192">this is <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0227">it's an omelette in a</u>
<u n="320" who="S0192">yeah it's like an omelette with some lamb and spiced lamb would you like some of it? we can</u>
<u n="321" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no I'm no I've got this</u>
<u n="322" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no please I can't eat er this is like a whole meal and I've got a whole</u>
<u n="323" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well you're joking look at that <vocal desc="laugh"/> er he's got to get a starter</u>
<u n="324" who="S0227">mm very good</u>
<u n="325" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I thought we were sharing</u>
<u n="326" who="S0227">yeah we are</u>
<u n="327" who="S0192">I'll have a bit of yours you have a bit of mine <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> please take some</u>
<u n="328" who="S0190">no honestly I leave me the little tiny bits at the end</u>
<u n="329" who="S0192">the erm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0190">to try them <pause dur="short"/> I was also wanna try and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I could eat an awful lot more</u>
<u n="331" who="S0227" trans="overlap">there's another piece of meat</u>
<u n="332" who="S0190">I'm hungry which is why I'm just nibbling at the poppadums</u>
<u n="333" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="334" who="S0190">and that because I didn't have a cake or anything cos I didn't want to spoil it cos I when you go out and you're paying for something and you only eat half I just feel it would be a <unclear/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="336" who="S0190">but I can't eat it now just literally can't</u>
<u n="337" who="S0192">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's fine it's definitely different to what I had before</u>
<u n="338" who="S0190">but isn't the we erm when we went to erm Italy skiing on one er night erm my brother and his wife and erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I went out for a meal and we went to a pizzeria and I had a erm was it Kawasaki? it is isn't it?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0192">calzone?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0227">calzagi</u>
<u n="341" who="S0190" trans="overlap">calzone calzone that's it</u>
<u n="342" who="S0227" trans="overlap">calzone calzone</u>
<u n="343" who="S0190" trans="overlap"><trunc>Kaw</trunc> Kawasaki's a bike isn't it?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0190">erm and I'd never had one before</u>
<u n="346" who="S0227" trans="overlap">you got confused with <unclear>butter</unclear></u>
<u n="347" who="S0190">and I have never ever anywhere had a pizza like it have you ever had one?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0192">it's folded isn't it?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="350" who="S0192">they're good</u>
<u n="351" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh it's</u>
<u n="352" who="S0192">so how was?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0190" trans="overlap">and it was in a creamy sauce and it was gorgeous it was so soft and and I've had them in this country and</u>
<u n="354" who="S0192" trans="overlap">not to be repeated</u>
<u n="355" who="S0190" trans="overlap">and even in in er even in Italian restaurants and they're nothing like so I think sometimes like you say you you had your expectation of what you thought that would be it's not what you had before is it?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0192">it's still good</u>
<u n="357" who="S0190">it's still well as long as it's good</u>
<u n="358" who="S0192">it's obviously gonna be a bit better and where it's from and</u>
<u n="359" who="S0190">of course</u>
<u n="360" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well yeah when you're having it in a country</u>
<u n="361" who="S0192">and this will be kind of what Korea calls it fusion food this will be a mixture of India plus England so it's not just gonna be Indian food</u>
<u n="362" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="363" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's gonna be suited out our palates</u>
<u n="364" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="365" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that's why there's <trunc>s</trunc>salad you know</u>
<u n="366" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0192">you know you never have a salad with this normally <pause dur="short"/> this is good</u>
<u n="369" who="S0190">good are you enjoying it?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0192">mm <pause dur="short"/> did you want me to leave a bit so you can taste?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah just just one little mouthful</u>
<u n="372" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0190">so just so I can say that I had a taste</u>
<u n="374" who="S0192">there you are <pause dur="short"/> and there's a piece of this as well</u>
<u n="375" who="S0190">no honestly that's fine that</u>
<u n="376" who="S0192" trans="overlap">just a little bit</u>
<u n="377" who="S0190" trans="overlap">that little tiny bit</u>
<u n="378" who="S0192">yeah have some of the egg with it it's quite nice</u>
<u n="379" who="S0190" trans="overlap">just want to have a taste no I haven't yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0192">so it's got oh you dropped the egg</u>
<u n="381" who="S0190">yeah no I gonna come back for it</u>
<u n="382" who="S0192">shall I carry it over?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0190">thank you</u>
<u n="384" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0190">that's lovely</u>
<u n="386" who="S0192">and try a bit of dad's</u>
<u n="387" who="S0190">is that hot?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="389" who="S0192">would you consider that spicy?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="391" who="S0192">I can't really tell I just I don't think it's spicy <pause dur="long"/> we'll just have to take it slowly we've ordered a lot of food so we'll just sit here until it's done</u>
<u n="392" who="S0190">there's no rush is there?</u>
<u n="393" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="394" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="395" who="S0190">mm it is nice</u>
<u n="396" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="397" who="S0190">meat's a little bit dry</u>
<u n="398" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="399" who="S0190">for me <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> we're very all our things we like is wet isn't it?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="401" who="S0190">whatever we do <trunc>grav</trunc> loads of gravy sauces and things</u>
<u n="402" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah dad's is dripping in everything</u>
<u n="403" who="S0190" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="404" who="S0227">have you done a erm have you used any of your lemongrass or erm the <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0192">I've made a mess on it</u>
<u n="406" who="S0227">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0192">would you like some more of this?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0227">no I'm fine</u>
<u n="409" who="S0192">go on just have one of of these <pause dur="long"/> how into er</u>
<u n="410" who="S0227">oh</u>
<u n="411" who="S0192">does give a good</u>
<u n="412" who="S0227">if erm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0192">it's got a good <trunc>go</trunc>good hit of coriander on this and I'm <trunc>su</trunc></u>
<u n="414" who="S0227">if you were staying here for more than a year I would have tried to grow you a kaffir lime but</u>
<u n="415" who="S0192">mm <pause dur="short"/> you've given me plenty of leaves</u>
<u n="416" who="S0227">mm <pause dur="short"/> same round here is about two or three at a time mm</u>
<u n="417" who="S0192">yeah that's why erm I've been used to using dried so I put too many in when I did it last time</u>
<u n="418" who="S0227">was it really limey?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0192">it was good but</u>
<u n="420" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0192">I forgot to put</u>
<u n="422" who="S0227" trans="overlap">really limey</u>
<u n="423" who="S0190" trans="overlap">overdid it</u>
<u n="424" who="S0192" trans="overlap">well yeah I think I put well what do you consider a leaf? the double bit?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah that's one leaf</u>
<u n="426" who="S0192" trans="overlap">or half of one that's one leaf</u>
<u n="427" who="S0227" trans="overlap">one leaf yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0192">I put in three then <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know whether that was three leaves or six leaves</u>
<u n="429" who="S0227">mm call it three <pause dur="short"/> but it does impart the flavour it's they're quite strong aren't they?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0192">mm <pause dur="short"/> it's a very unique flavour</u>
<u n="431" who="S0227">mm you can see why our investors have been buying that <unclear/> cos I knew that er after once the <trunc>initia</trunc>initial investment was paid for I'm just keep giving</u>
<u n="432" who="S0192">it's really good</u>
<u n="433" who="S0190">did you have any last year for your birthday or was it the year</u>
<u n="434" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no the year</u>
<u n="435" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no it was the year before that?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0227">it's two years old yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0190" trans="overlap">so it's two years old</u>
<u n="438" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0190">oh right</u>
<u n="440" who="S0227">I remember the first year I I I bought one it died it was too small I've got a bigger one now and it survived</u>
<u n="441" who="S0190">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="442" who="S0192">mm it was good <pause dur="long"/> so yeah children I may not be able to erm</u>
<u n="443" who="S0227">if you don't you don't</u>
<u n="444" who="S0192" trans="overlap">produce <pause dur="short"/> problem is <pause dur="short"/> practically if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I want to be lecturers in a European university we need a PhD <pause dur="short"/> now unless we are super intelligent to the point where we get complete funding for a PhD in the next couple of years we're gonna have to pay for a PhD which is gonna take a couple of years to save up and then a PhD is four years itself I can't have a child while I'm studying for a PhD</u>
<u n="445" who="S0190" trans="overlap">this is the dilemma that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got because like she's got another is it another three years isn't it? is it three?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0227">for what?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0190">until she finishes her erm <pause dur="short"/> her studies?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0227">I don't know she's</u>
<u n="449" who="S0190" trans="overlap">till she qualifies to gets her</u>
<u n="450" who="S0227" trans="overlap">she's a she's a registrar now</u>
<u n="451" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">have you finished your start?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0192">yes thank you very much</u>
<u n="453" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes lovely thank you what even if she wanted to become a consultant <pause dur="short"/> cos she's a registrar already</u>
<u n="454" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0192">thank you the problem there are things that get in the way you can't have a child at that point</u>
<u n="456" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well this is it that's what she says <pause dur="short"/> well she's I can have if I have a child then I'm not going to be able to look after it with the hours that I've done so then I'll have to either give up <pause dur="short"/> thank you and</u>
<u n="457" who="S0227" trans="overlap">can we have er do you want another beer? have another one</u>
<u n="458" who="S0192">I'm alright with this one you have another one</u>
<u n="459" who="S0227">can I have another erm Cobra please?</u>
<u n="460" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">is that a pint or a bottle?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0227">er pint please <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="462" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">a pint of Coburn and you're okay with your</u>
<u n="463" who="S0192">yeah I'm alright thanks</u>
<u n="464" who="S0227">no I'm fine thank you</u>
<u n="465" who="S0192">yeah things get in the way <pause dur="short"/> I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I have considered if we had a child we would like to both work part time and alternate so we didn't have to put it into care or anything you know</u>
<u n="466" who="S0190" trans="overlap">into care yeah cos otherwise what's the point?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0192">no that's what I think</u>
<u n="468" who="S0227">but your mum she's a <trunc>nur</trunc> she's a trained nursery nurse I mean</u>
<u n="469" who="S0192">yeah you know get the</u>
<u n="470" who="S0227" trans="overlap">trouble is you're gonna be living a very long way away and it won't be practical</u>
<u n="471" who="S0192">and if we want to work as lecturers in a university I need to be producing research and research is not easy to do or I can't</u>
<u n="472" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="473" who="S0192" trans="overlap">imagine how you'd do that with a child doing conferences and going round the country</u>
<u n="474" who="S0227">no have you broached the subject with her?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it just doesn't compute</u>
<u n="476" who="S0227">about children</u>
<u n="477" who="S0192">with who?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0227" trans="overlap">with your mum</u>
<u n="479" who="S0192">oh yeah I've as and being as I've been as frank with mum as I'm being with you</u>
<u n="480" who="S0227">what's her take on this?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0190">is she disappointed?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0227">she it's part of the <unclear/></u>
<u n="483" who="S0192"><unclear>covertly</unclear> disappointed yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0190" trans="overlap">because at the end of the day it's it's your dream</u>
<u n="485" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="486" who="S0190">that your children will carry on the same lifestyle that you have and they'll get married and they'll have children so that you have grandchildren but I think as life society changes you begin to think well life's different now we didn't go abroad and do all the sort of the you know working abroad and that like you've done so maybe it won't happen</u>
<u n="487" who="S0192">it changes I mean I think at the same time yes she's disappointed but I think she'll also if I do achieve what I'm setting out to achieve hopefully she'll be proud</u>
<u n="488" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0227">oh she'll be proud</u>
<u n="490" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you know regardless of having children</u>
<u n="491" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it it it's the erm</u>
<u n="492" who="S0192">and if I if I adopted could you do you think you can love an adopted child?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0227" trans="overlap">er <trunc>ch</trunc></u>
<u n="494" who="S0192" trans="overlap">like your own grandchildren?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0227">well <pause dur="short"/> erm I have two</u>
<u n="496" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean there are children now that don't have parents</u>
<u n="497" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I have two like adoptive sons so I've kind of got round my head round that so erm yeah obviously there's a there's a er a <trunc>disa</trunc> a little disappointment that erm not mine but that is not a <trunc>ver</trunc>very erm <pause dur="short"/> a it's not conditional are you with me?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0190">well the other bit the other take on that is the fact that one or the other of you mightn't be able to have children</u>
<u n="499" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes well yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0192" trans="overlap">which is which we've considered</u>
<u n="501" who="S0190" trans="overlap">so therefore the only way you could have a family erm is is to adopt</u>
<u n="502" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah er is is to adopt yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0190" trans="overlap">so why shouldn't er any other it should just be the same it's yours</u>
<u n="504" who="S0192">and when I look around and think of all the children who don't have parents</u>
<u n="505" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="506" who="S0192">I mean</u>
<u n="507" who="S0190">I just think that I mean I always laugh at this is that I would like to adopt erm and have another child and then I think you have to be I I wasn't wouldn't have been a strong enough person to accept that that child <unclear>directly</unclear> because you have no idea of how that child is going to turn out you can try everything possible but you wouldn't be there's no guarantee</u>
<u n="508" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="509" who="S0190">thank you</u>
<u n="510" who="S0227">although there isn't with your own children either</u>
<u n="511" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="512" who="S0190">well there isn't but</u>
<u n="513" who="S0227">you can stick with blood</u>
<u n="514" who="S0190" trans="overlap">you can have some it's like</u>
<u n="515" who="S0227" trans="overlap">you'll stick with blood a <trunc>lo</trunc> <trunc>lo</trunc> a lot longer</u>
<u n="516" who="S0192">it's definitely erm <pause dur="short"/> a bit of a quandary thank you thinking about how would I feel I mean a big part of us biologically does wanna pass on our DNA I wanna see</u>
<u n="517" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's your it's your</u>
<u n="518" who="S0192" trans="overlap">what a mixture of the two of us would look like</u>
<u n="519" who="S0227" trans="overlap">your your your problem your not your problem your your dilemma will be your your mortality er your legacy erm you've will pass on the baton on your what your like I said your mindset now my mindset at your age is totally different to my mindset now my mindset at your age would despise what I've turned into I quite like what I've turned into but this is talking to my my twenty-eight year old</u>
<u n="520" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you're a different person</u>
<u n="521" who="S0227">I'm a different my confidence was like the same but my <pause dur="short"/> likes and dislikes have changed erm <pause dur="short"/> it's <pause dur="short"/> you will look at it as in <pause dur="short"/> you're only here for a finite period of time your immortality is isn't free of <unclear>children</unclear> you will also look at this as then your life has been enriched by your experience do you want to pass that enrichment onto another generation?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0192">well what about if we have different philosophies what if I don't feel if I feel a genuine connection to everyone on this planet what if I thought like oh lovely thank you</u>
<u n="523" who="S0227">thank you</u>
<u n="524" who="S0192">my legacy might not necessarily have to be imparted through my own biology</u>
<u n="525" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="526" who="S0192">that I</u>
<u n="527" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="528" who="S0192" trans="overlap">feel more of a kinship with with the people around me</u>
<u n="529" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes you you might your legacy might be something totally different you might er have something written or something like that and er and you'll have a legacy in a different way</u>
<u n="530" who="S0192">this is the first thing this that is cementing me in history</u>
<u n="531" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="532" who="S0192">if anyone ever in the future looks back and wants to go what did the British public sound like in two thousand and fourteen? we are all recorded</u>
<u n="533" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="534" who="S0192" trans="overlap">this has probably cemented us in history more than anything else that we've ever done</u>
<u n="535" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> please send the royalties to erm</u>
<u n="536" who="S0190"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="537" who="S0227">account <anon type="financialDetails"/></u>
<u n="538" who="S0192">I hope that's not real</u>
<u n="539" who="S0190">it is real</u>
<u n="540" who="S0192">I mean they're only gonna</u>
<u n="541" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="542" who="S0192">give money to you right? they can't take money from you</u>
<u n="543" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/> please send royalty cheques to</u>
<u n="544" who="S0192">but seriously I mean <pause dur="short"/> this is going in the Cambridge University British National Corpus the only one in the whole country that does this</u>
<u n="545" who="S0227">mm <pause dur="short"/> I still want my royalties</u>
<u n="546" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="547" who="S0227">erm</u>
<u n="548" who="S0192">I thought that was quite interesting</u>
<u n="549" who="S0227">I think it's erm</u>
<u n="550" who="S0192">that's your legacy</u>
<u n="551" who="S0227">the it depends</u>
<u n="552" who="S0190" trans="overlap">that's strange wouldn't it to think that grandchildren sorry again it's that but grandchildren would look back and something would come out of that and and turn around and say that's my <trunc>grand</trunc> my grandpa or grandma did that</u>
<u n="553" who="S0227">yes well</u>
<u n="554" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0192">it will be they don't have many I mean it's a large project but they sent out a global email to me the other day with everyone else that's involved in the course there's only other one hundred people in the whole country doing this so there's not that many of us</u>
<u n="556" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="557" who="S0192">and they're now asking us where are you doing this? because they're looking for any gaps in the country</u>
<u n="558" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="559" who="S0192">so I am covering well I kind of told them it's a bit it doesn't seem right because actually I'm living in <anon type="place"/> but everyone I've recorded so far is from <trunc>Roch</trunc> from <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> so I kind of</u>
<u n="560" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah Bedfordshire and Northamptonshire</u>
<u n="561" who="S0192" trans="overlap">told them that really my area is</u>
<u n="562" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0192" trans="overlap">is that area so we will be the as far as I know they don't have anyone else recording from this area so eventually they'll make a map</u>
<u n="564" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="565" who="S0192">and the map will have lots of points on it and you'll click on a point and it'll have a recording from that area so you will be in the archive</u>
<u n="566" who="S0227">we'd better make sure we don't drop our Hs and and</u>
<u n="567" who="S0190" trans="overlap">they're not going they're not taking what we've said you said they're only they're not going to play back what we've said are they?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0192">I mean people will be able to listen to it</u>
<u n="569" who="S0190">you said that it wasn't that it was</u>
<u n="570" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I said that they're not they're not paying any attention to what you're saying but it's it's for use</u>
<u n="571" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well of course they will <pause dur="short"/> you can't not listen to a conversation</u>
<u n="572" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I don't think</u>
<u n="573" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they're not gonna know who you are there's no name attached and any time that we mention each other's name that will taken out so there's no</u>
<u n="574" who="S0227" trans="overlap">right in in fifty years' time</u>
<u n="575" who="S0192" trans="overlap">your identity is protected</u>
<u n="576" who="S0227" trans="overlap">they won't be paying much <trunc>com</trunc> you know what the detail maybe what's being said not</u>
<u n="577" who="S0192">it's the pronunciation they're focusing on the pronunciation</u>
<u n="578" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="579" who="S0192">and words that you use</u>
<u n="580" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="581" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and that kind of stuff but they they've told us and part of the sheet that you signed</u>
<u n="582" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="583" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they're saying that all of your personal identities</u>
<u n="584" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="585" who="S0192">will be discarded</u>
<u n="586" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I was going to say yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0227">I hope that</u>
<u n="588" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they won't know who you are</u>
<u n="589" who="S0227">I don't I don't want to sound <trunc>bombast</trunc></u>
<u n="590" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but your voice will be there for history</u>
<u n="591" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah I don't want to sound bombastic but I hope my words are bigger that maybe the</u>
<u n="592" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="593" who="S0227">the syllables of my words are big enough to</u>
<u n="594" who="S0192">a linguist would argue there is no judgement here <pause dur="short"/> we really have an elitist culture now where you know Received Pronunciation is what you understand</u>
<u n="595" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="596" who="S0192">and that's what you should aim for anything else is just incorrect it's wrong it's poor elocution but linguists would argue that there's no such thing and you describe language and there are so many variations and you I mean I've been selling <unclear>pigeons</unclear> in crowds for a very long time hundreds of years we called it you know broken English bastard English all sort of terrible names</u>
<u n="597" who="S0227" trans="overlap">pigeon English <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="598" who="S0192" trans="overlap">for these kind of things yeah erm but actually when you study it linguistically it's as much a fully formed language as any other language it's just different</u>
<u n="599" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="600" who="S0192">they use tense modality and aspect markers they have their own grammar they have everything there's a set <trunc>fe</trunc>features there's no <trunc>sh</trunc> worse than any other language you can't linguists would argue that you can't look at a language and say this is better than that language historically we've always argued that Latin based languages are the best because they're highly inflected they have a lot of you know inflection?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0227">erm <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="602" who="S0190">inflections?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0227">in in <trunc>inflec</trunc> are you on about like a</u>
<u n="604" who="S0190" trans="overlap">like this er yeah or like you put er over when you're using French</u>
<u n="605" who="S0227" trans="overlap">an emphasis or something like that?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0192">inflection's grammatical so</u>
<u n="607" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="608" who="S0192">plurality if I say dog and then I say dogs</u>
<u n="609" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="610" who="S0192">the S is an inflection we don't use much inflection when I say I play you play he plays the only one that's inflected is the third person he plays</u>
<u n="611" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0192">in Spanish it's <foreign lang="spa">habló</foreign> <foreign lang="spa">hablamos</foreign> <foreign lang="spa">hablaste</foreign> that's highly inflected</u>
<u n="613" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="614" who="S0192">they they indicate gender plurality they indicate all sort of functions through inflection</u>
<u n="615" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="616" who="S0192">we don't have that so for a long time grammarians said the best languages are ones with high inflection the Latin languages</u>
<u n="617" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="618" who="S0192">but we turned around and go well why is that? why is a language that has less inflection we still <pause dur="short"/> provide all those things in English we just use more themes to do it we use <trunc>e</trunc>extra little words we don't attach it to the same word we add another word to do it so there's no difference all languages they they argue that there are no simple languages</u>
<u n="619" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="620" who="S0192">a a human language will cover every avenue possible the only difference is some languages have fewer words than other languages some languages have more consonants or more vowels but again you can't really use that as a basis to argue that one language is <pause dur="short"/> basically linguists would argue you can't say that any language is superior than any other language provided they fully use every function</u>
<u n="621" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="622" who="S0192">which when you study the language you</u>
<u n="623" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well the</u>
<u n="624" who="S0192">they ought to</u>
<u n="625" who="S0227" trans="overlap">the ultimate erm er aim for a language is to communicate</u>
<u n="626" who="S0192">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="627" who="S0227">if you're talking in a language that no one else understands <vocal desc="laugh"/> you're not communicating you might be talking a language but the person <pause dur="short"/> but the recipient doesn't understand what you're saying</u>
<u n="628" who="S0192">I've confused it a little bit though when I said about pigeons a pigeon <pause dur="short"/> is simpler a pigeon is a contact language that is nobody's first language</u>
<u n="629" who="S0190">yeah that's right a bit of this and a bit of that isn't it?</u>
<u n="630" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="631" who="S0192">the it's it's structured they have a structure because there are different there's a continuum of pigeons they're <trunc>mea</trunc> eventually a creole is when a pigeon becomes used as a first language</u>
<u n="632" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0192">and it's actually the children that create the grammar but it's part of our language faculty the children realise that they are missing they they don't have the right words for things</u>
<u n="634" who="S0227">so if</u>
<u n="635" who="S0192">so they fill it in</u>
<u n="636" who="S0192">so there are fillers in</u>
<u n="637" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so a creole used to a pigeon <pause dur="short"/> a pigeon when it becomes a first language is therefore needs to have every function that every other first language has and it becomes a creole</u>
<u n="638" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="639" who="S0192">so effectively yes you could say a pigeon is simpler but a creole isn't it's no different</u>
<u n="640" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="641" who="S0192">how did we get onto this conversation what were we talking about?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0227">er not sure</u>
<u n="643" who="S0192">I've just reeled on</u>
<u n="644" who="S0227">er probably because I said about bombastic er that</u>
<u n="645" who="S0192">oh yeah you</u>
<u n="646" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's a your no</u>
<u n="647" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh yeah you oh yeah okay so they're not gonna be analysing the kind of words of you're using</u>
<u n="648" who="S0227">I I know how to use the language but its its construct <pause dur="short"/> I</u>
<u n="649" who="S0192">you have a tacit understanding of of language</u>
<u n="650" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah your on your knowledge of er the construct is far superior to mine and I have to smile because <pause dur="short"/> erm when I left school although I could speak reasonably well I could not communicate on paper one of my</u>
<u n="651" who="S0192">whereas that was probably the main part of your job</u>
<u n="652" who="S0227" trans="overlap">a girlfriend taught me how to do that and it's I it took me three goes to do it I got a D with it the first time an E the second <pause dur="short"/> er my love life's got more complicated</u>
<u n="653" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="654" who="S0227">and that's why I went for down E</u>
<u n="655" who="S0192" trans="overlap">went down the second time on the attempt</u>
<u n="656" who="S0227" trans="overlap">but then a third attempt I got a C it it it pleases me to know that that from my generation to yours from a person who could not write er because I've been I'd been writing what I thought were love letters but clearly the recipient was thinking this is a load of rubbish</u>
<u n="657" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="658" who="S0227">there's no syntax no grammar no nothing and you know in her own way kind of said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you can't write which was well for a person of my my ego was gonna be a bit difficult for me to accept but I accepted it and said okay teach me she did that enabled me to express myself <pause dur="short"/> and my progeny is able to</u>
<u n="659" who="S0190">do it just like that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="660" who="S0227">to to to be to really analyse the the language and it's and it's</u>
<u n="661" who="S0192">and it's my job</u>
<u n="662" who="S0227">yes exactly but when I look back at your father</u>
<u n="663" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="664" who="S0227">he came out of the school system and I I didn't know where full stops went commas inverted commas semi colons</u>
<u n="665" who="S0192">yeah I mean that's what should happen shouldn't it?</u>
<u n="666" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no <trunc>n</trunc>nothing</u>
<u n="667" who="S0192">you should improve on your your your forbearers and you should</u>
<u n="668" who="S0190">you don't think that if</u>
<u n="669" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well the improvement there was a there was if I hadn't of if I had not</u>
<u n="670" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> didn't set the bar too high</u>
<u n="671" who="S0227">if I had not of erm done that the it would be like you would might as well say that your your father was illiterate I could communicate verbally well I was illiterate I couldn't <trunc>w</trunc>well I could read I just couldn't write never picked up a</u>
<u n="672" who="S0192">what do you think about negative concord? I don't do nothing <pause dur="short"/> when you hear that</u>
<u n="673" who="S0227">no I I would say I don't do anything not nothing</u>
<u n="674" who="S0192">yeah that would be what we consider correct the concord</u>
<u n="675" who="S0190" trans="overlap">the correct way of saying it</u>
<u n="676" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah I'd say anything yeah yes</u>
<u n="677" who="S0192">do you think negative concord is is bad if you heard somebody say like don't do nothing?</u>
<u n="678" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yes well it's not it's not bad is it? it just <pause dur="short"/> it's <pause dur="short"/> it's like saying well that's a nice cake we used to get slammed something terrible for saying writing nice because nice is not a good word</u>
<u n="679" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's not descriptive</u>
<u n="680" who="S0190">no you can there are so many words in this language think of the one that you could use better there's there's like a lovely</u>
<u n="681" who="S0192">we do that today with <trunc>moth</trunc> er with intensifiers a lot of people will say oh it's very hot rather than it's scorching there are words to describe very hot</u>
<u n="682" who="S0190" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="683" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="684" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="685" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but we just stick very in front of everything</u>
<u n="686" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="687" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="688" who="S0192">that's a complaint that teachers have that people aren't using the their poetic</u>
<u n="689" who="S0190" trans="overlap"><trunc>th</trunc>that's right you have the language there you know <pause dur="short"/> make it come stronger pick out better words that will say what you want to say better</u>
<u n="690" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I would agree with that and I don't think a linguist would disagree with that I think you know we do have these words at our disposable one when argue that we do have antonyms but there are no synonyms we'll and although you think that there are synonyms there aren't no two words are exactly identical they have slightly different connotations slightly different register</u>
<u n="691" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="692" who="S0192">therefore we can use we should and I think I <trunc>s</trunc> try and study new words and then I think what's the point because if we say it in front of someone they just think I'm a bit of an idiot why why would I use this word? am I trying to make them sound unintelligent? so you end up learning these enormous words and</u>
<u n="693" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah but you never know when you're going to do</u>
<u n="694" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I I</u>
<u n="695" who="S0190" trans="overlap">when you're going to be able to use them do you?</u>
<u n="696" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="697" who="S0190">I mean you throw words in something and I think oh right</u>
<u n="698" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I I do if I</u>
<u n="699" who="S0190" trans="overlap">is this to muck around?</u>
<u n="700" who="S0227" trans="overlap">if I if I get upset or I feel erm</u>
<u n="701" who="S0192">you get cornered</u>
<u n="702" who="S0227">I the my words <trunc>beco</trunc> my I start <trunc>becom</trunc> I find that bigger syllables I remember throwing your your grandfather out of out of your mother's flat <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I'd said to him erm <pause dur="short"/> don't you cos he was <trunc>say</trunc> he was right he was springing from a a premise of of correctness he was saying <pause dur="short"/> your mum was <unclear>waiting</unclear> for you I didn't have a job but but they'd invited themselves they knew your mum wasn't there they knew your mum wasn't there I was there but they invited themselves and you see your nan and your grandad invited themselves er over and they were giving me a right lecture about what am I going to do and what are my prospects bugger all they had to be right <pause dur="short"/> maybe your grandad had said something and I said don't you think you're being a little overzealous? so he kind of came back with something that was completely you know like he didn't <trunc>un</trunc> you know er understand what I've said of course he completely you know the meaning of what I'd said so I had to repeat it and that's when I got on my horse and I said to him right I said if you don't <trunc>un</trunc> this was before I threw them out I said if you don't understand <vocal desc="laugh"/> what I'm saying would you like to continue this conversation in Spanish? I said I'm quite happy to accommodate you in either language I said because either you've lost the argument and it's time for you to go goodbye <vocal desc="laugh"/> and threw them out of your mum's flat</u>
<u n="703" who="S0192">I bet he loved you after that</u>
<u n="704" who="S0227">it took him a few years to forgive me for that yeah but I felt I felt cornered and the more cornered I felt the more upset I became was starting to use big er bigger words because I'd er used the words as weapons against you thinking you won't actually know what it is I'm talking about it</u>
<u n="705" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and people do that don't they?</u>
<u n="706" who="S0227" trans="overlap">and so I used overzealous aspect it was it was in the right connotation for the phrase but he didn't understand what it was I've just said</u>
<u n="707" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="708" who="S0227">so er yeah er so I I then became even more bombastic and said right if you can't understand this then why don't we speak in another language? I'll accommodate you either way erm but that that's it goodnight</u>
<u n="709" who="S0192">now the er er type of stylistic variation we accommodate we converge or diverge from the speakers that are around us we usually converge we like to sound more like the people around us so we have an affinity with those people</u>
<u n="710" who="S0227">I do at work</u>
<u n="711" who="S0192">but you can also do the opposite you can diverge because right at the moment I'm angry with you and I don't wanna sound like you I want to sound</u>
<u n="712" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="713" who="S0192">either superior to you or below you or whatever</u>
<u n="714" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah sooner er but I don't wanna be inferior</u>
<u n="715" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I don't wanna <event desc="unintelligible"/> with you yes</u>
<u n="716" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no you're gonna start to do that</u>
<u n="717" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so that that's convergence back to what I was saying about negative concord I don't have nothing sounds terrible to us</u>
<u n="718" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="719" who="S0192">but in most languages in the world Spanish <foreign lang="spa">no tengo nada</foreign></u>
<u n="720" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="721" who="S0192">I don't have nothing</u>
<u n="722" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well yeah yeah</u>
<u n="723" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's exactly the same translation there is nothing wrong and in fact in middle English we use negative concord grammarians neo grammarians turned around and said that's wrong you can't do that and it's through these er prescriptive grammarians that went around and said an adjective must end L Y <trunc>w</trunc> all these rules that they said didn't reflect the usage of the language and kind of spelling as well English orthography there's all sorts of things where they eventually got wrong do you know the word debt? D E B T?</u>
<u n="724" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="725" who="S0192">they presumed so they went back and decided to spell the words and they presumed that it was from the Latin <foreign lang="lat"/> which is like to owe somebody or other but it wasn't it actually came from Germanic so they added a B into the spelling incorrectly the spelling should just D E T not D E B T</u>
<u n="726" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes cos it's they so it's</u>
<u n="727" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they did it incorrectly</u>
<u n="728" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's a <trunc>te</trunc> it's a very silent B isn't it?</u>
<u n="729" who="S0192">there are lots of things the word knight used to be pronounced <unclear>kernicit</unclear> it was like a <vocal desc="misc"/> like a</u>
<u n="730" who="S0227">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="731" who="S0192" trans="overlap">lock like a <vocal desc="misc"/> a <vocal desc="misc"/> I think was the original one so old er orthography reflected how we used to pronounce things but now we don't pronounce it like that</u>
<u n="732" who="S0227">yes so it's gone <unclear/></u>
<u n="733" who="S0192">so it's why do we have these conventions? when I first got with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it pained me to hear her say we was</u>
<u n="734" who="S0227">we was</u>
<u n="735" who="S0192" trans="overlap">she she says not so much anymore because I <trunc>y</trunc> hey <trunc>y</trunc> we were you can't say that</u>
<u n="736" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="737" who="S0192">she'd say it all the time</u>
<u n="738" who="S0227">yeah for teaching English you can't use that no</u>
<u n="739" who="S0192">I spent some time with her mum recently her mum does not have the word were in her lexicon she doesn't say it</u>
<u n="740" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="741" who="S0192">she just say I was you was we was</u>
<u n="742" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="743" who="S0192">and that's regional that's</u>
<u n="744" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="745" who="S0192" trans="overlap">part of her dialect that's just</u>
<u n="746" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="747" who="S0192" trans="overlap">what they do if you go up north there are certain places in Scotland that I've read about that use double modal auxiliary verbs modal auxiliary verb can could shall should may might well well would so for example they'll say a sentence I would could do that which to us sounds ridiculous</u>
<u n="748" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="749" who="S0192">I should might be able to <pause dur="short"/> which just sounds really really wrong to us but actually she fills a bit of a lexical gap because it it gives more probability to the rest of the situation so they are actually in a way more astute in what they're saying than than we are more accurate or precise</u>
<u n="750" who="S0227">one thing that that</u>
<u n="751" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but there's nothing wrong linguists er would argue that it's that every dialect er provided they can communicate everything nothing is wrong the</u>
<u n="752" who="S0190">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> always it you have to like you say you have to respect that other people do do speak because er she always says I'll learn you to do this and I'll learn it's I'll teach you</u>
<u n="753" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I'll learn all the time yes yes</u>
<u n="754" who="S0192">yeah yes</u>
<u n="755" who="S0190">not I'll learn you to do something</u>
<u n="756" who="S0227">I the ones that irritate me especially if you hear it on TV people keep saying er you know or right and they're using it</u>
<u n="757" who="S0192">discourse markers</u>
<u n="758" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="759" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="760" who="S0227">you know you know you're right you're right right right right and you're going <pause dur="short"/> if you tried to write that that would look so wrong</u>
<u n="761" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="762" who="S0227">but they're saying it well yeah you know I know all about <event desc="unintelligible"/> and right and no I'm not agreeing with you so <pause dur="short"/> I used to get used get years ago I'm and this at work not recently but in the distant past some people say I'm sorry you know it's that you're they're arguing with you and I say no there's there's no need to apologise</u>
<u n="763" who="S0192" trans="overlap">there's nothing to be sorry about</u>
<u n="764" who="S0227">yeah you haven't done anything wrong</u>
<u n="765" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="766" who="S0227">and that really <trunc>irr</trunc>irritates people what do you mean I'm <trunc>apologi</trunc> well you just said you're sorry were didn't you? I never said I'm sorry well you</u>
<u n="767" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="768" who="S0227">you haven't done anything wrong so why are you apologising? yet they do it it they use the word to go <pause dur="short"/> saying they're I'm sorry</u>
<u n="769" who="S0192">have you noticed that certain words have taken on the opposite meaning as well? the word literally people use literally now but it actually they're using it to mean figuratively but they'll</u>
<u n="770" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="771" who="S0192">but they'll use it they use it to mean the opposite</u>
<u n="772" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="773" who="S0192">I literally love that guy that's figuratively</u>
<u n="774" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="775" who="S0192">but I don't really love him but they use literally to mean the opposite of what it actually means</u>
<u n="776" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well one the one of the words they don't like</u>
<u n="777" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's very strange</u>
<u n="778" who="S0227" trans="overlap">that is supposed to be like if you're saying that it's really good you now say it's sick</u>
<u n="779" who="S0192">yeah that's been around for a while yeah</u>
<u n="780" who="S0227" trans="overlap">that's that's ridiculous</u>
<u n="781" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's a bit of a <unclear/> word</u>
<u n="782" who="S0227">you see a connection with that a cockney</u>
<u n="783" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean we can argue it's ridiculous but is it? words change people use different things language varies</u>
<u n="784" who="S0227" trans="overlap">evolves</u>
<u n="785" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean it it does evolve it doesn't stop it never never stops</u>
<u n="786" who="S0190">er it doesn't stop evolving</u>
<u n="787" who="S0227">oh I thought you said <unclear/> fruit</u>
<u n="788" who="S0192">yeah it's very strange but I had to I had to break down those rules myself because I definitely would tell <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> off when she did that and it's only through formerly studying linguistics that I now realise that I shouldn't that she's not incorrect in what she's saying I just need to have less of an elitist approach to how people talk and it is elitist cos people struggle to get jobs that are like</u>
<u n="789" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh yes yeah</u>
<u n="790" who="S0192" trans="overlap">in these areas so I mean I personally have always really disliked the Birmingham accent</u>
<u n="791" who="S0190">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="792" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I think it sounds terribly uneducated</u>
<u n="793" who="S0190" trans="overlap">brummie</u>
<u n="794" who="S0192">yeah like well but apparently it was one of the poorest of areas of England for quite a while and so we have this affiliation with them being poor and therefore their accent being stupid and we just but they've done a test on foreigners and they get foreigners to listen to different British accents they really like the Birmingham accent there's no there is nothing negative about the way they speak there is nothing inherently negative about it <pause dur="short"/> it's strange</u>
<u n="795" who="S0190">I think it's again that's one of the things that that's gets muddled up and thank you <pause dur="short"/> with class and that too because depending on what class you come from as to how you should speak which is the correct way and which is the wrong way</u>
<u n="796" who="S0192">do you use flat adverbs? so for example do you say hold tight or hold tightly?</u>
<u n="797" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">Kashmiri jal?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="799" who="S0190" trans="overlap">erm that's</u>
<u n="800" who="S0192" trans="overlap">just put them all out and we'll share them all I think</u>
<u n="801" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="803" who="S0190">erm</u>
<u n="804" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">and gulab jamum?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0192">that was the gulab <pause dur="short"/> that one must be my one and that's the <unclear/></u>
<u n="806" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">sag aloo?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0192">thank you very much <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="808" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">one garlic naan</u>
<u n="809" who="S0192">have you got a garlic naan as well?</u>
<u n="810" who="S0227">erm back on this</u>
<u n="811" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no I think we must</u>
<u n="812" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's one of the two</u>
<u n="813" who="S0192">I thought you did</u>
<u n="814" who="S0190" trans="overlap">have you? is it?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0227">yeah it's two</u>
<u n="816" who="S0192">oh no</u>
<u n="817" who="S0227">no no I</u>
<u n="818" who="S0190" trans="overlap">alright</u>
<u n="819" who="S0227">no well I'll have a bit</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="820" who="S0192">we've only just got one yes</u>
<u n="821" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">two mushroom fried rice</u>
<u n="822" who="S0192">excellent</u>
<u n="823" who="S0190">yes</u>
<u n="824" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes I didn't get</u>
<u n="825" who="S0192">well please have some naan</u>
<u n="826" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I I I forgot to order a</u>
<u n="827" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="828" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">one mushroom rice</u>
<u n="829" who="S0192">lovely thank you</u>
<u n="830" who="S0190">great</u>
<u n="831" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's definitely hard to break those barriers down so yeah do you say hold tight or hold tightly?</u>
<u n="832" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">enjoy your meal</u>
<u n="833" who="S0192">thank you</u>
<u n="834" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well it depends on what erm what I think I would say hold tight</u>
<u n="835" who="S0192">that would be incorrect apparently if you follow the conventions of grammar</u>
<u n="836" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="837" who="S0192">you're using an adverb to modify the form hold tightly should be the word speak slowly hold tightly</u>
<u n="838" who="S0190">yes but if you're</u>
<u n="839" who="S0192" trans="overlap">if you say hold tight</u>
<u n="840" who="S0190" trans="overlap">if you were say you're like if you're putting a child onto a ride it sounds a bit silly to say hold tightly</u>
<u n="841" who="S0192">it does yeah</u>
<u n="842" who="S0190">doesn't it?</u>
<u n="843" who="S0192">but that's not the way we say it</u>
<u n="844" who="S0190">it's hold tight yeah</u>
<u n="845" who="S0192">and traditionally in the eighteenth century we used they're called a flat adverbs we and Americans use them a lot my friends will often say speak slow they won't say speak slowly</u>
<u n="846" who="S0227">slowly yeah yeah</u>
<u n="847" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they say speak slow erm I'm actually tempted to do my dissertation in flat adverbs</u>
<u n="848" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="849" who="S0192">because I've noticed more of a usage so I'm tempted to do a synchronic analysis of British public to see whether or not we are using more I can do a synchronic analysis by firstly analysing the youths and then analysing the elderly if the elderly don't do it but the youth do that suggests that it's changed</u>
<u n="850" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="851" who="S0192">if the elderly don't do</u>
<u n="852" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="853" who="S0192">but the youth do so therefore there's synchronic change</u>
<u n="854" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="855" who="S0190">would you like some rice?</u>
<u n="856" who="S0192">not much more rice I'm okay thank <trunc>yo</trunc> I've got the the <trunc>na</trunc> can we share the naan?</u>
<u n="857" who="S0227">yeah there's no mushroom there er</u>
<u n="858" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah there is</u>
<u n="859" who="S0227">well there's not much</u>
<u n="860" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I'm <trunc>o</trunc> anyway I can eat mushrooms I'm just alright without them</u>
<u n="861" who="S0227">which one's mine? I'm not sure</u>
<u n="862" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that one's yours</u>
<u n="863" who="S0227">oh okay</u>
<u n="864" who="S0192">but would you like to share?</u>
<u n="865" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="866" who="S0192">if I have a bit of yours</u>
<u n="867" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I think that's why it's good like this cos we can all share that</u>
<u n="868" who="S0190">would you like some potato this erm sag aloo?</u>
<u n="869" who="S0192">yeah I'll try a little bit <pause dur="short"/> it's really difficult to break those those boundaries though isn't it? to really look at it and think that's fine that right I still hear the the brummie accent and think that sounds awful</u>
<u n="870" who="S0227">I don't like the brummie accent</u>
<u n="871" who="S0192">no <pause dur="short"/> but what I'm saying to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is they've done studies into using foreigners and although we have a majority view of the the brummie accent</u>
<u n="872" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="873" who="S0192">as a people there's no real justification for that</u>
<u n="874" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="875" who="S0192">foreigners will listen to a variety of accents and they actually quite like the Birmingham accent there's nothing inherent within the sound that is negative</u>
<u n="876" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="877" who="S0192">it's purely our own negative connotation</u>
<u n="878" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="879" who="S0192" trans="overlap">through the society</u>
<u n="880" who="S0190">so what what is this one?</u>
<u n="881" who="S0192">this is a chicken jalfrezi</u>
<u n="882" who="S0190">but what is that hot?</u>
<u n="883" who="S0192">tomato bit of spice it's not well shall I try it and then I'll let you know?</u>
<u n="884" who="S0190">yeah what's yours like?</u>
<u n="885" who="S0227">erm <pause dur="short"/> erm I can't remember lamb something or other</u>
<u n="886" who="S0190">no that's chicken that's never lamb that's chicken that's lamb isn't it?</u>
<u n="887" who="S0227">I I've got a bit of either</u>
<u n="888" who="S0192">I think they're both chicken in here</u>
<u n="889" who="S0190">oh are they?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0192">yeah they're both chicken</u>
<u n="891" who="S0190">oh right</u>
<u n="892" who="S0192">let's see how spicy it is</u>
<u n="893" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh of course <trunc>y</trunc>yeah that's chicken yeah</u>
<u n="894" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah I was saying they don't look sort of</u>
<u n="895" who="S0227">well it's chicken it's er like chicken on the bone</u>
<u n="896" who="S0190">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="897" who="S0192">erm just <pause dur="long"/> medium medium spice</u>
<u n="898" who="S0190">right okay</u>
<u n="899" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah I would say</u>
<u n="900" who="S0227">right well</u>
<u n="901" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I'll eat mine</u>
<u n="902" who="S0192">please take some naan I can't eat the whole thing</u>
<u n="903" who="S0190">no I'm fine thank you <pause dur="short"/> it's you for the naan</u>
<u n="904" who="S0192">it's interesting how words have changed over time as well <pause dur="short"/> they've either ameliorated or</u>
<u n="905" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="906" who="S0192">yeah very strange</u>
<u n="907" who="S0227">we don't use the words like betwixt no er begat</u>
<u n="908" who="S0192">we used to have other pronouns like thee thine</u>
<u n="909" who="S0190">thy</u>
<u n="910" who="S0227" trans="overlap">like thou</u>
<u n="911" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no we don't use them anymore thou yeah</u>
<u n="912" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="913" who="S0192">they're only really used now in religious ceremonies</u>
<u n="914" who="S0227">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="915" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they don't really use them otherwise can I have a bit of yours?</u>
<u n="916" who="S0227">yeah go ahead see <unclear/></u>
<u n="917" who="S0192">I mean about <pause dur="short"/> I think about forty percent of our of our lexicon is Norman</u>
<u n="918" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0192">of French origin</u>
<u n="920" who="S0227">mm well it's dispersed</u>
<u n="921" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="922" who="S0227">it's like French words are like cul de sac erm</u>
<u n="923" who="S0192">but our grammar is still more Germanic</u>
<u n="924" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="925" who="S0192">we are of the proto indo European age it's very strange to think that our language is directly connected to India we're of the same language family</u>
<u n="926" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="927" who="S0192">which I find very strange</u>
<u n="928" who="S0227">you have er a bungalow er keep these are these are erm Indian words</u>
<u n="929" who="S0192">mm</u>
<u n="930" who="S0227">you know in our language</u>
<u n="931" who="S0192">yeah it's quite good</u>
<u n="932" who="S0227">erm you a lot of people</u>
<u n="933" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that's not because it's of the same family though</u>
<u n="934" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="935" who="S0192">that's cos we've colonised er</u>
<u n="936" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> people when they say the Houses of Parliament don't realise that <foreign lang="fre">parler</foreign> is the French word for</u>
<u n="937" who="S0192" trans="overlap">to speak</u>
<u n="938" who="S0227" trans="overlap">for speak it comes from</u>
<u n="939" who="S0192">yeah Parliament</u>
<u n="940" who="S0227">Parliament <foreign lang="fre">parler</foreign> ment <foreign lang="fre">parler</foreign> yeah er it erm <pause dur="short"/> mayday mayday you know distress? comes from the French <foreign lang="fre">m'aidez</foreign></u>
<u n="941" who="S0192" trans="overlap">m'aidez</u>
<u n="942" who="S0227">help me <foreign lang="fre">pouvez-vous m'aidez</foreign> can you help me me help</u>
<u n="943" who="S0192"><foreign lang="fre">m'aidez</foreign> there's so many aren't there? there's</u>
<u n="944" who="S0227" trans="overlap">cos I couldn't understand it before was why a mayday a day in May was a distress</u>
<u n="945" who="S0192">m'aidez</u>
<u n="946" who="S0227">then it made perfect sense</u>
<u n="947" who="S0192">help me</u>
<u n="948" who="S0227">help me yeah</u>
<u n="949" who="S0192">I do find etymology quite interesting <pause dur="short"/> where's the word come from?</u>
<u n="950" who="S0227">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="951" who="S0192">sometimes we don't know we just don't know</u>
<u n="952" who="S0227" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> the fact that you find language interesting is what will will help you er excel in it because you</u>
<u n="953" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I couldn't do a masters if I didn't find it interesting</u>
<u n="954" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="955" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you know <unclear/> it's a bit strange actually to think now if I get now I'm studying a masters I am effectively a linguist</u>
<u n="956" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="957" who="S0192">it's a bit weird to think that</u>
<u n="958" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="959" who="S0192">suddenly I'm a linquist <vocal desc="laugh"/> what's weird as well is when you tell people you're a linguist they go oh how many languages do you speak?</u>
<u n="960" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="961" who="S0192">but actually quite a few linguists don't speak a variety</u>
<u n="962" who="S0227">they just speak their own <unclear/></u>
<u n="963" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we can understand language</u>
<u n="964" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="965" who="S0192">and we can break down language</u>
<u n="966" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="967" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but you can't necessarily speak a variety of languages</u>
<u n="968" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="969" who="S0192">however I feel like if I am a linguist then I should be able to speak a few languages</u>
<u n="970" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="971" who="S0192">I want to at least be able to speak French and Spanish</u>
<u n="972" who="S0227">yeah <pause dur="short"/> apparently if you're <trunc>ed</trunc>educated you know English educated you speak French that's the language you speak</u>
<u n="973" who="S0192">don't how much French there is though in English</u>
<u n="974" who="S0227">erm I was discussing with your brother because he was you know coming up with a few Spanish words that he'd learnt while he was over there</u>
<u n="975" who="S0192">oh that's good</u>
<u n="976" who="S0227">and he was <trunc>try</trunc> he was trying to</u>
<u n="977" who="S0192">he's <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> <foreign lang="spa">estás estudiando al cuenta</foreign>?</u>
<u n="978" who="S0227">say again?</u>
<u n="979" who="S0192"><foreign lang="spa">estás estudiando al cuenta</foreign>?</u>
<u n="980" who="S0227">er no not at the moment no</u>
<u n="981" who="S0192">no? <foreign lang="spa">por que no?</foreign></u>
<u n="982" who="S0227">erm <pause dur="short"/> I'm studying French <pause dur="short"/> took me a while for my brain to transpose it</u>
<u n="983" who="S0192">I spoke very good French</u>
<u n="984" who="S0227">yeah yes you did but erm more importantly I did understand you</u>
<u n="985" who="S0192">my Spanish is very quickly going erm</u>
<u n="986" who="S0227">sorry?</u>
<u n="987" who="S0192">I'm very quickly losing my Spanish</u>
<u n="988" who="S0227">yes if you don't use it hence that's why I don't speak it <pause dur="short"/> so erm in everyday language so it took me a while to transpose what you'd said</u>
<u n="989" who="S0192">you have to have some respect for translators somebody that can sit there <pause dur="short"/> listen to what's being said <pause dur="short"/> and they they're translating about five to ten seconds later</u>
<u n="990" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="991" who="S0192">so they're talking or writing while they're hearing what's being said</u>
<u n="992" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="993" who="S0192">they have to not only translate but work out <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's all sorts of semantic issues of how to change that into that I mean German is very difficult quite often Germans are the final language so the verb the predicate the most important part of a sentence comes right at the end of a sentence</u>
<u n="994" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="995" who="S0192">so you've gotta listen to the whole sentence</u>
<u n="996" who="S0227">before you know what it is</u>
<u n="997" who="S0192" trans="overlap">before you know what it's about</u>
<u n="998" who="S0227">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="999" who="S0192">and yet they've gotta translate and they're doing it very you know potentially you know there are some very precarious scenarios</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0192">and they can't mistranslate this because</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0227" trans="overlap">they have to be aware er er a sentence produced wrong could maybe</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0192" trans="overlap">could start a war</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0227">yeah exactly yeah</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0192">so it's I I have a lot of respect for that job</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0227" trans="overlap">kind of I have no pressure no pressure there then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="1007" who="S0192">it's good though it's tasty</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0190">that'll be yours</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0227">yeah is yours alright? <pause dur="long"/> please have a bit of ours <pause dur="short"/> erm too big</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0190">I've got half of a load of rice there</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I'm gonna struggle now I'll let you</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah I'll</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0192" trans="overlap">can I nick a bit?</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0227">no I'm fine mm got mange tout</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0192">I'll take it home then <pause dur="long"/> yeah the more I study grammar the deeper it seems to get doesn't seem to be an end to it at the moment</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0227"><trunc>r</trunc> for that food you're taking home one food I never ever want to try again would be er er kimbap</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0192">oh you didn't like it?</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0227">oh no</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it grows on you it grows on you</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no it wouldn't grow on me</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0192">he didn't like that at all I took him to a couple of restaurants that were like</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh I know he didn't yeah</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and he was like</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0190">no I said to him well what's so how did you get on with the food did you enjoy it? as I say he's not a fish lover either</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0190">so it's just quite <unclear/></u>
<u n="1028" who="S0227">was it not <unclear/>? we went there twice</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0192">of course dad wants to go to a fast food burger restaurant <pause dur="long"/> we were in Brighton and he kept going where's McDonald's?</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0190">oh he's right if you don't have a McDonald's it's not he has to have a McDonald's in erm you didn't <event desc="unintelligible"/> Barcelona</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0192">oh god really?</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0227">only like cos er I had the snack not for your main meal</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0192" trans="overlap">the main no of course</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0227">no not for your main meal</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0192">of course you bring shame to the name</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0227">if you want a <trunc>fi</trunc> <trunc>fi</trunc> <trunc>fa</trunc> food fix it's erm great with that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1038" who="S0192">I must admit I have a bit of a I do like their McFlurry</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0190">yeah I do</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0190">about the only thing I do like</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0192">every so often <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I go in for a McFlurry <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1043" who="S0227">now which one's the really hot one? I can't remember one of them's really quite</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0192">spicy <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1045" who="S0190">yours and that you ordered</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0192">I'm not surprised he didn't like Kimbap it is seaweed wrapped rice with a bit of crabstick in the middle and some maybe some tuna or something else <pause dur="short"/> can you believe I was eating it though?</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0192">I would never have eaten that stuff if it</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0227">you liked it</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0192">yeah I do like it I still like it today the tuna's the best one <pause dur="short"/> at first I kept trying to have the beef one but it was terrible</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0192">not very good <pause dur="long"/> you'll never get me eating shellfish though</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0227">really?</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0192">er well it's horrible</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0190">crab's a shellfish</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0192">no I don't like crabs</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0190">oh right</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0192">that that bit of crabstick in in the Kimbap I I don't really taste it so I can</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0227" trans="overlap">they're lost in the process</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I'm fine with that but I've had have you ever had soft shell crab? like where you eat the whole crab pincers legs everything? it's not as soft shelled as they make out it was like eating a cockroach</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0227">yeah oh</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it was just crunch crunch crunch</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh no I couldn't eat the shell</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0192">it was horrible that was my first meal in Korea they took us to this fancy restaurant and they were right so all like and of course I'm around a lot actually <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> paid for a lot for me I just thought I don't wanna look like erm so I just ate the thing</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0190">oh</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0192">it was horrible <pause dur="short"/> I gagged so much that first year</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0190"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1068" who="S0192">I really really did</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0227">some of the stuff you had to eat yeah</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0192">I had dog twice</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0227">oh no</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0192" trans="overlap">liver kidneys dog liver dog kidneys</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0190">oh yeah I can eat</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0192">I had dog tail</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0190">do you remember what was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> saying? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> that he was erm when he went out with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they had pigs ears</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0227">yes pigs ears they didn't like them that that was a sheep</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0190">it was no it was a <trunc>donk</trunc> no I threw them out</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and I've I erm my coaches used to take me out for pig face soup</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0227">what?</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0192">pig face</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0227">oh</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0192">and the first time I had it an eye and an eyebrow floated up I had an eyebrow in my soup</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0227">oh oh my god</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0192">actually pig face soup's quite nice I I then later had with the same coaches pig trotters which was horrible <pause dur="short"/> the trotter was just like the cartilage lump</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it was like white and it really was and then even worse than that he took me for pig skin soup <pause dur="short"/> so it was just the skin and I like a bit of crackling and a nice bit of roasted skin or something but this was just rubbery</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0227">like like like like</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah all the skin yeah</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah like the skin</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0192">it wasn't very nice <pause dur="short"/> so pig face soup was actually one of the lesser of my evils to er</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0227">I don't think I could eat that cos it's expensive</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0227">no I'm sure we could <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1093" who="S0192">I've had worse out there have you have you ever eaten jellyfish?</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0192">that's not particularly nice</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0227">no <pause dur="long"/> oh no</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0192">it's the shellfish that really gets me did you hear mum got stung by a weever fish?</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0227">your mum did?</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0227">when? in Spain?</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0192" trans="overlap">when she went to Devon with</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0227" trans="overlap">in in Devon?</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0192" trans="overlap">with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0227" trans="overlap">how did she get well had she <trunc>ge</trunc> had she been down recently?</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0192">yeah I think they went not long ago have you ever heard of a weever fish?</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0227">yes yes</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah oh yeah</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0192">they're quite bad apparently</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes it's er it's a fish that's erm <pause dur="short"/> that's on the bottom but it's on the floor so it's got spikes you'd have to step on it not swim</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0192">it was on her bum</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0227">oh</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0227">oh god I pity the thought of the person who had to suck the poison out</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0192">she was telling <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to he was like no no</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0227">ah she sat on it oh did she have to go to hospital with it?</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0192">I can't remember she said it was really painful for a few days she's broken her foot actually</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0227">what?</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0190">at the moment?</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0192">yeah she's been like that for like the last couple of months</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0227">I tried to I passed her <trunc>to</trunc></u>
<u n="1121" who="S0192" trans="overlap">she broke her toe</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0192">she'd got it bandaged up you should see it she's like she's still getting about because there's nothing she can really do about it but</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes I I drove past her on the way to pick you up she must have been picking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> up I mean I tooted my horn and she realised it was me <pause dur="short"/> and I was coming to get you so er oh right so how when did she break her toe?</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0192">the same trip <pause dur="short"/> you know on the pebbly beach?</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0227">no I don't</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0192">she fell down those really steep steps <pause dur="short"/> she really hurt herself like proper cut her leg open</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0227">oh</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0192">and broke her toe <pause dur="short"/> her big toe as well</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0227">ouch</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0192">and of course having <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she can't really rest to like</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0192">had she rested her foot <event desc="unintelligible"/> oh this <unclear/> is building</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0227">yes yes <anon type="place"/> remember that?</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0192">no I haven't been to <anon type="place"/> since</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0227">I know</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0192">you guys split up a don't think</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0227">no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1139" who="S0192">I still have loose contact with grandad I always liked grandad</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0227">yeah did he remarry?</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0192">well he's not married he'd with a lady called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1142" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0192">she's nice but mum was a bit iffy about seeing her for quite a bit <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't want anything to do with him anymore</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0192">now I met her pretty much as soon as I <trunc>star</trunc> I never er really had a problem with her but</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0190" trans="overlap">why will <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> not see her?</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0192">I don't know</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0227">I don't think she was a great <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1149" who="S0192" trans="overlap">well it's cos she's a <trunc>fu</trunc> she's a funny one</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0227">I mean that was that was no er erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> not wanting to see to see your see your grandad again was no problem for him whatsoever they never really got it <trunc>o</trunc> they never really hit it off <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1151" who="S0192">she claims that it's because she came out as being gay and he didn't want anything to do with her <pause dur="short"/> but mum said it was just convenient for both them really</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0190">no <pause dur="short"/> my erm father's mother my grandmother erm <pause dur="short"/> lost her husband when my dad was he was only fifty-two not my dad my erm my grandfather <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so my grandmother she died when she was ninety-eight so she had all nearly a half of her life on her own but she became quite friendly with she lived she lived next door to her sister and she's got like a <trunc>broth</trunc> two younger brothers that lived with her as as well and after a while she got friendly with this gentleman who's had also lost his wife and they used to erm go to each other's houses for for a meal you know and she'd say oh come and have come back and have some tea or something and meant it as like a social <unclear>club</unclear> her brothers and sisters or her own <trunc>chil</trunc> but he couldn't they wouldn't accept him</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0192">oh why?</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0190">and you just think how can you be so awful for a woman who lost her husband?</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0192">she needs to move move she needs someone</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0190">he needs she needs someone and you think there was absolutely nothing more to it than just companionship</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0192">and even if there was and if there's been a period of mourning</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0192">and time has moved on</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0227">I was gonna say I <trunc>ha</trunc></u>
<u n="1162" who="S0192">you can't be alone for the rest of life you can't</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0192">I mean if you're gonna do that you might as well sati the Indian style and throw yourself on the funeral pyre</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0227">and and as well yeah</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well if that's what you do and my sister's doing fine erm sixteen years now on her own <pause dur="short"/> when she lost her husband <pause dur="short"/> but that's she's quite happy she doesn't feel it so we respect that and we don't push her into relationships and things but if somebody chooses that wants to do it then <pause dur="short"/> people don't have the right to <pause dur="short"/> well to be unkind I think it is</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0192">no I agree</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0227">plus it's not like she with your grandad must have to have this relationship with <unclear/> erm</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0227">you know</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0192">I am stuffed</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0227" trans="overlap">your mum really <pause dur="short"/> once yeah there'd been a a period of mourning <pause dur="short"/> should have been <pause dur="short"/> quite you know you accept it cos you know if you have any what you expect him to do but than build to build a shrine for him and live life like a hermit</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0192">yeah no that's why I didn't have a problem with it at all</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0192" trans="overlap">wouldn't you rather he be happy?</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0192">it must be hard enough that he's lost his his love of his life</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0227">yeah that's right yeah</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0192">his other half I can't imagine what that must be like to <pause dur="long"/> of course there should be period of er</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh yes and I I'm sure your grandad <pause dur="short"/> he really did have you know so</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean he didn't force her anyone I think hopefully he was quite pleased that I was happy to see her immediately</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0192">I I actually made an effort to say I wanted to see her and</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah fine yeah</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I wanted to chat and so</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well yeah</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0192">I think I met her in my second year of <anon type="place"/> at uni</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0192">so I met her very early</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0192">I mean she's not my nan I don't know who she is really but</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0192" trans="overlap">she's making my grandad happy so therefore</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1197" who="S0227">by by proxy yes <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="1198" who="S0192">but I'm not I don't have such strong emotional ties to people anyway so</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0192">it's difficult it's it's difficult to say it's some people are very emotionally tied up</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0227">yes see I think that your mum and her sister would have been you know <pause dur="short"/> it would have been <pause dur="short"/> just but not you know insurmountable</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0192">not impossible</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0227">not insurmountable no</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0190">well <trunc>do</trunc> and again it to me it's part of if you care for someone you do things to try and things that they</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0192">for them <trunc>ra</trunc></u>
<u n="1207" who="S0190">yeah for them and things that they they like and if you've got your you're going to make things uncomfortable then <pause dur="short"/> well to me I just it's it's</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's what humility and selflessness is</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0192">turning round and going okay I feel this but I can play this down because</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0192">my feelings don't outweigh your happiness</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0190">that's right definitely that's right</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0227">there's erm although <pause dur="short"/> there are fixes it seems does does your mum still have some kind of communication? I'd imagine</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0192">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0227" trans="overlap">there's some become</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so because she went down recently so they met up with him then</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh is she stayed there then?</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no no no nobody stays with them</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0192">as far as I know</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0227">but</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0192" trans="overlap">well it's the shame because it's the only way I could go and visit him is if he allowed me to stay with him</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0227">right yes</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0192">but I don't know if the offer is there or what</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0192">I'm sure it would be <pause dur="short"/> I mean he is is a fairly private guy wasn't it?</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0227">yeah he was always private yeah</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0192">you can respect that so he'd jar people</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0227">yes probably</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0192">he probably struggled it's so difficulty within our family because we're not a private family</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0227">no no I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s completely disappeared of the radar the only people that have seen him would be his</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah in our house in our house now as well basically all the men</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0192">just disappeared you've disappeared from my family very much</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah mm</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0192">as I said the <pause dur="short"/> cousins still ask after you</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0227">I <trunc>sh</trunc> thinks when when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> draw drew his side on which side he was gonna fall he towed the line on that and said you're next <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1239" who="S0192">oh am I? it's just a matter of time</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0227" trans="overlap">think think think on your position cos you're next</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0192">oh it's him that's reacting poorly now</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0192">the erm he's not building any <trunc>tu</trunc></u>
<u n="1244" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no he</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0192" trans="overlap">he has grandchildren right and he's got</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0192">he's he he ignored <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the supermarket</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes I <trunc>sai</trunc>said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about that erm <pause dur="short"/> with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he he's had the moral high ground cos his daughters actually were were <unclear>well</unclear> like to be on side of he's gone and and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was a pariah the the the fact that she's wanting to do things and he has done absolutely nothing they've gone loads of those <unclear/></u>
<u n="1249" who="S0192">the problem is when you have another half that is very demanding and</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0227" trans="overlap">and influences you yeah for a time</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and I guess from his perspective he thinks well I've done this part of my life and I need to it's all about me now <pause dur="short"/> and she's she's not giving him room to have both and he's being weak so he's he's</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah I thought a near death experience might have yes brought him closer to his family but</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0192" trans="overlap">maybe it pushed him further away rather than pushed him</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh yeah I think</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0192">it it seems to</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0227">it it does seem an interesting</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0192" trans="overlap">come in dear tuck in</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0227">I'm full up it does seem an interesting</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0192" trans="overlap">full? are we sure?</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0227">yeah it does seem an interesting erm reclamation that erm if you're gonna get the <pause dur="long"/> your grandmother's erm generation and then you move down to the daughters <pause dur="short"/> all the men were apart well I'd say certain <trunc>s</trunc> no cos we said were moved out because er your mum always talked about her nan <pause dur="short"/> she never talked about her grandfather ever</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no erm I don't hear much about him and I also</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0227" trans="overlap">what who was he did he exist? he must have been there for some some brief time moment in time <pause dur="short"/> so that's that was interesting</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0192">go on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have a small bit of that cake</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0190">no I can't I</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="1265" who="S0192">go on you can do it</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I'm gonna have a tiny bit but I'm quite I'm quite I am quite full</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0192" trans="overlap">a little bit there it's just a little bit look I I've done a good job on there actually see the trick is can you do it with one hand?</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0192">you can't use both</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0227">no I can't</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0192">if you're in India you can't use both</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0190">why not?</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0192">they this is</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0227">one hand for the toilet one hand for the</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0192">so you take the naan and rip it with your hand and eat out of it</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0192">you can't use two</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0227" trans="overlap">that's why in Who Do You Think You Are? they anything with the families was considered erm impolite</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0192">it took a while to get <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1280" who="S0227">oh go on</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no thank you</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0192">it's also very messy as well I mean certain parts of India I ate curry with my hand</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah we were watching it on the television when they were travelling around yeah</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0227" trans="overlap">southern India</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0192">yeah southern India</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh like yeah you <trunc>ge</trunc> I</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0192">you get it on a banana leaf</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0192">you get the banana leaf and then you get all your stuff and then you have a little bowl of water to wash your hand in and</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0227">yeah and then you throw the leaf in</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0192">it's I mean it's tasty the around there they argue that half of the flavour is in the texture and I mean to an certain degree when I eat an apple you know half of you know I enjoy holding it and I enjoy eating it so I I can understand that to a certain <trunc>degr</trunc> you wouldn't wanna eat a burger with a knife and fork would you? it would just be weird</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0192">part of the process is holding it</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0192">and eating it so they just feel the same about eating curry <pause dur="short"/> but it is a very messy affair it's not like a burger</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I don't think it's very yeah a burger's dry</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0192">so it takes some getting used to to to be a</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0227">and also it can't be too hot either can it?</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0192">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1302" who="S0227">if that's in your hand</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0190">but don't you find that? that the only fault that I've had <pause dur="short"/> with this restaurant <pause dur="short"/> is that the food is not piping hot</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0192">it's not no well</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0227">didn't it come on hot trays?</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0227">it's er it's still for hot</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0192">I mean Korean food quite often comes out in a ceramic clay pot still bubbling and you'll get it out and it'll bubble for another couple of minutes while it's sitting it's actually kind of tedious because you want it</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0192">and you have to wait for it to stop bubbling and then another few you know five minutes longer <trunc>befo</trunc></u>
<u n="1311" who="S0190" trans="overlap">the two or three dishes they brought out you can hear them sizzling in the pot when they bring them</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0192">I guess they do that to prove that it's been cooked here and now and it it's</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yes it's er what's the word? er is it a la carte?</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0192">no <pause dur="short"/> there's quite a few</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0227">erm</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0192">food options in Korea as well</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0192">that are cold have you ever had cold noodles?</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0227">no I haven't</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0192">it's very strange</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0227">is it quite rubbery?</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0192">it's called <foreign lang="kor">Naengmyeon</foreign> <pause dur="short"/> erm it's actually in North Korean South Korea actually <pause dur="short"/> it really took me a while to get used to it it's a nice broth the broth's like a beefy kind of broth but it's cold glass noodles er vermicelli erm with pear and it's got like bits of pear and bits of cucumber floating around in there and then just like and chunks of ice you've got like ice cubes and stuff</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh no I <trunc>do</trunc></u>
<u n="1324" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's very very strange</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh no I wouldn't that's like</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0192">it was never my favourite it's a summer food</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they'd eat it in the summer</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0227">your palate's definitely broader than ours</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but I never actually liked it</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0227">oh</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0192">I ate cos they give you a really big bowl of it</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0192">there's a lot of noodles in there</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0190">I don't like noodles</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0192">the first half was good I enjoyed the first half by the second half of the dish I'd be kind of like oh <pause dur="short"/> it becomes very repetitive and you tire</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0190">they don't have a lot of flavour though do they? <pause dur="short"/> as such but it's the what they no</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0192" trans="overlap">the noodles themselves don't no the noodles themselves don't <pause dur="short"/> have you ever had squid ink?</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0190">no I <trunc>haven</trunc> it's black isn't it?</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh oh yes yeah that's in Spain they have that</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0192">I've never tried it</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0227">no it</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0227">it looks it looks awful it's black kind of like the meal was black</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0190" trans="overlap">it's so</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0227">cos it's <pause dur="short"/> infused with the with the squid in and again</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0227">that really looks unappetising</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it looks unappealing yes we don't eat many things that are black do we? or what do you eat that's black?</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0227">er well it's normally</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0190" trans="overlap">olives</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0227">it's normally <trunc>boi</trunc> it's normally burnt isn't it if it's black?</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I don't trust black food generally</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0227">so black sausage</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0192">no I don't</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0190" trans="overlap">or black pudding</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0227">yeah that's what I mean black pudding</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0192">so there a couple of things</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I can eat that</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0192">is that black?</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I can eat <pause dur="short"/> it is quite black yeah the skin</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0227" trans="overlap">the outer bit is black</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0192" trans="overlap">is that with blood?</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0190">I yeah it's the actual cooked blood that's why it's black</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0227">like a <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1368" who="S0192">they have as similar dish in Korea called <foreign lang="kor">sundae</foreign> it's like kind of like <foreign lang="kor">kimbap</foreign> but instead of they don't have all the seaweed and all that stuff but it's that same kind of rice wrap wrap in a circle but they cut it in squares and inside it's rice mixed with pig's blood and like and stuff and then they cook them <pause dur="short"/> it's okay it's not great but I quite like blood</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0192" trans="overlap">cooked blood in</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0192">in soup is is great</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0227">we've certainly tried a <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1374" who="S0192">I like organs</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0227">I love <unclear>organs</unclear></u>
<u n="1376" who="S0192">liver's really good</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh I love liver and onions and bacon</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0192" trans="overlap">liver <event desc="unintelligible"/> it's tasty</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0227">yeah that was <unclear/> er it was one of them we go for is it lamb's or pig's?</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0190">I don't know</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0192">mm liver's good</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0227">lamb's liver is very very erm <pause dur="short"/> crumbly isn't it? can be and texture whereas the pig's liver's got a bit more body to it it depends</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0192">but it's how again isn't <pause dur="short"/> have you ever had brains?</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0190">yes</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0192">you have?</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0227">yeah I've eaten it at cookery in cookery class</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0192">I haven't never had brains</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0190">yeah it's erm</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0192">it's not like <unclear/> you know they were</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> what's it called? we don't call it brains do we?</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0227">faggots?</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0192">no that's that's</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no it's not faggots</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0227">brains <pause dur="short"/> I dunno another word for it</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0190">brawn <pause dur="short"/> brawn <pause dur="short"/> brawn in jelly it's brains in jelly it's brains it's</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0192">is it good?</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0190">yeah it's okay <pause dur="short"/> it's not as bad as you think it might be</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0192">gizzards another lovely one</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0190" trans="overlap">they did they don't have no I haven't had that</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0192">it's very common in Korea to eat er chickens' bottoms like the the <unclear>holes</unclear> for like</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0227">oh</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's kind of gross you get the</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0190">oh not what you mean</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0192">a whole plate of er rectum</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0190">oh</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah it's er</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0227">no I mean no that's</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you fry it up it's actually okay it's not</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's not though it's not like sort of something well evil</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no I don't believe you on that one</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh dear oh dear you've seen that's enough of that stuff</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they love it out there</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0190">well when the</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0192" trans="overlap">have you ever had chicken's feet?</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0192">you eat the feet</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0190">crispy yes</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0192">it's it's like <pause dur="short"/> very crunchy</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0227">they say you are what you eat and if you were a bit of a bit of an arsehole you're <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1423" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1424" who="S0192">sorry</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0190">oh god</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we eat any part of the animal right? you eat sausages and I'm sure they've got every part of the animal</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0190">well they were on Masterchef weren't they and they were cooking sausages and everything</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0192">oh gosh</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0190">oh god they</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh what like the kangaroo's ones?</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0192">oh</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0190">actually on Masterchef and it and he wasn't just like er well it's erm Get me Out of Here I'm a Celebrity sort of thing</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they're genuinely cooking</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0227">this was proper cooking yeah they were on the show don't you remember when there was?</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes I do yeah</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0190">plates of this?</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0227">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0192">why?</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0190">well why we eat everything else so why why distinguish? somebody had to to to eat a trotter didn't they?</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean okay but it</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0190">somebody had to eat the liver and the kidneys but have you ever had a heart?</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0190">have you had heart?</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0192">no I don't think I have had heart</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0190">nobody has I've had heart</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0227" trans="overlap">heart?</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah heart</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0192">unless I've kind of eaten it and didn't realised it that oh no I've had chicken hearts very small ones</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I've had I've had proper hearts stuffed my mum used to do that for my dad</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0227" trans="overlap">stuffed hearts yeah</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0192"><event desc="unintelligible"/> it's just <unclear/> isn't it so</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I think it's a</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0227" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0190">er I think it's a bit it's a cross between kidneys livers all that sort of thing trotters</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0192">offal <pause dur="short"/> I've had the tongue and I'd say it was really good</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0190">oh that</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0192">they cut here and had the hog roast like a piece of tongue or the mouth whereas it goes right down to the gullet</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0192">it was really tasty it was just like a piece of steak</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well yeah but you have tongue don't you a whole tongue like like ham yeah</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well a bit like yeah the hog tail</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0192">oxtail</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0190">that's lovely yeah</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0192">there's all sorts of odd things</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I love oxtail soup</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0192">I mean there is no distinction is there?</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0190">well that's what I was <trunc>say</trunc></u>
<u n="1475" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean it's just whatever is whatever</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0190" trans="overlap">it's because we just look at things and think</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it tasted of wine</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0190">mm are you <event desc="unintelligible"/>? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1479" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I know that's one thing I think I'd be like I mean have they brained them?</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0190"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1482" who="S0192">you know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1483" who="S0227">oh oh god</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0192">sorry to go into detail but</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1486" who="S0227">you could be eating our own children</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0192">exactly</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0227">your so your own brothers and sisters</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0227">oh god <vocal desc="laugh"/> that kind of reminds me</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0190" trans="overlap">we don't eat human things do you it's</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no no it's</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="1494" who="S0227">well if you watch Hannibal of all <event desc="unintelligible"/> there was an interesting erm okay it's fictitious but there's some interesting</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I imagine <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't like that</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0227">scene with erm do know like Eddie Izzard?</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0192">yes yes he's in quite a bit suddenly yeah</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes where erm he's it's the last supper</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0192">oh he's eating himself is he?</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0227">yeah the last supper yes that was interesting</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0227">cos he had no option really did he?</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0192">if you don't like some of the other things don't watch if you don't like and Hannibal is a bit <unclear/></u>
<u n="1504" who="S0190">no quite a lot of them erm that's why I have my own room with my own television in and I</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0192" trans="overlap">Hannibal is extreme but it's quite tastefully done at the same time</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's quite clever yeah</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0192">but it is extreme <pause dur="short"/> I mean very unbelievable extremely unbelievable</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0227">which Hannibal have you watched and seen as in erm Anthony Hopkins?</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0227">playing Hannibal Lecter? the Hannibal you're presented with is the man who's got caught and</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0227">all you're seeing is his ability to manipulate</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0192">I'm interested to see how the new Hannibal is once he's been caught</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0192">how <trunc>wh</trunc>?</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0227" trans="overlap">because the Hannibal you see in in Hannibal is the man who's not been caught</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0192" trans="overlap">charismatic</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0227">and you're seeing his charisma</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0192" trans="overlap">his culture and education</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0227" trans="overlap">his culture his education to be honest <pause dur="short"/> he comes over as being completely sane but clearly</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0192">too sane</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0227">yeah but clearly he's not</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0192" trans="overlap">much too sane</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0227">yeah it it's</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it is quite good</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0227">it is clever yeah</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean it's it's quite enough</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0227" trans="overlap">but it's gory but it's clever</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0192" trans="overlap">have you seen have you seen Rome?</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0227">sorry?</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0192">Rome</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0192">I think maybe you'd like that certainly the first season of Rome is excellent it's really really good whoever the guy the actor that plays Caesar is fantastic</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0227">oh</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0192">absolutely fantastic it's the story of erm Caesar's rise to power after Gaul and the</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0227" trans="overlap">you mean Julius Caesar?</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0192">yeah and then yeah not Octavia or</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0227">yeah right</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0192">erm and then <pause dur="short"/> erm Mark Antony has his side and then he eventually being stabbed by Brutus and Othello</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0227">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0192" trans="overlap">the senate and that kind of stuff</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's it's really very well acted it's all British actors and it's it's really quite it's very really well acted <pause dur="short"/> a little gory in places</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0190">no it's not that</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and a little sexual in places but it's not</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0190">if it's in</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0192" trans="overlap">there's not much swearing</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0190">part of the story as and again it's part of it I don't if it's when every other word's a swear word</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0192">yeah no I</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0190" trans="overlap">or it's just so</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I agree</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0190">certain language and certain things and I think just I just don't believe they should be on</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0227" trans="overlap">in</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I I'm quite <trunc>decen</trunc></u>
<u n="1555" who="S0227" trans="overlap">in Hannibal there is no swearing is there?</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0192">not a lot</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0227">no not <trunc>rea</trunc> and there's certainly not coming</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well Hannibal is so far fetched it's unbelievable</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's it's certainly not</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0192" trans="overlap">Hannibal is very slow</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0192">it's really slow paced</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> watched about</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's very very slow</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0227">fifteen minutes of the first one and made her mind up on the strength of that</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0190" trans="overlap">that was enough yeah</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah okay</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0227">which is is</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0192">well try Rome I'd recommend it</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's not into character developments</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it it kick started this out the <unclear>water</unclear> it's of a similar vein and was made</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0192">at the same time</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but it's just much much better acted</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0192">I was really quite engrossed in the first season I'm watching the second season now and since erm Julius Caesar has died I think it's lost a lot bit that actor was very good</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0192">er <pause dur="short"/> actually he's in Game of Thrones the man that plays Caesar which</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0227">which part did he play?</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0192">well he's one of the guys on the wall that dies quite early</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0227">oh right so he's</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah you'd recognise him if you saw him but</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0227" trans="overlap">right yeah</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0192">but he's such he's such a good Caesar</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0227" trans="overlap">right yeah</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0192">the character is really good I really really liked him <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0227">I'm <trunc>lo</trunc>looking forward to Hannibal the next</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0192" trans="overlap">the third</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0227" trans="overlap">the season three</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0227">it's season three they've got obviously they have to catch him at some time</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0192">yes well season four is Red Dragon</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0192">Manhunter</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0192">season five is Silence of the Lambs season six is Hannibal</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0192">season seven is <unclear/> so we've got one more season of his own division</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0192">and then it's going to follow more closely it's obviously gonna deviate quite dramatically from erm</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0192">but erm</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0227">they said he was when he was with Jodie Foster er Anthony Hopkins right he was caught <pause dur="short"/> he was he all you saw of him was his his his manipulation and not any of those other the</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no the characteristics</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0227" trans="overlap">and I say l like the actor Mads Mikkelsen cos he plays he's so cultured that's the trouble he is immaculate his cooking he's a he's like a Michelin style equivalent</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0192">what is that dish I've come across it a couple of times with that bird that use the very small bird and then they soak it in er alcohol and they set fire to the it's like a foetus of a bird and and then they eat the thing whole they do it <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0227">yeah I can't remember what it's called</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's kind of famous like</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I it was <unclear>referenced</unclear> or something else</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes always trying meals from all over the world but</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0192">yeah right</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0227">the the thing with him is I <trunc>th</trunc> his clothing he's always immaculate</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0192" trans="overlap">his outfits</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0227">he's immaculately dressed yeah he's he's he never has anything out of place he's <trunc>ver</trunc></u>
<u n="1617" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but that makes him very suspicious</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0227">yes he's very meticulous er</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0192">he is unbelievable yeah he's unbelievable</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah he is too good to be</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0190" trans="overlap">the whole series is just totally</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0227" trans="overlap">he's too</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah I</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0227" trans="overlap">he's too good to be true</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0192">oh oh and the the most jarring thing for me in that season is especially the first season there's a different serial killer in every <trunc>ev</trunc>every episode and yet they don't ever have to drive more than five miles to <trunc>fi</trunc></u>
<u n="1626" who="S0227" trans="overlap">they're always home grown aren't they?</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they just happen to have</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0227">yeah home grown</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0192">twenty serial killers or</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0227" trans="overlap">who live in about a two hundred mile radius yeah I mean</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0192">it's entertaining</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0227">although</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's very grotesque</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0227">although</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0192">and the dialogue's good and I like dialogue so</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0227">they they they reckon that there are point one percent of the population are serial killers which means there are three hundred in the States at any time</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><event desc="sound of restaurant"/> not psychopaths psychopaths they reckon in er in in in America there's about erm</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0192" trans="overlap">anyone would be</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0227" trans="overlap">to about thirty million</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0192">point one I mean if there's three hundred million people</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0192">one percent would be three million</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0192">point one percent would be</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0227">three <trunc>hun</trunc></u>
<u n="1647" who="S0192">thirty thousand</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0227">oh oh is it nought point one? er how many noughts have you got to take off? er nought <trunc>p</trunc></u>
<u n="1649" who="S0192" trans="overlap">regardless</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0227">one hold it one</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0192" trans="overlap">let's just say there's about three hundred</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah there's three hundred</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's easier yeah</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0227" trans="overlap">there's about three hundred</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0192">cos if there's about three hundred million people</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0227">cos I'm thinking one percent of three hundred million is</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0192">is three hundred</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0227">three million</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0192">so</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0227">isn't it?</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0192">point one percent of three million isn't three hundred</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's for the no so it's point nought point one percent yeah which they no nought point nought nought one percent</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we're getting into maths now aren't we? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1668" who="S0192">yeah nought point nought nought one percent yeah</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0227" trans="overlap">how's your maths then?</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0190">diabolical</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0227">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1673" who="S0190">absolutely diabolical</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0192" trans="overlap">mine too</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0227">yeah it's</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's as long I can do quick calculations</u>
<u n="1677" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">have you all finished?</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0190">yes we have thank you very much</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0192">are we having dessert?</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0190">oh well</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0227">yeah we'll so have a look on the dessert tray if you like</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's his birthday we're gonna have a <event desc="sound of restaurant"/> mine is a will be a cigarette I think</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0190" trans="overlap">how can you find a space?</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0227">yeah I know it's pretty I'm pretty full <pause dur="short"/> well you might as well look at the menu you're not ruling anything you're not</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0192" trans="overlap">are we <trunc>want</trunc> sorry are we wanting to take the leftovers will you eat it later?</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0227">no I won't no</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0192">no?</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0227">no unless you want it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1691" who="S0192">it seems such a waste</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0227">very nice thank you</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0190">it was lovely</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0192" trans="overlap">thank you very much</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0227">yes thank you</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0190">eyes bigger than our tummies</u>
<u n="1697" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1698" who="S0190">having a starter as well</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0192"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1700" who="S0227">the lesson is don't order too much but we always do every time <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1701" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1702" who="S0192">terrible</u>
<u n="1703" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1704" who="S0227">it's a bit <trunc>diffi</trunc> if it had Mads Mikkelson in I <unclear>wouldn't</unclear> probably watch it</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0227">erm because he does play the part erm and what's his name? who's his <trunc>pr</trunc> protagonist? erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1707" who="S0192">oh the name of the</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0227" trans="overlap">what's his name? his his character name what is it? erm it's amazing how quickly you forget</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0192">watch too many things I don't remember his character's name but I know who you're talking about</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0192">he frames him doesn't he?</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0227">yes he frames him and then wants to get him off cos he's basically showing how clever he is</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0192">and then they're they've been <unclear/></u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="1714" who="S0227">like I said it's cleverly done</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0192">are you having another drink? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would you like another drink?</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0227">yeah I'll have one if you have one</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0190" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0227">do you want J2O this time?</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0190">I don't know whether I want to drink or if I have an ice cream I won't want a drink <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1720" who="S0227">can we have another couple of Cobras please?</u>
<u n="1721" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah of course two pint of Cobras?</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0192">it's</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0227">did I say Cobra? Cobra</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0190">Cobra <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1725" who="S0192">Cobra Cobra the animal</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0190">it's obviously quite strong you know it is</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's <trunc>n</trunc> no I was I it</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0190" trans="overlap">there you go he did see it</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0192" trans="overlap">he said Cobra earlier</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0227">yeah it's</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I'm probably just gonna go for a beer</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah there's there's <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1733" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no I just let if we can have a look please if you're not I know you're not you're</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that looks brilliant doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0227">it is I mean it the American</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that strawberry fluff cake oh that looks good actually <pause dur="short"/> so does that they all look</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I was gonna say they do yeah I know so clever</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0192" trans="overlap">what will you go for?</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0190">I don't know that I really want anything else it would just be</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0192">oh go on</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0190">yeah but I suffer for it you know if you overeat</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0192" trans="overlap">should we get one to share?</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0227">yes have one to share go on get one</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0192">what would you go for? what would you recommend?</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0190">oh</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0227">I'd go for that one</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I really like the mango yeah</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0192" trans="overlap">well it's your birthday so</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah I'd I'd choose that one if</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so shall we share a mango?</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0227">okay yeah erm that there I I can <event desc="sound of shouting"/> we in English</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0192">well you're pronouncing it the Spanish way Cobra</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0227">yeah Americans would say Cobra but we would say Cobra Cobra</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0192">so the <unclear/> you'd say Cobra not</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no I would be say <trunc>Cob</trunc> I would be say Cobra</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I'd probably I I'd call it a Cobra</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I <trunc>sa</trunc> I say Cobra</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0190">yeah I say Cobra</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0227" trans="overlap">Cobra yeah yeah maybe</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0192">I think I think you're</u>
<u n="1761" who="S0190" trans="overlap">it's the same as scone and scone</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0192">I think you're attributing Spanish maybe even French pronunciation</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0227">yeah Cobra</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0192">in Spanish I would say Cobra</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0192">or Cobra</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0227">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0192">but in English I say Cobra</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0227"><trunc>Co</trunc></u>
<u n="1770" who="S0192">Cobra and America would sort of say Cobra</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0190">Cobra</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0192">Cobra that would work</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0227">there's a</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1775" who="S0227">there's a erm</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1777" who="S0227">he's</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it is I've studied phonetics and it is named more names</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0192">they use more names and they use more words if I say ah and I hold my nose I can still say ah there's no change if they say <vocal desc="misc"/> and they you hold your nose <vocal desc="misc"/> it changes the sound because it's the the air is coming through the nose they are literally more nasalised than we are</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes there's a village near Northampton that erm where the wedding where the where the where the erm wedding</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0190" trans="overlap">are they hot?</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0227">where the church was</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0192" trans="overlap">they are hot</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0227">if you put</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0192"><unclear/> do you <unclear/></u>
<u n="1787" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0227">yeah yeah they did if you put a if you put a F I E L D on that <pause dur="short"/> what would you call that?</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0192">Cobra field</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no that <pause dur="short"/> put field on the end of that what would you call it?</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0192">Branfield</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0227">Brafield</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0192">Brafield</u>
<u n="1795" who="S0227">but they don't they call it Brafield</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0192">oh <trunc>Bray</trunc></u>
<u n="1797" who="S0227">yeah where's the Y?</u>
<u n="1798" who="S0192">what about Towcester?</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0227">yeah I mean the</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0192" trans="overlap">Towcester</u>
<u n="1801" who="S0227">yeah yeah exactly there's other ones okay split it <unclear/> but there's one called Cogenhoe? you'd never guess Cogenhoe from erm the spelling would you?</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0190">oh</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0192">there's one erm</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0227">it's called Cogenhoe</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0192">it's in Brighton <trunc>Moul</trunc> Moulsescoomb Moulsecoomb and it's spelt like mouse <pause dur="short"/> it's spelt like mouse or comb</u>
<u n="1806" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0192">like comb you brush your hair and which when I lived in the West Country was comb they pronounced comb as comb</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0192">but it's kind of like</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no but it's got an e on the end when it's in er like Ilfracombe it's C O M B E</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0192" trans="overlap">B E yeah</u>
<u n="1812" who="S0190">but they if you're talking about a comb it's C O M B</u>
<u n="1813" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's M B you're right yeah</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0190" trans="overlap">isn't it so the E makes it say <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1815" who="S0192">traditionally we added the E to show the the longer vowel which I learnt again when I was</u>
<u n="1816" who="S0227">there are some nutty things in the English language erm one of them I'll say it in Spanish and see if you can translate you should be able to erm <foreign lang="spa">el hombre de araña</foreign></u>
<u n="1817" who="S0192">man of the spider spider of</u>
<u n="1818" who="S0227">yes now <pause dur="short"/> how can a spider be more important than a man? so really it should be a man of spider not spider of man <vocal desc="laugh"/> but it doesn't you know in English you go that would sound wrong</u>
<u n="1819" who="S0192">but in compounds the head is the second one blackbird isn't a type of black it's a type of bird</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0192">so the second compound</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0192">when you stick them together so spider man</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1825" who="S0192">it's a type of man not a type of spider</u>
<u n="1826" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0192">blackbird is type of bird</u>
<u n="1828" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah you would think it would be</u>
<u n="1829" who="S0192" trans="overlap">we put the stress on the second one because that's what it</u>
<u n="1830" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah you would think the stress should be on the first and not the second</u>
<u n="1831" who="S0192">yeah I know what you're saying whereas in Spanish the genitive you'd have to say man of the</u>
<u n="1832" who="S0227">yeah they'd say</u>
<u n="1833" who="S0192" trans="overlap">spider</u>
<u n="1834" who="S0227"><foreign lang="spa">el hombre de araña</foreign></u>
<u n="1835" who="S0192"><foreign lang="spa">de araña</foreign></u>
<u n="1836" who="S0227" trans="overlap">the man of spider</u>
<u n="1837" who="S0192">okay <foreign lang="spa">la araña</foreign></u>
<u n="1838" who="S0227"><foreign lang="spa">araña</foreign></u>
<u n="1839" who="S0192"><foreign lang="spa">hombre de araña</foreign></u>
<u n="1840" who="S0227"><foreign lang="spa">el hombre de araña</foreign></u>
<u n="1841" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">so two pint of Cobras?</u>
<u n="1842" who="S0192">yeah thank you very much</u>
<u n="1843" who="S0227">thank you</u>
<u n="1844" who="S0192">cheers <pause dur="long"/> I mean you were saying before about</u>
<u n="1845" who="S0190" trans="overlap"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1846" who="S0227">oh sorry yes</u>
<u n="1847" who="S0190" trans="overlap"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1848" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah we were gonna get one to share</u>
<u n="1849" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah we'd like to share one we just can't resist it</u>
<u n="1850" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1851" who="S0227">the mango one</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0192">the mango one yeah</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0190" trans="overlap">the mango please</u>
<u n="1854" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mango yeah?</u>
<u n="1855" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1856" who="S0192">thank you very much</u>
<u n="1857" who="S0190">thank you</u>
<u n="1858" who="S0227">and three spoons <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1859" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1860" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">thank you cheers then</u>
<u n="1861" who="S0227">erm <pause dur="short"/> it would be interesting when erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s learnt some French when I see her again I'll</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1863" who="S0227">give her a bit the <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1864" who="S0192">she's not bless her she's not amazing at picking up languages</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1866" who="S0192">she's okay</u>
<u n="1867" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1868" who="S0192">I definitely pick it up quicker than she does <pause dur="short"/> I'd say I speak double the amount of Spanish that she does she knows the same amount but she's not confident and I think that's partially my own fault because while our travels being a man I was approached a lot more than she was and therefore I had more practice so</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah and so you're doing the talking yeah</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I was speaking</u>
<u n="1871" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah you're doing the talking</u>
<u n="1872" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so it's not necessarily I guess that's wrong to say that she's not as good I've had more practice than she has so my Spanish is better</u>
<u n="1873" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="1874" who="S0192">if we're going for elitist my speech is better than hers <pause dur="short"/> it really jarred when we were first together every time she said something wrong it was oh mm she occasionally used like but it's from her family</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="1876" who="S0192">her parents aren't</u>
<u n="1877" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's a colloquial colloquial erm</u>
<u n="1878" who="S0192">her parents aren't particularly well educated so</u>
<u n="1879" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1880" who="S0192">it's kind of past</u>
<u n="1881" who="S0227">don't worry neither are yours <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1882" who="S0192" trans="overlap">like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1883" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1884" who="S0192">not terribly as you said if you get better each time then er <pause dur="long"/> I mean can you imagine if I got a PhD? <pause dur="short"/> did you ever think you'd have a son that could potentially?</u>
<u n="1885" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah I mean I have to say</u>
<u n="1886" who="S0192" trans="overlap">now I'm not saying I will but just</u>
<u n="1887" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><event desc="unintelligible"/> my son because</u>
<u n="1888" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1889" who="S0227" trans="overlap">because you must have well I must have been the nuisance</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0192" trans="overlap">your son your son <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1891" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1892" who="S0192">I'm not saying I will I may not succeed in an MA yet</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0192">I have</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0192">as so far</u>
<u n="1897" who="S0227" trans="overlap">you have aspirations</u>
<u n="1898" who="S0192">as so far for the last ten years everything I've said I'm gonna do I've done so hopefully</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well I think in</u>
<u n="1900" who="S0192" trans="overlap">if I continue along that route</u>
<u n="1901" who="S0227">I think in our lineage</u>
<u n="1902" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I think you stand a good chance of doing it because you enjoy it</u>
<u n="1903" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="1904" who="S0190" trans="overlap">basically</u>
<u n="1905" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well that's you're halfway there erm you're going to be the most erm <pause dur="short"/> in our family line I haven't done my family tree yet but I and this is just a presumption but you're probably going to be the most educated and the most travelled <pause dur="short"/> but none of our in our our ancestors my side or your mother's will have travelled as far as you <trunc>ha</trunc>have because we would have taken years to do that</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0192">yeah I mean I come from a time where I can</u>
<u n="1907" who="S0227">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean yes I've been to I've been to I've been to er California I've been to Mexico I've had the spray of Niagara on my face in Canada I've been to and I'm not and I'm not even worrying about Europe I've been to Taiwan</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0192" trans="overlap">which would and quite a few countries are and in Europe and seen</u>
<u n="1909" who="S0190">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1910" who="S0227">I've been to Taiwan I've been to Korea</u>
<u n="1911" who="S0192">but including layers that</u>
<u n="1912" who="S0227">but I haven't you know been as far as you have you know I haven't been as many places in your lifespan</u>
<u n="1913" who="S0192">I counted the other day I've been to forty-one countries</u>
<u n="1914" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1915" who="S0192">it's quite a few</u>
<u n="1916" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1917" who="S0192" trans="overlap">for twenty-eight rather it's quite a few</u>
<u n="1918" who="S0227">do we count Wales and Spain er like Wales and Scotland?</u>
<u n="1919" who="S0192">I count I haven't been to Scotland I counted Wales I've only been to Cardiff but</u>
<u n="1920" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="1921" who="S0192">but I counted it</u>
<u n="1922" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it that that</u>
<u n="1923" who="S0192" trans="overlap">like forty-one</u>
<u n="1924" who="S0227">yeah so that's two er do do you count England in that at all or not?</u>
<u n="1925" who="S0192">yes</u>
<u n="1926" who="S0227">yeah so that's three erm that's erm er <pause dur="short"/> spain Mallorca Majorca <pause dur="short"/> tenerife Gran Canaria and I think</u>
<u n="1927" who="S0192" trans="overlap">is Tenerife a country?</u>
<u n="1928" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah they're different islands aren't they?</u>
<u n="1929" who="S0192">are they countries though?</u>
<u n="1930" who="S0227">no they're different islands though they're islands</u>
<u n="1931" who="S0192">aren't they owned by Spain though?</u>
<u n="1932" who="S0227">yeah but they're like they're about eight hundred</u>
<u n="1933" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh not sure that that counts as a country</u>
<u n="1934" who="S0227" trans="overlap">they're eight hundred miles away</u>
<u n="1935" who="S0192">oh I'm not sure if it counts as a country though dad</u>
<u n="1936" who="S0227">er</u>
<u n="1937" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1938" who="S0227">Taiwan <pause dur="short"/> er</u>
<u n="1939" who="S0192">it's debatable what a country is</u>
<u n="1940" who="S0190" trans="overlap">Fuerteventura</u>
<u n="1941" who="S0227"><trunc>ye</trunc> say er you go Fuerteventura Lanzarote Tenerife and Gran Canaria</u>
<u n="1942" who="S0192">adds four</u>
<u n="1943" who="S0227">that's four</u>
<u n="1944" who="S0190">Canaria</u>
<u n="1945" who="S0227">Gran Canaria</u>
<u n="1946" who="S0190">no it's not Canaria</u>
<u n="1947" who="S0227" trans="overlap">Canaria Canaria</u>
<u n="1948" who="S0190">it it's with I A</u>
<u n="1949" who="S0227">alright A Canaria okay that's four because there are four different islands that are separated by quite a bit of water</u>
<u n="1950" who="S0192">but then I could argue you know I went to the Andaman Islands I went to Little Andaman I went to Button Island I went to Neil Island</u>
<u n="1951" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh <trunc>ye</trunc> oh yeah</u>
<u n="1952" who="S0192">I went to Ross Island I went to</u>
<u n="1953" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah I know but they're not</u>
<u n="1954" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah bet they all are they all all what do they come under the category of?</u>
<u n="1955" who="S0192">well they're all part of India but they're a thousand miles away from India and they're they're</u>
<u n="1956" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1957" who="S0192">you know</u>
<u n="1958" who="S0190">yes but are they called so and so like the Channel Islands or the something islands?</u>
<u n="1959" who="S0192">the Andaman Islands</u>
<u n="1960" who="S0190">the Andaman Islands yes that's the</u>
<u n="1961" who="S0192" trans="overlap">the Andaman and Nicobar Islands but I've only been to the Andaman Islands</u>
<u n="1962" who="S0227">right so okay so</u>
<u n="1963" who="S0192">but but they're owned by India so I just count India I don't say I've been to India and and you know the Andaman</u>
<u n="1964" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="1965" who="S0227">okay so if I count all those four as one alright I'll <trunc>cou</trunc> oh</u>
<u n="1966" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1967" who="S0190">no let's really not do that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1968" who="S0227">there was Scotland England</u>
<u n="1969" who="S0190">but then you could say that about the British Isles it's just one country because there's no you need water between them</u>
<u n="1970" who="S0192"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="1971" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="1972" who="S0227">no it's effectively three countries that's the United Kingdom</u>
<u n="1973" who="S0192">it's it's one country and four countries actually</u>
<u n="1974" who="S0227" trans="overlap">right well oh we'll go</u>
<u n="1975" who="S0192">the United Kingdom</u>
<u n="1976" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh we've got three there then we've got France</u>
<u n="1977" who="S0190" trans="overlap">alright</u>
<u n="1978" who="S0227">then I've got Germany then I've got Belgium then I've got erm Spain man mainland the Canary Islands Minorca</u>
<u n="1979" who="S0192">still Spain</u>
<u n="1980" who="S0227">you can say I've got yes but but there's</u>
<u n="1981" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's still Spain</u>
<u n="1982" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1983" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah but the Andaman Islands were a five day boat journey from from <trunc>pe</trunc></u>
<u n="1984" who="S0227">that narrows it that look I lose all the Minorcan Islands and all the</u>
<u n="1985" who="S0192">it's still Spain</u>
<u n="1986" who="S0227">sorry all if I lose all the Iberian Islands</u>
<u n="1987" who="S0192">I mean I could say in Greece I went to Folegandros and Sifnos and Santorini and</u>
<u n="1988" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="1989" who="S0192"><trunc>nu</trunc> there are numerous islands that are separated but</u>
<u n="1990" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well that that that</u>
<u n="1991" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but that's Greece it's just like Greece</u>
<u n="1992" who="S0227" trans="overlap">in that case so er right Spain</u>
<u n="1993" who="S0190" trans="overlap">it is going down further and further <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1994" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1995" who="S0227">Wales Scotland England France</u>
<u n="1996" who="S0192">I'll give you those they are countries</u>
<u n="1997" who="S0227">Belgium</u>
<u n="1998" who="S0192">I mean it's debatable what's a country you know</u>
<u n="1999" who="S0227" trans="overlap">Spain that really knocks a lot out then Taiwan <pause dur="short"/> korea Mexico Canada USA</u>
<u n="2000" who="S0190">I've been more than you then if you look all like that</u>
<u n="2001" who="S0227">no I've been to twelve</u>
<u n="2002" who="S0190">so?</u>
<u n="2003" who="S0192">I mean twelve's pretty good</u>
<u n="2004" who="S0190" trans="overlap">Luxembourg Belgium France Holland Switzerland erm Italy England Scotland Wales oh where's that?</u>
<u n="2005" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">you wanna leave it in the middle?</u>
<u n="2006" who="S0190">thank you</u>
<u n="2007" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh that's fantastic thank you very much</u>
<u n="2008" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">thanks</u>
<u n="2009" who="S0227">that's not twelve</u>
<u n="2010" who="S0190">pardon? well I didn't want you going up then did I? I haven't finished yet</u>
<u n="2011" who="S0227">well you've got you can't yeah Spain</u>
<u n="2012" who="S0190" trans="overlap">that that and then I've got the Canary Islands</u>
<u n="2013" who="S0227">no no I <trunc>could</trunc> didn't count them</u>
<u n="2014" who="S0192" trans="overlap">well we said that's one</u>
<u n="2015" who="S0190">no yeah just one</u>
<u n="2016" who="S0227">that's one</u>
<u n="2017" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I haven't counted them I just said the Canary Islands</u>
<u n="2018" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2019" who="S0190">France Spain</u>
<u n="2020" who="S0227">no that comes under Spain</u>
<u n="2021" who="S0190" trans="overlap">Italy</u>
<u n="2022" who="S0227">apparently according to</u>
<u n="2023" who="S0192">well it does I mean it's in the same country</u>
<u n="2024" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah so yeah so</u>
<u n="2025" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh alright then</u>
<u n="2026" who="S0227"><trunc>ye</trunc> so it I lost all of those</u>
<u n="2027" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2028" who="S0190">so I'm not far behind considering how</u>
<u n="2029" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no you're not far behind</u>
<u n="2030" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="2031" who="S0192">it's pretty good</u>
<u n="2032" who="S0227">distance wise you are because like take</u>
<u n="2033" who="S0190">oh yes</u>
<u n="2034" who="S0227">that way going back up into</u>
<u n="2035" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well I knew you'd have to be one better <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2036" who="S0227" trans="overlap">and up into erm</u>
<u n="2037" who="S0192" trans="overlap">got to get pedantic about it</u>
<u n="2038" who="S0227" trans="overlap">did I put Mexico in there?</u>
<u n="2039" who="S0192">you said Mexico yeah you did say <trunc>Mex</trunc></u>
<u n="2040" who="S0227">right yeah you the furthest west I've been in <trunc>Califor</trunc> er is erm Los Angeles er is west the furthest east I've been in erm Puglia Puglia the furthest south I've been is Taiwan the furthest north I've been is but not landing is Iceland</u>
<u n="2041" who="S0192">out of the countries you said I haven't been on Luxembourg and I haven't been to Canada but otherwise I've been on those</u>
<u n="2042" who="S0227">yes Mexico</u>
<u n="2043" who="S0192">I've been to Mexico I spent six weeks in Mexico</u>
<u n="2044" who="S0227">of course you did you did most of the <trunc>sum</trunc>summer over there didn't you?</u>
<u n="2045" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2046" who="S0227">yeah yeah so you've done</u>
<u n="2047" who="S0192" trans="overlap">Belize Honduras Nicaragua</u>
<u n="2048" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes yeah you've been to many</u>
<u n="2049" who="S0192" trans="overlap">forty-one in all fairness I haven't met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have not met anyone of our age that has travelled as much as we have I've never met anyone</u>
<u n="2050" who="S0227">no no</u>
<u n="2051" who="S0192">which is quite a statement because I've met quite a few people on our travels</u>
<u n="2052" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="2053" who="S0190" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="2054" who="S0192">I haven't met anyone that's kind of been</u>
<u n="2055" who="S0227">yeah it's a</u>
<u n="2056" who="S0190" trans="overlap">and you seen the cultures that you like that you've seen</u>
<u n="2057" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I I can't I can't <trunc>com</trunc> I can't compete to it I think it's safe to say</u>
<u n="2058" who="S0192" trans="overlap">if you can imagine if we keep going because</u>
<u n="2059" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="2060" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean potentially in two years we're gonna go to Africa</u>
<u n="2061" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2062" who="S0192">and when we go to Africa we're probably gonna do another ten countries over a year I would imagine</u>
<u n="2063" who="S0227">yeah the one that's really well travelled</u>
<u n="2064" who="S0192" trans="overlap">what's it gonna be like when we're forty?</u>
<u n="2065" who="S0227">is the queen she has been to a hell of a lot of countries erm</u>
<u n="2066" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I'm not sure if she's roughed quite as well as the</u>
<u n="2067" who="S0227">no not at all</u>
<u n="2068" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2069" who="S0227">erm so</u>
<u n="2070" who="S0190">I don't think somehow she'd be on the beach you know</u>
<u n="2071" who="S0227">if you go down both</u>
<u n="2072" who="S0192">getting mugged</u>
<u n="2073" who="S0227">if you go down both both your parents' lineage I can't see any of your er our ancestors who have been to so many countries there's no way how would they <trunc>h</trunc>? they'd have spent all of their life travelling they'd have never have been here they'd never have once they were born here and were got to the age of eighteen they never came back because</u>
<u n="2074" who="S0192">so there you go and regardless of getting married or having children I've made my mark I have two superlatives in the <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> name</u>
<u n="2075" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="2076" who="S0192">most countries <pause dur="short"/> perhaps if I get my masters and potentially a PhD most educated</u>
<u n="2077" who="S0227">yes well you're the most educated now</u>
<u n="2078" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that's</u>
<u n="2079" who="S0190">you're the only one with a degree</u>
<u n="2080" who="S0192">is there nobody in our family that's got a degree? nobody?</u>
<u n="2081" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="2082" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="2083" who="S0227">no er I my my</u>
<u n="2084" who="S0192">there's no in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s family either</u>
<u n="2085" who="S0227">my <trunc>hi</trunc> my highest accolade is erm <pause dur="short"/> I've got <pause dur="short"/> I have A level equivalents</u>
<u n="2086" who="S0192" trans="overlap">is this gonna be nice?</u>
<u n="2087" who="S0190">go on have a go go and taste it</u>
<u n="2088" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no I have A level equivalents</u>
<u n="2089" who="S0192">it's dad's birthday he should really first <pause dur="long"/> is it like a mousse? <pause dur="long"/> or is it?</u>
<u n="2090" who="S0227">er er</u>
<u n="2091" who="S0192">oh it is quite firm isn't it? how sweetened?</u>
<u n="2092" who="S0227">it's quite sweet but it's nice it cuts through <pause dur="long"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="2093" who="S0192">is this what you? <event desc="sound of restaurant"/></u>
<u n="2094" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2095" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="2096" who="S0192">is there like something on the bottom?</u>
<u n="2097" who="S0190">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="2098" who="S0192">it's good</u>
<u n="2099" who="S0227">it's quite still quite hard</u>
<u n="2100" who="S0192">hold it steady <pause dur="short"/> go on birthday boy you're going to have the chocolate <pause dur="short"/> gosh I just tried it sorry <pause dur="long"/> and hold it steady there we go</u>
<u n="2101" who="S0227">yeah they do go with a spicy meal cuts it cleans the palate</u>
<u n="2102" who="S0192">there's a dessert in India that I used to hate</u>
<u n="2103" who="S0190">you used to hate?</u>
<u n="2104" who="S0192">yeah I absolutely hated it it it came it's not really a dessert it came it's like a I don't know a digestif of some sort it's not a drink but at the end of every meal they bring it out in a plant of some sort it's very aniseedy I'm not I don't know if it was aniseed but it's like seeds and it just tastes like aniseed and you eat it with sugar so you get like a handful of sugar and a handful of these seeds and everyone eats it after every meal a square pretty much the entire country over everyone I've never seen it anywhere outside of India it was horrible I really didn't like it quite often there'd be ants in the sugar</u>
<u n="2105" who="S0190">oh</u>
<u n="2106" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and they'd put some sugar on your hand and you've got like ants in there and stuff and you've got to blow the ants out but you know when you get sick and the last thing you ate have you ever had this experience?</u>
<u n="2107" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2108" who="S0192">and you just go off it like you really just</u>
<u n="2109" who="S0227">what caused you to be sick?</u>
<u n="2110" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="2111" who="S0192">I remember I got I mean obviously I was ill quite a few times in India and and one of the times I associated it with this and after that and the problem is it was rude to turn it down they'd often just put it in your hand afterwards and you'd be like oh I really don't want</u>
<u n="2112" who="S0190"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="2113" who="S0192">yeah I dropped it they'd just give you more I think</u>
<u n="2114" who="S0190">well you <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2115" who="S0227">do you not like aniseed?</u>
<u n="2116" who="S0192">I don't mind aniseed I don't have a problem with aniseed but</u>
<u n="2117" who="S0227">no er or the only reason I'm saying that was <trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc>it's interesting because that when we went to France your mum and I we didn't realise that she was pregnant with you she had Pernod which was aniseed based and she was violently sick</u>
<u n="2118" who="S0192">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2119" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2120" who="S0192">so maybe that's why then</u>
<u n="2121" who="S0227">yes <pause dur="short"/> that could be a reason why you don't like aniseed</u>
<u n="2122" who="S0192">it's possible I've gone off a few things though because of being sick I tell you one of the worst experiences I've ever had was being sick on a camel safari in the desert in India and they camped us downwind from these terribly flatulent camels it was horrible I was so ill and like everything tasted bad my own <unclear>gas</unclear> was bad the all we had to eat was chapatti and a bit of dal and I just remember these camels kept farting and it was just horrible and we were sleeping out in the open as well you had like a scarab beetle like dung beetles like going around yourself</u>
<u n="2123" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="2124" who="S0192">I just I remember thinking at that point I wanna be at home in my bed just like lying in the desert</u>
<u n="2125" who="S0227"><event desc="unintelligible"/> camels going on safari</u>
<u n="2126" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah I know yeah</u>
<u n="2127" who="S0227">because we've been on there without the</u>
<u n="2128" who="S0192">we have been on yeah</u>
<u n="2129" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2130" who="S0192">I'm not sure if that was quite a safari but</u>
<u n="2131" who="S0227">no but</u>
<u n="2132" who="S0190">it was er no across the dunes wasn't it?</u>
<u n="2133" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it was on camels it was on camels and it was in the dunes yeah yes cos we saw that didn't we? we went the camel place we never went on a camel</u>
<u n="2134" who="S0190" trans="overlap">we did what was it called?</u>
<u n="2135" who="S0227">erm it was on Gran Canaria I can't remember what it was called</u>
<u n="2136" who="S0190">and that</u>
<u n="2137" who="S0227" trans="overlap">but there was lots of big lizards there weren't there?</u>
<u n="2138" who="S0190">yeah lots of</u>
<u n="2139" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="long"/> camels are terribly uncomfortable</u>
<u n="2140" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="2141" who="S0192">if you actually have to sit on one for hours it was horrible I had a really old one for</u>
<u n="2142" who="S0190"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2143" who="S0192">a really old and bony one er</u>
<u n="2144" who="S0227">I think it's just Arab habits because er the health and safety's out the window</u>
<u n="2145" who="S0192">with him standing on the elephant</u>
<u n="2146" who="S0227">and <unclear/> the tent it's like if you you couldn't do that in this country</u>
<u n="2147" who="S0192">oh you couldn't do a lot of things we've done</u>
<u n="2148" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2149" who="S0192">in this country it was this is</u>
<u n="2150" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well what about that one the picture we've got of you sitting in the erm in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s bedroom?</u>
<u n="2151" who="S0227">the tigers</u>
<u n="2152" who="S0190" trans="overlap">with the tigers that weren't tigers</u>
<u n="2153" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got a similar photo hasn't he</u>
<u n="2154" who="S0190">has he?</u>
<u n="2155" who="S0192">yes he went to the same place</u>
<u n="2156" who="S0190">did he?</u>
<u n="2157" who="S0192">yeah so he has a similar photo you'll have to see it it's up there</u>
<u n="2158" who="S0190">yeah it's <event desc="unintelligible"/> that's it mind you he was gonna show is the erm</u>
<u n="2159" who="S0227">yeah he showed me the erm</u>
<u n="2160" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah that was a erm an unchained tiger was and some people had been scratched only a few people before me had a big like gash down his arm and it was like oh okay</u>
<u n="2161" who="S0227">is that like in its sleep when it's?</u>
<u n="2162" who="S0192">yeah I I've been in a few instances that I've definitely thought I could perhaps die this is not good I actually had one experience where I really thought I was going to die I genuinely thought I was going to die have you ever heard of a banded sea krait? it's a type of snake</u>
<u n="2163" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's a snake</u>
<u n="2164" who="S0192">yeah a banded sea krait</u>
<u n="2165" who="S0227" trans="overlap">that that's a very <trunc>painf</trunc></u>
<u n="2166" who="S0192" trans="overlap">very very very poisonous snake it's</u>
<u n="2167" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2168" who="S0192">it's like the most poisonous snake in the world I've seen them three times first time they swam around my feet in the Andaman Isles most remote the remotest place I've ever been swam around my feet didn't quite know what it was at the time second time I was scuba diving and it was curled up just like beautiful snake really really beautiful third time it swam to the surface took a breath and then went back down under the water really again very beautiful I've been told and I always heard David Attenborough's voice in my head you know the voice of god that if you get bitten by this snake you'll die within about</u>
<u n="2169" who="S0227">not long at all</u>
<u n="2170" who="S0192">ten seconds to a minute</u>
<u n="2171" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2172" who="S0192">it's got such a powerful neurotoxin but because its prey can swim away fast</u>
<u n="2173" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah so it needs</u>
<u n="2174" who="S0192" trans="overlap">so it needs something that</u>
<u n="2175" who="S0190" trans="overlap">stuns it yeah</u>
<u n="2176" who="S0227" trans="overlap">that kills it quick yeah</u>
<u n="2177" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you know can <trunc>s</trunc> yeah very quickly but they're quite docile and their mandible their mouth is very small so they can't and they are quite small they have a small head they can only bite you here and here and maybe in between your toes they can't get their mouth around another part of you</u>
<u n="2178" who="S0227">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2179" who="S0192">I was scuba <trunc>di</trunc> I was sorry snorkelling in erm Indonesia and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s not a very strong swimmer so quite often she didn't she doesn't come out with me and I don't actually like snorkelling on my own</u>
<u n="2180" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="2181" who="S0192">if I have somebody else with me I am infinitely more confident</u>
<u n="2182" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2183" who="S0192">than when I'm on my own and it was very murky and I felt like suddenly I got hit numerous times by something and I kind of panicked and swam in and I come out and I saw two teeth mark here right on my hand where it knew that it could be bitten no joke and I stood there my heart was racing</u>
<u n="2184" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2185" who="S0192">and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think this is it I think I've been bitten by one of those <trunc>sn</trunc> I think this is me gone and for the next five minutes I really thought I was gonna die and I just stood there like</u>
<u n="2186" who="S0227">was there any blood?</u>
<u n="2187" who="S0192" trans="overlap">sweating there was a little bit there were two pin pricks like</u>
<u n="2188" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2189" who="S0192">I mean it looked perfectly like two teeth</u>
<u n="2190" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2191" who="S0192">but in hindsight when it happened I actually pulled something out of it and I think what happened was when I felt like I got hit by a few things I think I got hit by a shoal of fish and I think you know fish have spines on their back?</u>
<u n="2192" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2193" who="S0192">I think two of the spines were in my hand but it was just conveniently exactly like two fangs</u>
<u n="2194" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2195" who="S0192">and I I tell you what I just <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't react very much but in internally I was freaking</u>
<u n="2196" who="S0227" trans="overlap">you want to suck the poison out</u>
<u n="2197" who="S0192">and I was kind of going this is it</u>
<u n="2198" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2199" who="S0192">I'm I've gone</u>
<u n="2200" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2201" who="S0192">and I was thinking to myself at least if I die now I'll die happy to a certain degree</u>
<u n="2202" who="S0190"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2203" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2204" who="S0192">but this could be it</u>
<u n="2205" who="S0227"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sucked the poison out</u>
<u n="2206" who="S0192">I really thought I really thought that was it it took a good it took half an hour</u>
<u n="2207" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2208" who="S0192">cos in your head you're going okay maybe maybe a minute's an exaggeration maybe it'll be five minutes</u>
<u n="2209" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2210" who="S0192">maybe it'll be ten minutes</u>
<u n="2211" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2212" who="S0192">ten minutes passes oh maybe half an hour and it's</u>
<u n="2213" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2214" who="S0192">it was horrible absolutely horrible</u>
<u n="2215" who="S0227">how many days had passed before you said I think I'm in the clear?</u>
<u n="2216" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2217" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2218" who="S0192">I told you I mean <trunc>i</trunc> the Andaman Islands where I said they are literally <pause dur="short"/> it's I mean maybe you could go to some island in the middle of the pacific and it would be more remote</u>
<u n="2219" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2220" who="S0192">but these islands are a thousand miles off the coast of India they're south of Myanmar which doesn't exactly have many tourists anyway</u>
<u n="2221" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="2222" who="S0192">erm they still have cannibals they used to be called the cannibal isles there are tribes on these islands that we've never had any contact with you know those videos where you see a helicopter flying over and they're throwing the spears and stuff? that's there that's on the Andaman Islands we were swimming on these this most beautiful beach I've ever been on and the it wasn't until a few months later that we actually read an article somebody on that beach got eaten by a salt water crocodile three months after we were there</u>
<u n="2223" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2224" who="S0192">and everyone was saying you know why haven't they put signs up? like you need to be and other people were saying this is one of the most remote places in the world like</u>
<u n="2225" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2226" who="S0192">how can you put a sign up?</u>
<u n="2227" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2228" who="S0192">when there's no one there</u>
<u n="2229" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2230" who="S0192">I actually got stung there by erm have you ever heard of fire coral? it's a type of coral that lays a living creature in you effectively and if you scratch it it spreads</u>
<u n="2231" who="S0190">mm</u>
<u n="2232" who="S0192">I didn't know what it was at the time and it I woke up with my arm on fire after I'd been scuba diving in this area it lasted for about two or three weeks it was like thousands of of mosquito bites like</u>
<u n="2233" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2234" who="S0192">all over my arms it was horrible absolutely horrible it's only in hindsight that I realised how kind of dangerous that area was</u>
<u n="2235" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2236" who="S0192">that we were in</u>
<u n="2237" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2238" who="S0192">and like I looked at a map of where salt water crocodiles are and it was there this is one of their most prolific areas and like they grow up the biggest salt water crocodile ever <trunc>c</trunc> seven metres</u>
<u n="2239" who="S0227">yeah they're big</u>
<u n="2240" who="S0192">well two metres</u>
<u n="2241" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2242" who="S0192">can you imagine a a crocodile that's three and a half times the size of dad?</u>
<u n="2243" who="S0190">well we were watching erm on the <trunc>oth</trunc> the other night weren't we? Impossible Creatures</u>
<u n="2244" who="S0227">erm</u>
<u n="2245" who="S0192">and that was crocodiles and this one it was <trunc>hu</trunc> absolutely huge what was it supposed to be? bigger than what?</u>
<u n="2246" who="S0227">it was about erm it was erm about erm a thousand pounds in weight is what the biggest crocodile</u>
<u n="2247" who="S0192">I imagine these were quite similar</u>
<u n="2248" who="S0190" trans="overlap">absolutely massive</u>
<u n="2249" who="S0192">it seems er ridiculous but they exist</u>
<u n="2250" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="2251" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="2252" who="S0192" trans="overlap">real salt water crocodile exists they're all off the I was crawling around on my belly in the mudflats and mangroves of Calcutta and around the area of the Sundarbans which I only found out in hindsight is notorious for massive salt water crocodiles</u>
<u n="2253" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2254" who="S0192">and there's I went on a tour you know I mean I call it a tour but it's very low key wishy washy and we they took us into the mangroves and they're like yeah you can just slide around on the mud and stuff we were told there were crocodiles there but we didn't know the extent <pause dur="short"/> it's only in hindsight you get any</u>
<u n="2255" who="S0227">I did think when erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <event desc="sound of restaurant"/> about two weeks ago it was on the news that erm a couple an English couple</u>
<u n="2256" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh yeah I heard about that</u>
<u n="2257" who="S0227">they got killed in Thailand</u>
<u n="2258" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2259" who="S0227"><trunc>ne</trunc> there's been</u>
<u n="2260" who="S0192">Koh Tao</u>
<u n="2261" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah Koh Tao</u>
<u n="2262" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it was on the island</u>
<u n="2263" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah Koh Tao and it was like erm</u>
<u n="2264" who="S0190">thank you very much</u>
<u n="2265" who="S0227">I think there's since about two thousand and nine there's been about eleven couple er eleven people English people killed er</u>
<u n="2266" who="S0192">just English I mean in India I was in a place called Jodhpur</u>
<u n="2267" who="S0227">Jodhpur is that where they do the trousers?</u>
<u n="2268" who="S0192">yeah yeah well we</u>
<u n="2269" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="2270" who="S0227">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2271" who="S0192">a month after I left there was a stampede at a temple I was at killed three hundred men a piece of wall fell over and it caused a stampede three hundred men died in the crush it was a month after I was there</u>
<u n="2272" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well you know have you heard on the news just recently about that couple on the island that er got murdered?</u>
<u n="2273" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah I just said yeah</u>
<u n="2274" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah I was just saying yeah yeah it was in Thailand</u>
<u n="2275" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh right sorry I was watching yeah and that's where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was there</u>
<u n="2276" who="S0192">I've been there I spent quite a while on Koh Tao <pause dur="short"/> we hear about these things and I mean I was in Baños in Ecuador erm a couple of months after I left it er it erupted the volcano erupted and they evacuated the whole city and like loads of people died</u>
<u n="2277" who="S0227">so</u>
<u n="2278" who="S0192">I've been in a couple of places where massive volcanoes have erupted like</u>
<u n="2279" who="S0227" trans="overlap">like <unclear/> erm three four nine where from erm <trunc>mo</trunc> erm from Malaysia where you were that</u>
<u n="2280" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that was only a few days prior</u>
<u n="2281" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2282" who="S0192">yeah and I flew almost exactly the same route</u>
<u n="2283" who="S0190" trans="overlap">and then we were waiting <event desc="unintelligible"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2284" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2285" who="S0190">he said oh shall we go where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and and er where</u>
<u n="2286" who="S0192" trans="overlap">couple of days couple of days later the same same journey</u>
<u n="2287" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2288" who="S0192">same flight goes off</u>
<u n="2289" who="S0227">mm</u>
<u n="2290" who="S0192">there's been a few instances I mean you only have to come close to England <trunc>Septem</trunc> er sorry seventh of the seventh the London bombings I was meant to be in London in Kings Cross at that time</u>
<u n="2291" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2292" who="S0192">I was going to see a gig with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the only reason that we didn't go was he woke up late</u>
<u n="2293" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="2294" who="S0192">so we got to the train station as just as it had been bombed and they wouldn't let us on the train</u>
<u n="2295" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="2296" who="S0192">er we sat in a pub and watched the whole thing unfold but we were we'd organised to be on the seven o'clock train or the seven thirty train to go to London and we should have been on in</u>
<u n="2297" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2298" who="S0192">there's a a few instances now where you think whoa</u>
<u n="2299" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="2300" who="S0192">a month earlier or a few hours earlier that would have</u>
<u n="2301" who="S0227">mm I think it fate dictates when you when when it's your time it's your time and that's it</u>
<u n="2302" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's your time yeah</u>
<u n="2303" who="S0227">and that's it yeah you have these nine lives</u>
<u n="2304" who="S0192">yeah but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s bad on flights you wouldn't think so would you with the amount of flying that?</u>
<u n="2305" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no she no she's <trunc>fl</trunc> I want to go to the loo again she's</u>
<u n="2306" who="S0192">she's not terrible but</u>
<u n="2307" who="S0227" trans="overlap">she's flown a lot</u>
<u n="2308" who="S0192" trans="overlap">she's erm</u>
<u n="2309" who="S0190">but don't you think sometimes?</u>
<u n="2310" who="S0227" trans="overlap">but she used to <trunc>statis</trunc>statistician</u>
<u n="2311" who="S0192">yeah it's statistics</u>
<u n="2312" who="S0227" trans="overlap">where she's looking at yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2313" who="S0192" trans="overlap">cos you start thinking well I've been on this a few times now</u>
<u n="2314" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2315" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah that's the trouble though you've been haven't you and the more you've been you've been the more you tend to realise just what you've putting yourself in for but then you have to weight that up in for the same reason driving on a bus or walking down the street</u>
<u n="2316" who="S0192">absolutely</u>
<u n="2317" who="S0190">the chances of that are higher of that than on a plane so</u>
<u n="2318" who="S0192">I mean in Nepal we were only about twelve cars behind a humungous avalanche that I mean people must have died in it because there was a village there and I couldn't see a village er the whole side of the mountain collapsed and the road had collapsed and we had to wait for about three or four hours while diggers undug the road but our bus was only about twelve vehicles behind the the collapse so I mean</u>
<u n="2319" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="2320" who="S0192">I was about twelve vehicles away from a landslide I don't know how many how much time that was I mean it could have been one vehicle every five minutes it could have been a vehicle every couple of minutes it could have been half an hour or it could have been five minutes but all I know is you walk up to it and you look at it and go <trunc>w</trunc> literally the whole mountain was gone you could see roofs like poking out and stuff so there were people in there I'm literally standing where people have died it was bad <pause dur="short"/> another time in Nepal I didn't know but the whole area had flooded I went to an area that was like you know a refugee camp there were like tents like aid tents and like dead buffalo in the water and all this kind of stuff and it was it was horrific to try and travel really it was like I spent about twelve hours trying to get through</u>
<u n="2321" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I think it makes it must make you feel I should say really lucky</u>
<u n="2322" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2323" who="S0190">in that some people suffer so much and see so much in in their lives</u>
<u n="2324" who="S0192">yeah I feel very privileged I do feel very privileged</u>
<u n="2325" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2326" who="S0192">it also helps me to feel connected I think with these people as well to have been and seen and to talked to them and to be there and to just realise that there are big differences between us but there are much more similarities between us between cultures but <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> I I probably will die doing something I like at some point but if I do</u>
<u n="2327" who="S0190" trans="overlap">but you will have enjoyed it</u>
<u n="2328" who="S0192">yeah know that I died happy</u>
<u n="2329" who="S0190">well it's like my dad you know my mum is is I think part of it is because when you've lived with somebody or had a partner for such a long long time you just rely on them to be there I mean the thought of one one losing the other and one of them being left is something but my mum tends to get sort of like over protective and my dad keeps turning around and saying well he would much rather die doing something that he loves than sitting around or laying in a hospital bed</u>
<u n="2330" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2331" who="S0190">so you know it like his skiing he'd love to ski again he knows he can't do anything like he used to because he'd go down a black run erm and what have you but and it's like</u>
<u n="2332" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and skiing's really dangerous</u>
<u n="2333" who="S0190">yeah it can be yeah</u>
<u n="2334" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's not that safe yeah</u>
<u n="2335" who="S0190">erm <pause dur="short"/> what else are you horse riding he really and truthfully at eighty-three to go out on the roads and ride his horse then you've got to have one of these arctic</u>
<u n="2336" who="S0192" trans="overlap">is he still doing it?</u>
<u n="2337" who="S0190">oh he still does it</u>
<u n="2338" who="S0192">oh wow</u>
<u n="2339" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah and it's only like</u>
<u n="2340" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that's phenomenal</u>
<u n="2341" who="S0190">if a lorry go down the side is the horse <trunc>g</trunc> dropping in front of it he's gone but he loves it he's loved horses from when he was a little boy and that I mean I was brought up in a saddle was sitting on the in a basket on the back of a horse and what have you that's how he was and he enjoys it you take all these things away unfortunately he now he he doesn't ride quite as much he hasn't been skiing and he likes his <unclear>crops</unclear> in here so he's got a more sedate kind of thing but</u>
<u n="2342" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I mean you take it away for that person then the living doesn't look an absolute joy anymore and what's the point?</u>
<u n="2343" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no that's precisely it and that's how it should be the end of your life you've worked so hard and you've done all these things but he's still working now so I mean he's still <trunc>ma</trunc> and he deserves</u>
<u n="2344" who="S0227" trans="overlap">he's still going yeah and he he's supposed to be retired but he's not</u>
<u n="2345" who="S0190" trans="overlap">he he's beginning to they're you know and like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying cos she's erm you know they're they're trying desperately hard and they wanna get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> going far so they can drop dad's hours right back down like he'd got to sort of like a odd day a week because at eighty-three he's getting tired</u>
<u n="2346" who="S0227">yeah and you can see it</u>
<u n="2347" who="S0192">what's he working? I mean at eighty-three most people aren't working</u>
<u n="2348" who="S0190">I know</u>
<u n="2349" who="S0227">most people are dead <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2350" who="S0192">well</u>
<u n="2351" who="S0227"><vocal desc="laugh"/> never mind <trunc>d</trunc> working</u>
<u n="2352" who="S0190" trans="overlap">but to me that's him he's always been that way he can't sit for very long he does a bit more now because he's been busy with the work and he's retired and what have you</u>
<u n="2353" who="S0192">I mean it's it's being active that keeps some people going isn't it yeah?</u>
<u n="2354" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well that's what it is it's true yeah they say once you stop doing something you get off and you won't restart it</u>
<u n="2355" who="S0192">I can imagine that <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2356" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah he's very he's very <pause dur="short"/> good for his age isn't he compared to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2357" who="S0190">oh god <trunc>ye</trunc> mind you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s a lot better than he wasn't isn't he now?</u>
<u n="2358" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="2359" who="S0190" trans="overlap">he really is</u>
<u n="2360" who="S0227">but er but if you</u>
<u n="2361" who="S0190" trans="overlap">you're not allowed to smoke in here are you?</u>
<u n="2362" who="S0192">I was gonna er</u>
<u n="2363" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2364" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh right you've prepared it</u>
<u n="2365" who="S0192">would would you mind?</u>
<u n="2366" who="S0190">no I don't go on</u>
<u n="2367" who="S0227">compared with your dad even though he's improved he's still er are not in the same league as</u>
<u n="2368" who="S0190">as <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> no no</u>
<u n="2369" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no he doesn't</u>
<u n="2370" who="S0190">yeah but then er in all fairness give him his due my dad has <unclear/> and a quarter of what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s had my dad has been very lucky when my dad went he had <event desc="unintelligible"/> doctors for?</u>
<u n="2371" who="S0227">he hadn't been for sixty years</u>
<u n="2372" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh well and my mum made him go because he had a cyst</u>
<u n="2373" who="S0227">a <trunc>cy</trunc></u>
<u n="2374" who="S0190" trans="overlap">didn't he?</u>
<u n="2375" who="S0227">a sebaceous cyst</u>
<u n="2376" who="S0190" trans="overlap">a sebaceous cyst <trunc>be</trunc>behind his his up here and</u>
<u n="2377" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2378" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah and on my head too</u>
<u n="2379" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2380" who="S0190">on the top of his ear</u>
<u n="2381" who="S0192">like this</u>
<u n="2382" who="S0190">yeah we've had this discussion before</u>
<u n="2383" who="S0227" trans="overlap">your mum's got</u>
<u n="2384" who="S0192" trans="overlap">the whole family's got one here it's like a divorce bump</u>
<u n="2385" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes your mum's got one yes yes</u>
<u n="2386" who="S0192" trans="overlap">or something I don't know what it is</u>
<u n="2387" who="S0227">er I don't know if your mum's</u>
<u n="2388" who="S0192" trans="overlap">do you know what I mean? even if you're like</u>
<u n="2389" who="S0227" trans="overlap">your mum's had hers treated or not your mum had one before me and it was on her head in the same place</u>
<u n="2390" who="S0192">it's weird it's like some flesh coloured mole or something</u>
<u n="2391" who="S0227">yeah I had mine lanced</u>
<u n="2392" who="S0190">lanced?</u>
<u n="2393" who="S0227">yes lanced that's what I was saying lanced</u>
<u n="2394" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh sorry I thought you said lanched <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2395" who="S0227">no lanced</u>
<u n="2396" who="S0192" trans="overlap">lanched lanched</u>
<u n="2397" who="S0190" trans="overlap">lanced yeah</u>
<u n="2398" who="S0227">I had it lanced by well so that was the first time he's been for one</u>
<u n="2399" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah why they they hadn't got any any records of him though and but at the doctors</u>
<u n="2400" who="S0192">that's fantastic</u>
<u n="2401" who="S0227">he hadn't been for about sixty years</u>
<u n="2402" who="S0190" trans="overlap">he's been so lucky</u>
<u n="2403" who="S0192" trans="overlap">that's pretty healthy</u>
<u n="2404" who="S0190">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2405" who="S0227"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for the last ten years has been</u>
<u n="2406" who="S0190">he didn't had anything he never had anything and all of a sudden wham <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2407" who="S0192">you've just gotta I mean <pause dur="short"/> people and different people enjoy doing different things and provided you continually if you can continue doing what you enjoy then</u>
<u n="2408" who="S0190">yeah that's right or you have to get something out of life</u>
<u n="2409" who="S0192">yeah and it's it is different for different people I mean for a long time I struggled with the idea you know I enjoy this so much how can you not? and I guess as I've gotten older I realised that you know not everyone is the same so what I may find pleasurable other people don't find pleasurable <pause dur="short"/> but I did struggle with for a while <pause dur="short"/> I did struggle would you mind if I have a cigarette?</u>
<u n="2410" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="2411" who="S0192">is that alright? shall I stop this or will you guys continue talking?</u>
<u n="2412" who="S0190">yeah you stop it</u>
<u n="2413" who="S0227">no we won't talk to each other when you're gone will we?</u>
<u n="2414" who="S0190">we don't talk</u>
<u n="2415" who="S0192">you don't talk? I'm gonna leave it on and I'll listen when I go home and see what you say</u>
<u n="2416" who="S0227">you're gonna be disappointed</u>
<event desc="sound of restaurant"/>
<u n="2417" who="S0190">I feel like <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2418" who="S0227">er however much er</u>
<u n="2419" who="S0192">if I just do it</u>
<u n="2420" who="S0227">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's restarted again</u>
<u n="2421" who="S0190">he told me had</u>
<u n="2422" who="S0227">pressure pressure</u>
<u n="2423" who="S0190">I'm surprised he he was saying that erm he was anxious you know he he they went through a <trunc>se</trunc> a session being anxious about things things have settled down now at uni and he feels better but I find I find that very difficult to that he just finds something to be anxious about <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2424" who="S0227">mm what after he's done everything he's done?</u>
<u n="2425" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="2426" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2427" who="S0190">you know he's so you know</u>
<u n="2428" who="S0227">I think it <trunc>manife</trunc>manifested in this at the start cos he he he was inclined to agree that when like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> started I said I think it's it's nerves and it's not he doesn't think it's nerves but it's his body reacting</u>
<u n="2429" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh yes it is</u>
<u n="2430" who="S0227">and he said yeah I think so because I think I've gone through something similar going back to uni now that my I would say like your stomach and stuff like that you may think that consciously that there's no problem but subconsciously you might your body is going er these are changes er and I'm responding to those changes in the way that you know <pause dur="long"/> yeah he went really</u>
<u n="2431" who="S0190" trans="overlap">has have you er have you spoken to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at all?</u>
<u n="2432" who="S0227">no he hasn't yeah I did feel a bit <event desc="sound of restaurant"/> the last time he emailed was a couple of days ago</u>
<u n="2433" who="S0190">did he say whether he's going to the doctors and how his stomach was?</u>
<u n="2434" who="S0227">no no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had mentioned in his email to him cos it was a global email er to his mum and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't mention it</u>
<u n="2435" who="S0190">well he obviously he does feel a bit better</u>
<u n="2436" who="S0227">mm <pause dur="short"/> but I never I can't I accept that but I'm surprised I didn't get an email or a phone call from him er when I said</u>
<u n="2437" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well you are part have yourself</u>
<u n="2438" who="S0227" trans="overlap">you don't have to give me a present er that was kind of like yeah that's fine but the the thought might have been nice</u>
<u n="2439" who="S0190" trans="overlap">but you see well</u>
<u n="2440" who="S0227">there you go</u>
<u n="2441" who="S0190">I think you have you do partly have that to blame because he did ask you what you would like and say well what can we get you? and was going don't worry son just don't don't do it like this</u>
<u n="2442" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah so don't go over yeah</u>
<u n="2443" who="S0190">sort of thing and I suppose he just thinks oh well you you obviously don't probably see he takes it the wrong way</u>
<u n="2444" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well no I said I said you know you to money you can't afford it so don't do it you know <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't like I'm not interested in it it was like because of your financial situation</u>
<u n="2445" who="S0190">well yeah I know but I'm saying perhaps because it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's taken it literally whereas you know like somebody else I mean I always say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> well don't do this and don't do the other I mean the you know the with the boys where I said about I wanted to erm I asked <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to get you your satnav you see I said look I don't know what I'm doing erm I'm fed up with it cos that wasn't working properly <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> uses it a lot can you get me will you get me a satnav for him and that? so I don't know how much they are or what I'm paying you know what's the best to do you see so he's he said then and that's then when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came back with where he said well we wanna come in with you that sounds a good idea this that and the other and that so I said no you don't need to do this mum we're doing it you see and I don't they don't they just don't argue they just don't <unclear/> if they decide something I don't get to</u>
<u n="2446" who="S0227">no they write the rules <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2447" who="S0190">yeah so but I mean as I say <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't have to spend a lot of money he could have just sent you an email</u>
<u n="2448" who="S0227">yeah or phoned before or a phone call</u>
<u n="2449" who="S0190">and just rung up you see <pause dur="short"/> that's why I think you</u>
<u n="2450" who="S0227">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I knew he was coming but he sent me a a a happy birthday text as well you know so he said I haven't got you a card well I said well you sent me a text and you're here you know so</u>
<u n="2451" who="S0190">I think that's what men are more like this and then you get older it depends on how well whether you appreciate it or not doesn't it?</u>
<u n="2452" who="S0227"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s there's a light pull the string <pause dur="long"/> weather's supposed to be quite nice I think</u>
<u n="2453" who="S0190">yeah <pause dur="long"/> get the hedges cut that's nice well we might as well be out in the garden</u>
<u n="2454" who="S0227">right I hope we've got er that <unclear>shower</unclear> next door they decide to have their er next <event desc="unintelligible"/> tonight</u>
<u n="2455" who="S0190">I think I heard <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I in I was in the garden what was I doing? oh I was just er going up the path I got as far as the greenhouse I was going and I started to clear up and I heard some it sounded like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they're going daddy daddy erm so the it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so I guess I should think that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might be back cos I haven't seen him for a couple of weeks</u>
<u n="2456" who="S0227">yeah has he gone away has he gone away for?</u>
<u n="2457" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well I don't know all he said to me was when he looked over the wall one day he said something about erm I'm working away now I have to work so it's easier or something now I have to work away <pause dur="short"/> and it's as much as I know <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2458" who="S0227">if it was just erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the daughter and a few friends hopefully in</u>
<u n="2459" who="S0190"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2460" who="S0227">you would hope in a few years' time they're not gonna be having parties where you know them like what the opposite the the bungalow opposite you know like there were male young lads there and they were like <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2461" who="S0190">oh yeah</u>
<u n="2462" who="S0227" trans="overlap">and <event desc="sound of restaurant"/></u>
<u n="2463" who="S0190"><event desc="sound of restaurant"/></u>
<u n="2464" who="S0227">that kind of arrangement <event desc="sound of restaurant"/> they've been on <unclear/> with her and a couple of friends and about <event desc="sound of restaurant"/></u>
<u n="2465" who="S0190">because I get I tried to work out when you said to me how old she is she was</u>
<u n="2466" who="S0227">yeah <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2467" who="S0190">I can't remember how no she's gotta be older than that because she was about sort of she must have been at least <trunc>te</trunc>ten we moved in we've been there ten years but she can't have been cos she's not twenty</u>
<u n="2468" who="S0227">no no not she's not she <trunc>loo</trunc></u>
<u n="2469" who="S0190">so she's gotta be fifteen or sixteen cos I'm sure when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said about his moving back <pause dur="long"/> we've erm our next door neighbours if you're looking up the garden the neighbours to the left erm they've got a a <unclear/> in the garden and for the last three Fridays</u>
<u n="2470" who="S0192">they've had a party</u>
<u n="2471" who="S0190">they've had a party yeah</u>
<u n="2472" who="S0192">yeah they've had those before I think yeah</u>
<u n="2473" who="S0190">they're not as loud as they were last time and they don't they're touch wood don't speak too soon they haven't had the drums have they?</u>
<u n="2474" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="2475" who="S0190">mm and they just <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2476" who="S0192">what just it's Friday tonight</u>
<u n="2477" who="S0190">yeah that's what I said</u>
<u n="2478" who="S0227">last time it was two Fridays and then the last the third one was a Saturday</u>
<u n="2479" who="S0190">was it?</u>
<u n="2480" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="2481" who="S0190">was the last week Saturday?</u>
<u n="2482" who="S0227">yeah they erm</u>
<u n="2483" who="S0192">can you hear it in every room?</u>
<u n="2484" who="S0227">you can't hear it in the front <pause dur="short"/> you hear it in the</u>
<u n="2485" who="S0190" trans="overlap">you can hear it well you</u>
<u n="2486" who="S0227">no you can't hear it in front <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2487" who="S0190" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to be able to hear it</u>
<u n="2488" who="S0227">I've never can't hear it in the front room because it's right on the other side the house</u>
<u n="2489" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh the and the</u>
<u n="2490" who="S0227">there's no connection to that side</u>
<u n="2491" who="S0192">which one's the front bedroom?</u>
<u n="2492" who="S0190">the one you used the one before</u>
<u n="2493" who="S0227" trans="overlap">where you slept before</u>
<u n="2494" who="S0192">okay</u>
<u n="2495" who="S0227">erm</u>
<u n="2496" who="S0190">but your dad went last last weekend into your room where you are because you can't hear it in there so well</u>
<u n="2497" who="S0227" trans="overlap">you don't hear it initially but they get louder as the <event desc="sound of restaurant"/></u>
<u n="2498" who="S0192">what time do they normally finish?</u>
<u n="2499" who="S0190">quarter to two</u>
<u n="2500" who="S0192">oh gosh that's quite late</u>
<u n="2501" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2502" who="S0190">it is</u>
<u n="2503" who="S0227">so er <pause dur="short"/> before they moved away and they came back again cos it's they'd let they've let the house and they used to use it the all <event desc="sound of restaurant"/> between two and three when it's sunny one of them came from they were er from Holland and a drum and they'd be well well you've seen that little drum kit that</u>
<u n="2504" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2505" who="S0227">yeah that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got</u>
<u n="2506" who="S0192" trans="overlap">well drums are loud drums are extremely loud</u>
<u n="2507" who="S0227" trans="overlap">think of a full sized one and now in the garage find that at three o'clock in the morning and no one can hear <pause dur="short"/> but you'd think only</u>
<u n="2508" who="S0192" trans="overlap">any people complaining?</u>
<u n="2509" who="S0227">oh er I complained I complained I knocked on the door and unfortunately he <event desc="sound of restaurant"/> when they moved back I said well what I said at the time I wanna have a meaning to have words to you about saying no no no no I said like I knocked on the door and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> answered that's the daughter I said <pause dur="short"/> er now welcome back I said if you're thinking of having parties I said firstly let us know I said and secondly I</u>
<u n="2510" who="S0192">refrain from playing the drums</u>
<u n="2511" who="S0227" trans="overlap">take it well I didn't mention the drums I said well though take no it's alright you know to stay out in the pond in the pool till midnight and then go in</u>
<u n="2512" who="S0192">and that's respectable</u>
<u n="2513" who="S0227" trans="overlap">but no they were coming out at midnight to go in the pond and like they're all screaming</u>
<u n="2514" who="S0192" trans="overlap">trouble is the more you drink the less you care</u>
<u n="2515" who="S0227">yeah yes exactly so now what they've done is A they haven't told us and B they're going out</u>
<u n="2516" who="S0192">so not being where very respectful of their neighbours</u>
<u n="2517" who="S0227" trans="overlap">not at all no so so no</u>
<u n="2518" who="S0190">and then the they're not and it's like</u>
<u n="2519" who="S0192" trans="overlap">but has no one else complained?</u>
<u n="2520" who="S0190">no I don't think</u>
<u n="2521" who="S0227">well not that we know of</u>
<u n="2522" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well I don't see the other the thing thing is our bedroom is out the back</u>
<u n="2523" who="S0227" trans="overlap">but we're never away</u>
<u n="2524" who="S0190" trans="overlap">and we have a vent er a vent in the wall erm and it it just sort of permeates through it's just so loud but the thing is we've shut the ventilators down because it's got a bit colder and there's quite a breeze in but you don't such a light sleeper if you can't settle for me I just sleep through them I just</u>
<u n="2525" who="S0227" trans="overlap">see some people it doesn't bother</u>
<u n="2526" who="S0192" trans="overlap">have you tried ear plugs?</u>
<u n="2527" who="S0227">I got pieces of paper in my ears and I can still hear it</u>
<u n="2528" who="S0192">do you know what's really good and what I use travelling because I'm not gonna lie some of the places I've slept in are horrific? I've actually <trunc>s</trunc> tried sleeping above a club I I turned up to a place in Belize and there was no they were having a festival but I didn't know and I'd just arrived in the country and the only place to sleep was above a club and it was the whole <trunc>roo</trunc> I mean literally it's as loud as a club in my room and I've got if you can I think are better than ear plugs inner ear headphones <pause dur="short"/> do you know the ones that go right in your ear not not the buds but the ones that go right in your ear?</u>
<u n="2529" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="2530" who="S0192">and I sleep with one ear on the pillow and one in I can't put them both in because it's uncomfortable</u>
<u n="2531" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2532" who="S0192">if you sleep with one ear on the pillow and one ear in it helps a lot a lot I would recommend getting some because they're my godsend now and there's numerous <trunc>ti</trunc> I used to be a really light sleeper and like I couldn't believe it I mean the amount of times there's somebody just beeping or I've had people in India knocking on my door it's quite scary like at night people are trying to get in to your door like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I are lying in bed like please you know whoever this is please go away people like clearly turning the door handle's turning and stuff and we're like I don't wanna die right now this is please go away so I've I've I've got good with that now I and pretty much it doesn't block all of the sound out but it really distances it it makes it sound like it's quite far away</u>
<u n="2533" who="S0190" trans="overlap">far away</u>
<u n="2534" who="S0192">erm</u>
<u n="2535" who="S0227">you might need that tonight er it depends on what's going on</u>
<u n="2536" who="S0192">I've got my headphones with me so</u>
<u n="2537" who="S0190" trans="overlap">it won't be it won't be</u>
<u n="2538" who="S0192">hopefully not paper doesn't work <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2539" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="2540" who="S0192">that's no good</u>
<u n="2541" who="S0227">no it</u>
<u n="2542" who="S0192" trans="overlap">these inner earplugs are good I'd recommend you investigate it</u>
<u n="2543" who="S0227">er that was the girl on the line to me I gave you you know I was I I asked two simple things one erm tell me when you're gonna do it</u>
<u n="2544" who="S0192">you weren't saying don't do it you were just saying be respectful</u>
<u n="2545" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah and can you erm do it the other way round rather than take cos her answer was oh well we're too old for that now</u>
<u n="2546" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="2547" who="S0192">too old for what?</u>
<u n="2548" who="S0227">to to do the erm</u>
<u n="2549" who="S0190">to be out late at night in <unclear/></u>
<u n="2550" who="S0227" trans="overlap">out like doing the things</u>
<u n="2551" who="S0192">right so who was doing that then? were they all just?</u>
<u n="2552" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I think she's she's definitely party to it yeah</u>
<u n="2553" who="S0192" trans="overlap">going for it as well yeah</u>
<u n="2554" who="S0227" trans="overlap">so my my my line would be erm I I I asked two simple things from you one let us know if you're doing this so we can be aware of it two erm take it er you know inside after midnight not the other way round</u>
<u n="2555" who="S0192">have you not called not the police but there's like noise police there's like?</u>
<u n="2556" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh you <trunc>ca</trunc> yeah er no it's not that that bad but erm and then say well you've failed in those in those in those er</u>
<u n="2557" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you've been disrespectful</u>
<u n="2558" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2559" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no well when when erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cut the hedge down what the garden the other and he's he just burns it all well A we're in a smokeless zone so you're not really supposed to do that but I wouldn't say anything because we burn coal</u>
<u n="2560" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2561" who="S0190">and what have you and we burn some wood and it's not always smokeless coal so I wouldn't do that but if you're gonna light a bonfire in a garden he won't come round to see if I've got any washing and peep over the fence and that so I get you're running to get the washing in the other week it <trunc>absolut</trunc> the house stunk because it was a it's because it was fresh you know like green and it <trunc>make</trunc></u>
<u n="2562" who="S0227" trans="overlap">he he was he was trying to burn fresh wood and like</u>
<u n="2563" who="S0190" trans="overlap">the smoke you couldn't see the garden it was that smoky and that so you know if you <trunc>t</trunc> if you go and knock on the door and say that I've got we've got all this it will take me ages to take it to the tip and I want to have a bonfire you know is that alright? are you? <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2564" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah if you've asked</u>
<u n="2565" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I was gonna say yeah</u>
<u n="2566" who="S0192">I'll bring my washing in and <event desc="sound of restaurant"/></u>
<u n="2567" who="S0190">well</u>
<u n="2568" who="S0227"><event desc="sound of restaurant"/></u>
<u n="2569" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well I'm not saying he would just do it</u>
<u n="2570" who="S0227">see my tactic</u>
<u n="2571" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2572" who="S0227">my my tact will well when that <trunc>ta</trunc> if you can go about this is about <event desc="sound of restaurant"/> of this party is just knock on the door at six o'clock in the morning and say I'm sorry have I woken you up?</u>
<u n="2573" who="S0192">yeah definitely do it</u>
<u n="2574" who="S0227" trans="overlap">erm yeah erm</u>
<u n="2575" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well I'm sorry but I don't think that would work because the other morning when they did the little boy was screaming outside and it was about quarter to seven</u>
<u n="2576" who="S0227">yeah they don't seem to sleep that's like they're like robots and they don't have much sleep <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2577" who="S0192">it's not on is it?</u>
<u n="2578" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="2579" who="S0192">don't get me wrong it's not all the time and this is why it was you know he was saying this time it's not ever so late it's not ever so loud and I just don't wanna get <event desc="sound of restaurant"/></u>
<u n="2580" who="S0192">and you don't know how they're gonna react</u>
<u n="2581" who="S0190">and if the worst comes to the worst your dad can move bedroom I could get <unclear/> it doesn't bother me if they'd have been as loud as they were last time with the drums at half past three I would have start saying something</u>
<u n="2582" who="S0227">cos I I just go round and say I'm sorry erm if you said you were too old erm have you got younger since then cos you were too old</u>
<u n="2583" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2584" who="S0227">what's happening here? I asked you I gave you I asked for I asked two simple things I ask one tell me</u>
<u n="2585" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yes you're repeating yourself yeah</u>
<u n="2586" who="S0227">two and was this beyond your <trunc>comp</trunc> you know could you not understand that? you know</u>
<u n="2587" who="S0192">I've never understood I've got friends it was difficult in Korea because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I <pause dur="short"/> now we're a little bit older I don't like to stay up I mean it's still quite late but if I I don't like to be up any later than one thirty or two I feel terrible the next day if I stay up any later</u>
<u n="2588" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2589" who="S0192">I used to I used to stay up until the sun came up you know?</u>
<u n="2590" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2591" who="S0192">there was no problem so now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I would like to go out with people we would like to go out and start the evening at five or six or something like this but everyone will be like let's meet at ten or eleven</u>
<u n="2592" who="S0227" trans="overlap">or eleven yeah</u>
<u n="2593" who="S0192">I'm like I'm already quite tired by that point but like</u>
<u n="2594" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes exactly</u>
<u n="2595" who="S0192">am I going to have a couple of drinks that that's it?</u>
<u n="2596" who="S0190" trans="overlap">they're going out to the pubs here at nine o'clock at night to get their</u>
<u n="2597" who="S0227" trans="overlap">they're loading up with like a few erm erm well cases and stuff like that at home before they've even gone out they're quite they're sozzled before they go</u>
<u n="2598" who="S0192">it's some idea that if you're not up until the early hours you're not having a good time</u>
<u n="2599" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2600" who="S0192">well just move it forward so instead of starting at nine start at six and then finish at midnight rather than at three</u>
<u n="2601" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah they're not going out till about ten or eleven</u>
<u n="2602" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no er it makes <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I feel old because we're different other people don't think like that</u>
<u n="2603" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2604" who="S0192">but we we are totally like just <trunc>st</trunc></u>
<u n="2605" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was only saying the other week wasn't he? he said you know they're quite happy to stay out three five in the morning he said I'd rather be at home by two o'clock he said that's enough for me</u>
<u n="2606" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I'm the same <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I feel horrible if we stay out later than than because because it's</u>
<u n="2607" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well you've got good active lives haven't you and other things on and you your body pattern changes and you can't get it up so then it mucks the next day up and the next day's even worse</u>
<u n="2608" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah that's exactly it</u>
<u n="2609" who="S0190">you know</u>
<u n="2610" who="S0192">and you've gotta sort food for the week and all the kind of chores and everything and I mean regardless of what time we go to bed <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I will only ever sleep for seven hours <pause dur="short"/> once it's if we go to bed at five in the morning I'll sleep for seven hours and wake up and I just can't do that if I go to bed that late I just feel terrible so even then too I don't really like normally <trunc>s</trunc> have you ever heard of ghosting? it's a modern term meaning that you don't say goodbye at a party you just disappear it's called ghosting yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s terrible for it I try and have a go at her because she just disappears sometimes actually to the point where she doesn't tell me she's going she'll just go and I get quite angry with her because like</u>
<u n="2611" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well yeah because you won't know where she's going</u>
<u n="2612" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I don't know where you've gone or</u>
<u n="2613" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2614" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes yes she should tell you</u>
<u n="2615" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="2616" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah and also you're cutting my evening short because I'm worried about you</u>
<u n="2617" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2618" who="S0192">I don't know where you are or what's going on</u>
<u n="2619" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2620" who="S0192">she doesn't do it so much anymore but she she goes through a point where she goes I'm drunk I need to go to bed and she doesn't say anything to anyone else I will I'll have a word with her about it</u>
<u n="2621" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="2622" who="S0192">but erm</u>
<u n="2623" who="S0190">especially if you've got to go walk any distance on your own</u>
<u n="2624" who="S0192">thankfully we didn't usually have to but <pause dur="short"/> I worry where's she gone? what is she okay? what's going on?</u>
<u n="2625" who="S0190">well that's right yeah</u>
<u n="2626" who="S0192">you carry on</u>
<u n="2627" who="S0190">shall I call for the man for the bill?</u>
<u n="2628" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's just being consulted isn't it really?</u>
<u n="2629" who="S0192">do you tip in an establishment like this?</u>
<u n="2630" who="S0190">cos I didn't know I didn't look on the menu to see whether if there's ten percent</u>
<u n="2631" who="S0192">I don't know how it works in England</u>
<u n="2632" who="S0190">it depends generally speaking they always make it look they will say ten percent charge on it erm and then it's up to you but otherwise it's ten percent of the bill</u>
<u n="2633" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and if there's no ten percent you add a tip?</u>
<u n="2634" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="2635" who="S0192">I'll have a look at the bill</u>
<u n="2636" who="S0190" trans="overlap"><trunc>accord</trunc>according to what erm you say you know you reckon the meal's worth if they say</u>
<u n="2637" who="S0227">if this was Korea you wouldn't tip would you?</u>
<u n="2638" who="S0192">no no not at all</u>
<u n="2639" who="S0227">no they'd be <trunc>insult</trunc> they'd be insulted</u>
<u n="2640" who="S0192">yeah you don't tip in Korea <pause dur="short"/> okay I'll go and pay the bill I'll start</u>
<u n="2641" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no it's alright</u>
<u n="2642" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="2643" who="S0227">no no it's alright</u>
<u n="2644" who="S0192">how do you mean?</u>
<u n="2645" who="S0227">no don't worry about it er if you pay you can cover the tip if you like</u>
<u n="2646" who="S0192">dad I'm paying for the bill this is your birthday present</u>
<u n="2647" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no no no oh no no no you paid to get up here don't worry</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<event desc="background talk"/>
<u n="2648" who="S0227">I feel quite full anyway</u>
<u n="2649" who="S0190">no well and you eat so little</u>
<u n="2650" who="S0227">yeah no I just didn't feel that hungry to be fair</u>
<u n="2651" who="S0190">you drink the beer er I mind you did have two muffins and a handful of sweets</u>
<u n="2652" who="S0227">yes <pause dur="short"/> I had a starter</u>
<u n="2653" who="S0190">yeah the <trunc>star</trunc>starters were quite large tonight weren't they? not like there's like a little erm</u>
<u n="2654" who="S0227">the other meal was was too spicy for me it was too not spicy hot I yeah but I I was full I just didn't feel like eating anymore otherwise I'd have been eating all the er like the bit of potato erm saag aloo erm</u>
<u n="2655" who="S0190">that all went</u>
<u n="2656" who="S0227">no there was still one potato left in that</u>
<u n="2657" who="S0190">oh was it?</u>
<u n="2658" who="S0227">there was still one potato in there er I'd have eaten all my mushroom rice <event desc="sound of restaurant"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2659" who="S0190">I think they'll bring it to the table you don't have to go to the bar they'll come to the table with it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2660" who="S0227">well that was easy I can't see where he is</u>
<u n="2661" who="S0190" trans="overlap">he's standing he's standing at the bar I don't know whether they're serving him or not <pause dur="short"/> he could have just called for the bill no he's talking to them down there <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2662" who="S0227">go and get him or is it seven? <pause dur="long"/> we'll watch erm did you watch? <event desc="sound of restaurant"/></u>
<u n="2663" who="S0190"><event desc="sound of restaurant"/></u>
<u n="2664" who="S0227">no well whatever what time it's on we'll watch it afterwards if you want you asked if I wanted to watch Strictly when you get home <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2665" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="2666" who="S0227">so what sort of taste but what?</u>
<u n="2667" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well that it didn't start till nine did it? <event desc="sound of restaurant"/> so it'll still be going</u>
<u n="2668" who="S0227">yeah it's still recording we can watch it if you like <event desc="sound of restaurant"/> yeah well <event desc="sound of restaurant"/></u>
<u n="2669" who="S0190">I'm not tired as such I've just had a slow day to be honest till <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came round at lunch er when was it? he came round about <pause dur="short"/> up to eleven? and he was talking for quite a while yeah well we couldn't go yeah he came to see if I I've got a spare phone and I suggested he went down to get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s was the only one I could take the sim out and his phone wasn't erm er working at all he couldn't get it to switch on and he's got to go to Birmingham from tomorrow to take the <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> team on his own you know his team that he trains at the academy? he's got to take them all up to erm Birmingham I think he said erm and that and erm he said if any of the parents try to ring him that they can't make it or any contact he needs or he said nobody can get through to me so erm anyway erm he rang <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but they were just gonna go out so er said I'll go and see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and see what he's gonna do erm cos he his contract runs out erm ah</u>
<u n="2670" who="S0192">there's a mint</u>
<u n="2671" who="S0227">right how much was that?</u>
<u n="2672" who="S0192">enough <pause dur="short"/> happy birthday</u>
<u n="2673" who="S0190">thank you ever so much</u>
<u n="2674" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I didn't get you a card or anything</u>
<u n="2675" who="S0227">no no that's alright</u>
<u n="2676" who="S0192">no don't be silly</u>
<u n="2677" who="S0190">we didn't intend for you to pay</u>
<u n="2678" who="S0227">no no no not at all</u>
<u n="2679" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no I said I was gonna pay I wanted to take you out for food</u>
<u n="2680" who="S0227">take a contribution</u>
<u n="2681" who="S0192">no I'm not taking a contribution</u>
<u n="2682" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><event desc="unintelligible"/> er yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2683" who="S0192">are they mint? it looks like an After Eight or something</u>
<u n="2684" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="2685" who="S0227">but you you paid to come over here</u>
<u n="2686" who="S0190">mm it cost you a lot why don't?</u>
<u n="2687" who="S0192" trans="overlap">don't worry about it</u>
<u n="2688" who="S0190" trans="overlap">why don't why don't we go halves?</u>
<u n="2689" who="S0227" trans="overlap">come on I mean I haven't I haven't been for your birthday before have I?</u>
<u n="2690" who="S0227">are you sure?</u>
<u n="2691" who="S0192">yes</u>
<u n="2692" who="S0190">it's a lot of money <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2693" who="S0192">I'm recording and hopefully that'll cover it</u>
<u n="2694" who="S0227">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2695" who="S0190"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh I won't feel quite so bad then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2696" who="S0192">exactly</u>
<u n="2697" who="S0192">not a bad job hey? it's difficult to get the hours though I'm not gonna lie</u>
<u n="2698" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="2699" who="S0192">so far we've done fifty hours</u>
<u n="2700" who="S0190">it's lovely chocolate</u>
<u n="2701" who="S0192">mm it's not bad is it? we had erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friends came over and we I cooked for them and we had them food and we managed to record them for eight eight hours straight we were just talking yeah I mean that's about a hundred and forty pounds and you know and it's recording so it's good</u>
<u n="2702" who="S0227">there'll be a lot of ambient background noise</u>
<u n="2703" who="S0192">this may not be usable I'll have to listen to it later</u>
<u n="2704" who="S0227">although they can use that stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/> they can't hear what they're saying</u>
<u n="2705" who="S0192">yeah well hopefully it'll be okay but I mean people were singing Happy Birthday earlier</u>
<u n="2706" who="S0227">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="2707" who="S0192">all all sorts of stuff so we'll see</u>
<u n="2708" who="S0190">at least the children moved</u>
<u n="2709" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2710" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I thought that was going a bit of a nightmare</u>
<u n="2711" who="S0192">yeah yeah I had to stop it earlier cos it was like it's just no good <pause dur="short"/> okay are we ready?</u>
<u n="2712" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="2713" who="S0192">that was good</u>
<u n="2714" who="S0190">that was lovely</u>
<u n="2715" who="S0192">happy birthday</u>
<u n="2716" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh sorry</u>
<u n="2717" who="S0227">yes thank you</u>
<u n="2718" who="S0192">fifty-five</u>
<u n="2719" who="S0227">yeah don't remind me</u>
<u n="2720" who="S0192">time marches on</u>
<u n="2721" who="S0227">yeah one day this will be you</u>
<u n="2722" who="S0192">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> but if I don't have a son it may not be reciprocated</u>
<u n="2723" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="2724" who="S0192">we'll see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I we were talking about adoption earlier <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I thought that the best best route to adoption would be to adopt a child</u>
<u n="2725" who="S0227">about fourteen</u>
<u n="2726" who="S0192">when they're about eighteen pay for them to go to university and then cut a deal with them that says you know I'll pay for you for uni and then you cover me when I'm old</u>
<u n="2727" who="S0227">when I yeah er they'll be able to choose the old people's home they're gonna put you in</u>
<u n="2728" who="S0192">yeah basically <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2729" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2730" who="S0192">thank you very much</u>
<u n="2731" who="S0227">thank you</u>
<u n="2732" who="S0192">thank you goodnight <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2733" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay sir?</u>
<u n="2734" who="S0192">okay thank you</u>
<u n="2735" who="S0227">thank you very much</u>
<u n="2736" who="S0192">oh it's cooled down not too bad though that's a nice restaurant</u>
<u n="2737" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="2738" who="S0190">it is isn't it? been two or three times haven't we?</u>
<u n="2739" who="S0227">yeah we went for one of my birthdays didn't we?</u>
<u n="2740" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yep yes erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came over</u>
<u n="2741" who="S0227" trans="overlap">and and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="2742" who="S0190" trans="overlap">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="2743" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2744" who="S0190">yeah and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> come? yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came as well</u>
<u n="2745" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="2746" who="S0192">was that your fiftieth?</u>
<u n="2747" who="S0190">I was gonna say yes I think it was your fiftieth</u>
<u n="2748" who="S0227" trans="overlap">my fiftieth</u>
<u n="2749" who="S0192">blimey five years ago</u>
<u n="2750" who="S0190" trans="overlap">the special one</u>
<u n="2751" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2752" who="S0190">I know</u>
<u n="2753" who="S0192">it flies</u>
<u n="2754" who="S0227">oh was it? no it couldn't it might not have been my fiftieth cos I had a surprise party</u>
<u n="2755" who="S0190">we never did</u>
<u n="2756" who="S0227">I thought you all turned up <pause dur="short"/> at my house you did</u>
<u n="2757" who="S0190">you all <trunc>tur</trunc> well you all turned up at my house <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2758" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes yeah oh <trunc>ye</trunc> our house sorry</u>
<u n="2759" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2760" who="S0227">our house erm</u>
<u n="2761" who="S0190"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2762" who="S0227">remember we went</u>
<u n="2763" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was already there wasn't she?</u>
<u n="2764" who="S0227" trans="overlap">we went away we were we were away</u>
<u n="2765" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh yes that's right yeah</u>
<u n="2766" who="S0227">and they all turned up</u>
<u n="2767" who="S0190">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="2768" who="S0227" trans="overlap">so it wasn't the fiftieth</u>
<u n="2769" who="S0190">no I knew it was all happening</u>
<u n="2770" who="S0227">yes it wasn't our it wasn't fiftieth in there at all</u>
<u n="2771" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="2772" who="S0227">it's been since then</u>
<u n="2773" who="S0192">yeah it was after that</u>
<u n="2774" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="2775" who="S0192">for <pause dur="long"/> it's not far from your house either is it?</u>
<u n="2776" who="S0190">no it's not</u>
<u n="2777" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's not too far</u>
<u n="2778" who="S0190">it's quite handy</u>
<u n="2779" who="S0192">it's only round the corner <pause dur="long"/> do you ever go to Domino's?</u>
<u n="2780" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="2781" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="2782" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="2783" who="S0227">that's</u>
<u n="2784" who="S0190" trans="overlap">to be fair we don't eat out that much at all really</u>
<u n="2785" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="2786" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="2787" who="S0190">dad usually cooks a curry on Friday or Saturday don't you?</u>
<u n="2788" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2789" who="S0190">sometimes you'll cook something and we'll have something a bit different erm <pause dur="short"/> and may have my parents over at the weekend sometimes on Sunday lunch</u>
<u n="2790" who="S0192">British people in general don't really eat out too much do they that much?</u>
<u n="2791" who="S0227" trans="overlap">does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cook?</u>
<u n="2792" who="S0192">not really no</u>
<u n="2793" who="S0227">so are you doing most of the cooking?</u>
<u n="2794" who="S0192">yeah I do all of the cooking</u>
<u n="2795" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="2796" who="S0192">yes</u>
<u n="2797" who="S0190">a bit like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he does all the cooking really I don't whether</u>
<u n="2798" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's strange isn't it? men nowadays seem to be cooking more out of all of my male friends pretty much all of my couple friends sorry pretty much the men explicitly cook er</u>
<u n="2799" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2800" who="S0192">always <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can cook we just have a a bit of a deal I don't really like washing up so</u>
<u n="2801" who="S0227">so she does that does she?</u>
<u n="2802" who="S0192">she does the washing up I do the cooking but</u>
<u n="2803" who="S0227">right</u>
<u n="2804" who="S0192">she sous chefs</u>
<u n="2805" who="S0227">right okay</u>
<u n="2806" who="S0192" trans="overlap">she still goes through the process with me I'm just kind of in control of the whole thing</u>
<u n="2807" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2808" who="S0192">and I do wash up because there's quite often she's not actually there when I cook and I have to wash up as I'm going along</u>
<u n="2809" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah of course</u>
<u n="2810" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and do all that sort of stuff</u>
<u n="2811" who="S0227">is she like watching the telly or something?</u>
<u n="2812" who="S0192">what when she's cook when she's washing up?</u>
<u n="2813" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no when you're when no when you're cooking you said she's not often here she she's</u>
<u n="2814" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no no I mean if she's at uni or if she's doing whatever</u>
<u n="2815" who="S0227" trans="overlap">oh I see what you mean</u>
<u n="2816" who="S0192">if she's teaching or</u>
<u n="2817" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2818" who="S0192">whatever yeah so but erm I prefer cooking to washing up</u>
<u n="2819" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="2820" who="S0192">I'll wash up if I have to</u>
<u n="2821" who="S0227">I cook and wash don't I?</u>
<u n="2822" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah you do</u>
<u n="2823" who="S0227">I cook and dry</u>
<u n="2824" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2825" who="S0227">don't I?</u>
<u n="2826" who="S0190">no you cook and</u>
<u n="2827" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I criticise the washing up</u>
<u n="2828" who="S0190" trans="overlap">you cook and pick</u>
<u n="2829" who="S0227">I <trunc>crit</trunc> I criticise</u>
<u n="2830" who="S0190">oh he is the worse worse dryer upper</u>
<u n="2831" who="S0192">world's worst?</u>
<u n="2832" who="S0227">well I'd much</u>
<u n="2833" who="S0190" trans="overlap">dryer upper</u>
<u n="2834" who="S0192">worst dryer upper</u>
<u n="2835" who="S0227">I'm not I'm quite good because I spot all the defects</u>
<u n="2836" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2837" who="S0227">and like no that's not the that's still dirty</u>
<u n="2838" who="S0192">so he nitpicks?</u>
<u n="2839" who="S0227">no it's like yeah</u>
<u n="2840" who="S0190" trans="overlap"><trunc>ye</trunc> yeah he picks it up and he goes <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="2841" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2842" who="S0227">still dirty put it back</u>
<u n="2843" who="S0190" trans="overlap">like this</u>
<u n="2844" who="S0192" trans="overlap">what's that? put it back do it again</u>
<u n="2845" who="S0227">there's still this bit missed a bit</u>
<u n="2846" who="S0190">and it's probably you know you</u>
<u n="2847" who="S0227" trans="overlap">was it yesterday or the day before? I sent a pot <trunc>ba</trunc> the same pot back three times</u>
<u n="2848" who="S0192">I do</u>
<u n="2849" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I was doing it on purpose</u>
<u n="2850" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I do it to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yeah</u>
<u n="2851" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah and it's still dirty</u>
<u n="2852" who="S0190">yeah but the thing is</u>
<u n="2853" who="S0227" trans="overlap">she doesn't thank me that I'm the last line of defence you know what I mean or she's going oh I feel sick</u>
<u n="2854" who="S0190" trans="overlap">oh no stop it</u>
<u n="2855" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2856" who="S0227">right well thank me for like</u>
<u n="2857" who="S0190">so you make me sound so have you ever had a dirty plate? no because if I get it out of the cupboard or the washer dishwasher</u>
<u n="2858" who="S0227" trans="overlap">you know oh</u>
<u n="2859" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and it's dirty you put it back</u>
<u n="2860" who="S0190" trans="overlap">and it's dirty I wouldn't use it</u>
<u n="2861" who="S0227">I'd say oh that must have slipped through and past my so</u>
<u n="2862" who="S0190" trans="overlap"><trunc>w</trunc> oh dear it it takes me twice as long to wash up with him</u>
<u n="2863" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's quality assurance</u>
<u n="2864" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is the same though she does miss quite a bit and I kind of take the argument if I treated the cooking with the same disregard</u>
<u n="2865" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="2866" who="S0192">as your washing up</u>
<u n="2867" who="S0227">yeah I said</u>
<u n="2868" who="S0192" trans="overlap">you'd be eating crap</u>
<u n="2869" who="S0227"><trunc>exact</trunc> I said if you went into a restaurant and they gave you a plate that looked like that would you eat off it? no</u>
<u n="2870" who="S0190" trans="overlap">but you wouldn't you'd send it back but I wouldn't</u>
<u n="2871" who="S0227" trans="overlap">exactly that's what I'm doing I'm sending it back <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2872" who="S0190">yeah why?</u>
<u n="2873" who="S0227">but the look oh my and the and the comment afterwards it's like oh</u>
<u n="2874" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2875" who="S0190">I tell you something</u>
<u n="2876" who="S0227" trans="overlap">it's like saying look</u>
<u n="2877" who="S0190" trans="overlap">if it wasn't for the sake of my of my saucepans I'd hit him over the head with it</u>
<u n="2878" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2879" who="S0190">I tell you I get so cross</u>
<u n="2880" who="S0227" trans="overlap">I'm saying</u>
<u n="2881" who="S0192">you'd break them on that head</u>
<u n="2882" who="S0227">I'm saying to her look don't thank me for pointing this out but she's taking it all the wrong way <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2883" who="S0192">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I kind of have our different roles a little bit she doesn't deal with money at all or I kind of</u>
<u n="2884" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no I don't deal with money only spend it</u>
<u n="2885" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2886" who="S0190"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2887" who="S0192">I plan everything I do all the emails and all the</u>
<u n="2888" who="S0227" trans="overlap">actually no she's quite frugal yes</u>
<u n="2889" who="S0192">she's quite frugal?</u>
<u n="2890" who="S0227">yeah she's quite good yeah</u>
<u n="2891" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will do that</u>
<u n="2892" who="S0192"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s quite frugal too which is beneficial</u>
<u n="2893" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="2894" who="S0192">I can't imagine being in a relationship with somebody that just spends money all the time you know?</u>
<u n="2895" who="S0227">if you if you've got yeah it's it's better to have two people on the hand break on the roller coaster than none of you and the damn thing's going</u>
<u n="2896" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2897" who="S0227">like like billyo</u>
<u n="2898" who="S0192">his analogies and <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2899" who="S0190">oh yes the analogies</u>
<u n="2900" who="S0192" trans="overlap">now I know where I can them from</u>
<u n="2901" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="2902" who="S0190">but the trouble is he's he's quite frugal on the way you know which is fair dos I tend to but the trouble is <pause dur="short"/> yes with the money but he'll like won't use the last bit of er kitchen roll and if you're using the kitchen roll he won't use the dish cloth</u>
<u n="2903" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh why not the last bit?</u>
<u n="2904" who="S0190">no we don't use the last bit on the roll we don't use the last piece of toilet paper</u>
<u n="2905" who="S0192">why? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2906" who="S0190">cos he just doesn't he won't</u>
<u n="2907" who="S0227">the dishcloth it's like oh it's a dishcloth it harbours so many germs and it's oh my god</u>
<u n="2908" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2909" who="S0190" trans="overlap">so he cleans his glasses on three pieces of kitchen roll and then just drops them in the bin and it's such a waste</u>
<u n="2910" who="S0192">a first world problem</u>
<u n="2911" who="S0190">well</u>
<u n="2912" who="S0227">I don't actually dry those ones a lot it's just water</u>
<u n="2913" who="S0192" trans="overlap">why don't you use the last bit of the toilet roll?</u>
<u n="2914" who="S0190">cos he doesn't</u>
<u n="2915" who="S0227">cos it's like stuck to the it's like unclean it's stuck to it</u>
<u n="2916" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="2917" who="S0227">it's stuck to it it's like you pull it off and there's nothing left of it</u>
<u n="2918" who="S0192">it just rips apart</u>
<u n="2919" who="S0190">no it doesn't that's a load of rubbish for goodness sake</u>
<u n="2920" who="S0192">I've been used to cheap toilet roll for a while now</u>
<u n="2921" who="S0190" trans="overlap">well so do we we only pay ninety-nine P from Iceland</u>
<u n="2922" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2923" who="S0190">for four so</u>
<u n="2924" who="S0192">you don't wanna go too cheap with toilet roll though do you? it's just</u>
<u n="2925" who="S0227">no there's there's three grades there's thin</u>
<u n="2926" who="S0190" trans="overlap">go on then</u>
<u n="2927" who="S0227" trans="overlap">thinner and oh</u>
<u n="2928" who="S0192">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh why was it at school you always got the worst at school did you get that like</u>
<u n="2929" who="S0190" trans="overlap">awful</u>
<u n="2930" who="S0192" trans="overlap">greaseproof paper that's like?</u>
<u n="2931" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2932" who="S0227">oh yeah</u>
<u n="2933" who="S0190" trans="overlap">cor you felt as it was cutting as you</u>
<u n="2934" who="S0192" trans="overlap">oh gosh it's horrible</u>
<u n="2935" who="S0190">mm and you'd be desperate</u>
<u n="2936" who="S0192">at school</u>
<u n="2937" who="S0190">and you'd be hanging on and you'd just be dash when you got off the bus</u>
<u n="2938" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that was horrible</u>
<u n="2939" who="S0190" trans="overlap">fortunately our bus stopped <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2940" who="S0192">it hurt</u>
<u n="2941" who="S0190">it did hurt</u>
<u n="2942" who="S0192" trans="overlap">why would you why would you do that?</u>
<u n="2943" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="2944" who="S0192">encourage children not to go at school</u>
<u n="2945" who="S0190" trans="overlap">even I'd rather have used newspaper</u>
<u n="2946" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2947" who="S0190">at least that's soft</u>
<u n="2948" who="S0192">definitely</u>
<u n="2949" who="S0227">dad used to wait until about a hundred and</u>
<u n="2950" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="2951" who="S0227">I never bothered that never er bothered me</u>
<u n="2952" who="S0192"><vocal desc="misc"/> the type of food you eat in Korea you just can't wait</u>
<u n="2953" who="S0190">you're not doing this are you now?</u>
<u n="2954" who="S0192">oh yeah it's recording</u>
<u n="2955" who="S0190">you're not</u>
<u n="2956" who="S0192"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's recording</u>
<u n="2957" who="S0190">oh you horrible</u>
<u n="2958" who="S0192" trans="overlap">it's it's heard worse so <vocal desc="laugh"/> I've had to cut stuff with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> if I talk to him he starts talking about incriminating stuff and I'm like oh god I have to</u>
<u n="2959" who="S0227" trans="overlap"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="2960" who="S0192">there's a little button on here that I press</u>
<u n="2961" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="2962" who="S0192">and it makes a mark so I can go back to that point</u>
<u n="2963" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="2964" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and I kind of have to like cut it out</u>
<u n="2965" who="S0227">yeah that's the that this could use editing</u>
<u n="2966" who="S0192">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so no this don't worry it's fine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2967" who="S0227">have you heard from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="2968" who="S0192">no no he's a terrible friend an absolutely terrible friend</u>
<u n="2969" who="S0227">friendships you do have to keep spinning those plates</u>
<u n="2970" who="S0192">yeah he's not very good at that</u>
<u n="2971" who="S0227">he thinks I'm seeing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> next Friday</u>
<u n="2972" who="S0192">I'm being a bit stubborn at the minute I've</u>
<u n="2973" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2974" who="S0192">I've spent too much time trying to instigate it</u>
<u n="2975" who="S0227">yes</u>
<u n="2976" who="S0192">and he's not reciprocating</u>
<u n="2977" who="S0227" trans="overlap">no it has to be</u>
<u n="2978" who="S0192" trans="overlap">and so right now I'm like</u>
<u n="2979" who="S0227">it has to be two way traffic</u>
<u n="2980" who="S0192">I'm a little bit too busy to care at the minute so</u>
<u n="2981" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah yeah no it has to be two way traffic</u>
<u n="2982" who="S0192">erm I'm sure he'll get in contact with me at some point <pause dur="short"/> it's a shame</u>
<u n="2983" who="S0227">I'm sure if his relationship goes with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="2984" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="2985" who="S0227">you'll be the first to know <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="2986" who="S0192">oh <pause dur="short"/> it's getting on a bit now isn't it?</u>
<u n="2987" who="S0227">sorry?</u>
<u n="2988" who="S0192">must be fairly late</u>
<u n="2989" who="S0227">yes it's</u>
<u n="2990" who="S0192" trans="overlap">ten to ten</u>
<u n="2991" who="S0227">yeah it's ten minutes to ten</u>
<u n="2992" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="2993" who="S0192">what time do you normally go to bed?</u>
<u n="2994" who="S0227">er</u>
<u n="2995" who="S0192" trans="overlap">on a weekday if we don't do such ten</u>
<u n="2996" who="S0227" trans="overlap">ten thirty</u>
<u n="2997" who="S0192">if we have a glass or something</u>
<u n="2998" who="S0227">ten thirty</u>
<u n="2999" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="3000" who="S0192">yeah same as <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I really ten thirty</u>
<u n="3001" who="S0190">in my <unclear/></u>
<u n="3002" who="S0192">eleven maybe sometimes</u>
<u n="3003" who="S0227" trans="overlap">weekend later</u>
<u n="3004" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="3005" who="S0227">weekend about twelve but</u>
<u n="3006" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="3007" who="S0227">between eleven and twelve</u>
<u n="3008" who="S0192">do you ever go to bed before ten?</u>
<u n="3009" who="S0227">no</u>
<u n="3010" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="3011" who="S0192">sometimes <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I just like oh I feel terrible but I really want to go to bed</u>
<u n="3012" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="3013" who="S0192">I'm just so tired <pause dur="short"/> I mean we wake up at six thirty or seven for university so</u>
<u n="3014" who="S0190" trans="overlap">no you do</u>
<u n="3015" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah well it's er yeah</u>
<u n="3016" who="S0190">we don't we often don't often get out of bed until nine</u>
<u n="3017" who="S0192">oh <unclear>fair</unclear> right</u>
<u n="3018" who="S0227" trans="overlap">but that's one week weekends</u>
<u n="3019" who="S0190" trans="overlap">but weekends I mean</u>
<u n="3020" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="3021" who="S0190">I</u>
<u n="3022" who="S0227">erm</u>
<u n="3023" who="S0190" trans="overlap">I</u>
<u n="3024" who="S0227">I need at least seven hours at least</u>
<u n="3025" who="S0192">yeah seven hours for me as well</u>
<u n="3026" who="S0227">I can't function very well on less</u>
<u n="3027" who="S0192">no</u>
<u n="3028" who="S0190">we get up and make a cup of tea don't we? usually any time between half past eight and nine o'clock</u>
<u n="3029" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="3030" who="S0190" trans="overlap">and if it's you see I have to take a tablet half an hour before I eat and so we make a drink</u>
<u n="3031" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="3032" who="S0190">and then lay in bed for half an hour so</u>
<u n="3033" who="S0192">I feel groggy if I sleep too long and I can't</u>
<u n="3034" who="S0227">yes I find if <trunc>th</trunc>there's a there's a balance that if I go over that I feel groggy</u>
<u n="3035" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="3036" who="S0227">if I feel if it's under that I feel I feel sleep deprived</u>
<u n="3037" who="S0192">yeah definitely <pause dur="short"/> and the worst thing I hate pulling all nighters there's been a few instances where I'm travelling and I just can't</u>
<u n="3038" who="S0227" trans="overlap">sleep no</u>
<u n="3039" who="S0192" trans="overlap">I can't go to sleep but there's no option yeah</u>
<u n="3040" who="S0227" trans="overlap">well you've got to keep <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="3041" who="S0192" trans="overlap">there's no option and I just feel terrible <pause dur="short"/> your cognitive functions</u>
<u n="3042" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="3043" who="S0192">just go right out the window I can't <pause dur="short"/> it's won't work do you normally go through the fence?</u>
<u n="3044" who="S0190">pardon?</u>
<u n="3045" who="S0227">there's a gate</u>
<u n="3046" who="S0192">yeah sorry through the gate</u>
<u n="3047" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="3048" who="S0192">go through or go through the fence</u>
<u n="3049" who="S0190">thank you he's a gentleman</u>
<u n="3050" who="S0227">I did I opened it</u>
<u n="3051" who="S0190" trans="overlap">you didn't get that from your dad</u>
<u n="3052" who="S0227">I opened it</u>
<u n="3053" who="S0192" trans="overlap">did I not? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="3054" who="S0190">no</u>
<u n="3055" who="S0227">er</u>
<u n="3056" who="S0192">does he not do that?</u>
<u n="3057" who="S0190">no <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="3058" who="S0192">does this shut? <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah</u>
<u n="3059" who="S0190">the light's gone again why?</u>
<u n="3060" who="S0227">dunno maybe it's</u>
<u n="3061" who="S0190" trans="overlap">some space</u>
<u n="3062" who="S0227"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="3063" who="S0192">I take it you've had no more problem with theft or people sort of thing?</u>
<u n="3064" who="S0190" trans="overlap">don't speak too soon</u>
<u n="3065" who="S0227" trans="overlap">there you go</u>
<u n="3066" who="S0190">we had a bit of street theatre</u>
<u n="3067" who="S0192">street theatre?</u>
<u n="3068" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="3069" who="S0227" trans="overlap">yeah all night fights</u>
<u n="3070" who="S0190">all swearing and women and screaming and shouting</u>
<u n="3071" who="S0192" trans="overlap"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="3072" who="S0190">sometimes it's not very often though</u>
<u n="3073" who="S0192">is that locked properly?</u>
<u n="3074" who="S0227">yeah</u>
<u n="3075" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yes that'll be</u>
<u n="3076" who="S0192">ah</u>
<u n="3077" who="S0227">oh</u>
<u n="3078" who="S0192">yeah <anon type="place"/> feels quite safe <pause dur="short"/> which has been nice I haven't</u>
<u n="3079" who="S0190" trans="overlap">good even get is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s light on?</u>
<u n="3080" who="S0227"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="3081" who="S0227">oh right</u>
<u n="3082" who="S0192">hasn't been left on <pause dur="short"/> do you take your shoes off before or not?</u>
<u n="3083" who="S0190">we're meant to I do it we made a big thing because <pause dur="short"/> at this one stage <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was wearing a lot of trainers and it's like and he'd come in or his mates would come in then if you go upstairs with trainers on you leave all the tread and if they're wet and they're mucky</u>
<u n="3084" who="S0192">yeah</u>
<u n="3085" who="S0190">so we've always said that <trunc>we</trunc> if the back door you we don't usually use the front door anyway and then you put take your shoes off or put slippers on so but when we come in the front door if it's late and night and it's been dry and my shoes are not dirty <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="3086" who="S0192">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm tired now</u>
<u n="3087" who="S0190">well you travelled too and obviously that's pretty tiring</u>
<u n="3088" who="S0192" trans="overlap">yes it takes a while as well</u>
<u n="3089" who="S0190" trans="overlap">it does doesn't it?</u>
<u n="3090" who="S0192">it's not very far but <pause dur="short"/> don't see why I take three hours to do a hundred and ten miles</u>
<u n="3091" who="S0190">well especially on train</u>
<u n="3092" who="S0192">yeah I know</u>
<u n="3093" who="S0190">it's supposed to be fast isn't it?</u>
<u n="3094" who="S0192">I was on a fast train as well</u>
<u n="3095" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="3096" who="S0192">it's always really busy that line as well cos you go right through London and</u>
<u n="3097" who="S0190">yeah</u>
<u n="3098" who="S0192">it's not too pleasant</u>
<u n="3099" who="S0190">how long how long did you say it took you? three hours?</u>
<u n="3100" who="S0192">about three hours yeah maybe maybe two</u>
<u n="3101" who="S0190" trans="overlap">just sitting on a train</u>
<u n="3102" who="S0192" trans="overlap">no I got on a faster train today so it would be two and a half but it's gonna take me four four and a half to get home</u>
<u n="3103" who="S0190" trans="overlap">yeah you were saying the that mm</u>
<u n="3104" who="S0192">it's a lot a long time to do a hundred and ten miles</u>
<u n="3105" who="S0190"><event desc="sound of bang"/> yeah</u>
<u n="3106" who="S0192">that's just like third world speeds it's not it's not <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="3107" who="S0190">oh I'll have to <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="3108" who="S0192">oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
