<text id="SNMA">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:21:34</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-07-29</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0421 S0423</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Manchester</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Melon, helicopter, cinema, weather, sun cream, medical bills, doctor’s surgery, receptionists, hospitals, punctured lung, surgery, squeamishness, irrational fears, crowds, </topics>
		<activity>Father and daughter converse on the way to the cinema</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0421">
				<exactage>18</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lancashire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lytham St Annes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2>Hungarian</l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0423">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bolton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Manchester, England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Mossley</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Customer Services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0421">no I've not had any yet</u>
<u n="2" who="S0423">have you not? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0421">no it looks good though that melon</u>
<u n="4" who="S0423">mm helicopter</u>
<u n="5" who="S0421">where? oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0423">must be new we're not seeing the <unclear/> one are we?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="8" who="S0423">I don't want to pay thirty pounds to see it</u>
<u n="9" who="S0421">what time is it? <pause dur="short"/> nearly twelve there's one on at twelve twenty</u>
<u n="10" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0421">that's two D</u>
<u n="12" who="S0423">oh right what time is it now?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0421">twelve <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0423">twelve?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0423" trans="overlap">right we'll see the twelve twenty-one will we?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0423"><unclear/> Ant Man do you want to see that?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0423">okay let's head off then</u>
<u n="21" who="S0421">if that's the right cinema I'm looking at anyway</u>
<u n="22" who="S0423"><anon type="place"/> Cineworld</u>
<u n="23" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> Cineworld</u>
<u n="24" who="S0423">yeah there is an Imax there now <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> plus it's not as big as the one <unclear/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0421">mm but it should be if Imax has got standard size doesn't it?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0423">I know you would think <unclear/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0421">you'd be disappointed if you went to the Imax and it was just like a normal screen</u>
<u n="28" who="S0423">yeah especially with the prices they charge <pause dur="long"/> it's a nice day too wish we went outside and done something</u>
<u n="29" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0423">shouldn't we?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0421">no <pause dur="long"/> should have put sun cream on?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0423">you did?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0421">yeah I should have done <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0423">yeah although I don't think you're going to be seeing a lot of sun in the cinema</u>
<u n="35" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0423">are you?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0423">oh am I going the right way now? <unclear>think I am</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <pause dur="long"/> the receptionist there was trying to say oh we might not treat him we'll charge you your grandad</u>
<u n="39" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well I don't know if he told you</u>
<u n="40" who="S0423">eh?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0421">I don't know if he told you but they sent him a letter</u>
<u n="42" who="S0423">well he he didn't but I mean he was saying on the way oh <pause dur="short"/> erm I think I might be charged I said no don't be silly you're not you won't be charged then then the receptionist saying you should have been sent a letter</u>
<u n="43" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0423">and then I had a look at it and I thought oh right and then erm I think grandad explained that he did send away</u>
<u n="45" who="S0421">yeah the the documents</u>
<u n="46" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0421">cos he got a letter on Monday and our postman comes at midday sometimes our postman comes at three o clock in the afternoon so that's when we got this letter and it was like oh if you don't send us these photocopies you may be charged but even if you do send us these photocopies you still may be charged if you're not eligible erm so yeah anyway we've not got so grandad had to go yesterday to <anon type="place"/> to get these photocopies like cos the post office the local post office doesn't do it neither does the newsagents so he got them and he sent them off erm and it says we <trunc>ne</trunc> we got it on Monday and then it says they need to have it by Thursday which is it's a bit short notice really isn't it?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0423">oh yeah so they must have a note on the system cos she said oh you need to be interviewed by another supervisor or erm <pause dur="short"/> they must have had a note saying may be not entitled to treatment</u>
<u n="49" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0423">and to you know wait for the interview but this this receptionist a little bit of information she gets it all blown out of proportion she starts saying</u>
<u n="51" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0423">she starts making up her own things</u>
<u n="53" who="S0421">that's what reception oh right did you? you know that? you know that reception?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0421">well cos you know when we went to the doctor's and they wouldn't take us? and then we were and <trunc>the</trunc></u>
<u n="56" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0421"><trunc>c</trunc> and they were like no you're not in our area so we rang the NHS and they were like you <trunc>should</trunc> they should've taken you</u>
<u n="58" who="S0423">yeah I know</u>
<u n="59" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and then the surgery said oh no it never happened they never came in</u>
<u n="60" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="61" who="S0421">well mammy left a review on the NHS website for that surgery and she said how disappointed she was with the receptionist that they didn't take them on</u>
<u n="62" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0421">and she the the surgery replied and said I'm sorry but you weren't in our catchment area so they actually acknowledged that we went on the website so now mammy is sending a formal complaint she's written an email</u>
<u n="64" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah now they've admitted it yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0421">yeah cos now they've admitted that she's been</u>
<u n="66" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> how stupid is that if you're going to deny that someone's been and then answer their comment on the internet saying oh well our system wouldn't accept you</u>
<u n="68" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well it just shows you that <unclear/> this woman this morning</u>
<u n="69" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0423">they went in said oh he's going to have to pay and I said well erm he's he he's an E U citizen</u>
<u n="71" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0423">and she said oh that that doesn't mean he doesn't have to pay he that doesn't give you everything erm I said well I've got a a card and when I go to Europe I I I thought that I could have whatever treatment's needed and she said no no that'll just cover a consultation</u>
<u n="73" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0423">I said oh right oh I didn't know that</u>
<u n="75" who="S0421">no</u>
<u n="76" who="S0423">and then it got me thinking oh maybe</u>
<u n="77" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0423">cos then she said oh when I was in Amsterdam erm I had to go and see a doctor and I had to pay but it didn't you know it it just covered me for the erm <pause dur="short"/> the consultation</u>
<u n="79" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0423">so then erm <pause dur="short"/> so then oh right <pause dur="long"/> erm I said oh I I thought with the er with the card you get <trunc>what</trunc>whatever treatment it's a reciprocal arrangement you get whatever treatments you need and she said no I had to pay for my prescription in Amsterdam they said well <unclear/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0421" trans="overlap">you pay for it over here as well</u>
<u n="82" who="S0423">well well you pay a a set fee</u>
<u n="83" who="S0421">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0423">but in other European countries a lot of them you pay whatever the medicine costs</u>
<u n="85" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0423">and I said well yeah in lots of European countries you have to pay for a prescription that's what that <trunc>i</trunc> so obviously all you had to pay was for the prescription</u>
<u n="87" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0423">so she wasn't charged for treatment cos she probably didn't have treatment so you know? she's just making things up herself cos I said well he's you know? he's he's got the card and said oh that's er that doesn't mean this is very expensive you know? and I said yeah but we have a reciprocal arrangement with EU countries and she said erm well no no you can't just have anything if if if you just have them treated being allowed to be treated for anything we'd be full of people coming over for treatment</u>
<u n="89" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0423">it's just making up our own thing</u>
<u n="91" who="S0421">yeah but you'd get treated for free at home</u>
<u n="92" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I I mean I can't quite <unclear/> thinking well yeah you basically we bill them anyway</u>
<u n="93" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0423">so your grandad's thinking oh well can they invoice me? I'll go and see the medical people that I've got back home in <anon type="place"/> I think just wait for the the interview because I just thought she doesn't know what she's on about but then I said oh have you got that letter? so I started reading that that letter</u>
<u n="95" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0423">kind of indicated that he might have to pay because</u>
<u n="97" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0423">it said if you're not normally resident</u>
<u n="99" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0423">I thought you know I can't believe this yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0421" trans="overlap">it's ridiculous isn't it?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0423">so then anyway this this <pause dur="short"/> person come for the interview said oh it's just that we hadn't received the eye grandad said oh he's sent it off</u>
<u n="103" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0423">erm Monday but she said okay if you've got the <pause dur="short"/> the NHS thing in your passport I'll just make a copy of that for them to come back and say right okay that's all we need</u>
<u n="105" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0423">it's she didn't mention anything oh you might have to pay you have to pay erm you know? and this receptionist</u>
<u n="107" who="S0421">I know</u>
<u n="108" who="S0423" trans="overlap">they're they're bloody <trunc>ridi</trunc> they're ridiculous receptionists you give them a bit of information</u>
<u n="109" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I know yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0423">they think they have you know? they they <unclear/> just so stupid</u>
<u n="111" who="S0421" trans="overlap">like whenever whenever we ring up for the doctor's they're like oh so what is it that's wrong? and then if you tell them they're like right well we can't that doesn't sound very serious so we can't make erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> an appointment for you <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0423">so they have to be half dead?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0421">yeah well <trunc>we</trunc> so</u>
<u n="114" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well you know? I think they are told by doctors now to ask that it's a bit intrusive isn't it?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0423">especially if you just walk in and just want to make an appointment</u>
<u n="117" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0423">and you have to say what's wrong in front of the waiting room</u>
<u n="119" who="S0421">you <trunc>ju</trunc> you could just lie <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0421">because erm I don't know what I was going in for it think it was something around my ear or something</u>
<u n="122" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="123" who="S0421">and erm it didn't hurt or anything but it was a bit fuzzy or something the sound</u>
<u n="124" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0421">and erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah but it <trunc>i</trunc>it was really annoying me so mammy was like yeah well we'll ring in the morning and you can go in and erm at first she said oh yeah it's just eh that's what she said and the receptionist was like right well we'll make you an appointment in two weeks or something</u>
<u n="126" who="S0423">jesus</u>
<u n="127" who="S0421" trans="overlap">and then so mammy was like yeah but she's in a lot of pain you know? she can't sleep at night and she's like oh oh right then you can come in this morning</u>
<u n="128" who="S0423">mm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0423">so you just have to tell them you're in pain</u>
<u n="131" who="S0421">yeah but then when you go into the doctor's it's just like they don't mind like</u>
<u n="132" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0421">they they don't know what you've said</u>
<u n="134" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0421">and the receptionist thinks oh you know? like but like for all like if someone's going in and they're like not necessarily in pain and they can see something that's wrong with them and then the receptionist like oh no you're going to have to wait two they might be in agony by the time they've waited two weeks</u>
<u n="136" who="S0423">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0421">they don't know what it is</u>
<u n="138" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I think it is it I mean they do have problems cos I think it is sort of a lot of people go in there's nothing wrong with the and they're just trying to weed out people aren't they? so I know why they're doing it but it's very frustrating if if you do have a problem and it's like they're trying to not see you isn't it?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/> I know but you'd rather people who don't have anything wrong with them go rather than people think oh there might not be nothing <trunc>wr</trunc> there might be nothing wrong with me so they don't go and then they end up with like a problem</u>
<u n="140" who="S0423">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I just think <vocal desc="misc"/> cos they are under a lot of pressure aren't they?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0421">yeah but if you look up anything online it's like you should have this seen by a doctor</u>
<u n="142" who="S0423">yeah well that's why you shouldn't look anything up online</u>
<u n="143" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0423">should just go to the doctor if you're ill don't <trunc>bo</trunc>bother looking it up online</u>
<u n="145" who="S0421">no but if you look up something and you're like oh right I've had like a pain or something <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="146" who="S0423">yeah but if you look up anything <unclear/> they tend to tell you you'll be dead in a few minutes</u>
<u n="147" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0423">if you don't get seen go to the doctor immediately</u>
<u n="149" who="S0421">no they don't always no but some</u>
<u n="150" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well well a lot of the time they do <unclear/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0421" trans="overlap">no but sometimes there's something and it's like oh <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> it could be nothing but go and see the doctor anyway</u>
<u n="152" who="S0423">yeah it's a it's it could be nothing or you could be about to have a brain haemorrhage</u>
<u n="153" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0423">so you better go immediately</u>
<u n="155" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0423">cos that's probably for a headache or</u>
<u n="157" who="S0421">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0423">oh <trunc>d</trunc> our <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s had to go to the hospital she had problems breathing and had pains in her chest and and erm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0421" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0423">I think she called an ambulance out er <unclear>when</unclear> she had a problem ah she was going back home</u>
<u n="161" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0423">she had a problem breathing so they came out to the ambulance and they said oh can't find anything wrong it must be just a panic attack</u>
<u n="163" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0423">she had pains in her chest but then afterwards it carried on so she went to the doctor's</u>
<u n="165" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0423">and the doctor checked her chest and said well there doesn't seem to be anything there I'll give you some antibiotics cos he heard like a rattling noise</u>
<u n="167" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0423">when he was listening to her chest and assumed it must be an infection and then erm <pause dur="short"/> she she was still in pain like quite a bit of pain so she she rang the doctor again I think the doctor did say if it's not right at a certain time come back and or ring me</u>
<u n="169" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0423">or so she rang him I think had a phone consultation or something so he arranged for her to have an X ray <pause dur="short"/> so the X ray <unclear/> erm <pause dur="short"/> she's had to stay in hospital cos <unclear/> the wall of her lung is punctured</u>
<u n="171" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0423">there's a hole in it so it's amazing isn't it?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0421">I know</u>
<u n="174" who="S0423">cos I mean I guess pains in your chest and problem breathing they must have listened to her heart and checked if there was any problems there</u>
<u n="175" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0423">so it wasn't until they did the X ray cos it continued that and they say tall young skinny females it can happen to them</u>
<u n="177" who="S0421">mm</u>
<u n="178" who="S0423" trans="overlap">I don't know whether it's cos of your rib cage <unclear/> skeleton or something</u>
<u n="179" who="S0421" trans="overlap">maybe</u>
<u n="180" who="S0423"><unclear/> on the outside you're a <pause dur="short"/> of your lung or something but</u>
<u n="181" who="S0421">cos it's unusual that cos usually you can get a punctured lung if you break a rib</u>
<u n="182" who="S0423">well yeah I thought <unclear/> first when I heard I thought she'd been involved in an accident</u>
<u n="183" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0423">you know? it's usually only if you've had an accident <unclear/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah you break a rib and then it punctures your lung yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0423">but yeah supposedly tall and skinny sort of slim young girls get it <pause dur="short"/> and erm I don't know it must be cause some must be to do with the everything is so tight in there I don't know</u>
<u n="187" who="S0421">yeah maybe yeah maybe if you've got like quite erm</u>
<u n="188" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0421">if you're not like you're necessarily like skinny as in like lost weight or something but like have a generally skinny frame</u>
<u n="190" who="S0423"><unclear/> yeah and that's what it is</u>
<u n="191" who="S0421" trans="overlap">do you know what I mean? cos some people do yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0423">so they had to cut a hole in her side and put something on it to let</u>
<u n="193" who="S0421" trans="overlap">er</u>
<u n="194" who="S0423">cos there was air building up on her side of her her lung and have to let the air escape so it's not worked it's like something <unclear/> but so they've had to put a new one on last night so that there's a slight suction so that will suck out <unclear/> so yeah it is best checking things isn't it?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0421">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0423">if you have got a persistent something that's not going away you need to make sure you persist and say well this isn't still a problem</u>
<u n="197" who="S0421">yeah because there was this child erm and their parents took them to six different doctors and each one said there's nothing wrong with them some of them said it's a flu some of them said it was <trunc>ju</trunc> or you know it was just a cold one of them even said it was like some psychological problems or something and then the child died because it was like I don't know it was like tuberculosis or something</u>
<u n="198" who="S0423">really?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0421">yeah and they went to six different doctors</u>
<u n="200" who="S0423">mm <pause dur="short"/> I mean it it must be a hard job being a doctor isn't it?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0421">I know but <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0423">but everyone seems to be having medical problems <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been off work he's got kidney infection your grandad <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0421"><unclear>yeah</unclear> <pause dur="long"/> do they keep you awake while they cut a hole in you?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0423">yeah they gave her erm a sedative</u>
<u n="205" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0423">so erm be like a local anaesthetic but you're awake</u>
<u n="207" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't understand why do they not just put people asleep?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0423">well they're reluctant to do that unless it's absolutely necessary because that can cause complications in itself having an anaesthetic</u>
<u n="209" who="S0421">I know but</u>
<u n="210" who="S0423">some people react against it can have an effect on your heart on you know? <pause dur="short"/> it it does have some dangers people going asleep doesn't it? used to be a very they'd always put people asleep <unclear/> routine of things wasn't it?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0423">now they're not they're a bit more reluctant now they tend to give keep you awake for a lot of stuff unless it's kind of a major operation I think <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0421">I just don't know how people do it while they're awake</u>
<u n="214" who="S0423">I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s was at hospital like she's well that's just a consultation she wants she's going to have her tonsils out</u>
<u n="215" who="S0421">oh does she want them out?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0423">well she's always off <unclear/> she's having it all the time yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0421" trans="overlap">oh from tonsillitis</u>
<u n="218" who="S0423">and er so they think that it's best to have them out cos she's keep getting it back all the time</u>
<u n="219" who="S0421">oh I'd rather just suffer I wouldn't have them out <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well no it's a routine operation if you're if you're having tonsillitis all the time then you would want them out cos it's not good</u>
<u n="221" who="S0421">no because nothing's worse than having an operation <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0423">well no it's <trunc>n</trunc> it's not that bad you soon get over it and then you never have a problem with your tonsils again do you?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0421" trans="overlap">cos <pause dur="short"/> no but you have to suffer they get like a knife on you and they like <trunc>they</trunc></u>
<u n="224" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you don't know anything though do you?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0421">well they do they get a knife</u>
<u n="226" who="S0423">but you don't know anything about that do you?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0421">course you do oh do they put you asleep for that?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0423">I would imagine they would <pause dur="short"/> unless the technique is different now</u>
<u n="229" who="S0421">cos they don't for erm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0423">maybe they don't</u>
<u n="231" who="S0421">a <unclear/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0423" trans="overlap">mm yeah it's considered routine as well now so it's possible that they don't <pause dur="long"/> we might actually be on time</u>
<u n="233" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> no but if people are awake while they're like cutting them open do they not just start screaming?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0423">why would you? you wouldn't feel anything</u>
<u n="235" who="S0421">no but you would know I would just be like screaming</u>
<u n="236" who="S0423">why?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0421">cos I'm getting cut open</u>
<u n="238" who="S0423">yeah but you don't know do you?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0421">yeah but I do because they've just told me they're about to cut me open</u>
<u n="240" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> well what's wrong with that?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0421">it's awful er I don't wanna be <trunc>cu</trunc></u>
<u n="242" who="S0423">the only problem is if you're in pain and if it's not going to cause you pain then I don't see the problem with it they're doing it to help you</u>
<u n="243" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> I know but</u>
<u n="244" who="S0423" trans="overlap">it's not as if they're doing it oh let's just cut this little girl open for no reason</u>
<u n="245" who="S0421"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0423">then you'd have reason to scream <pause dur="short"/> what's made you so squeamish?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0421">I'm <trunc>al</trunc> I've always been like that <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0423">why?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0421">I don't know I was born like this</u>
<u n="250" who="S0423">you weren't born like this</u>
<u n="251" who="S0421">of course I was</u>
<u n="252" who="S0423" trans="overlap">you've never had a problem with doctors and hospitals when you were a toddler</u>
<u n="253" who="S0421">yeah I probably didn't know what was going on</u>
<u n="254" who="S0423">no you wouldn't have done</u>
<u n="255" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> now that I have a full understanding of</u>
<u n="256" who="S0423" trans="overlap">so you weren't born like that were you?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0421">what?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0423">you weren't born like that</u>
<u n="259" who="S0421">well because I was born without knowledge</u>
<u n="260" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> imagination probably</u>
<u n="261" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no but if you told me if when I was younger you'd said right they're going to put you to sleep and cut you open I don't think I would've been very happy if I was going to get cut <trunc>o</trunc> if you well I'd never got</u>
<u n="262" who="S0423" trans="overlap">well I don't think anyone would tell you that when you were young</u>
<u n="263" who="S0421">yeah well they yeah but now because people tell me like oh right so you know this is what I I like it's because it's cos I've been educated</u>
<u n="264" who="S0423">no it's a it's a it's a matter of <trunc>igno</trunc>ignorance and lack of education <unclear/> of being having an operation</u>
<u n="265" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no it's not</u>
<u n="266" who="S0423">it is cos if it's the right thing and the good thing for you you shouldn't fear anything</u>
<u n="267" who="S0421">no because it's like inside the body it's horrible I just want to rip everything out</u>
<u n="268" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> that's well that's ignorance isn't it?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0421">why?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0423">it's stupidity</u>
<u n="271" who="S0421"><trunc>stu</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0423">well your body is your body is what it needs to be kept in working order</u>
<u n="273" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0423">and if they need to go in there and sort it out sometimes then that's the right thing to do</u>
<u n="275" who="S0421" trans="overlap">er but it's awful</u>
<u n="276" who="S0423">it's your body why is it awful?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0421" trans="overlap">because ever since ever since I've learned ever since I've had biology lessons I've been like this ever since I was <trunc>fi</trunc></u>
<u n="278" who="S0423" trans="overlap">yeah you haven't said what's cause that it's cos you've learned about <unclear/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0421" trans="overlap">in what's inside the body yeah that's what's caused it but it's not like eh obviously if I never knew what was I wouldn't be that bothered would i?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0423"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0421">it's as soon as they teach you like oh inside you you have blood and it's like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0423">so you'd rather be ignorant?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0421">yeah I would I would rather not know if I'd never known that I have like <trunc>muscl</trunc></u>
<u n="284" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I don't understand what's wrong with blood and muscles that's what keeps it working doesn't it?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0421" trans="overlap">I don't know it's an irrational fear isn't it? it's irrational</u>
<u n="286" who="S0423">well you need to start being more rational</u>
<u n="287" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> have you not got any irrational fears?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0423">I'm sure I have yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0421">oh yeah mm next time you're scared of something I'm going to be start being more rational</u>
<u n="290" who="S0423">well yeah it's good advice</u>
<u n="291" who="S0421"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and you're going to be like yeah and I'm sure you'll be able to follow it won't you?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0423" trans="overlap"><unclear/> this has changed a bit <unclear/> used to be around about here <unclear/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0421">I think most people have irrational <trunc>fe</trunc>fears to be honest <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0423">mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0421">and to be honest it's not that irrational if you're going to have an <trunc>op</trunc> if someone's cutting you open it's not really an irrational fear is it?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0423">well it's alright to have a little bit of an inkling of</u>
<u n="297" who="S0421" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0423">of apprehensiveness but it's busy in here look at this</u>
<u n="299" who="S0421">why?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0423" trans="overlap">cos it's the holidays isn't it?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0421"><vocal desc="misc"/> so many people they all need to go home</u>
<u n="302" who="S0423">well you know what it is? It's cos they do the kids club early morning</u>
<u n="303" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah but that's ten</u>
<u n="304" who="S0423">no yeah they'll be coming out now won't they? at twelve? they're all just coming out</u>
<u n="305" who="S0421" trans="overlap">all these human beings everywhere <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0423">you sound like an alien who wants to wipe all the humans off the <trunc>pl</trunc> face of the planet</u>
<u n="307" who="S0421">I probably am you know? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0423">yeah maybe you don't have blood and all <unclear/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0421" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="310" who="S0423">maybe you've got something else</u>
<u n="311" who="S0421">yeah I'm an alien</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
