<text id="SNNG">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:39:00</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-05-06</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0517 S0518</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Cafe, Lichfield)</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>resignation at work, drama auditions, relationships and potential affairs</topics>
		<activity>Hearing about a friend’s complicated life.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0517">
				<exactage>47</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sutton Coldfield</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lichfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>14 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Self employed - marketing &amp; Proofing services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- working knowledge; German -- Working knowledge</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0518">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Staffordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lichfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>19 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Customer Services Team Leader</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0517">there we go which one is mine?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0518">yours is that one they're not very</u>
<u n="3" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="4" who="S0518">big are they?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0517">they're not actually no</u>
<u n="6" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well mine's bigger than <trunc>y</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0517">yours er yes <vocal desc="laugh"/> mine's bigger than yours there you go</u>
<u n="8" who="S0518">this is gonna sound so rude but I thought what</u>
<u n="9" who="S0517">oh whispering now?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0518">oh is it on?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="12" who="S0518">oh</u>
<u n="13" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0518">I was going no but it's fine I was gonna say what a grumpy unattractive set of serving ladies</u>
<u n="15" who="S0517">er yes she she wasn't happy then <trunc>sh</trunc> did you hear her comment when we walked in?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0518">no</u>
<u n="17" who="S0517">that's why I said to her she said</u>
<u n="18" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh I didn't</u>
<u n="19" who="S0517">I knew this would happen</u>
<u n="20" who="S0518"><vocal desc="gasp"/> I didn't hear</u>
<u n="21" who="S0517" trans="overlap">cos they'd just sat down hadn't they?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0518">I heard you say I</u>
<u n="23" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and then I I said oh I'm sorry</u>
<u n="24" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I <trunc>h</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0517">you know you feel a bit embarrassed to be there as a customer</u>
<u n="26" who="S0518">I heard</u>
<u n="27" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but she went oh I knew this would happen</u>
<u n="28" who="S0518">I didn't I I <trunc>kn</trunc> obviously I heard what you said but I didn't know</u>
<u n="29" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah no and she's that look on her face and she was a bit grumpy at having to serve us but there we go</u>
<u n="30" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0517">we've got our tea</u>
<u n="32" who="S0518">yes thank you</u>
<u n="33" who="S0517">so who who resigned then and why?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's in my team she's been</u>
<u n="35" who="S0517" trans="overlap">has she been there a long time?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0518">er few years but she's had behavioural difficulties she's twenty-four</u>
<u n="37" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0518">she's a good worker she's very intelligent she's very very attractive but she doesn't believe this and she is constantly having counselling for her weight issues of which she doesn't have any</u>
<u n="39" who="S0517">oh god</u>
<u n="40" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but you know it all stems back to <unclear>stuff</unclear> and erm she's been put into my team and she didn't want to come into it because she liked the desk where she was sitting before and but I always get given the slightly difficult ones because</u>
<u n="41" who="S0517">oh yeah you said yes</u>
<u n="42" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I'm a bit more patient and like she's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s cousin so he couldn't manager her anyway but also he wouldn't have the patience for her and</u>
<u n="43" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="44" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so anyway so she came into my team and like I say <trunc>sh</trunc>she made it quite clear that</u>
<u n="45" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh that's hot mm</u>
<u n="46" who="S0518">she didn't want to move desks and she <unclear>didn't wanna be</unclear> in the back desk team anyway she's been great and we've had catch-ups and one-to-ones and then we've just had a PDR in which she's said all of my worries and fears were unfounded because I've actually really <trunc>c</trunc> enjoyed coming into your team I feel like I've developed really well taken on extra responsibility</u>
<u n="47" who="S0517">how long ago</u>
<u n="48" who="S0518" trans="overlap">er</u>
<u n="49" who="S0517" trans="overlap">was this?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0518">erm January</u>
<u n="51" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="52" who="S0518">when she first came into our team</u>
<u n="53" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so not long</u>
<u n="54" who="S0518">no</u>
<u n="55" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no the PDR when she said all this</u>
<u n="56" who="S0518">oh the PDR was erm week before last</u>
<u n="57" who="S0517">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0517">so a week before last she says all this</u>
<u n="60" who="S0518">yes</u>
<u n="61" who="S0517">and resigns today</u>
<u n="62" who="S0518">yeah erm so she said all of this then she said what her plans were for the future and would we support her in getting there and she wanted to be</u>
<u n="63" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0518">more involved in the health and safety process she wanted to be the contact for risk assessments and erm insurance claims and all of that sort of thing so we set her up with people to get into contact with and she's developed this erm <pause dur="short"/> this process which she sent out to all the team and gave us another thing that she <trunc>neede</trunc> a marketing thing to do each week</u>
<u n="65" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="66" who="S0518">and erm she's responded really really really well really well then last week she said cos I've always known it's her ambition to be cabin crew</u>
<u n="67" who="S0517">oh really?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0518" trans="overlap">she yeah she got asked for an interview from Virgin</u>
<u n="69" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="70" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and she said months ago she had the first stage and she thought nothing of it and then about three months after she got a telephone interview and then that was er about another five months ago and she said it</u>
<u n="71" who="S0517" trans="overlap">gosh that's a slow process isn't it?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah and I think every so often they do these recruitments</u>
<u n="73" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="74" who="S0518">and she was now onto the third stage so she got called for an actual like a day</u>
<u n="75" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0518">but we have a holiday process where you have to give in any holiday erm requests at a certain of time before</u>
<u n="77" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="78" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and she was like asking for it last week for this week and it was bank holiday week and she just thought it'll be declined but anyway she spoke to me and I just said <trunc>li</trunc> I don't think we can stop you from going for an interview can't stop you from</u>
<u n="79" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh she told you it was an interview?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0517" trans="overlap">she didn't try and hide that?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0518">well she told <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> her cousin and he told me and</u>
<u n="83" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="84" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and then I just said can I have five minutes with you? so I said look it's just best to be honest and open because I said if you just don't if you ring in sick and anybody finds out</u>
<u n="85" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="86" who="S0518">you know</u>
<u n="87" who="S0517">yeah it's just awkward</u>
<u n="88" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so just tell me what it's about so she did I went to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said we're not gonna stand in the way of her career we've always known that</u>
<u n="89" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0518">long term she wants to do this so we made it possible for her to have the day off which was yesterday I texted her wished her well she text me halfway through the day and went oh I'm halfway through now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> woo like this so and it was down in <anon type="place"/> so then I said</u>
<u n="91" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh gosh</u>
<u n="92" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I look forward to hearing about it tomorrow come in today I said morning how did you get on yesterday? she went oh I'll tell you about it later and then I heard her say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she wouldn't hear for five weeks</u>
<u n="93" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="94" who="S0518">and at one o'clock she's going on her lunch I'm just sort of finishing stuff off and erm I didn't even know it was her cos normally she'll go that way but somebody came behind me and literally just threw a letter like it went like you know this</u>
<u n="95" who="S0517"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="96" who="S0518">just landed and I went</u>
<u n="97" who="S0517" trans="overlap">how rude</u>
<u n="98" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I I went oh and then I couldn't see who it was and <trunc>t</trunc> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said that how rude</u>
<u n="99" who="S0517">that is rude</u>
<u n="100" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so I said I said who was it? he said it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so I said oh and I looked at it and it was to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I thought this is probably to say that she's been successful and she's gonna be leaving and I opened it and it said dear <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm it is with regret that I wish to hand in my notice I'm not happy working at the company any more since the takeover my final day will be the twenty-sixth of June <pause dur="short"/> and that was it so nothing about anything <unclear/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0517" trans="overlap">how weird</u>
<u n="102" who="S0518">and she'd just just <trunc>g</trunc></u>
<u n="103" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and she won't have heard from the job yet you don't think?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0518">well I've got a feeling</u>
<u n="105" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so <trunc>d</trunc> have you spoken to her?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0518">no</u>
<u n="107" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="108" who="S0518" trans="overlap">because she was going on lunch one till two and</u>
<u n="109" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and then you were finishing</u>
<u n="110" who="S0518">I was due I was due to leave at half past one but then I had to take this letter to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said that is out of order how rude and also she's had these mental health issues which I understand how that feels and so she's asked for appointments I've supported her in getting appointments to go to counselling and it's all about food issues and everything</u>
<u n="111" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0518">and then I've talked to her about it and I've said oh not I can't delve into it I don't you don't have to tell me all about it but obviously as your manager I need to support you and if you need time from work or whatever it is given the the twenty-four hour help number for employee assistance helpline you know all this sort of thing</u>
<u n="113" who="S0517" trans="overlap">all that yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0518">so I've stood by her and erm as I say made it possible</u>
<u n="115" who="S0517" trans="overlap">that's</u>
<u n="116" who="S0518">for her to go to this interview</u>
<u n="117" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so rude</u>
<u n="118" who="S0518">but it was more the way she didn't</u>
<u n="119" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0518" trans="overlap">say to me</u>
<u n="121" who="S0517">didn't speak to you threw it at you</u>
<u n="122" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="123" who="S0517">didn't give you <trunc>sh</trunc> that's terrible</u>
<u n="124" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no so I had to go and speak to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos the letter was addressed to her as well</u>
<u n="125" who="S0517" trans="overlap">is she on two months' notice then? May June</u>
<u n="126" who="S0518">erm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0517" trans="overlap">that's quite a long notice period</u>
<u n="128" who="S0518">I'm just saying the twenty-sixth of June</u>
<u n="129" who="S0517">maybe it was May</u>
<u n="130" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I knew it should be four weeks from</u>
<u n="131" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh so</u>
<u n="132" who="S0518" trans="overlap">today really so whatever that is</u>
<u n="133" who="S0517" trans="overlap">start of June</u>
<u n="134" who="S0518" trans="overlap">in June</u>
<u n="135" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0518">maybe it was the second of June</u>
<u n="137" who="S0517" trans="overlap">fourth of June</u>
<u n="138" who="S0518">I can't</u>
<u n="139" who="S0517" trans="overlap">fifth sixth of June</u>
<u n="140" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I'm sure it was a double number anyway</u>
<u n="141" who="S0517">that</u>
<u n="142" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I can't remember I can't remember</u>
<u n="143" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you were in shock I think</u>
<u n="144" who="S0518">well I just thought I expected</u>
<u n="145" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so did you speak to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? does he know anything?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0518">no no <trunc>co</trunc> because the team we've had an unbearable week so much work the team have been immense they've done so well and it's been quite stressful so I suggested to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> why don't I get them ice lollies on Friday? because I said</u>
<u n="147" who="S0517">ah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0518">it's a nice day and it's hot and that would just be really nice for a treat so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had gone out to buy <vocal desc="laugh"/> the ice lollies so he wasn't there and</u>
<u n="149" who="S0517">oh so</u>
<u n="150" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I was</u>
<u n="151" who="S0517">well so now you're not gonna know anything till Monday?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0518">well I spoke to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0517" trans="overlap">or will <trunc>y</trunc>?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0518">and she just said this is rude</u>
<u n="155" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0518">and out of order and she said I accept this resignation and she said you need to get off and go erm but and she said but I'll speak to her this afternoon but she said I'll tell her that the way that she delivered this was just unacceptable</u>
<u n="157" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0518">and especially in view of all the support that you've given her in the recent weeks it's just</u>
<u n="159" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="160" who="S0518">out of order</u>
<u n="161" who="S0517" trans="overlap">that's not a very nice way for you end the week is it?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0518">well not really but then erm and five minutes later <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was there <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s our recruitment HR recruitment person so <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was straight on it we need to speak to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about getting a replacement <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0518">because we can't we can't wait for</u>
<u n="165" who="S0517" trans="overlap">can't function</u>
<u n="166" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear>a four week gap</unclear> we need to get someone in</u>
<u n="167" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0518">and get them trained</u>
<u n="169" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0518" trans="overlap">in this four weeks so erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said</u>
<u n="171" who="S0517" trans="overlap">gosh</u>
<u n="172" who="S0518">I'll speak to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this afternoon and if she retracts it and says I'm sorry I just did it in a moment of she'll sorry it's too late you've</u>
<u n="173" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0518" trans="overlap">done it now</u>
<u n="175" who="S0517">I would think so</u>
<u n="176" who="S0518">but she had a face on her all morning and I said I wouldn't be surprised if she's told <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she won't hear for five weeks I think they've said at the end of the session sorry you haven't been successful she's peed off cos she hasn't got the job but she's decided</u>
<u n="177" who="S0517" trans="overlap">she's just</u>
<u n="178" who="S0518">I'm having a change I'm not working here</u>
<u n="179" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0518" trans="overlap">if I can't do that I'm gonna do something else because if the day had gone really well she would have</u>
<u n="181" who="S0517" trans="overlap">she'd have been in a happy mood</u>
<u n="182" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and she'd have been</u>
<u n="184" who="S0518">and if she'd have been offered the job she would have resigned saying I thank you for your support</u>
<u n="185" who="S0517" trans="overlap">for your support yes yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0518" trans="overlap">letting me go yesterday and I was successful in in gaining the position</u>
<u n="187" who="S0517" trans="overlap">in getting it yes</u>
<u n="188" who="S0518">and you know I've enjoyed my time with you but</u>
<u n="189" who="S0517" trans="overlap">not just say I don't like working here any more</u>
<u n="190" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="192" who="S0518" trans="overlap">it just said er yeah I've decided I don't like it here any more</u>
<u n="193" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0518">since the takeover two weeks ago on your PDR you were telling us da-da-da-da a week later you're telling us your dream come true of being an airline hostess was coming to fruition and now</u>
<u n="195" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it is a strange dream isn't it?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0518" trans="overlap">you're leaving <pause dur="short"/> cabin crew</u>
<u n="197" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0518">she looks like cabin crew she'd she'd do really well</u>
<u n="199" who="S0517">yeah oh <pause dur="short"/> I always think it would just mess with my body clock too much</u>
<u n="200" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well I she wants</u>
<u n="201" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I wouldn't know where I was</u>
<u n="202" who="S0518">her dad works in Florida all the time</u>
<u n="203" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="204" who="S0518" trans="overlap">she's just been to Florida for two weeks</u>
<u n="205" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="206" who="S0518">with him he was on business but she went along with him</u>
<u n="207" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="208" who="S0518">the they spend three weeks in Florida as a family every year anyway</u>
<u n="209" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="210" who="S0518">so erm she loves</u>
<u n="211" who="S0517" trans="overlap">probably yes yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0518">the long</u>
<u n="213" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="214" who="S0518">haul flights and</u>
<u n="215" who="S0517">Virgin's the one she'd wanna be with then I suppose</u>
<u n="216" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0517" trans="overlap">isn't it they</u>
<u n="218" who="S0518" trans="overlap">when she first</u>
<u n="219" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="220" who="S0518">came for an interview with us probably two and a half years ago erm I think one of the questions was who inspires you and she said Richard Branson and she talked about him then er and Virgin and that her long term goal was to be you know cabin crew</u>
<u n="221" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="222" who="S0518">going backwards and forwards to America or long haul flights so you know we've always known that about her</u>
<u n="223" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0518">and in our company we don't sort of say well we don't want them because</u>
<u n="225" who="S0517" trans="overlap">as yeah yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0518" trans="overlap">because we're quite you know I'm old in the team and erm</u>
<u n="227" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0518">we're a young company in terms of we recruit quite young people and</u>
<u n="229" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="230" who="S0518" trans="overlap">we believe in erm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0517">training</u>
<u n="232" who="S0518" trans="overlap">to yeah</u>
<u n="233" who="S0517" trans="overlap">developing them</u>
<u n="234" who="S0518" trans="overlap">developing them</u>
<u n="235" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0518">and</u>
<u n="237" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0518">developing and retaining we'd rather retain them but also if we know that somebody is young then they probably have got</u>
<u n="239" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0518">other prospects and we're not gonna</u>
<u n="241" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0518">hold that against them</u>
<u n="243" who="S0517">oh well interesting times</u>
<u n="244" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so it just</u>
<u n="245" who="S0517" trans="overlap">then oh</u>
<u n="246" who="S0518" trans="overlap">delayed me</u>
<u n="247" who="S0517">er yes</u>
<u n="248" who="S0518" trans="overlap">it delayed me you know</u>
<u n="249" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I've been getting a bit of hay fever today do you get that?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0518">no</u>
<u n="251" who="S0517">oh today</u>
<u n="252" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="253" who="S0517">I even took a tablet actually lunchtime which is the first one this year</u>
<u n="254" who="S0518">is it bad you sitting outside then?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no no no cos I've taken a <trunc>ta</trunc> well it's just just get itchy</u>
<u n="256" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0517">no it makes no difference</u>
<u n="258" who="S0518">well do you know what? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has had to go and sleep on the sofa two nights now</u>
<u n="259" who="S0517">oh cos of the snoring?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0517" trans="overlap">was he snoring again?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0518">last night</u>
<u n="263" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="264" who="S0518">but I felt bad for him <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos he was erm cos he was erm presiding officer in a polling station he have I told you?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="266" who="S0518" trans="overlap">he always does that</u>
<u n="267" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I forgot his does that what so he was there all day?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0518" trans="overlap">he was up at half five yeah got home about eleven</u>
<u n="269" who="S0517">what a shame cos it was such a nice day</u>
<u n="270" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I know but he was <trunc>exhaust</trunc> he looked pale he was exhausted</u>
<u n="271" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="272" who="S0518">and then he wanted to go to bed I came in after my auditions all absolutely full of everything that had happened which was</u>
<u n="273" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0518">another drama everything went wrong last night</u>
<u n="275" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0518">and he was just nodding off to sleep but then he was snoring</u>
<u n="277" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="278" who="S0518">and in the end</u>
<u n="279" who="S0517" trans="overlap">god</u>
<u n="280" who="S0518">about quarter to two I was sat up in bed and said I'm gonna do what you did the other night I'm gonna go downstairs and he went no I'll go cos it's my fault I said no cos you've had the tough day I'll go and he went I've gone already</u>
<u n="281" who="S0517">ah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but he came back at <pause dur="short"/> five</u>
<u n="283" who="S0517">does he sleep when he's on the sofa?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0518">yeah I said did you get any sleep and he said yeah and he said better because you weren't prodding me</u>
<u n="285" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0518">so</u>
<u n="287" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and making him turn over</u>
<u n="288" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0518">and but he's he what he worries is that erm if he stays there till the morning the boys wake up and come downstairs and find him on the sofa they're gonna think we've fallen out <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0517">oh really?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0517">why can't he just say I was snoring?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no well he said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this morning erm can't remember what it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> made a comment about something and he kind of just went oh you and me both <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I was banished to the sofa last night</u>
<u n="295" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is like what do you mean? and he said oh I was snoring so he said I went downstairs so that mum could sleep and I could sleep <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said why didn't you go with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got a double bed and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said have you ever tried sleeping with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is like</u>
<u n="297" who="S0517">oh is he?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0518">all like</u>
<u n="299" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he spreads out into it</u>
<u n="300" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah and then if he senses that anyone's in bed with him he <trunc>ha</trunc><trunc>ha</trunc>has to get all around you like an absolute like this</u>
<u n="301" who="S0517">oh gosh</u>
<u n="302" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and it's he's and he's so bony and</u>
<u n="303" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0518">thing and it's just not comfortable <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0517">oh no what a nightmare</u>
<u n="306" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and so I know so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so did you get any sleep last night?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0518">yeah but it was like probably would have been two three four five <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came back er I momentarily woke up and then I slept till half six then</u>
<u n="309" who="S0517">oh gosh</u>
<u n="310" who="S0518">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to me he said he felt like the soft palate in his upper in the top of his roof of his mouth and then his back of his throat was sore and he wondered if he was hay fevery</u>
<u n="311" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="312" who="S0518" trans="overlap">that was all</u>
<u n="313" who="S0517">that yes</u>
<u n="314" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear/> hay fever</u>
<u n="315" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah and it might be it has been <trunc>ba</trunc> I think it's been bad this just this week it's the sun's come out hasn't it?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="317" who="S0517">it's got warm the sun's come out yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0518">fortunately touch wood I know things change I've never nothing</u>
<u n="319" who="S0517">never had it</u>
<u n="320" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I've ever suffered with no</u>
<u n="321" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh good</u>
<u n="322" who="S0518">cos I just feel so</u>
<u n="323" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well that's alright cos you do have enough to deal with</u>
<u n="324" who="S0518" trans="overlap">probably yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0518">something like that</u>
<u n="327" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so what happened at rehearsals?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0518">well <pause dur="short"/> erm I was doing my auditions <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is my producer and my committee member so I as the director I have the overall artistic decision but I have to have somebody with me to make sure that I'm not giving favouritism and stuff like that</u>
<u n="329" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0518">and erm my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wanted to come down and</u>
<u n="331" who="S0517" trans="overlap">stalker <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0517">stalker <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> one?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0518">yes</u>
<u n="335" who="S0517">as opposed to stalker <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> two?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0518">yes but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they both turned up last night both of them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> turned up to the to the</u>
<u n="338" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="339" who="S0517">to the <trunc>au</trunc></u>
<u n="340" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0517">how did he know where to go?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0518">well</u>
<u n="343" who="S0517">how does he know where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> lives?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0518">no it wasn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house it was in the <anon type="place"/> pub last night</u>
<u n="345" who="S0517">I thought oh have I got</u>
<u n="346" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="347" who="S0517">the wrong date? Wednesday</u>
<u n="348" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="349" who="S0517">was at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house wasn't it?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so Wednesday some <trunc>peo</trunc> auditions were Thursday</u>
<u n="351" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh god</u>
<u n="352" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and three people contacted me and said we can't audition Thursday so we give them an opportunity to audition on another night but it has to be prior to the final</u>
<u n="353" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="354" who="S0518" trans="overlap">audition</u>
<u n="355" who="S0517">so you just</u>
<u n="356" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="357" who="S0517">have one night of auditions then it's like you choose everyone there and then do you? on that</u>
<u n="358" who="S0518">yeah and if you can't</u>
<u n="359" who="S0517" trans="overlap">usually oh okay</u>
<u n="360" who="S0518" trans="overlap">you have to go away and ring round and maybe think about it but I was able to choose last night not the <trunc>t</trunc>team that I really wanted but anyway that's a part of the story but erm <pause dur="short"/> so yeah Wednesday night was at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house</u>
<u n="361" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay right I was getting confused</u>
<u n="362" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but Thursday</u>
<u n="363" who="S0517" trans="overlap">was the actual auditions</u>
<u n="364" who="S0518" trans="overlap">was in the back room of the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0517">so what did he know you were there?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0518">well he must have done</u>
<u n="367" who="S0517" trans="overlap">stalker <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> two?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0518">he must have done because I think I'm had a conversation with them when they came to see my play about the next play</u>
<u n="369" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="370" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and all this kind of thing and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was saying like where do you rehearse? and all of this I I I'm only guessing this because I know we had a conversation about it I can't remember it in detail</u>
<u n="371" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="372" who="S0518">but he was obviously lapping it all up taking it all in</u>
<u n="373" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he's probably phoned the pub and asked them when the auditions are taking place</u>
<u n="374" who="S0518">oh no</u>
<u n="375" who="S0517">probably has <trunc>ju</trunc> based on what I now know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I wouldn't</u>
<u n="376" who="S0518" trans="overlap">probably</u>
<u n="377" who="S0517">put that past him</u>
<u n="378" who="S0518">probably I don't now but that's</u>
<u n="379" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and it's all a bit</u>
<u n="380" who="S0518">the yeah that's not till ten that bit doesn't happen till quarter past ten but erm so other <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> number one <trunc>sa</trunc>said he wanted to come and help he's in Shakespeare so he can't be in it but erm he wants to come and help and support me and all this kind of stuff so he would be a meeter greeter and I was thinking <vocal desc="laugh"/> well we've never had a meeter greeter before well welcome to the pub have a drink while we wait to call you through but I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's trying to be really supportive so I'll let him come down and do it but then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like I'm your helper</u>
<u n="381" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh oh my god</u>
<u n="382" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I will call people in I said look <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants to meet and greet people and then send them through for audition it didn't work out like that cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got himself a pint of beer and then he sat down chatting with everybody so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had to keep going and calling people through</u>
<u n="383" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="384" who="S0518">and then when one person finished for an audition I'd say shall I see if there's more Siobhans want to come in and audition? so then they go through anyone else want to audition for Siobhan? so it didn't quite work out</u>
<u n="385" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right yeah yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0518">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> stalker one was drinking beer from half past seven till when we finally came through which was er just <trunc>aft</trunc> about five past ten and he was well away</u>
<u n="387" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="388" who="S0518">so</u>
<u n="389" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well he would be three hours of drinking</u>
<u n="390" who="S0518">I said I'm sorry I didn't there wasn't any reading in for you to do cos I said there wasn't a lot of men reading in to do no fine I've had a brilliant night I've had a brilliant night and I said I was hoping that you sort of herd people in you know but I said when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> popped out he said that you were quite happy with the meeting and greeting and you were having a nice social night so he said well I was having a nice social night so he said but thanks <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for taking my job away when that's the only reason I turned up and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like oh you know</u>
<u n="391" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh god</u>
<u n="392" who="S0518" trans="overlap">if you'd have <trunc>wa</trunc></u>
<u n="393" who="S0517" trans="overlap">that's so childish</u>
<u n="394" who="S0518" trans="overlap">if you'd have wanted to do it you should have not sat down with a pint of</u>
<u n="395" who="S0517">of beer</u>
<u n="396" who="S0518" trans="overlap">of beer you know</u>
<u n="397" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0518">so I was like boys it's alright anyway erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had come down he was on a chair and then just to see how things had gone and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> auditioned you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos he played the guy in the leather coat that did the tango in Allo Allo and he played</u>
<u n="399" who="S0517">oh yes</u>
<u n="400" who="S0518">Bertie Wooster in Jeeves and Wooster</u>
<u n="401" who="S0517">yes yes</u>
<u n="402" who="S0518">with the mad curly hair</u>
<u n="403" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yes I know him</u>
<u n="404" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and everything</u>
<u n="405" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0518">he came and auditioned</u>
<u n="407" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="408" who="S0518">and erm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0517">how many people were you looking for?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0518">well</u>
<u n="411" who="S0517" trans="overlap">how many is in the cast?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0518">it's er you can do it as a small version or as an ensemble version so the small version has five ladies and one man and</u>
<u n="413" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="414" who="S0518">they all play all the different roles because I wanted to open it up more and give more people opportunity I did the ensemble version that has potential for more roles where you get <unclear>race</unclear> marshals and policemen and erm <pause dur="short"/> er yeah a few other little parts</u>
<u n="415" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0518">so I said we'll do that version just to give a few more opportunities</u>
<u n="417" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="418" who="S0518">erm but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was auditioning for one like for the main male role which he got erm but afterwards when we were round the table and I'd sort of announced he was having the part so then we were just having a drink in the pub suddenly was aware and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was really excited and it's Thursday night and there's live music in so there was singers and there a guy playing the guitar and</u>
<u n="419" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0518">it's quite noisy and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like oh and whooping and lots of clapping suddenly aware of him kind of you know backslapping and shaking hands with this somebody or other and erm I sort of looked and it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0517">stalker <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> two?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0518">and I was like</u>
<u n="423" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so he knew did how did you know that they knew each other?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0518">no so anyway so they were having this chat da-da-da-da and I said</u>
<u n="425" who="S0517" trans="overlap">was <trunc>t</trunc> who was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> with?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0518">himself so</u>
<u n="427" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="428" who="S0518">and he was really</u>
<u n="429" who="S0517" trans="overlap">spookier and spookier</u>
<u n="430" who="S0518" trans="overlap">he was really dressed up smart and I thought oh and erm so I I <trunc>sai</trunc> I was sitting at this tall table and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was opposite to me and I went oh</u>
<u n="431" who="S0517">oh did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> know who he is?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0518">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came round and said</u>
<u n="433" who="S0517"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0518">are you alright? so I said you know who that is talking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? and he was like no oh is oh okay he said I thought your facial expression was a bit odd it was a kind of a look like oh my god what are you doing here?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0517" trans="overlap">what's he doing here?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I said</u>
<u n="437" who="S0517" trans="overlap">blimey</u>
<u n="438" who="S0518">oh gosh was it that obvious? so anyway <trunc>h</trunc>he said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I want to go now he said but what's gonna happen? he said do you want me to walk you back to your car? well I'd just got a glass of wine I said no because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s here <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s here <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are still here <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <trunc>h</trunc> the I'll be fine so he said alright he said text me to let me know that you've got home okay so then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> made like a big whole scene of saying oh goodbye and</u>
<u n="439" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="440" who="S0518">you know well done for tonight and we'll be in touch you and I we've got to have some meetings and all of this and I it's like oh yeah yeah like this anyway <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was <trunc>talk</trunc> and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I've got eight minutes till my train now I said what till it leaves? he went no eight minutes to get to the station so I'm gonna say goodbye to you so I said okay so then cos he's really just outgoing and stuff</u>
<u n="441" who="S0517" trans="overlap">theatrical</u>
<u n="442" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0518">he erm give me this big hug and he went I'm so happy to be in this play it's gonna be such fun <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and then he sort of got me in this dance pose and like waltzed me around and stuff and then he as he was doing this he said to me who the is that guy? he said he's acting like he knows me</u>
<u n="445" who="S0517">oh they didn't know each <trunc>oth</trunc></u>
<u n="446" who="S0518">no so I said <pause dur="short"/> do you? I said</u>
<u n="447" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="448" who="S0518">he he's seen you in plays he went is that what it is? because he said he walked straight over to me pats me on the back shakes me by the hand hi <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> how are you? and he's <trunc>goi</trunc></u>
<u n="449" who="S0517">really?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0517">so he didn't know him? that's weird</u>
<u n="452" who="S0518">so I said I can't tell you now I can't tell you now I can't tell you now I'll tell you when I said <trunc>becau</trunc> I'll tell another time he goes make sure you do and <trunc>sai</trunc> let me know you get home safe I will do I will do like this so he goes so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> bye like <trunc>ni</trunc>nice to see you like this and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says yeah bye <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like this</u>
<u n="453" who="S0517"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0517">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="456" who="S0518">so</u>
<u n="457" who="S0517" trans="overlap">that is freaky</u>
<u n="458" who="S0518">then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says to me</u>
<u n="459" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I'm worried for you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> well</u>
<u n="461" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I'm not gonna lie</u>
<u n="462" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says to me I'm going in a minute</u>
<u n="463" who="S0517">which <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><trunc>stalk</trunc> okay</u>
<u n="466" who="S0518">so he's got this pint so he said I've been to see my dad and it's erm <pause dur="short"/> it's been really difficult and he really needed a hug and I got I just felt</u>
<u n="467" who="S0517" trans="overlap">who needed a hug? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or his dad?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no his dad</u>
<u n="469" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="470" who="S0518">so I said why didn't you give him one? and he said well I tried to but it's not really me he needs one from it's my mum but she won't acknowledge anything so she just talks as if everything's normal and he said but it's not really while we're there that he needs a hug it's in the middle of the night when he wakes up frightened and upset and there's just like a strange nurse there you know so he's telling me all of this and I just thought do you know I think he's just he's really upset and I don't think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> gets it and don't think she gives <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> any time or any sympathy and I think he's just thought <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna go and tell <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about it</u>
<u n="471" who="S0517">picks his moments doesn't he? when you're in the middle of that with er you know auditions that's just</u>
<u n="472" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well I was with all my friends</u>
<u n="473" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><trunc>whe</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0518">and they're obviously wondering</u>
<u n="475" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he must have he he's gone to the trouble to <trunc>fi</trunc></u>
<u n="476" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I mean it's quite brave isn't it?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it is he's gone to the trouble to find out where you're doing it and when he knows it's the pub he's rung them up found out when they're on</u>
<u n="478" who="S0518">I don't no I don't know about that</u>
<u n="479" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I do absolutely</u>
<u n="480" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I haven't I didn't ask him I didn't</u>
<u n="481" who="S0517">absolutely</u>
<u n="482" who="S0518" trans="overlap">ask him I didn't even ask him I didn't even say what are you doing here? because I'd just <trunc>li</trunc> when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went I just looked at him and he said erm I'm don't worry I'm going in a minute</u>
<u n="483" who="S0517">and did he go?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0518">yeah so he drank his beer really quickly and he said erm <pause dur="short"/> how have you got on tonight? and I said well I've cast it I said much older than I wanted to but I said they're all good actresses I've just probably just have to change the <pause dur="short"/> the kind of emphasis on the story a bit so erm he said oh when er that couple left they said see you Tuesday is that when the rehearsals start then? so I said oh no rest for the wicked but rehearsals on Tuesday are aren't they're somewhere else so</u>
<u n="485" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay yeah don't let on where</u>
<u n="486" who="S0518" trans="overlap">somewhere else he doesn't know where they are so and the rehearsals on Thursday are somewhere else as well so erm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0517">so just going back to what you were saying the other day did you actually tell him you weren't interested romantically? or are you interested romantically?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no I'm not</u>
<u n="489" who="S0517">okay</u>
<u n="490" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I just wanted to confirm that with you</u>
<u n="492" who="S0518" trans="overlap">just to make that clear</u>
<u n="493" who="S0517" trans="overlap">clear for the tape</u>
<u n="494" who="S0518">for the</u>
<u n="495" who="S0517">erm so did you make it clear to him that you weren't? <pause dur="short"/> cos you've been</u>
<u n="496" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I</u>
<u n="497" who="S0517">very very kind to him considering everything that he's done</u>
<u n="498" who="S0518"><trunc>becau</trunc> I <trunc>th</trunc> because and this is my own stupid fault isn't it? I find it hard to be <pause dur="short"/> to be hard with anybody</u>
<u n="499" who="S0517">you well I know that and you've always been nice to him and you've always listened to him but I think you might need to erm</u>
<u n="500" who="S0518">we've had</u>
<u n="501" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well spell it out really from the sounds of it</u>
<u n="502" who="S0518">we've had a lot of <pause dur="short"/> very er I don't know the word heartfelt upset conversations where I've got really angry and and then I've cried as well and obviously he's got angry and punched the car because I said to him we're just singing off two different hymn sheets how we view our friendship is completely different I'm in a completely different place to where you are and he wants to make some common ground going forward and what I've said is I want us to be able to be civil with one another on the side of the football pitch and he said is that it? is that all? is that all that you want? and I was like yeah and erm for the sake of the boys and the other parents and you know it's would be no good for you</u>
<u n="503" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so does he not accept the fact that you don't want an affair with him?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="505" who="S0517">he thinks seems to think that's</u>
<u n="506" who="S0518" trans="overlap">he won't accept it and he wants to talk me into it and</u>
<u n="507" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0518">it was based on the fact that why should anybody need to know and you can have your cake and you can eat it and you know who invented monogamy anyway? it's a manmade rule and now he's found out that the pope had a friend who was a lady</u>
<u n="509" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="510" who="S0518">and all of that did I tell you that?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes but it yes you did but if you're not interested romantically you're not interested that's where it has to end and that's what I think you're</u>
<u n="512" who="S0518"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0517">gonna need to push home to him</u>
<u n="514" who="S0518">in his mind though we're not I've told you I think I think I told you this when I say to him and it was funny because I just just telling you hi <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> how was your day? and then when he turned up on Wednesday the</u>
<u n="515" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh I couldn't <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="516" who="S0518" trans="overlap">first thing I said was hi <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> how was your day?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I know did you did you see my laugh?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="519" who="S0517" trans="overlap">cos I just couldn't I was <trunc>fa</trunc> cos of course his answer was dying and I felt terrible</u>
<u n="520" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="521" who="S0517">that I'd laughed but it was just because of what you'd said</u>
<u n="522" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="523" who="S0517" trans="overlap">before of that</u>
<u n="524" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and I said it on purpose because that's what</u>
<u n="525" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I know you did and that's what made me laugh and I'm thinking</u>
<u n="526" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and that's what <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's what</u>
<u n="527" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh I hope he didn't see me cos his answer was dying</u>
<u n="528" who="S0518">and that's what I always say</u>
<u n="529" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="530" who="S0518">you know hi how was your day? and I do ask him and I I feel disloyal to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because now obviously all this has developed</u>
<u n="531" who="S0517">that kiss was weird wasn't it that they had?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0518">what kiss?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0517">oh you see you didn't notice</u>
<u n="534" who="S0518">no</u>
<u n="535" who="S0517">and I'm sure it was for your benefit you know they were talking behind us and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was gonna leave and</u>
<u n="536" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I didn't really notice no</u>
<u n="537" who="S0517" trans="overlap">we were talking there they never kiss in public I've never seen them and he kissed her either hello or goodbye or something</u>
<u n="538" who="S0518">they don't kiss each other full stop</u>
<u n="539" who="S0517">no I know so I thought</u>
<u n="540" who="S0518" trans="overlap">according to him <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0517">I thought to myself that's for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s benefit that kiss</u>
<u n="542" who="S0518">I</u>
<u n="543" who="S0517">I can't believe you missed it</u>
<u n="544" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I didn't even notice it</u>
<u n="545" who="S0517">how did you not notice it?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0518">I don't know but I had a I had a text from him shortly after he left and it said I'm really sorry that I <trunc>h</trunc> I'm really sorry that I I was distracted by <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when you were telling us about your dad it sounds really sad he sounds equally as bad as mine if not worse isn't it awful that you can live all these years and finish your life in this state? erm</u>
<u n="547" who="S0517">so now he's using your dad as common ground to make</u>
<u n="548" who="S0518">well I just said</u>
<u n="549" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="550" who="S0518">I just I text back and said and he said I hope your auditions <trunc>g</trunc> I hope your auditions go well tonight because obviously I was doing some at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s wasn't I? and erm he <pause dur="short"/> and also as well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had texted to say I can't remember what time you're coming but I've got to have a shower so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s just</u>
<u n="551" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="552" who="S0518">popped out so</u>
<u n="553" who="S0517" trans="overlap">let yourself in yes</u>
<u n="554" who="S0518" trans="overlap">let yourself in</u>
<u n="555" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0518">so I <trunc>ma</trunc> I made a big joke I said oh he's in the shower I said let's have a cos I wanted to show to him that this is how just how I am with lots of friends and we'll just have a banter and there's no nothing meant in it you know</u>
<u n="557" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="558" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't literally mean come and get in the shower with me he's</u>
<u n="559" who="S0517">he meant let yourself in the house</u>
<u n="560" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah in the house and</u>
<u n="561" who="S0517">and they <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>and they all did</unclear></u>
<u n="562" who="S0518" trans="overlap">you know</u>
<u n="563" who="S0517">yeah I know I know</u>
<u n="564" who="S0518">and all of it but I don't know whether <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> gets that or not and cos he doesn't like my drama friends and erm even cos now</u>
<u n="565" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well he appears to be erm</u>
<u n="566" who="S0518" trans="overlap">he's trying to get in with them ingratiate himself in my social life</u>
<u n="567" who="S0517" trans="overlap">what's his best friend that's so weird</u>
<u n="568" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I'll go back to that but erm I just <trunc>te</trunc> when he text me on Wednesday night I was literally going to <unclear/> so I didn't text him at all and then I text him yesterday morning and just said look no worries you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had stuff to talk about so</u>
<u n="569" who="S0517">mm mm</u>
<u n="570" who="S0518">not offended at all erm</u>
<u n="571" who="S0517">I think you're gonna need to be a bit more</u>
<u n="572" who="S0518">well for ages I've not answered his texts I haven't engaged in any conversation</u>
<u n="573" who="S0517">what are you gonna do on Wednesday? cos I can't I won't be there are you gonna run with him if he asks?</u>
<u n="574" who="S0518">I I don't really want to</u>
<u n="575" who="S0517">you're gonna have to make an excuse and be somewhere else you're gonna have to drop him off and go aren't you? you can run in a different place</u>
<u n="576" who="S0518" trans="overlap">somewhere else</u>
<u n="577" who="S0517">well yes otherwise it's just gonna get awkward for you if you don't want to</u>
<u n="578" who="S0518">I just think I'm just wary now because if I say it's alright to run and then it's just me that turns up then it looks like I'm giving an invitation to be alright with this</u>
<u n="579" who="S0517">yes yeah</u>
<u n="580" who="S0518" trans="overlap">because</u>
<u n="581" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I don't think I would run with him by myself if I were you</u>
<u n="582" who="S0518">I mean I've <trunc>r</trunc> swam on a Monday night for years nine till ten and it follows the triathlon club</u>
<u n="583" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="584" who="S0518">which he joined with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and which is why I started taking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> running in the first place because he could swim and</u>
<u n="585" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0518">cycle but he couldn't run and he didn't like the triathlon running coach so that's why I took <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in the first place but then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> grew out of it and I think did one biathlon and then he just lost interest but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> carried on swimming with erm her <unclear/> so <unclear>he</unclear> didn't swim for over a year</u>
<u n="587" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="588" who="S0518">so I used to just go on Mondays and obviously not see him wait for the triathlon to finish get in do my swim now he's come back to it like he said to me he wrote on this letter or did he wrote a letter or text me? I can't remember and just said erm I know you want to see me because you're coming swimming on a Monday night and I was like I've swum for years on a Monday night I don't come to see you and he said well the fact that you were there waiting to get in when we get out he said you could easily have come five minutes later so the next week I went later</u>
<u n="589" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="590" who="S0518">cos I just thought if that's what he thinks</u>
<u n="591" who="S0517">he's reading stuff into all sorts of things</u>
<u n="592" who="S0518" trans="overlap">into</u>
<u n="593" who="S0517">that's not there isn't he?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0518" trans="overlap">stuff that I just do normally</u>
<u n="595" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="596" who="S0518">so that's my worry I'm being</u>
<u n="597" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><trunc>n</trunc> if I were you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I honestly wouldn't run with him and if it means saying oh no I've got to be somewhere else make an excuse go somewhere I mean the run's only half an hour long you've got an hour I would cos I I</u>
<u n="598" who="S0518">mm I just er you said you've been nice and considering that he's done all of this but I think you know somewhere along the line I'm obviously partially to blame because I've been too friendly and</u>
<u n="599" who="S0517">well no I don't think you're partially to blame I think that you need to appreciate that he's made his feelings clear that he wants more than friendship</u>
<u n="600" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="601" who="S0517"><trunc>i</trunc>if you've said no I don't want more than friendship he needs to back off</u>
<u n="602" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="603" who="S0517">you haven't done anything wrong he needs to back off</u>
<u n="604" who="S0518">he gave he's given me a necklace</u>
<u n="605" who="S0517"><vocal desc="gasp"/> god have you accepted it?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0518">no I I</u>
<u n="607" who="S0517" trans="overlap">when did he give it you?</u>
<u n="608" who="S0518">Christmas</u>
<u n="609" who="S0517">is it an expensive one?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0518">it's erm I don't know it's in a box it's got a butterfly and two little diamond four diamonds in it</u>
<u n="611" who="S0517">diamonds?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0518">little tiny little <unclear/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0517" trans="overlap">are they diamonds actual diamonds?</u>
<u n="614" who="S0518">erm well I don't know it's all marked I don't know erm but diamond <unclear>a thing</unclear></u>
<u n="615" who="S0517" trans="overlap">did you open it on front of the family?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0518">no no</u>
<u n="617" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you see that's slightly alarming</u>
<u n="618" who="S0518">no</u>
<u n="619" who="S0517" trans="overlap">why not?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="621" who="S0517">why not?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>becau</trunc>because I first of all he gave this thing to me and I erm <pause dur="short"/> said that I could I said I don't want it but <trunc>the</trunc> and then he but then he got really like upset and got and mad and erm I said I can't accept a gift from you I can't accept a gift from you but and but then he was <trunc>rea</trunc> he was upset because he'd been and bought it and chose it especially and all this kind of business and it was supposed to be a peace offering and all of this erm</u>
<u n="623" who="S0517" trans="overlap">a peace offering for what?</u>
<u n="624" who="S0518">for all the upset that he'd caused I need to go back a bit really don't I? I feel bad cos I've told you too much already but erm</u>
<u n="625" who="S0517" trans="overlap">has he caused you a lot of upset?</u>
<u n="626" who="S0518">yeah yeah because because he hasn't taken no for an answer and then he said</u>
<u n="627" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well he's still not then is he?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0518">no he isn't but I think he's in a mess you see I think he's in a really bad mess and erm</u>
<u n="629" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he does sound a little bit unstable I'd be a bit concerned if I were you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos he's not taking no for an answer he's getting more and more obsessed</u>
<u n="630" who="S0518">last</u>
<u n="631" who="S0517">gifts and flowers and letters and</u>
<u n="632" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0517">texts and turning up now at the thing I would be a little bit concerned</u>
<u n="634" who="S0518">well I am concerned but I'm concerned as to what his and I <trunc>s</trunc> I've said to him you're unstable and I don't know what action you're gonna take next and I said and it really worries me because one minute you're just really normal and grounded and calm and acting like the person that I know and the next minute you're erm</u>
<u n="635" who="S0517">a stalker</u>
<u n="636" who="S0518">yeah doing</u>
<u n="637" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="638" who="S0518">really bizarre and then sending a really nasty horrible text to me and then sending a really nice text and then and and then and I just ignore them all and then he <trunc>s</trunc> he'll say you know one time when you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it was at the <anon type="place"/> and you saw us sitting in the car you've seen us sitting in the car</u>
<u n="639" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="640" who="S0518">a few times</u>
<u n="641" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="642" who="S0518">we're having these big conversations and and then</u>
<u n="643" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh is that the time he didn't want to get out the car cos he said you'll just go and talk to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="644" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah and you'll</u>
<u n="645" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and then you'll leave me out?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0518">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="647" who="S0517" trans="overlap">like some sort of child</u>
<u n="648" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="649" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="650" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="651" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah no no my husband just thinks he's weird he always has done</u>
<u n="652" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well I think he's right</u>
<u n="653" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and I'm not gonna tell him anything <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because I do hate it when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s right and he calls it so often with people</u>
<u n="654" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="655" who="S0517">it really annoys me I think</u>
<u n="656" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would not approve anyway</u>
<u n="657" who="S0517">oh my goodness no he'd just would think really badly of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and then he'd just go why is your friend putting up with that? what's wrong with her? why is she putting up with that? cos he's a bit like that</u>
<u n="658" who="S0518" trans="overlap">because erm</u>
<u n="659" who="S0517">cos he's a bit black and white</u>
<u n="660" who="S0518">and because also</u>
<u n="661" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but it doesn't want</u>
<u n="662" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I'm stupid I am</u>
<u n="663" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no you're not stupid</u>
<u n="664" who="S0518">I am stupid</u>
<u n="665" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but he calls it he does I don't know how he does that he's always said it right from the start from the minute we met him</u>
<u n="666" who="S0518">but I you know you used to tease me and say it and I'd say no no no no no I used to think where have they got this from where have they got this from? if I'm perfectly honest last this happened this started last July because it was you can't believe the timing of it in the very week that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> challenged <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and said I know that you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are friends and we were doing Alternative Accommodation and it was the festival</u>
<u n="667" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="668" who="S0518">and we were at the <anon type="place"/> the hotel and then we were taking it for two nights to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="669" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="670" who="S0518">in that very same week and I've got all of that stuff going on</u>
<u n="671" who="S0517" trans="overlap">is that last July is that the play that I got the <trunc>wr</trunc> tickets the <trunc>wro</trunc></u>
<u n="672" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0517">that's never last July that</u>
<u n="674" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="675" who="S0517">I think</u>
<u n="676" who="S0518" trans="overlap">it is</u>
<u n="677" who="S0517">that's really</u>
<u n="678" who="S0518" trans="overlap">can you believe it? it's nearly a year ago</u>
<u n="679" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no I can't actually</u>
<u n="680" who="S0518" trans="overlap">this time last year we were rehearsing it and erm it was part of the <anon type="place"/> festival in that very same week this is when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm</u>
<u n="681" who="S0517">they'll take his name out don't you worry <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="682" who="S0518" trans="overlap">okay erm chose to declare his feelings and decided to cycle to <anon type="place"/> hall to barge into the performance and say all of this but in</u>
<u n="683" who="S0517" trans="overlap">in front of anyone?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0518">no just in front of me</u>
<u n="685" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="686" who="S0518">but he didn't realise that the cycle ride was so long and he didn't get there on time <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> how long did it take?</u>
<u n="688" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="689" who="S0517">that's hilarious</u>
<u n="690" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="691" who="S0517">so <vocal desc="laugh"/> so what had you gone home?</u>
<event desc="sound of phone"/>
<u n="692" who="S0518">erm <pause dur="short"/> I no I think he just he decided it was just too late by that stage</u>
<u n="693" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="694" who="S0518">is that you?</u>
<u n="695" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="696" who="S0518" trans="overlap">the ring?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0517">it was you <pause dur="short"/> oh my goodness</u>
<u n="698" who="S0518">right let me just see what this says <pause dur="short"/> okay I don't it's just to do with the play I don't need to look at that just now erm yeah he was he oh I can't even remember <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> how it</u>
<u n="699" who="S0517">so when</u>
<u n="700" who="S0518" trans="overlap">happened</u>
<u n="701" who="S0517" trans="overlap">did he tell you then? if he missed you at that point after cycling all the way to <anon type="place"/> hall that is hilarious</u>
<u n="702" who="S0518">he well he'd <trunc>sai</trunc> he he said something it must have been the Wednesday whatever day the boys had <trunc>f</trunc> and he'd got this new car and he said oh come and sit in my new car and</u>
<u n="703" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh I remember you telling me that</u>
<u n="704" who="S0518"><unclear>all that</unclear></u>
<u n="705" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="706" who="S0518">and and then he said something to me in that car and I was like horrified and got out of the car and then</u>
<u n="707" who="S0517" trans="overlap">what did he say?</u>
<u n="708" who="S0518">that just basically that he thought that we should you know have an affair together</u>
<u n="709" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="710" who="S0518">and I got out of the car and he sent me a text the next day and said I'm never gonna let you ever sit in my car again and erm you teased me by sitting in my car</u>
<u n="711" who="S0517"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="712" who="S0518">wearing stockings how would anybody know that? how would anybody know that?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0517">were you?</u>
<u n="714" who="S0518">well they were pull holdups pull up <vocal desc="laugh"/> holdups</u>
<u n="715" who="S0517" trans="overlap">how well</u>
<u n="716" who="S0518">so I</u>
<u n="717" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm not being funny yes you are partly to blame you should have put a stop to it there and then what were you thinking still being so nice to him?</u>
<u n="718" who="S0518">but I wasn't that was the that was that was yeah okay I'm partly to blame because I just thought this is ludicrous what is this? where has this all sprung from?</u>
<u n="719" who="S0517"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="720" who="S0518">this is just out of nowhere and I was just like I <trunc>ha</trunc> don't be absolutely so ridiculous I'm getting out of this car now but you see at the time <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I was in absolute meltdown</u>
<u n="721" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><trunc>mel</trunc> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0518" trans="overlap">over everything else and that was all that I could focus on and I was just like what? in the middle of all of this?</u>
<u n="723" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="724" who="S0518">what how dare you?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0517" trans="overlap">which he didn't know about did he?</u>
<u n="726" who="S0518">oh absolutely not so erm</u>
<u n="727" who="S0517">oh my goodness no I didn't mean that you're not partly to blame <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="728" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well I am</u>
<u n="729" who="S0517">you're not</u>
<u n="730" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><trunc>becau</trunc> I am <trunc>becau</trunc></u>
<u n="731" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I didn't mean that erm</u>
<u n="732" who="S0518" trans="overlap">because I thought I could sort it out you see so then he</u>
<u n="733" who="S0517">so but you haven't</u>
<u n="734" who="S0518" trans="overlap">told me that he'd erm <pause dur="short"/> whatever day it must have been it must have been <pause dur="short"/> was it well it was the Wednesday and Thursday so it was the Wednesday night that he then the following week that he decided that he would I'm gonna make her know how serious I am about this I'm gonna cycle to her performance at <anon type="place"/> hall and I'm gonna walk in and I'm gonna ask to see her and I'm gonna tell her this and can you imagine that Wednesday night <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I are acting in this play together and his wife on the very front row we've already got that to contend with without that happening but I didn't find out about it till the next day when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> texted me and said by the way last night I started to cycle out to see you my intention was however <vocal desc="laugh"/> I didn't realise how far it was</u>
<u n="735" who="S0517">oh god</u>
<u n="736" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and I I thought the performance would probably nearly be finished <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I just turned around and came home so I agreed to</u>
<u n="737" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="738" who="S0518">meet him for a serious talk on that Friday and I just said to him <pause dur="short"/> I said look you can't you can't know all of this but I said there's some other stuff that's happened in my life really really important awful stuff and I just need to tell you now that er being anything but friends with you would be absolutely just it it we can't do it because I said it will go pear shaped I don't want to anyway</u>
<u n="739" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no you see you've phrased that wrong because that gave him a hope that</u>
<u n="740" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well I probably didn't say it in that order</u>
<u n="741" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I should hope you didn't because that would give him an <trunc>or</trunc> an idea that</u>
<u n="742" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I probably didn't say it in that order</u>
<u n="743" who="S0517" trans="overlap">if other things hadn't happened you'd say yes</u>
<u n="744" who="S0518">no because I didn't</u>
<u n="745" who="S0517">okay</u>
<u n="746" who="S0518">I didn't</u>
<u n="747" who="S0517">as long as you're sure you didn't</u>
<u n="748" who="S0518" trans="overlap">because he told me I'd stuck a dagger between his ribs and</u>
<u n="749" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="750" who="S0518">punctured his heart</u>
<u n="751" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="752" who="S0518">so whatever I said</u>
<u n="753" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="754" who="S0518">I'd obviously made it clear</u>
<u n="755" who="S0517">oh good</u>
<u n="756" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but but basically</u>
<u n="757" who="S0517" trans="overlap">okay okay</u>
<u n="758" who="S0518">because I knew everything that had gone happened with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had all gone so bad and that we were gonna lose our friendship because of our own just lustful selfishness erm</u>
<u n="759" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="760" who="S0518">that risking another friendship that involved children and something much bigger just wasn't even worth it it just wasn't even worth the thought of it whether I'd wanted to or not it just wasn't even worth it and I had to I just had to make that really really clear but then I suppose</u>
<u n="761" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so since then so for nine months he hasn't taken no for an answer?</u>
<u n="762" who="S0518">no because obviously then I was poorly I was signed off work</u>
<u n="763" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="764" who="S0518">then these flowers arrived saying erm I'm sorry that you're ill</u>
<u n="765" who="S0517">did you know they were from him then secretly?</u>
<u n="766" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="767" who="S0517">did you think?</u>
<u n="768" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no no but I</u>
<u n="769" who="S0517">did you <trunc>a</trunc> you asked him didn't you?</u>
<u n="770" who="S0518">no because I didn't even consider that and because I hadn't had really had any contact with</u>
<u n="771" who="S0517" trans="overlap">does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> ever ask whether you found out who they were from?</u>
<u n="772" who="S0518">not now cos it's all water under the bridge</u>
<u n="773" who="S0517">I know that but I yeah</u>
<u n="774" who="S0518">he's not there's no</u>
<u n="775" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so he doesn't know anything? <trunc>d</trunc> you've never you've not told him any of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="776" who="S0518">I've told him</u>
<u n="777" who="S0517">bad behaviour?</u>
<u n="778" who="S0518">I've told him</u>
<u n="779" who="S0517" trans="overlap">that's what it is</u>
<u n="780" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wanted to stop running with us and he obviously I told him some stuff that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s told me erm about when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s met me swimming and said like oh I heard that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came swimming and you were swimming for the night was she okay to you? and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said to me just I know what he said I know what men are like for talking to you and telling you their problems and he said it's happened before and you've been really understanding and he said you're a really good listener I mean you take on board people's problems and he said and they just read something else into it and that's probably</u>
<u n="781" who="S0517">so that's what he thinks?</u>
<u n="782" who="S0518" trans="overlap">what</u>
<u n="783" who="S0517">and that is what's happened</u>
<u n="784" who="S0518">yeah and <trunc>bec</trunc> but because we've been friends and known each other for a long time and I don't <pause dur="short"/> I felt it very difficult to just <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="785" who="S0517" trans="overlap">cut him off sort of thing</u>
<u n="786" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="787" who="S0517">yeah no I can understand that</u>
<u n="788" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and because I've always said look whatever we need to get over this awkwardness because we need to be</u>
<u n="789" who="S0517">they're the boys</u>
<u n="790" who="S0518" trans="overlap">normal</u>
<u n="791" who="S0517">are on the same team and all this</u>
<u n="792" who="S0518" trans="overlap">we can't suddenly be</u>
<u n="793" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but he obviously hasn't and he's getting worse</u>
<u n="794" who="S0518">and if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> says to me oh can you bring <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> home and stuff I don't want to say no I can't I want to be comfortable enough to say yeah that's fine so that's why in my stupid naïve ignorance I just thought I can have a conversation with him I can make it clear to him and we can just move on but I had no idea and I said to him I had no idea that you felt like this because as far as I'm concerned he said I can't believe you don't know that that I loved you and I said every time I see you you say <pause dur="short"/> what are you dressed in black for? you shouldn't be wearing that to run in you should be this you should be that you <trunc>sh</trunc> you go too fast you're too chatty calm down you shush me at football matches when I cheer there's a goal and I said so really you've always given me the impression that I'm too over the top for you you're constantly criticising oh surely not in another play again erm you're just too dramatic all these drama stories all these drama friends they're just too over the top and all of this he said so all the time really you just</u>
<u n="795" who="S0517" trans="overlap">secretly you're in love with me</u>
<u n="796" who="S0518" trans="overlap">you've just laughed at me criticised me made fun of me teased me so I never got that impression and I said whenever you say something to me you say it in a riddle</u>
<u n="797" who="S0517" trans="overlap">that's like what that's that's what children children do though isn't it?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="799" who="S0517">when they fancy someone</u>
<u n="800" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="801" who="S0517" trans="overlap">they're mean to them</u>
<u n="802" who="S0518">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="803" who="S0517" trans="overlap">that's what children do when they're <trunc>fir</trunc> when they're first <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but I said to him I'm a talker and I tell people how I feel and I said I don't speak in riddles and I said you have just spoken to me just in riddles and I don't understand what you're saying and you're saying oh you were obviously saying something to me that I'm just not getting and I take it</u>
<u n="805" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="806" who="S0518">on</u>
<u n="807" who="S0517">face value</u>
<u n="808" who="S0518" trans="overlap">face value</u>
<u n="809" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="810" who="S0518">of what it what you actually mean and and obviously there's some <trunc>hi</trunc> other hidden message that I just <trunc>ha</trunc>haven't got and erm <pause dur="short"/> I so I said I am I said I knew you liked me because obviously you wouldn't spend time running with somebody or asking your children to run with them or saying shall we share a lift to a rugby match and stuff like this</u>
<u n="811" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="812" who="S0518">if you if you <pause dur="short"/> you'd just say to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> oh god</u>
<u n="813" who="S0517">yes but you know <pause dur="short"/> er <trunc>w</trunc>well for instance take <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I mean he doesn't run but that he he I wouldn't think twice if he if we shared a lift somewhere if the boys were going <trunc>somethi</trunc></u>
<u n="814" who="S0518" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="815" who="S0517">it just wouldn't think twice about it because</u>
<u n="816" who="S0518">so say if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then said all of this to you out of the blue you would find that probably well maybe you wouldn't but you would find that because of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is friends with</u>
<u n="817" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="818" who="S0518" trans="overlap">to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="819" who="S0517">I'd find that particularly weird but I</u>
<u n="820" who="S0518" trans="overlap">what</u>
<u n="821" who="S0517">probably would tell <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I don't know actually <pause dur="short"/> yeah the I dunno and it hasn't even</u>
<u n="822" who="S0518" trans="overlap">see</u>
<u n="823" who="S0517">occurred to me because it would never happen hasn't</u>
<u n="824" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well it</u>
<u n="825" who="S0517">happened but I can see the</u>
<u n="826" who="S0518">you're put in that</u>
<u n="827" who="S0517">the similarity that</u>
<u n="828" who="S0518" trans="overlap">sort of terrible situation</u>
<u n="829" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="830" who="S0518">where this is a family</u>
<u n="831" who="S0517">family friends</u>
<u n="832" who="S0518" trans="overlap">friend and</u>
<u n="833" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I know where the kids are friends and everything but erm</u>
<u n="834" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah and it's just disappointing</u>
<u n="835" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but I mean the whole if he hasn't he hasn't taken no for an answer the flowers the gift at Christmas that's a bit</u>
<u n="836" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so I said I'm not gonna <trunc>r</trunc> I'm not responding to your texts and then he's saying that's not the person that I know because you're a really warm open person and he said and now you're just not even showing any kindness you're being <trunc>un</trunc> called me cold and unkind and he said you've got er like a heart of stone and all of this</u>
<u n="837" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="838" who="S0518">and I've said like that's the furthest away from a description of me furthest away but I can't enter into any communication with you because every time I do it leads you believe</u>
<u n="839" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="840" who="S0518">that there's some hope</u>
<u n="841" who="S0517" trans="overlap">something different</u>
<u n="842" who="S0518">and er I have to tell you though that there isn't and he said well you know you're obviously not happy with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because you're out all the time you're constantly in these plays and everything and then he did and then obviously these flowers came but they were at the beginning of my sickness and I thought that they were from from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I thought they were from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I thought they were from all different so from work and then and they weren't and then the florist wouldn't tell me and then when I went back to work I got these other flowers and then at some point I can't remember not that long ago he said to me <pause dur="short"/> a valentine card came to work and I guessed it was from him I just ignored it and erm I just got this Shakespeare sonnet written in it and</u>
<u n="843" who="S0517">oh had it?</u>
<u n="844" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="845" who="S0517">oh thoughtful</u>
<u n="846" who="S0518">it was and it was all about the person who loves no matter what erm no matter what happens will not be swayed from their position so the object of your affection whether they change course whether they put a wall up whether they say no because that because the lover truly loves they won't we dissuaded from it and that's what this sonnet was about it's a famous one</u>
<u n="847" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="848" who="S0518">and he said his heart was like a a dry desert and</u>
<u n="849" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="850" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/> longing for a drop of <unclear/></u>
<u n="851" who="S0517">look you don't think about that</u>
<u n="852" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="853" who="S0517">of an engineer do you?</u>
<u n="854" who="S0518">and so so</u>
<u n="855" who="S0517">I mean he's an engineer isn't he?</u>
<u n="856" who="S0518">but this is what I said to him I've got</u>
<u n="857" who="S0517" trans="overlap">that's just</u>
<u n="858" who="S0518">no idea</u>
<u n="859" who="S0517" trans="overlap">not what you</u>
<u n="860" who="S0518">I have got no idea because I said you're so guarded you don't show any emotion you don't show you know and I said like I say I I say oh I'm excited I'm really annoyed I'm upset about this da-da-da-da in all of our times running together talking walking whatever just lifts or stuff I'm just articulate it all and I'm not saying I'm right and he's wrong but what I've said to him is</u>
<u n="861" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but that's just how people are and then so how would you know from him?</u>
<u n="862" who="S0518" trans="overlap">how could I have guessed?</u>
<u n="863" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="864" who="S0518">how could I have possibly guessed from how you are that all of this was going on inside you and why have you suddenly</u>
<u n="865" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so did you</u>
<u n="866" who="S0518">picked now?</u>
<u n="867" who="S0517">say to him that you'd got the card?</u>
<u n="868" who="S0518">so he text me a few days or so after and said he said you either obviously never received the cards and the flowers or you didn't like them</u>
<u n="869" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="870" who="S0518">or you've just chosen to ignore it I purposefully made sure that things arrived so that erm <pause dur="short"/> been so that you so that it was a last last ditch attempt or something to make you know how I felt and that you would change your mind and arrange to meet me or something of course I just ignored it and ignored it and ignored it and erm</u>
<u n="871" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="872" who="S0518">like I say then there was this erm pope thing and I was at the auction at <anon type="place"/>'s with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad's stuff at reams and reams and reams of texts coming through and in the end and it just said the pope was a lucky man because he had someone who truly loved him on his deathbed and it makes me stop and say looking at my dad in the state that he is when that happens to me who will be there for me? and all of this kind of stuff and in <trunc>th</trunc> and he said you're naïve and you you <unclear/> and he's criticised my faith he's criticised religion he's criticised belief and all this sort of thing</u>
<u n="873" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="874" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and I've said you know you criticise everything that's at the core of what I stand for and you know er that's horrible because it's like criticising me and everything I believe in so you say that you love me but actually you don't love what's the essence of me at all you love what you think that I can be for you which I can't be so actually</u>
<u n="875" who="S0517"><unclear/></u>
<u n="876" who="S0518">this is me and if it doesn't fit with what you want then actually you don't love me you don't and you certainly don't understand me so I just text him after all of this stuff at the auction and I just said all you were doing is winding yourself up more and more and more I'm at an auction I cannot text you back I will respond in full to every miniscule point that you have made in these constant reams of text so just get ready and literally</u>
<u n="877" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="878" who="S0518">you know when your text won't go any further? I've</u>
<u n="879" who="S0517">no no I've never got that far</u>
<u n="880" who="S0518" trans="overlap">okay well mine have and I filled up and filled up and filled up and filled up and I just went and another thing and another thing and another thing and another thing and another thing</u>
<u n="881" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it must have taken you hours to write</u>
<u n="882" who="S0518">it did and then he text back and said I think you'll forgive me for not responding to all of that and I said yeah but you can never criticise me again for not because he criticised me for he's <trunc>t</trunc> he said I send you my thoughts now and I send you my feelings and you ignore them</u>
<u n="883" who="S0517">and it's cos he wants them reciprocated and if you're not</u>
<u n="884" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="885" who="S0517">prepared to reciprocate them he needs to learn to back off</u>
<u n="886" who="S0518">so when I was poorly</u>
<u n="887" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I think you oh</u>
<u n="888" who="S0518">he said I'll take you on a picnic I'll take you to the theatre so he said to me it's what's hurt me more than anything is when you were poorly you wouldn't let me help and he said erm other people he said you know you did exercise classes with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> he said you met your friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in Birmingham you erm he said oh you were constantly meeting <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? he's some mental nutcase that spends half of his life on a Scottish island and</u>
<u n="889" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="890" who="S0518">he said you know who who are these people? and I said to him these people are people that I've known for years for thirty odd years some of them and I said who I know really well I said we've been through all sorts of</u>
<u n="891" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="892" who="S0518" trans="overlap">we've been through each other's marriages people's parents dying our babies being born you know all of this</u>
<u n="893" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah you can't just wipe all that out oh no</u>
<u n="894" who="S0518" trans="overlap">you know who know me really well</u>
<u n="895" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so are you you should be <trunc>s</trunc> I think you should be slightly alarmed</u>
<u n="896" who="S0518">and I said</u>
<u n="897" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I do</u>
<u n="898" who="S0518">I am alarmed and I said to him I erm the reason that I can spend time with them is because they're not the root of my problem I said they are actually I can go and talk to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about his art gallery and his latest crazy project and his current</u>
<u n="899" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="900" who="S0518">walk that he's planning on the isle of Skye and I said and it cheers me up I said er I come and talk to you and it's all about why don't you love me? why won't you love me and all this sort of thing and he and I said and it just churns me up I'm supposed to be getting better and he said I feel I am partly responsible for you being poorly and not sleeping well and I said well you are because I said how can I recover when you you're putting all of this on me? and in the end <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> he said to me I get a distinct feeling that if you weren't with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you still wouldn't be with me and I said</u>
<u n="901" who="S0517"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="902" who="S0518">that's</u>
<u n="903" who="S0517" trans="overlap">hallelujah</u>
<u n="904" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I wouldn't and he said there's somebody else because he said all you've said to me on and on and on is I've got first-hand experience that anything like this goes ends in tears so he said you you've obviously you've obviously had a situation I said yeah</u>
<u n="905" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh you didn't tell him did you?</u>
<u n="906" who="S0518">yeah but not in detail so I said to him cos he told me loads and loads of stuff and I'd just in that moment in time</u>
<u n="907" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you know he'll hold that against you when it all comes out that he's he's suffering with his unrequited love?</u>
<u n="908" who="S0518">well it probably will and he'll probably <unclear/></u>
<u n="909" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he probably will hold that against you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="910" who="S0518">but he doesn't know</u>
<u n="911" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you have to be careful</u>
<u n="912" who="S0518">he doesn't know any details nobody can say anything he doesn't know any who these people are</u>
<u n="913" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="914" who="S0518">and erm but I just said to <trunc>hi</trunc> I just said to him you know I've got another friend that spoke to me about personal stuff and I said and I listened and listened and listened and we became close because of it he didn't have anyone else to speak to and I said mm you know we acted together and I said and then suddenly out of the blue his wife challenged him and said have you have you discussed our problems with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? and I said and it shocked him and he said yes and I said and now we can't even be friends so I said you know we can't</u>
<u n="915" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="916" who="S0518">we can't even be friends and he said so you say like you've talked to him what other things have you done with this guy? and I said that really is none of your business and I really resent you asking me that what I'm trying to make the point is he thought his wife knew nothing about me</u>
<u n="917" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="918" who="S0518">wasn't in my circle of friends I wasn't in hers as far as she was concerned he was off rehearsing</u>
<u n="919" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="920" who="S0518">and I said but she obviously knows his pattern of doing things knows what time he should get back every time he'd had a rehearsal he'd stayed for a drink that probably wasn't in his normal</u>
<u n="921" who="S0517">right yeah</u>
<u n="922" who="S0518" trans="overlap">pattern of things so she thought who's in that play?</u>
<u n="923" who="S0517">mm mm</u>
<u n="924" who="S0518" trans="overlap">four people <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s ninety-two it's not gonna be her</u>
<u n="925" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="926" who="S0518">you know and he he she knew that it she knew <trunc>sh</trunc> that he and I were friends or acquaintances and she just put two two and two together</u>
<u n="927" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="928" who="S0518">she didn't actually have any proof cos there was none really to have but she just on the off chance thought she'd challenge him and he was obviously</u>
<u n="929" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="930" who="S0518" trans="overlap">taken off guard and erm so I said you know <trunc>sh</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is already suspicious she didn't want you to run with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and with me and I said you know that really really hurt me at the time and I said you didn't stick up for us at all you just bowed down to what she wanted and he didn't say don't be ridiculous woman he just went oh I can't do it that you know and I said and now I can understand what what she's thinking I can that's</u>
<u n="931" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="932" who="S0518" trans="overlap">probably why you know and erm so all I said to him what I'm saying is that I've got personal experience because I said I've lost a really really</u>
<u n="933" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="934" who="S0518">good friend who I I said er I I loved with all my heart and I said it really really upsets me and it really upsets him that we can't even have that normal friendship now and I said I don't want that to happen to us you are prepared to jeopardise a nice friendship that we had</u>
<u n="935" who="S0517">mm <pause dur="short"/> and what did he say to that?</u>
<u n="936" who="S0518" trans="overlap">for for a <trunc>s</trunc> a fling</u>
<u n="937" who="S0517">fling yeah</u>
<u n="938" who="S0518" trans="overlap">that that you know and he just said I don't know who this guy is but if he if he knew how valuable your friendship was he would have done this and he would have done that and he would have <trunc>th</trunc> I said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you don't know the first thing about it</u>
<u n="939" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he's no oh</u>
<u n="940" who="S0518">and I said I haven't told you this so you can start criticising another of my friends and he said well it's quite apparent that you you know that you really love this other person and I said I do and I miss his friendship so but you don't need to know about that I said but I don't want to be in the same situation with you you know where</u>
<u n="941" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="942" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and I said and it's worse because our children are friends I said his children and my children don't know each other but our children are friends and you know oh well not going anywhere</u>
<u n="943" who="S0517" trans="overlap">how's it gonna end? where do you see this going?</u>
<u n="944" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="945" who="S0517">how er I where what do you think</u>
<u n="946" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="947" who="S0517">is gonna happen?</u>
<u n="948" who="S0518">he has said as a result of all of this he's come to a new way of thinking so three weeks three Fridays ago I met him for a cup of tea at <anon type="place"/> marina and erm because he's he'd got some stuff to discuss and I just thought you know I haven't been responding to him and in fairness I need to just hear him out he'd sent this letters to me and I have just ignored them not responded to them or anything erm I've started going swimming ten minutes later so I don't have to come</u>
<u n="949" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="950" who="S0518">face to face with him</u>
<u n="951" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="952" who="S0518">and I just thought I know how upset I feel when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has not responded to me about stuff so I thought I kind of see from that point of view how hurtful it is so I will</u>
<u n="953" who="S0517">yeah but that's different</u>
<u n="954" who="S0518" trans="overlap">respond to him it is different</u>
<u n="955" who="S0517">cos the two of you felt the same about each other</u>
<u n="956" who="S0518">it is different</u>
<u n="957" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you two don't so</u>
<u n="958" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I've told myself that a million times because I've said why can't I see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s point of view? because I get frustrated when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can't see mine and then I've gone hang on a minute that's completely different</u>
<u n="959" who="S0517" trans="overlap">completely different it is completely different</u>
<u n="960" who="S0518" trans="overlap">completely different so anyway erm I met him for this cup of tea and he sat down in the chair and I sat down and he and then he moved to sit next to me and I went like this</u>
<u n="961" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="962" who="S0518">and my body language was like this and he was like you can sit closer you know and I said I don't want to</u>
<u n="963" who="S0517">good for you</u>
<u n="964" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I want to sit here so I said I don't want to</u>
<u n="965" who="S0517" trans="overlap">is this before or after the incident after the pool?</u>
<u n="966" who="S0518">I can't remember same week maybe can't remember I can't remember anyway I can't remember <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm and he said to me I've been doing a lot of thinking and he said I've thought I I used to think that I made this pledge that I was gonna hold my family together and I was gonna keep <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> happy and just put on a front just to keep her happy and I had to just hold erm my family together and he said and then I met you he said I'd known you for a long time but he said then obviously I approached you to go running and stuff and then when we got to know each other a bit more and he said and I just thought the boys are getting older now I've got myself in a life sentence which I don't have to have it's time</u>
<u n="967" who="S0517">a life sentence?</u>
<u n="968" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="969" who="S0517">that's how he described his marriage that's a shame isn't it?</u>
<u n="970" who="S0518">I know and he said it's time now that I had</u>
<u n="971" who="S0517">get release <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="972" who="S0518">something for me a bit of love and affection and he said and I thought that you could be the person and then the more I've got to know you then the more I thought that and <pause dur="short"/> and he said and now all of this happened and he said it's made me realise that probably I'm approaching it completely wrong</u>
<u n="973" who="S0517"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="974" who="S0518">that actually what I shouldn't be doing is holding the family together and living in a marriage that's miserable I should be addressing the problem and sorting them out and making plans to split up really this is all I shouldn't be saying all of this</u>
<u n="975" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh well no well I'm not gonna tell anyone <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="976" who="S0518" trans="overlap">this is <trunc>confiden</trunc> this is</u>
<u n="977" who="S0517">yeah no I wouldn't say</u>
<u n="978" who="S0518" trans="overlap">this is what I mean you won't trust me now to you won't tell me anything now about ever if you needed to you'll think I won't speak to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because she'll go and</u>
<u n="979" who="S0517" trans="overlap">cos she'll pass it on no I won't think that</u>
<u n="980" who="S0518" trans="overlap">tell it to someone else</u>
<u n="981" who="S0517">I won't think that</u>
<u n="982" who="S0518">because this because obviously this it's</u>
<u n="983" who="S0517" trans="overlap">confidential er yeah no but is he actually gonna go with it?</u>
<u n="984" who="S0518">well I've got no idea but what he's obviously come to thinking that</u>
<u n="985" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="986" who="S0518">and what he's thought is he needs someone in his life to give him some love and affection that is missing and I've made it clear that it isn't me but what everything that I've said to him and I've given him some home truths about I don't expect everybody I know to be like one of my lovely drama friends showing it all on their sleeve</u>
<u n="987" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="988" who="S0518">I said but I I you know I've said to him said I can't nobody can read you nobody you've got these feelings but you don't say them to anybody</u>
<u n="989" who="S0517" trans="overlap">to to yeah yeah</u>
<u n="990" who="S0518">and he said he's been brought up to just get on and manage himself and to push feelings inside and</u>
<u n="991" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="992" who="S0518">it was always expected you didn't show these feelings and his aunt has always said about him you're a cold one <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you are a cold fish you are cos you never show any emotion</u>
<u n="993" who="S0517">lots of people lots of British people are like that though</u>
<u n="994" who="S0518">yeah and that</u>
<u n="995" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was bought up a bit the same he was at boarding school he had to suppress everything and look at him now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="996" who="S0518">yeah he's he's just out there isn't he? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="997" who="S0517">completely repressed that man <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="998" who="S0518">but</u>
<u n="999" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0518">so you'll understand a little bit of that</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but no yes yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0518">so he's been brought up to know that never had a good relationship with his dad never had a proper conversation</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0518">doesn't know how his dad ticks and now his dad's dying and he's got massive regrets because he didn't really know his dad only as a person to shake hands with doesn't really know him at all and</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0517" trans="overlap">do you know what?</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0518">it's too late</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it's weird it's quite similar to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1008" who="S0518">is it?</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0517">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> never lived with his dad cos he went to boarding school</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0517">from a really young age never really <trunc>live</trunc> well when until he was about six but he doesn't really remember that and then didn't live with him again after that</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0517">so mm</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0518">and did his dad die before or did he move from boarding school to university and then like that?</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad only died about ten years ago so if he had we it well he went he didn't like boarding school so he came back to he his mum came back to the UK</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0518">right</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and he went to as a day boy they called it</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0518" trans="overlap">were they split up then?</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0517">no no no</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0518">oh</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0517" trans="overlap">they were still together but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't like <trunc>b</trunc>boarding school he didn't get on with it</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0517">he was only young he came back so his mum came back</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0517">and in term time she lived in Southend</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0518">right</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0517">and he went to his day <trunc>sch</trunc> and then</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0517">every holiday they'd fly back to where his dad was</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0517">until he went back to boarding school at about thirteen</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0518">right</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0517">and when she went back abroad</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0517">for good</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0518">and he used to fly back then to see them didn't he?</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he used to fly back in er all the holidays so and then he went off to college and then</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0518" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0517">got a job and then his dad <trunc>retir</trunc> dad retired and they came back to the UK and he said a lot more of him then</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0517">but of course by then he was in his</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0518">a grown up man with his own</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you know yeah twenty sort of thing</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0518">own life</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0517">yes and wasn't about to move back home so he didn't really ever live with his dad so it's not that there was ever any bad feeling or he didn't</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0517">feel like he knew him it's so it's not similar</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0517">to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1050" who="S0518">I understand</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but but he didn't he never I remember him saying to me he never really felt like he had a close relationship</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0517">because he'd never lived with him</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0518">mm</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0517">and was at boarding school so he was never <trunc>allo</trunc> you know</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0517">stiff upper lip type of attitude</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0517">erm but I don't think he's as he's not <trunc>weir</trunc> I mean it goes with the name <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's not weird though like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's not</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no he isn't like that at all er he is not like that well I don't know he him well enough but</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no he's not</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0518">from what I</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he's not</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0518">get from him he's not like that at all but in all of this that's happened maybe the only good thing that's come out is that our friendship maybe will be preserved on some</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0518">formal level but that that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> knows now that actually he's probably been thinking about it the wrong way around and that somewhere there will be a future in a relationship with somebody else</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0517" trans="overlap">somebody so he do you think do you think? I dunno you say all that</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear>that's the point</unclear></u>
<u n="1069" who="S0517">but it wasn't erm it didn't seem like he'd moved on on <trunc>rehear</trunc> audition night which was</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0517" trans="overlap">only what? last night?</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0518">Wednesday night oh last night oh sorry when he turned up</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0517">yeah was that</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0517">just last night?</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0518">yeah so</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0518">we had this talk anyway and I said to him I'm glad that you've done this thing here and that you've he he said he feels at a calmer place now and that he felt like the old proverb of the wind and the sun and I was like the man walking along in the coat and he was the wind and the harder he blew the tighter I've put the coat around and that as soon as the sun came out the coat would come off and he he'd done this thinking and then I said to him this is like the first bit of sense that you've spoken for a long time and he said I'm glad as painful as it's been that you've come to this understanding</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you know what he's gonna hope for though don't you? he's gonna hope that if he backs off a little bit and tells you that he's taking that approach that eventually you'll come round to your own way of thinking and tell him</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no cos I've made it quite clear cos in that conversation I said to him but I said I hope in saying this that you haven't got this in your head that I am that person</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0517">okay</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0518">so I said if whatever decision you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> come to</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0518">and that'll be really you know potentially really sad erm but you will make it for your own reasons and I said you've explained those now and I said and I feel confident that you're clear in your head about those</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0517">right okay</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I said but I have to make it clear to you that do not be doing anything along those lines</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0517" trans="overlap">on my account</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0518">on my account because I will not be waiting for that to happen</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0518">and I will not be that person to give you that</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and do you think he took that on board?</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0518">well he said he did because then he talked about erm just not really knowing where to look for anybody else you know how he would possibly meet anybody else</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0517">he's still married he's got a lot to get through first</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0518">well and yeah</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0518">and <trunc>s</trunc> he talked in a lot of detail which I won't you know I've given you the bare bones then but he talked in a lot of personal detail about stuff and I won't disclose that because it all</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no no no</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0518" trans="overlap">quite upsetting</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I don't</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0518">and erm but then he said it er I said look I need to go because I said erm said you're not gonna like this but going to see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s latest production</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1102" who="S0518">and I need to go and do some shopping first of all so he said can we meet again? and I said I don't know really if it's necessary he said there's a couple of things that I've thought about that I still haven't spoken to you and I need to</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0518"><trunc>e</trunc>explain certain behaviours that I have he said I don't really you've really understood why I've been like that and he said I think if we're going to maintain our friendship going forward it's important that you do understand why I did and was the way I was so I said okay which he said</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0518">are you available next Friday? and I said no because it's the play next Friday and I said I don't want the pressure and it I just don't so he said okay I'm not gonna pester you and say what about that Friday and what about that Friday he said I'll leave it to you when you feel ready that your feel you can have a normal chat with me</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0518">you let me know so it's like okay great so then his</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0517">but that hasn't been the case</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0518">no</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0517">has it?</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0518">he and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> well sort of he and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were coming to see the <trunc>pl</trunc> my play on the Saturday and erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had said oh we'll meet you for a drink after in the <anon type="place"/> cos I know that's where you go well it was closed for a private party so they went in the <anon type="place"/> and we went to <anon type="place"/> and she</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh yeah you said yeah</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0518" trans="overlap">she text me and said you know we're in <anon type="place"/> said well we can't see you but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has been in and I was like oh we've gone to the <anon type="place"/> anyway they turned they then she and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> turned up at the <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said oh well we'll leave you with your <unclear/> and they went off and then I was just chatting to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she went to the toilet and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just said I just want to tell you that you were brilliant so I said well I appreciate you coming to support us and he went not in play he said you know that you were brilliant in the play he said the way you spoke to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just now the way you handled her knowing everything I said I didn't handle her I just talked</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0517" trans="overlap">just having a normal conversation</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0518" trans="overlap">talked I said you know I like her I've always liked her I said she's done bonkers things but I kind of understand now why I said I didn't handle her I said that's not what people do you know I just talked to her</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no just talked to her be normal</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0518">anyway we walked</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he does sound like he's got a few issues</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0518" trans="overlap">they went she was driving they walked off to their car and went home and that was it that was the end of it and then he text me the following week and said you were brilliant in the play and erm let me know on Friday where you want to meet because I want you to see most receptive and comfortable to everything I've got to say</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1122" who="S0518">so I just messaged back and said oh erm I've got a meeting on Friday <unclear/></u>
<u n="1123" who="S0517" trans="overlap">was that last Friday cos we were yes we were gonna get together weren't we?</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so I said I've got a meeting on Friday and then I got this whole tirade of texts then saying well I hope you're going to change that meeting and whoever has the meeting on a Friday afternoon and whatever is discussed won't be remembered by Monday just ignored it then he came back and said what is this meeting anyway? just ignored it and then he came back and said are you moving this meeting? so then I text him and said I will not be moving this meeting somebody is coming especially from Birmingham to have this meeting and if all goes well it will be a really successful and important meeting to have and then he <trunc>te</trunc>text back and said this meeting sounds too good to be true to be work what exactly is it?</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0517"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1126" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and I just ignored it because I decided I</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so he hasn't learnt anything?</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0518">I was putting that tone of voice onto those texts because actually the text might have been like what you've arranged a meeting for a Friday afternoon?</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0518">cor I hope you can change this meeting <trunc>go</trunc> you know sounds as what is it? what is it what is it about do you have to have it on a Friday? cos</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0518" trans="overlap">you know and it could have been much more upbeat so I thought I'm not gonna respond because maybe I'm <trunc>r</trunc> putting a tone on it that isn't there so I just ignore it so I just ignored it all and then he text me on Friday and said I hope your meeting goes exactly how you wish it to today</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0517">oh the sarky sod</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0518">and I er I said to him well you know when I see you I'll tell you about it if you like <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know but anyway erm so I didn't meet him on Friday and then he asked about this Friday and I said I'm meeting <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's been arranged for a couple of weeks so I reckon he just thought he's sad his dad's dying he obviously had an awful weekend he said he spent most of it in hospital</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0517" trans="overlap">in hospital yeah</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0518">er he said it was really really bad <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't I don't think she gives him any affection or</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0517">well they were kissing at the football field</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0518">well I didn't see it</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0517" trans="overlap">that's just that was for your benefit I think</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0518" trans="overlap">never seen them kiss before ever</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0517">no that's why it stuck out with my and I thought</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0518">she told him off at a Christmas party because he</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I was gonna send you a message about it but my phone's a little bit public property so I didn't like to write it you know</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0517">in my house</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0517">so I didn't like to write anything down about it</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0518">but apparently last night he'd been to the hospital and he'd been to <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/> and then he come off on some to meet it was something about a cricket meeting or something</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I don't know I don't know about anyway he <trunc>kn</trunc> he knew we were at the <anon type="place"/> I was I I think I told them that</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0517">well mm</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0518" trans="overlap">when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> asked me I think I said oh</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0517">I I don't think he's really</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I can't remember I can't remember anyway but he turned up there but the hilarious bit was that obviously he's seen <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in Allo Allo then they came to see me in Hedda Gabler at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1155" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0518">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came that night and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> were waiting to see me after and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was waiting to see me after so I introduced them all and I said you will recognise <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> from Allo Allo</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0517" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0518">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said yes I know I know but he wouldn't recognise us cos we were in the audience so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like oh right you know like this sorry I'm standing here waiting to see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and not realising that you were as well and we're like you know</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0517">oh so that's where they'd met</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah so I introduced them</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so they had actually right</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0518">and then they came to see Jeeves and Wooster so I said erm you'll recognise who it is because it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know that you met at <anon type="place"/> and that and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like oh yes yes of course</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right right</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0518">so they feel cos people in the audience feel that they know you</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0517" trans="overlap">they know yes but the <trunc>au</trunc> yes but the cast members can't</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0517">no no of course not</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> met him last when did we do it?</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0517" trans="overlap">last July or <trunc>whate</trunc></u>
<u n="1170" who="S0518" trans="overlap">October no it was October</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay October</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0518" trans="overlap">guess the performance was so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was introduced to</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0518">last October at</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0517" trans="overlap">briefly</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0518"><anon type="place"/> hall</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0518">briefly and</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0517">yeah so of course</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0518" trans="overlap">he wouldn't <trunc>re</trunc></u>
<u n="1181" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he wouldn't remember</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0518">so a guy comes up to him</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0518">in the pub going oh hi <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> nice to see you again how's it gone? have you been auditioning tonight? and all of this <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s thinking well I don't want to say what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was thinking cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <unclear/></u>
<u n="1185" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1186" who="S0518">who is this guy that knows all about my life you know?</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and knows my name</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0517">yeah mm</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0518" trans="overlap">like this and then he's dancing round with me going</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1192" who="S0518">and I said I have to tell you later but to <trunc>i</trunc>in honesty <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> two or three weeks ago asked whether he could come to meet me at the pub after my drama rehearsal and I said no</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I said</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0517">I don't think he's got the message at all really <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1196" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I said no I said it would be really difficult I said I'll I organise this social event I'll be sitting around the table with my friends and then you turn up and that's gonna be so awkward</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0518">so awkward <pause dur="short"/> so especially seeing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> knows that he</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear>pushed me</unclear> against the car it's gonna be so awkward like and erm so I said I think it would be better if you just stayed away and I <trunc>s</trunc> and he said if you could just give me a little bit of time I said I couldn't I'd be there with my friends after my rehearsal</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0518">I couldn't give you any time</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0517">I'm not liking this</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I couldn't give you any time so</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0517">he's getting more and more needy</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0518">he's <trunc>st</trunc> I honest er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I told him I said to him <pause dur="short"/> he said why are you so frustrated with me? he said like you've everything I do is wrong and I said well first of all I don't do needy I cannot stand needy people or sick people and I said and you're constantly ill so</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and very needy at the minute</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0518">anyway he went mad about that when we had this chat at at <anon type="place"/> where did I tell you?</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0517"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1210" who="S0518"><anon type="place"/> a few weeks ago he said to me one thing I want to tell you that <trunc>m</trunc> he said it was really upset me how you've learned on other people and not on me and he said and it also really upset me that you said that I was needy because out of everybody I know I'm the most capable person I'm building a garden house in the I said I'm not talking about</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1212" who="S0518">how practical you are</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><trunc>c</trunc> no</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0518">and I said you</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0517" trans="overlap">needy</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0517" trans="overlap">as in demanding my time</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0517">all the time</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0518" trans="overlap">all the time all the time</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0517" trans="overlap">texts or in person no</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0518">I can't and I</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0517" trans="overlap">does he not know what needy means?</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0518">I said it's a real real</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0517">hello</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0518">turnoff to be honest and I said I don't do sick people either I said my boys get up in the night and vomit and play rugby the next morning I said I can't stand this</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0518">scarf round the neck I can't run because I've got a little bit of a sore throat</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1230" who="S0518">you know I said</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0517" trans="overlap">did you think that about me when I said I couldn't run last week cos I had a cold?</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no not really because I know how tough you are</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm not I don't really do sick people either</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0518">so I well I just said I told him all of that erm what was I gonna say? I so he wants us to meet reach some common ground but I don't I'm not I am not happy with</u>
<event desc="sound of phone"/>
<u n="1235" who="S0518">I am not happy for the common ground to involve my drama life because</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0518" trans="overlap">that's something that I do separately I'm happy for him to come and watch that's fine but I really don't want to</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0518" trans="overlap">all that and can I just check this in case this is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0517">you can what time is it? cos I'll need to go soon</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh no <trunc>s</trunc>sorry what time?</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no no oh no it's okay</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0518">what time is the?</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0517" trans="overlap">the football's not till no we're fine still</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0518">what time do you need do you want another cup of tea?</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0517">well they shut don't they? do you remember we were in here and they shut?</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0518">oh did they?</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0517">what time was that?</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0518">I don't know it's six minutes past four now cos I haven't given you a chance to say anything</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0517">no you haven't no I've pity the person that's gotta write this down it's just one long</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0518">but I haven't told you about</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0517" trans="overlap">monologue</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yet</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0517">no you haven't and I'm keen to <trunc>hea</trunc> what is this dog doing? you've got his ball <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're upsetting him</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0518">he brought it to me</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0517">there have it back want me to throw it for you? I don't want to touch it it's a bit skanky oh he wants you to play <pause dur="short"/> look oh that didn't go far <vocal desc="laugh"/> about a foot</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0518">he's I think he's blind <unclear/></u>
<u n="1258" who="S0517">looks like he's rubbed up against some paint look</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I know have I sent this? no send that's just <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1260" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I don't know if we've got time to hear the whole er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thing</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0518" trans="overlap">mm I'll just</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0517" trans="overlap">can I have a condensed version?</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0517">go on</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0518" trans="overlap">it's alright</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0517">no go on</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0518" trans="overlap">no I just talk too much</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0517">yeah you talk way too much</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0518" trans="overlap">erm on this Thursday this social night at the <anon type="place"/> that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> asked whether he'd come and I said no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has not been allowed to come to</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0517">by his wife?</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0518">yeah because he was <trunc>au</trunc> he wants to audition for the Shakespeare in the Park</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0518">but they were away at Center Parcs that weekend so he wasn't at the open meeting and he messaged me and said I won't be there will you be there? can you get listen out and get any information for me? so I said okay so after it I messaged back and said everything that you need is in the Shakespeare in the Park website so you can download all the audition pieces from there <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did say quite a lot of other stuff which do you want me to email to you I said cos I think it would be beneficial before you audition cos it's stuff that he wants people</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0518" trans="overlap">to bear in mind for their audition so he didn't respond and he didn't respond and he didn't respond that was like on the Sunday after the meeting and then suddenly on Thursday four days later I got a text to say sorry for the late response erm I'll have you organise the social for the pub tonight I'm going to try and get a pass out come down and get the information then so I said yeah it's on Facebook I put it on Facebook with we're going to the <anon type="place"/> probably there about ten o'clock after our rehearsal so I can't remember what time I it was during our rehearsal so my phone was on silent but then when we finished at ten I spotted this message from him to say I've got a pass to come out I've got to <trunc>ta</trunc> <trunc>pi</trunc> drop <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> home after her youth club so I'll be there about twenty past ten</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0518">well there were loads of people there and there were lots of Shakespeare people there so I thought he's not gonna need this information from me because he can speak to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1278" who="S0517" trans="overlap">anyone yeah</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0518">lots of people there so you know and there was a load of us around a table and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had come back from New Zealand and they came down and it was a really really <trunc>suc</trunc><trunc>suc</trunc>successful social night and I'd organised that and I was really happy about it then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> arrived and he went and sat like miles down there and he was chatting with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I thought he'll be getting all that Shakespeare stuff from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then I was er er offered to get a few drinks so <trunc>w</trunc> got up to go the bar and he'd sort of went oh hiya like this as I went by so I said hi like this and erm nice to see you so we greeted each other with a hug because that is normal because everybody knows that we're friends and it would be</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0518" trans="overlap">odd not to and then he said oh are you going to bar? so I said yeah said oh I'll come with you so he came up to the bar with me so I said do you want a drink? so he said oh oh alright then another pint of Peroni so I said oh I've got a few to get so he said oh I'll help you carry them back so I said you'll know all the Shakespeare stuff now cos you've he said well I want to hear it from your perspective cos I trust you so I just said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you've been chatting with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I said she told you all of the no no no tell me tell me so we're taking drinks back and forward and I was telling him but then our two drinks are last on the bar</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0518">so I was gonna take my drink and go back to my place thinking he would go back to his</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0518">but what we took our drinks and then he just paused at this other table this on sort of imagine everyone else is sitting there</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so he just paused here</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0517" trans="overlap">there</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0518">and put his drink down and just carried on the conversation so we just carried on talking and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came up and chatted and then other people</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0518">came and chatted and it was just actually really nice we just talked about loads of different stuff introduced him to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> asked how the rehearsal had gone and all this kind of stuff so it was really</u>
<event desc="sound of phone"/>
<u n="1292" who="S0518">it was really nice and then erm I just thought this is normal this is lovely this is just</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0518">good</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0517">how it should be</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0518">yeah anyway but then it was only a a few people who went oh we're going now and they sort of went and I said oh gosh look at the time we should go and I said and also you've been given a pass out you don't want to abuse that so he said no no you're right I need the loo though don't go without me so he went off to the loo and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said I need to go so do you mind if I just go? so I'll get off so he was going to Dubai the next day so he went</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1298" who="S0518">so that just left me waiting for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he then came back and then put his bottom onto the table and just said oh I haven't told you about my latest project so he had to tell me about this latest thing that he's doing which sounds amazing and I was listening to it and said look we're the last people in this pub and it's got later and we're still talking we need to go you're right so we walked out to the cars so I said it's been really nice to see you and good luck with the Shakespeare audition and da-da-da he says yeah good luck with and hope you get to direct it next year cos I was waiting to hear at that point</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0518">so I said yeah I said that could be awkward though cos if I direct it you are gonna struggle to be in it and you always do it I'm very sorry about that he said a year is a long way away a year is a long way away we don't know what's gonna be happening in a year okay yeah he said don't you worry about it don't want you to be worrying about it okay good luck with the audition anyway I give him a hug goodbye and erm and then er he said I could have been happy with you you know</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh did he? oh</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0518">I said I know</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0517">well yeah could have been happy with you too</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0518">and he said I really miss you he said I miss the person that I am and he said when I was friends with you he said I felt good about the person that I was and he said and I don't now he said</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0517">ah</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0518" trans="overlap">because I feel inadequate <trunc>n</trunc>not living up to anyone's expectations always doing everything wrong grumpy not a good person and he said and when I was</u>
<event desc="sound of phone"/>
<u n="1307" who="S0518">with you he said</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0517">was that you then again?</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0518">maybe</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0518">I think erm I just think I've got a group message going on on the app</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh I see okay</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0518">so it's other people chiming into it so he he just said all of this and <pause dur="short"/> and he said I know you think because I don't contact you and I'm quite guarded you think that I don't care any more and he said please don't misunderstand me he said I do and he said erm I do still care and he said erm I think you're brilliant he said I can talk to you like I like I can't talk to anybody else and he said we get on really really well and he said and I miss the way you make me feel about myself and I said to him I said yeah but that's the thing though isn't it? I said you miss me because I made you feel better about yourself and I was like going like this with my hands and he like got hold of my hand and he said isn't that the nicest compliment?</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0518">he said</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0518" trans="overlap">isn't that the nicest compliment? you made me feel like I was a worthwhile person but my point is that I'm always there to support him whenever he's having a erm a</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0518">something's upset him he he'll always get in contact with me for a kind word for a shoulder to cry on</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0518"><unclear>then I go</unclear> I'm dumping on you it's not fair I'm sorry you're the last person I should dump on but <pause dur="short"/> if ever I need any support</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0517">he just doesn't <trunc>resp</trunc></u>
<u n="1323" who="S0518" trans="overlap">he's like</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0517">he doesn't reply</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I can't I can't I can't go down that route I can't</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0518">it's too dangerous if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> ever <trunc>fou</trunc> oh I can't I can't</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0517">so it's a bit one-sided it</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah and so I was just thinking the only reason that he misses me is because I made him feel better about himself so I was probably a little bit</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0518" trans="overlap">sarcastic I dunno if that's the right word when I said to him well we yeah yeah and that's the only reason because you'll never you'll never say to me I miss you because I miss something</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0517" trans="overlap">like this about you</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0518">yes</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0517" trans="overlap">or that about you yes</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I miss your smile I miss your laughter I miss your conversation or whatever it's just I miss you because you made me feel</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0517" trans="overlap">make me feel good</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0518" trans="overlap">better</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0518">and he said no no you're misinterpreting me you are you're misinterpreting me and he said you know I think about you</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0518">all the time and he said <pause dur="short"/> I think I think that we could be happy I do and he said I'm not I'm just not happy now but he said</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0517">oh but he's still they're still together?</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0518">yeah but they're not he said they're existing he said we are just coexisting and then he said shall I let you into a secret? so I said okay and then he said <trunc>sin</trunc>since July since last July when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> challenged me whether I whether I've been talking to you and everything he said he said we've had no he said she and I have had no relationship with each other</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0518">whatsoever not he said <unclear>nothing</unclear></u>
<u n="1350" who="S0517" trans="overlap">nothing</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0518">nothing not not even anything he goes to work yeah fine see you later you know he said we just exist he said we're a brilliant team and we're sticking together for the children</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you'd be surprised though how many people are like that I think</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0518">well I've been</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you sort of you hear <trunc>snip</trunc> I</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0518">it's obviously coming to my attention more and more <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0517">clearly</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0518" trans="overlap">this that this is what they are but that wouldn't be the life for me and that is not the life for him that is not what he wants and obviously he knows that I that I would love him but I thing is I think he's a brilliant person and he never gets told that he never gets told that he's clever or that he's done something good or er ever</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0518">his kids just take all the holidays that are going and expect loads of stuff and you know oh I don't know anyway anyway but there's nothing that can be done about it and</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0517">do you still think that though? do you still think that you're not gonna do anything?</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0518">all I all I feel is now that it makes me really really sad because this time last year and it was wrong because we were talking to each other about things that we shouldn't have been talking about</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no yeah I know I know but it's</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and it was completely wrong but I was not happy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wasn't not pulling his finger out the house was in a complete state and it you know</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0517" trans="overlap">has that got better?</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0518">a little bit but you asked me the other day about the floor</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0517">I did and I didn't</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0518" trans="overlap">it's not</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0517">and I didn't like to press that cos I thought oh has things slipped back to</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0518">well</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0517" trans="overlap">unless you do it it's not gonna happen?</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0518">yeah but it's because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is in in the middle of marking his final set of TMAs</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0518">and he spent Saturday Sunday and bank holiday Monday marking</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0517" trans="overlap">marking</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0518">and before the floor can go down we need to move furniture out of the kitchen the washing machine and tumble dryer need to be</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0517">mad</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0518" trans="overlap">dissembled and it I can't do that</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0518">on my own</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0517">so he hasn't got <trunc>ti</trunc> well why don't you ask?</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0517">I'll send <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> round he'll do it</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0518">let <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> see our house</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0517">don't be silly</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0518">er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1386" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he'll do it but I mean if that's what you're</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0518" trans="overlap">how can I ask somebody else to come when I've got a perfectly good husband? so he will do it but we have to</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but you've got to wait</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0518" trans="overlap">wait we have to just wait</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so is the floor chosen? it's <trunc>or</trunc></u>
<u n="1391" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0517">on order?</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0518">it's all chosen</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0517" trans="overlap">they're just waiting for you to give them a date?</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0518">I've got a price erm they</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0517" trans="overlap">how long can it take to dismantle the washing machine and the <trunc>tumb</trunc>?</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well the the because of other stuff we've got various furniture which is <unclear>hurled</unclear> in the dining part of the kitchen so we need to put</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0517">oh okay so it's a bit of a</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0518" trans="overlap">our awning thing out our what do you call it? gazebo in the garden and we need to put everything underneath</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0517" trans="overlap">put it out there</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0518">in case it rains</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0518">so it's sheltered</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0518">and we need to know when we are clear to do that so we can book</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0517" trans="overlap">can book the floor</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0518" trans="overlap">the floor people to come</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah that all makes sense</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0518" trans="overlap">then so it's this</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0518">so at the moment I I we've I've got some offcuts of carpets down that when they did the stairs there was a big offcut</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0518">so the hall is actually carpeted</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so <trunc>ha</trunc>has he finished his marking?</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0518">no he's in the middle of it now</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0517">oh still doing it?</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0518">but this is the final</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0517">right so at the end of this</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0518" trans="overlap">batch</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0517">he should be able</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0518">so when all this twenty is done</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0518" trans="overlap">he'll be free more freed up</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0517">okay</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0518">so that's just an aside so in my mind in my with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in my not in the mind in my feeling I've come to feel that everything happens for a reason and things will come right in the end and I feel and I said this when we were in the carpark talking and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I I feel that I feel that stuff like this doesn't just happen and er it's happened for a reason and it will all come right in the end</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and we'll look back in a year's time and you and</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0517">and see where all this fitted into</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will have sort she you will have sorted yourselves out</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0518">or you will have <trunc>m</trunc><trunc>m</trunc> gone your separate ways and you will have found love with somebody else and know and</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0518">that part of your life is <trunc>f</trunc> or we'll be together and we'll be together because something else has happened if it's been the right thing</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm mm mm yeah</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0518">and he was like I can't believe that I can't think that like that I think that we've had the end to our story and and that's it</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0517">oh did he?</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0518">erm but then but then he said he'll say but I know that we can be happy together and I miss you and all of this so anyway I went home</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no wonder you didn't sleep that night</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0518">I didn't</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0517">all that going round your head</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0518" trans="overlap">well no that was just no that was this</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no wonder</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0518">no this yeah this was seven weeks ago</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0518">something else since then so but it made me happy because er all I wanted to know was that cos I honestly felt that he hated me and that he felt that I'd ruined his life and that he felt that that like oh my god what on earth was I doing? she was nobody why was I even bothered about her? but actually cos it's so important to me and so against what I would normally do that I wanted to feel that</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0517">that it had some</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0518" trans="overlap">at least it had mattered to him</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0517">yes yeah and now you do realise that</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0518">yeah</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0517">yes so that's good</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0518" trans="overlap">so I actually felt better because of that</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0518">and I was in a better place of understanding <pause dur="short"/> and then but then the next day I went to London with the children and then he text me and he'd offered me jokingly offered me this job but</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0517">oh yes yes</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0518" trans="overlap">but and obviously he said</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0518" trans="overlap">you're perfectly qualified for it but I can't give it to you I said I <vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0517" trans="overlap">don't want it</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0518">I know but he said I'm in the pub it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s leaving do <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says good riddance but I'm more diplomatic flowers and chocolates da-da-da</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0518">then the next I've just <trunc>deli</trunc> taken delivery of my seventh pint and I know</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1465" who="S0518">when he's had beer</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0518" trans="overlap">he gets all and I just thought oh god anyway it didn't come it didn't come I think he'd had enough and went home and went to sleep</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0517">oh thank goodness</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0518">they never came</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0517" trans="overlap">cos otherwise it could be yeah</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0518">nothing came but this week last week last the Thursday was his fiftieth birthday and I'd wanted to just meet him for a drink or a cup of tea or something</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0518">got a present for him and erm yeah from us and I wanted to give it to him and he was he was really I can't see you I can't do that no no no no no and really really pushed me away so from I could be really happy with you it was like suddenly I don't want anything to do with you and it really hurt me</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0518">it really hurt me and I wished him a happy birthday and he <trunc>s</trunc> all he said was thank you that was it and but then he posted all these pictures of his brilliant cake <pause dur="short"/> my brilliant cake thank you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> all over Facebook and stuff and loads of people commented on it and all of that you know and erm it was horrible it's really hard and then at May holiday they go away to it's like a Center Parcs thing but it isn't</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0518">with these people in the New Forest Forest of Dean or somewhere and I knew he'd gone there and posted pictures on Facebook and on like a family walk and stuff like this and it hurt</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0518">it really hurt so last week I felt really low and on Tuesday had a committee meeting and they had a Shakespeare in the Park read-through and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> texted me and said oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I have gone to the pub why don't you after your committee meeting come and join us we've gone to the <anon type="place"/>? so I went and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was there</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0517">oh god</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0518">and it was fine and we're just all</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0518" trans="overlap">chatting absolutely fine but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said I'm gonna go home before you cos we've left our boys long enough now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so he went off home a bit earlier than I did and <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I finished our drinks we walked to the carpark <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said goodbye and went off in his car so that left us two talking but I didn't really want to talk cos I felt really <pause dur="short"/> upset with him</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0517">look everybody's going home yeah</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0518">what time have you got to go?</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0517">well er I'm alright for another five or ten <trunc>minu</trunc> er five</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh well</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0517">five minutes really yeah but I'm just wondering why they didn't come and clear the tray away <pause dur="short"/> and now they've closed up and gone home anyway go on so yeah</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0518">so really <unclear>it's really boring</unclear> erm</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1491" who="S0518">so I didn't really want I just felt low I didn't feel like chatting at all</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0518">and I'd got I got this bag and I was just like I was standing there like this</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0518">not looking at him just holding my bag like this and er and he just said <pause dur="short"/> this feels a bit awkward doesn't it coming to this pub? because that was where we used to go for a drink after our rehearsal</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0518">and I said I know and he said I didn't know you were coming until you came and I said <pause dur="short"/> was it awful? and he went no it wasn't it was really nice but he said it's just <pause dur="short"/> this time last year we were in the middle of our rehearsals and Shakespeare's kicking off again and he said for me this is a first foray back into <anon type="place"/> and he said to me <anon type="place"/> is you so he said coming back to Shakespeare in the Park coming back to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1498" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0518">and coming back to this pub</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it's bringing it all back</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0518">it's you and he said I know I know that I know that you he said I know that you hate me I said I don't hate you how could you ever say that I'd hate you I don't hate you and I said I'm just feel really sad this week I said it was your birthday and I said he said I know I stomped on all your dreams I said yeah you big stomper and he said</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1503" who="S0518">I feel really guilty but he said I'm really sorry and he said I'm just a constant source of disappointment to you I said you're not and I said I understand the situation fully understand the situation I said but memories are memories and I said I haven't purposefully thought of this but I said you know you do think when it was your forty-ninth birthday we went for a drink at the <anon type="place"/> and you told me that you cherished our brief time together and you would love me forever and I said and now a year on you're not even speaking to me so</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0518">so it's difficult I said I can't help feeling low I said I completely understand the decisions that we've made and I'm completely in favour of them but I said I am an emotional person and I can't help feeling a little bit low</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0518">and he said oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and he just gave me this big hug and I've still got my arms like this</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1509" who="S0518">and then he let go and he said you've not hugged me back so I said I'm sorry so I <trunc>hu</trunc> I hugged him back and erm and I can't remember then how the conversation went I just hugged him back and said we need to go and he said yeah we do but erm he said what I said before he said everything was from the heart he said I spoke from my heart and I absolutely mean everything he said if I could design my perfect girl he said it would absolutely be you apart from the fact you're married but he said</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1511" who="S0518">it would absolutely be you and nothing about that changes but he said it's really unfair of me to keep in touch with you or contacting you or you know</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well and he's got a point there because it just makes it harder and harder doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0517">if you don't but I dunno mm</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and he said I wanted to share my birthday with you but he said how can I wrap all of that up in a nicety? I really want to share my birthday with you however I'm not going to</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0517" trans="overlap">going to</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0518">he said that's really hurtful to you and he said and I know you're hurt already and he said I meant what I said the other night he said I really really miss you and he said I'm gonna see lots of you now because I'm rehearsing Shakespeare</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0518">and you're rehearsing Cheshire Cats and the two groups will meet for a drink on a Thursday</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0518">and he said so we'll see each other and we'll be fine</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0517">see if you can just be</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0518" trans="overlap">we'll be fine and erm so</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0517" trans="overlap">do you think that's gonna be too hard for you though?</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0518">no it'll be okay so I said let's go so I said you need to go so we had another hug and he said to be honest he said it's just really nice to hug somebody he said it's just really</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0517" trans="overlap">gosh there's a lot of men in your life that don't get any love and affection</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0517">isn't there?</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0518" trans="overlap">it's surprising it's really nice just to hug somebody and erm and then he gave me a kiss not a snog gave me a kiss</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1531" who="S0518">goodbye and I went home and I was just that just couldn't sleep then</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh I bet</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0518">I couldn't sleep and I just I sent him a big long message which I knew he wouldn't look at for days and days and days but then last night he looked at it like the night a couple of nights ago but really late like at half past midnight didn't respond</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0518">and then last night he messaged me and said I hope your <trunc>h</trunc> I hope your auditions go well I hope you've managed to cast Cheshire Cat I'm gonna speak to you later I'm just in the pub with a mate that's at ten o'clock by the time then he started messaging me he was walking home he'd had a few pints of beer</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0518">and he was like I'm feeling sorry he said I'm an empty vessel</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1539" who="S0518">I've</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0517">oh you don't wanna</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0518" trans="overlap">am lonely</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0517">take it too seriously when they're drunk</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I want</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0517">but you know</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I want to be loved</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0518">and you've got this love to give and I can't have it and all of this and I'm really sorry and da-di-da-di-da-di-da-di-da-da-da and he just poured it all out so</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0517" trans="overlap">do you think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> appreciates how many people you've got after you?</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0518">no</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0517">just there to snap you up if you were to ever I am gonna have to go in a minute <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0518" trans="overlap">you must</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0517">do you think he?</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you haven't said a single word</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0517">no I know</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0518" trans="overlap">I'm so sorry</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0517">but do you think he doesn't appreciate it you don't think?</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said when we had our chat in the summer he said to me don't you think I don't know that people are lining up to take you off my hands said don't you think I don't know that? he said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would run off with you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would go off with you so <trunc>th</trunc> you know he said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wanted you years ago he said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> next door you know</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1559" who="S0518"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so he said I know all of that and he <trunc>sai</trunc> and it I think I told you he said to me he said I've become complacent and</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0517">well yes but has he not really upped his game?</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0518">well we did some stuff to the house didn't we?</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0518">but there's other stuff <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that we haven't done that I wanted to do to do with wills and things like that that to me you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was talking to me shall we walk back to the car?</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0517">yes yeah</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0518"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was talking to me the other night and he said I've been doing a lot of studying about <trunc>Mas</trunc>Maslow's theory and I said oh I know that</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0517">oh and me</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0518">and he said I've got my basics I've got my house I've got my shelter I've got the <unclear>feelings</unclear></u>
<u n="1568" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0518" trans="overlap">yeah he said level two emotion</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0517" trans="overlap">emotion yeah</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0518">he said I have zero he said the the only place I've got that is with you and he said and that's that's you know it it's it's not where we should get it from is it?</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0517">no</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0518">that's the thing he said I've got <trunc>n</trunc>none of that he said I'm missing a massive fundamental level</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0517" trans="overlap">a massive layer of Maslow <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1575" who="S0518" trans="overlap">inside I've got a nice car I've got a great house people will say to me god got</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you've got everything</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0518" trans="overlap"><unclear>three lovely children</unclear></u>
<u n="1578" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0518">and I said to him I've had this conversation with my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I said because she's talked to me about her mum you know and</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0518">feeling like I've got everything why do I feel lonely? because you want <unclear>got my dad</unclear> and this is you know I've got whatever a perfectly lovely life and yet I said there's something missing</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0517" trans="overlap">missing yeah</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0518">that I got from you but you know it's erm I dunno</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0517">well I was talking about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but anyway</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0518" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0518">so erm I can't remember what I was gonna say about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1588" who="S0517">you were trying to do wills and stuff but he wasn't doing the</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0518">oh no fundamental things</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0517" trans="overlap">tal <trunc>pract</trunc> yes</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0518">and Maslow's theory</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0518">to to feel safe to feel secure to feel that you can achieve all these other things you need to have the foundations</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0517" trans="overlap">foundations</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0518">and I feel if you're in a lifelong commitment with somebody and you've got children things like wills and a a proper non-damp roof over your head are important</u>
<u n="1596" who="S0517" trans="overlap">are important have you</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and if</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0517">not got wills you two?</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0518">well we've well we've got them but they're wrong and I want to they need to be</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0518">put right because if anything happens to us</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0518">things aren't gonna go in the right place</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0517">oh my yeah you do need to get onto that</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0518" trans="overlap">and that to me</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0517">is is important</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0518" trans="overlap">is our children's future</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it is to me yes</u>
<u n="1609" who="S0518">my future if anything happens to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> his future if anything happens to me</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0517" trans="overlap">that is important <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1611" who="S0518">and that's the stuff he doesn't help me with he's a really good man and I love him completely to pieces and he's absolute just</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0517">but</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0518">but that that to me it says to me you don't really love me if you're not prepared to do that</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0517" trans="overlap">to do that</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0518">if you asked him that he'd be devastated absolutely devastated</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well yeah</u>
<u n="1617" who="S0518">because he's just laid back</u>
<u n="1618" who="S0517">I know</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0518">he's just laid back</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but that's just annoying isn't it? I'd best stop this <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> now yeah</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0518" trans="overlap">okay</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
