<text id="SNQB">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:24:11</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-12-11</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0320 S0442</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's home, Totnes, Devon</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Christmas, Family life, work and conferences</topics>
		<activity>discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</activity>
		<conv_type></conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0320">
				<exactage>34</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Torquay</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Totnes</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>TEFL teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- advanced; French -- intermediate; German -- beginner</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0442">
				<exactage>35</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Paignton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South West</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Paignton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>EFL Senior teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Italian -- level unspecified; Spanish -- level unspecified; French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0320">so how what were the kids in the play?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0442">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was a lady</u>
<u n="3" who="S0320">a lady?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0442">yes</u>
<u n="5" who="S0320">that's very specific a lady</u>
<u n="6" who="S0442">she had to come she was a lady there was a hundred and twenty kids</u>
<u n="7" who="S0320" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0442">in this</u>
<u n="9" who="S0320">in one play?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0442">in one play</u>
<u n="11" who="S0320">oh my god</u>
<u n="12" who="S0442">there were three year groups did a performance of Robin Hood</u>
<u n="13" who="S0320">oh</u>
<u n="14" who="S0442">and erm</u>
<u n="15" who="S0320">well that's not very nativity that's quite nice</u>
<u n="16" who="S0442">yeah but not very nativity</u>
<u n="17" who="S0320"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no it's good</u>
<u n="18" who="S0442">and erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was in the first scene and she was one of the rich ladies</u>
<u n="19" who="S0320" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="20" who="S0442">that Robin Hood stole from</u>
<u n="21" who="S0320">okay</u>
<u n="22" who="S0442">and she was really good</u>
<u n="23" who="S0320">ah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0442">yeah really good</u>
<u n="25" who="S0320">did she have some lines?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0442">yes she did and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was a dancer</u>
<u n="27" who="S0320">oh wow</u>
<u n="28" who="S0442">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0320">oh was she?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0442">yes</u>
<u n="31" who="S0320">oh bless her</u>
<u n="32" who="S0442">they gave <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that part because because she's been struggling at school and they wanted to boost her confidence so</u>
<u n="33" who="S0320" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0442">that's why they gave her a part</u>
<u n="35" who="S0320">wow brilliant</u>
<u n="36" who="S0442">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0320">ah and what about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0442"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has got his carol service tonight</u>
<u n="39" who="S0320">oh okay oh god it's all go isn't it</u>
<u n="40" who="S0442">three nights the performance was three nights</u>
<u n="41" who="S0320">really?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0442">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0320">oh bless them they must be shattered</u>
<u n="44" who="S0442">they are really tired</u>
<u n="45" who="S0320">ah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0442">they are so tired</u>
<u n="47" who="S0320">yeah I bet</u>
<u n="48" who="S0442">I'm dropping them off at five o'clock every night and then picking them up at half past seven</u>
<u n="49" who="S0320" trans="overlap">oh bless</u>
<u n="50" who="S0442">and then <pause dur="short"/> so we went on the last night</u>
<u n="51" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0442">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0320">brilliant</u>
<u n="54" who="S0442">it was really good it was the best one I've seen at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0320">yeah mm I like the Robin Hood choice</u>
<u n="56" who="S0442">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0320">I like that it's not Christmassy at all <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0442">it was really good</u>
<u n="59" who="S0320">oh bless</u>
<u n="60" who="S0442">and they're only six years old</u>
<u n="61" who="S0320">yeah ah one of the play groups <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> goes to one of the church ones they were er yes this week they were handing out nativity costumes so they could go to a nativity play theme thing and the church on Sunday I was like I can't <trunc>ju</trunc> mm <pause dur="short"/> luckily I was like well I've got a friend who is arriving at ten thirty so I'm not going to be able to go to the church but I was like what I can't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can't be anything he'll just run off</u>
<u n="62" who="S0442">do you know what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did when he was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s age?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0320">no</u>
<u n="64" who="S0442">he used to go to playgroup in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0442">and he was meant to be sat at the front singing</u>
<u n="67" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0442">and there was Mary and Joseph with their baby in the manger on the stage</u>
<u n="69" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0442">and he ran up to the stage took baby Jesus out of the manger and started shaking it</u>
<u n="71" who="S0320">brilliant</u>
<u n="72" who="S0442"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0320">I just there's just no way that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got the attention span to do any of that I'm surprised when he does do things you know like all the other kids do but I was just like do you know what I'm going to wait <vocal desc="laugh"/> to put him in anything nativity until he absolutely has to because it will just be</u>
<u n="74" who="S0442" trans="overlap">it is funny</u>
<u n="75" who="S0320">a bit much I think</u>
<u n="76" who="S0442">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0320">and they will they've got Santa I <trunc>sh</trunc> I should imagine it's the same Santa going to the two different groups next week on Monday and Tuesday so if I go to the Monday one then he'll get to meet Santa twice and scream and cry like they all do I believe <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0442">good <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> lost her <trunc>fir</trunc> first tooth</u>
<u n="79" who="S0320">oh my god</u>
<u n="80" who="S0442">two days ago so the tooth fairy came and left her a note and it was all really good and then this morning she found the tooth</u>
<u n="81" who="S0320">oh where was it?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0442">on my dressing table</u>
<u n="83" who="S0320">oh no how did you explain that one?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0442">I went that's not your tooth <vocal desc="laugh"/> and threw it across the room</u>
<u n="85" who="S0320">did you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0442">I didn't know what to do <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0320">what do you what do other people do with the what do parents do with the teeth? I've never thought this</u>
<u n="88" who="S0442">I don't know I I've kept <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s I put them somewhere</u>
<u n="89" who="S0320">that's going to be that's going to be a nice thing to find isn't it oh what's this oh teeth <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0442">she's like mummy this is my tooth? because she thinks it's on because she got a note from the tooth fairy</u>
<u n="91" who="S0320" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="92" who="S0442">saying your tooth is lovely I'm going to put that on my mantelpiece</u>
<u n="93" who="S0320">okay and so your dressing table</u>
<u n="94" who="S0442">so she was going yesterday my tooth is on the mantelpiece</u>
<u n="95" who="S0320"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="96" who="S0442">with the tooth fairy</u>
<u n="97" who="S0320">do you do they get money still?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0442">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0320">and what's the going rate for teeth these days?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0442">a pound</u>
<u n="101" who="S0320">well that's not bad</u>
<u n="102" who="S0442">some kids get five pounds</u>
<u n="103" who="S0320" trans="overlap">that's quite a lot though</u>
<u n="104" who="S0442">some get ten pounds mine get a pound</u>
<u n="105" who="S0320">how many teeth have you got? that's a good question isn't it how many teeth do we have? twenty something? or is that the alphabet? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0442">it's twenty-two isn't it? and then</u>
<u n="107" who="S0320" trans="overlap">twenty-two?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0442">grown up teeth is</u>
<u n="109" who="S0320">so twenty-two twenty-two pounds for a whole mouth that's not bad</u>
<u n="110" who="S0442">when you've got three kids</u>
<u n="111" who="S0320"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0442">it's like <vocal desc="laugh"/> six children <unclear/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0320">it's not bad though throughout the course of a lifetime</u>
<u n="114" who="S0442">no</u>
<u n="115" who="S0320">yeah a pound I <trunc>thi</trunc> yeah that seems good to me five pounds for one tooth that's ridiculous do you think they then go out and spend it on sweets so that they could lose all the rest of them?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0442"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants to buy me a Christmas present with it</u>
<u n="117" who="S0320">mm <unclear/> mm ah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0442">bless her</u>
<u n="119" who="S0320">take her to the ninety-nine P shop</u>
<u n="120" who="S0442">I said no and then she said oh can I buy ice creams?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0320">yeah that's more that's more like it isn't it <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh bless her <pause dur="short"/> oh dear so how was work last week?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0442">alright</u>
<u n="123" who="S0320">quiet?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0442">very quiet</u>
<u n="125" who="S0320">I met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0442">yes how was that?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0320">yeah it was alright I was sat next to her I didn't recognise who she was the best thing about the the conference was really good this year by the way</u>
<u n="128" who="S0442">was it?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0320">one of the best things about it massive name tags so you didn't have to like squint and peer at people's like chest to work out who they were</u>
<u n="130" who="S0442">did she know who you were then when you said?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0320">when I said I'm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she said oh do you know what she said? she said do you know what I've heard so much about you I thought I would recognise you instantly <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0442">bless her <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0320">but yeah we're in a really interesting talk actually a CLIL which was really good erm by the same guy that did the erm FCE talk but he was a lot better and he was talking about his own thing erm <pause dur="short"/> and yeah yeah we just had a chat and she said why haven't you worked at <anon type="place"/>? it was a bit weird for me at the conference cos Kaplan were there <unclear></unclear> <unclear>support for English</unclear> were there <anon type="place"/> were there <anon type="place"/> were all there and I was like oh like and also some people Kaplan from Kaplan in Salisbury were there as well so I got to scope out the guy who I'm probably going to have to have some contact with this summer which was quite good because they're always notoriously difficult</u>
<u n="134" who="S0442">mm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0320">and the principal who I've met on various occasions had lots of conversations with either didn't recognise me or didn't want to talk to me which was fine because he's not <unclear>so weird</unclear> but yeah it was a bit odd <vocal desc="laugh"/> especially like so who do you work for then? I was like last year I worked for <anon type="place"/> and they're probably going to expect me to work there next year and secretly I'm going to go and work for <anon type="place"/> but really I'd like to go and work for <anon type="place"/> so you know <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's all just a bit it was it was really good but it was a bit weird</u>
<u n="136" who="S0442">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0320">erm yes so I talked to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she said why haven't you worked at <anon type="place"/>? and I just said well I don't know which I don't know why I haven't then I'd worked everywhere else so yeah yeah that was it really but yeah it was nice and she was talking about she is going back into the classroom</u>
<u n="138" who="S0442">is that what she said?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0320">teaching students yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0442">is she?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0320">that's what she said and she described it as a demotion</u>
<u n="142" who="S0442">she <pause dur="short"/> yeah she's all over the place</u>
<u n="143" who="S0320" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0442">at the moment</u>
<u n="145" who="S0320">I also saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the other Sunday at this Christmas fair and she was like yes I'm going to managing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? and I sat there thinking that place next year until everyone finds their feet sounds like an absolute nightmare yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0442">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s new role is a bit of everyone's role</u>
<u n="147" who="S0320">yeah that's yeah that's what she said</u>
<u n="148" who="S0442">yeah and a lot of people weren't happy about it but</u>
<u n="149" who="S0320">so a bit of everyone's? who's then?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0442">a bit of everyone a bit of mine a bit of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a bit of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a bit of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0320">okay</u>
<u n="152" who="S0442">they just created this role for her and</u>
<u n="153" who="S0320">yeah and how are you about it? you've worked with her quite a lot this year though haven't you? you alright with it?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0442">we get on yeah well we get on really well</u>
<u n="155" who="S0320">yeah so you're fine with a bit of because you've worked together this year so you know what it's like working with her with you in your position and her <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> not happy then?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0442">no</u>
<u n="157" who="S0320">why not?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0442">she feels victimised at the moment</u>
<u n="159" who="S0320">oh</u>
<u n="160" who="S0442">she feels like</u>
<u n="161" who="S0320" trans="overlap">everything to do with work? or not everything to do with work? <pause dur="short"/> but she had to go off and do that <unclear/> job didn't she?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0442">yeah she feels that they're trying to make her quit her job</u>
<u n="163" who="S0320">okay</u>
<u n="164" who="S0442">that they're pushing her out they're trying to <pause dur="short"/> so <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0320">do you think they are?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0442">I don't know they're not making her feel very comfortable or welcome</u>
<u n="167" who="S0320">but there's so few people that could do <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s job well</u>
<u n="168" who="S0442">but no one understands her job</u>
<u n="169" who="S0320" trans="overlap">I totally understand it</u>
<u n="170" who="S0442">that's the problem</u>
<u n="171" who="S0320">yeah you have to be yeah I would say I haven't met them all <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s the only one who can do it because you have to <trunc>trav</trunc> partly because you have to travel so much they'd be silly to try and push her out because other people aren't going to be able to do it you wouldn't be able to travel so much <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wouldn't be able to travel <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> probably could do it but probably wouldn't want to</u>
<u n="172" who="S0442">mm mm I know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is doing three out of the seven summer schools and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is doing the others</u>
<u n="173" who="S0320">well that's quite enough for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> though on the on the other hand like how is she gonna do seven summer schools? that's far too many just for her</u>
<u n="174" who="S0442">mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0320">I bet she doesn't like that?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0442">no I don't think that's a problem erm <pause dur="short"/> I don't really know what the problem is</u>
<u n="177" who="S0320">mm well but yes no it was nice to meet her but yeah the conference was really good out of all the years to miss you really shouldn't have missed this one it was really good it was actually genuinely good not just good for a southwest conference</u>
<u n="178" who="S0442">okay</u>
<u n="179" who="S0320">and most and lots of people who I spoke to said <trunc>the</trunc> talks were their talks were really good</u>
<u n="180" who="S0442">mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0320">it's really interesting so they had the new chair or chief exec whoever he is of English UK who was kind of blah blah blah blah blah blah you know like they are erm until this really pompous guy asked the most stupidest question which was really long-winded and clearly designed to test this guy's knowledge and trip him up so he said well you said this but obviously according to so and so's research from 1985 blah blah blah oh it was awful and the guy the guy that was doing the plenary very politely very thoroughly completely slammed him it was brilliant <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was really good</u>
<u n="182" who="S0442">oh good</u>
<u n="183" who="S0320">erm so he was really interesting and then</u>
<u n="184" who="S0442">wasn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> there?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0320"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was there in the afternoon he was wasn't saying particularly groundbreaking but as always had a slightly different slant on things it was he was talking about <unclear>automaticity</unclear> erm that he'd read some book and therefore was talking about it in the terms of the book that he'd read but yeah and how we learn and stuff but yeah he was interesting it was at the end of the day though so it's a bit much</u>
<u n="186" who="S0442">bit brain-dead</u>
<u n="187" who="S0320">yeah erm and I went to a talk on about teaching advanced learners which was really interesting</u>
<u n="188" who="S0442">oh yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0320">with a guy who's a doctor <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> I think he's written quite a lot of course books</u>
<u n="190" who="S0442">his wife died last year and that's why he didn't go</u>
<u n="191" who="S0320">oh</u>
<u n="192" who="S0442">that's why the one the other one got cancelled last year erm how to make the best out of your team</u>
<u n="193" who="S0320">he did that this year</u>
<u n="194" who="S0442">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0320">oh I didn't realise he was supposed to go last year oh god well he did both of those this year how to make the best of your team I talked to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about that it sounded interesting however he was coming at it from the point of view of working in a university</u>
<u n="196" who="S0442">oh</u>
<u n="197" who="S0320">where you have minimum the minimum length of course is what four weeks? erm so it's quite different for having a permanent team of teachers as opposed to having a very fluid team of teachers</u>
<u n="198" who="S0442">yes</u>
<u n="199" who="S0320">it's interesting though they'd erm I think I might do try and implement a couple of <unclear>members</unclear> at the summer school actually one of things they do is to have certain things that you have each lesson so erm every teacher puts a list of ten vocabulary words on the board and they all put them in the same place so either on the right-hand side or the left-hand side each lesson has three aims erm at the beginning of the lesson you write at the top of the board and they'd also introduce things like colour uniformity so you use colour for the same things so</u>
<u n="200" who="S0442">that's what we tried to do for the inspection week</u>
<u n="201" who="S0320">oh just for the inspection week?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0442">well</u>
<u n="203" who="S0320"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0442">the inspectors were there well it's something that came up leading to because we did so many workshops leading to this</u>
<u n="205" who="S0320">yes yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0442">and one of the things was to standardise the way we do we mark <pause dur="short"/> stress for example</u>
<u n="207" who="S0320">yes yeah exactly</u>
<u n="208" who="S0442">because if you have a teacher then you go and get another teacher and the other teacher does it a different way it's just</u>
<u n="209" who="S0320">well yeah I thought erm it sounded it sounded interesting erm and one of the benefits I think was when the students come and say well I don't like my teacher I don't feel like I'm learning enough if there's a clash of personalities he can go well actually I know that all the teachers do this in their class so the kind of the director of studies has a clear idea of what's actually going on and can talk to the students go well I know what's happening in your class because it happens in every class <unclear/> was nice I think I might try and <pause dur="short"/> they they'd done it as a negotiated thing with the permanent with the sort of permanent teachers so so they've negotiated all of these different things and without standardisation but with a summer school that's not really going to be possible I didn't want to have have to impose it because there's not time to negotiate with the teachers and if you've got an <trunc>un</trunc> <trunc>unex</trunc> inexperienced teacher then they don't really know yeah I think I might talk to the <unclear> dossers</unclear> and implement it have it as a top down thing you must do it like this I think although I think one of the London schools is going to have the Director of Studies and possibly some teachers from the London Kaplan school so I'm sure they won't do it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0442"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0320">but yeah no I didn't go to that one I went to <pause dur="short"/> what did I go to when that one on? I went to teaching advanced learners and CLIL I went to a CLIL talk which was really interesting by that guy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he was wearing a turquoise silk shirt with a gold and black waistcoat <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was I was like <trunc>th</trunc> not what you looked like yesterday <vocal desc="laugh"/> that was really interesting erm not really <trunc>of</trunc> offering money solutions to problems but interesting</u>
<u n="212" who="S0442">mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0320">and then I went to one on storytelling</u>
<u n="214" who="S0442">ah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0320">which was really interactive like almost I almost didn't go because he <vocal desc="laugh"/> I walked in and it was all set up in a horseshoe and I was like oh no we're going to actually have to do something <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was really nice though he's part of the charity called The Philosophy Foundation so partly storytelling it wasn't anything majorly interesting but it was mostly discussing philosophical ideas</u>
<u n="216" who="S0442">ah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0320">tricking people tricking the students into discussing philosophical ideas it was very interesting actually it was all really good I was really surprised I didn't go last year and then this year it was great</u>
<u n="218" who="S0442">okay so what freebies did you get?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0320">no bloody tickets</u>
<u n="220" who="S0442">no?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0320">I was really annoyed just loads of pens and books and I don't know but no tickets I was I was quite annoyed by that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0442">what did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> say about the guy that got run over?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0320">erm that they <pause dur="short"/> the school is closed on Friday morning out of respect that <pause dur="short"/> because he was here with his brother there were two of them and the body is still in <anon type="place"/> or another but they're sixteen brothers I think brothers possibly brothers and sisters erm I I covered a class one the day that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went off to hospital and covered a test day for one of the teachers down at down at a hotel on the seafront erm <anon type="place"/> maybe</u>
<u n="224" who="S0442">uh huh</u>
<u n="225" who="S0320">really nice</u>
<u n="226" who="S0442">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0320">so I covered that and the two boys were in that class and after they finished their test we just had a chat with them they were very sweet Yemeni boys not Saudi but I think they possibly lived in Saudi</u>
<u n="228" who="S0442">oh I thought they were Saudi</u>
<u n="229" who="S0320">Yemeni so really hard working and sweet not your typical lazy arse Saudi boys erm and they they've the school had been in in contact with the mosque in <anon type="place"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> taking lots of advice from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about how to handle everything and how to deal with it so the two the two boys were here they had some cousins in Plymouth of course and another brother has flown over to help deal with everything really sad</u>
<u n="230" who="S0442">it is really sad</u>
<u n="231" who="S0320">I <trunc>ca</trunc> I could only remember one of them because I just taught them I just had them in the class once and I I'm not sure which one it is but they were just both very didn't cheat once in the test there were three of them sat in this hotel room and me no cheating whatsoever like none <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was totally unprecedented</u>
<u n="232" who="S0442">do you know any of the details of?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0320">no I no</u>
<u n="234" who="S0442">because who was on the mobile phone? the driver or him?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0320">I don't know that I I only know what I read in the Herald Express the other day and what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has told me I don't know that many details someone was on the phone though</u>
<u n="236" who="S0442">well that's what I've heard I don't know if it's true because</u>
<u n="237" who="S0320">yeah it just could've been either of them really couldn't it but it was just</u>
<u n="238" who="S0442">where was it?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0320">just</u>
<u n="240" who="S0442">because I heard that he was the driver was blinded by the sun</u>
<u n="241" who="S0320">yeah I remember you told me that it hasn't been very sunny recently though has it? not exactly blinding sunshine weather is it?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0442">when you come round that bend and the sun's</u>
<u n="243" who="S0320">which bend was it?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0442"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0320">which one's that?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0442">you know where the train station is?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0320">is it? was it on the pedestrian crossing? or sort of between the two pedestrian crossings?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0442">between the two I think</u>
<u n="249" who="S0320">it is so hard to drive fast around there</u>
<u n="250" who="S0442">mm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0320">was he not driving very fast?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0442">I don't think so no</u>
<u n="253" who="S0320">but that's quite hard to it's quite hard to <pause dur="short"/> a drive fast and B hit someone in that short space because you've got the pedestrian crossing then you've got the <pause dur="short"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="254" who="S0442">mm</u>
<u n="255" who="S0320">no I don't really I don't know anything else other than that</u>
<u n="256" who="S0442">and his poor family</u>
<u n="257" who="S0320">yeah so sad</u>
<u n="258" who="S0442">and the driver has got to live with that</u>
<u n="259" who="S0320">yeah but why are they appealing for witnesses? cos I <trunc>pres</trunc> I thought it might've been a hit and run but then they said the forty-two year old man blah blah blah blah blah but there was they were still appealing for witnesses</u>
<u n="260" who="S0442">I guess to see if anyone was on their phones if he was looking the right way</u>
<u n="261" who="S0320">mm</u>
<u n="262" who="S0442">erm if there were any other cars that might have caused him to</u>
<u n="263" who="S0320" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0442">swerve</u>
<u n="265" who="S0320">I suppose <pause dur="short"/> I think erm I think his brother was with him did you tell me that?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0442">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0320">yeah yeah must be yeah devastating and so unexpected as well because whenever you talk to them I'm going to do this I'm going to university then I'm going to go home and ah you know <pause dur="short"/> I think he was eighteen I don't think he was sixteen</u>
<u n="268" who="S0442">really? I thought he was sixteen</u>
<u n="269" who="S0320">yeah I'm pretty sure he was</u>
<u n="270" who="S0442">I thought he was sixteen</u>
<u n="271" who="S0320">yeah I don't think he was sixteen I know ages tend to be quite fluid with the <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm <trunc>Saud</trunc> with the Arabic boys but I'm pretty sure he wasn't sixteen even though it said so in the paper I don't I really don't think he was possibly seventeen or eighteen but I'm pretty sure he wasn't sixteen he never came up in any of the safeguarding things which he'd have to if you're sixteen so I'm pretty sure they got it wrong I don't think he was sixteen <pause dur="short"/> unless of course they lied <vocal desc="laugh"/> which is always possible <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0442">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0320">yeah right then shall we go into town?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0442">yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0320">what time is it? what have we got to do in town?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0442">I don't know</u>
<u n="277" who="S0320">I've had my charity shop purchase for the week which was this I'm very pleased with it</u>
<u n="278" who="S0442">oh cool it's nice</u>
<u n="279" who="S0320">yeah it's good isn't it? no black</u>
<u n="280" who="S0442">no</u>
<u n="281" who="S0320">impressive isn't it?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0442">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0320"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm yeah I know erm yeah four pounds fifty I think</u>
<u n="284" who="S0442">cool</u>
<u n="285" who="S0320">love it</u>
<u n="286" who="S0442">it is nice</u>
<u n="287" who="S0320">yeah erm yeah so I've had my <trunc>char</trunc> I've got to buy lots of like secret Santa presents but I haven't got any money until next week oh I've been invited to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s school Christmas party</u>
<u n="288" who="S0442">have you?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0320">finally after whinging nonstop for about the last month I never get invited to parties I've worked for like seven different people and nobody <unclear/> I got a call from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> er we'd like to invite you to the Christmas party</u>
<u n="290" who="S0442">what is it? what do they do?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0320">going to the Church House in next Friday for lunch</u>
<u n="292" who="S0442">oh that will be nice</u>
<u n="293" who="S0320">yeah three course meal</u>
<u n="294" who="S0442">do they pay for it?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0320">yup and I think <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> is not going to be working so I can go and I can have some wine</u>
<u n="296" who="S0442">cool</u>
<u n="297" who="S0320">erm but the vegetarian option looks pretty gross</u>
<u n="298" who="S0442">oh</u>
<u n="299" who="S0320">it's erm chick spiced chickpea with homemade curd cheese wellington</u>
<u n="300" who="S0442"><unclear/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0320">it sounds a bit weird <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> reckoned it would be alright seeing as she was like</u>
<u n="302" who="S0442">is she going?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0320">no but I did ask her about it and she said well we put curd cheese on everything in Canada so that sounds quite nice to me I was like alright I'll take your word for it but the starter and the dessert look nice so I'm sure I'll survive or I'll just eat the vegetables <vocal desc="laugh"/> but it looked really gross</u>
<u n="304" who="S0442">er mine is next Friday as well</u>
<u n="305" who="S0320">is your up in London? oh my god so when yeah when are you up?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0442">it's a shame though when the company is meant to be doing so badly and they're cutting back here there and everywhere why are they going to spend like ten grand or so</u>
<u n="307" who="S0320"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0442">to send us all to London</u>
<u n="309" who="S0320">is that how much it's going to cost?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0442">well I imagine so there's like</u>
<u n="311" who="S0320" trans="overlap">I I agree</u>
<u n="312" who="S0442">thirty people staying in a hotel going on a cruise up the the <trunc>ri</trunc> river</u>
<u n="313" who="S0320">I agree on the one hand but on the other hand I think it's yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0442">it's too extravagant</u>
<u n="315" who="S0320">er yeah I suppose it is actually they could just pay for a meal down here couldn't they?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0442">yeah or give us some money</u>
<u n="317" who="S0320">yeah I think it's nice to do something Christmassy like I'm <trunc>firm</trunc> I'm firmly I think it's a great idea and I think it's a good company thing to do but yeah there are I suppose there are limits so you're going up when you going up? on Friday?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0442">Friday</u>
<u n="319" who="S0320">are you going to take are you getting the train? are they paying for your train?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0442">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0320">how you getting?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0442">we're going up in a minibus</u>
<u n="323" who="S0320">flipping heck</u>
<u n="324" who="S0442">a school bus</u>
<u n="325" who="S0320">oh that's going to be a long journey so you're going up on Friday and then where are you staying?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0442">getting a hotel in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0320">oh by the school and then you're going on the river</u>
<u n="328" who="S0442">from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0320">oh lovely oh <anon type="place"/> lovely</u>
<u n="330" who="S0442">mm</u>
<u n="331" who="S0320">really nice <anon type="place"/> have you been to <anon type="place"/> park? that's brilliant isn't it</u>
<u n="332" who="S0442">mm</u>
<u n="333" who="S0320">so you're going to <anon type="place"/> okay and then</u>
<u n="334" who="S0442">up the river</u>
<u n="335" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0442">on the boat</u>
<u n="337" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0442">have a meal</u>
<u n="339" who="S0320">on the boat</u>
<u n="340" who="S0442">then back to Richmond back to the hotel and then home the next day</u>
<u n="341" who="S0320">wow and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is not going?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0442">no</u>
<u n="343" who="S0320">that'll be ace what are you going to wear?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0442">I don't know</u>
<u n="345" who="S0320"><vocal desc="laugh"/> are you going to go and look for something in the charity shops today?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0442">I haven't got any money</u>
<u n="347" who="S0320">so no</u>
<u n="348" who="S0442">no</u>
<u n="349" who="S0320">okay</u>
<u n="350" who="S0442">I'll just have to wear something I've already got</u>
<u n="351" who="S0320">you could wear that black dress</u>
<u n="352" who="S0442"><vocal desc="gasp"/> oh the black dress</u>
<u n="353" who="S0320">black dress wear the black dress it looks lush</u>
<u n="354" who="S0442">it does look lush but it's got <unclear/> burns on it</u>
<u n="355" who="S0320">it's got what?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0442">burns</u>
<u n="357" who="S0320">has it?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0442">yeah that's why do you remember the message I asked you sent you?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0320">no what message?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0442">about you smoking in it?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0320">ah ah does it really show up? so you can't wear that</u>
<u n="362" who="S0442">no I can wear it</u>
<u n="363" who="S0320">yeah a bit of black marker maybe? something underneath I don't know it's got lots of netting on it under it hasn't it</u>
<u n="364" who="S0442">yeah but I haven't got any black shoes either</u>
<u n="365" who="S0320">I've got some grey shoes</u>
<u n="366" who="S0442">what size are you?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0320">six</u>
<u n="368" who="S0442">oh are you?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0320">yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0442">oh</u>
<u n="371" who="S0320">I'll go and I'll go and find them</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
