<text id="SNRP">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:12:02</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-01-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>The boiler, a camping trip</topics>
		<activity>Talking about the boiler, discussing a camping trip.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0037"><trunc>D'y</trunc> so d'you think it's been warmer in here today? Like with the heating d'you think it's improved?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="3" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you know cos the boiler's been funny</u>
<u n="4" who="S0115">well there's been a <trunc>ri</trunc> a bit of uh uncertainty I mean <pause dur="short"/> I but I looked at the the dial of it and I realized</u>
<u n="5" who="S0037">in the cupboard?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0115">yeah that you can <pause dur="short"/> I mean it it goes <pause dur="short"/> it has that flame doesn't it which looks a bit like like the symbol of the red flame it looks a little bit like you know</u>
<u n="7" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's like a reset button though I think</u>
<u n="8" who="S0115">you know the symbol of the flame on the  on the  dial at the top <pause dur="short"/> sort of twelve eleven o'clock on the dial there's like a red flame symbol</u>
<u n="9" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> oh I don't know</u>
<u n="10" who="S0115">on the dial on the temperature dial?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0037">I hadn't noticed</u>
<u n="12" who="S0115">I I thought you said that we weren't supposed to go past the flame</u>
<u n="13" who="S0037">we're not supposed to go past that little mark have you seen the little like pencil line?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah that's what I meant like the flame thing?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0037">what flame?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0115">that's that's what it looked to me like a flame the mark</u>
<u n="17" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> it's just a bit of marker pen that the <trunc>b</trunc> landlord put on there</u>
<u n="18" who="S0115">yeah so said we we shouldn't need to go past that</u>
<u n="19" who="S0037">Cos he said we shouldn't go past that because it's hard water and then it like gets clogs in the pipes or something</u>
<u n="20" who="S0115">yeah if <trunc>y</trunc> if it gets too hot</u>
<u n="21" who="S0037" trans="overlap">if you put it on really high it makes the water like more likely to</u>
<u n="22" who="S0115" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> I reckon that that might</u>
<u n="23" who="S0037" trans="overlap">which is probably what's happened anyway</u>
<u n="24" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it may be happening anyway yeah but uh <pause dur="short"/> well it has been quite hot uh <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="25" who="S0037">I wasn't cold this morning or anything</u>
<u n="26" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it has been like the <trunc>f</trunc> the <trunc>ca</trunc> the floor's been reasonably hot</u>
<u n="27" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> d'you think I should ring him then?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0115">uh we'll probably have to get in touch with <pause dur="short"/> I mean I could do a couple of experiments but</u>
<u n="29" who="S0037">no well</u>
<u n="30" who="S0115">uh I mean I could</u>
<u n="31" who="S0037">I don't like the idea of the boiler just like blasting away and then</u>
<u n="32" who="S0115">well no I don't mean turn it really high I just mean just recording what the temperature is in the room</u>
<u n="33" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0115">if we did but actually I had I hadn't set that one on the right temperature though cos <pause dur="short"/> the room was a the rooms are all programmed according to a reasonably complicated system actually where you</u>
<u n="35" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I <trunc>ju</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> aha <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> there's so many options</u>
<u n="36" who="S0115" trans="overlap">each <pause dur="short"/> we've got three rooms and each room has <pause dur="short"/> you can set the weekdays</u>
<u n="37" who="S0037">I know</u>
<u n="38" who="S0115">and you can set the weekend but uh</u>
<u n="39" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the wake and the waking and leaving and returning and sleeping times</u>
<u n="40" who="S0115">yeah including so a total of say like four per day different times</u>
<u n="41" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0115">um and for the three rooms so there's a lot of different <trunc>one</trunc></u>
<u n="43" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think you can add other ones as well if you wanted to</u>
<u n="44" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there's a lot of different <trunc>w</trunc> ways that you can program these and and I'd sort of I'd only put the bedroom on to twenty-one degrees</u>
<u n="45" who="S0037">ah right so it wasn't</u>
<u n="46" who="S0115">it wasn't programmed our bedroom wasn't programmed to do twenty-two</u>
<u n="47" who="S0037" trans="overlap">aha</u>
<u n="48" who="S0115">and I was complaining that it hadn't done <trunc>t</trunc> twenty-two without actually realizing that I didn't hadn't asked it to do twenty-two but</u>
<u n="49" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah I see</u>
<u n="50" who="S0115">if you put this one here and the living room on twenty-two for an hour it probably won't get there on the current settings</u>
<u n="51" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no but it used to though didn't it?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0115">I don't know</u>
<u n="53" who="S0037">I think so</u>
<u n="54" who="S0115">I don't know for certain</u>
<u n="55" who="S0037">unless it was just warmer I mean</u>
<u n="56" who="S0115">I don't know for certain <pause dur="short"/> I think it's partly the outdoor temperature as well so there is</u>
<u n="57" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it has been freezing it was so cold today</u>
<u n="58" who="S0115" trans="overlap">to be honest we <trunc>d</trunc> we don't know for certain whether <pause dur="short"/> but I suppose in order to be  in order to be  sure we'd have to ask him but on the other hand yeah we should do the this is what my my point was we should  we should  do some tests first</u>
<u n="59" who="S0037" trans="overlap">we need to do some empirical tests <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0115">uh cos it may just be the fact that it's colder outside <pause dur="short"/> uh and uh we may've put up with um twenty-three degrees in the past</u>
<u n="61" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Cos I can't remember what happened last year like I can't remember if it was freezing last</u>
<u n="62" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh well we had a really cold um winter</u>
<u n="63" who="S0037">did we have to put the boiler up? Did I turn the boiler up or not?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0115">I think we just cranked  we just cranked  the boiler up a bit higher</u>
<u n="65" who="S0037" trans="overlap">did we?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0115">and and just put up with that I I kind of suspect that it's just a combination of cranking the boiler up and <pause dur="short"/> like I <trunc>s</trunc> kind of suspect there isn't really anything that wrong with it but</u>
<u n="67" who="S0037">okay</u>
<u n="68" who="S0115">I thought it might need bleeding so I obviously took all of the stuff out of the way to check</u>
<u n="69" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0115">and <trunc>j</trunc></u>
<u n="71" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know I need to</u>
<u n="72" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there are  there are  the sort of two bleeding holes there</u>
<u n="73" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0115">but I suppose I wouldn't wanna bleed it myself</u>
<u n="75" who="S0037">two bleeding holes <pause dur="short"/> waay <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> very <trunc>fe</trunc> very funny yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0037" trans="overlap">all that <pause dur="short"/> so I need to put that <pause dur="short"/> d'you think we should put that away then all those bits on the bed or d'you think we should leave them in case that he comes <trunc>rou</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> suppose it depends if we're gonna ring him</u>
<u n="78" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well just <pause dur="short"/> we'll do the experiments and then</u>
<u n="79" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0115">um and then uh we'll see what happens then <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="81" who="S0037">Cos there's all those like</u>
<u n="82" who="S0115" trans="overlap">if <trunc>s</trunc> if if <trunc>a</trunc> if I put it on in this room to go to twenty-two it probably wouldn't get up there on the current dial setting but if I turn the dial up it might</u>
<u n="83" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="84" who="S0115">so I don't know it</u>
<u n="85" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0115">or the <pause dur="short"/> someone's gonna have to come round and unplug the pipes at some point but uh</u>
<u n="87" who="S0037">I know <pause dur="short"/> get some Calgon in there or whatever</u>
<u n="88" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but it might  it might  make more sense for him to do for us to do that lot when we move out of here</u>
<u n="89" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> I dunno when that'll be</u>
<u n="90" who="S0115">no</u>
<u n="91" who="S0037">but um <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I mean we might need those those stuff that stuff out of the cupboard anyway <pause dur="short"/> like those sleeping bags and stuff <pause dur="short"/> if <trunc>w</trunc> if we're going to that thing at Easter</u>
<u n="92" who="S0115">yeah um</u>
<u n="93" who="S0037">have you asked your mum about it yet?</u>
<u n="94" who="S0115" trans="overlap">we <pause dur="short"/> no we were waiting for um something we had to actually get a uh sort of schedule from the if we've go</u>
<u n="95" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Will your mam not know?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0115">if we're <pause dur="short"/> yeah well we'll probably have to <pause dur="short"/> I need to find out when uh</u>
<u n="97" who="S0037">Cos your parents might not even be going <pause dur="short"/> did they not say something about going away? Or does that <trunc>w</trunc> is that what they mean?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> go so many times a year and I don't know all the times that they go <pause dur="short"/> but I was hoping to get some kind of plan <pause dur="short"/> cos I imagine they go at the bank <trunc>ho</trunc> the Easter bank holiday</u>
<u n="99" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0115">then they uh one of them and the when they start  when they start  the caravan cos they don't use at winter so they they have to sort of</u>
<u n="101" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah that's right it goes to sleep I forgot about that</u>
<u n="102" who="S0115">yeah so in the  in the  sort of April one that they go at</u>
<u n="103" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0115">they have to sort of wake it up</u>
<u n="105" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0115">for the <pause dur="short"/> so they have to plug um do something with the pipes uh</u>
<u n="107" who="S0037" trans="overlap">all the stuff in? The electricity?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0115" trans="overlap">then <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="109" who="S0037">I forgot about that</u>
<u n="110" who="S0115" trans="overlap">then so they go <pause dur="short"/> then they go in April then they go uh a couple more times over the year so</u>
<u n="111" who="S0037" trans="overlap">in the summer  in the summer  holidays?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0115">yeah <trunc>w</trunc> we probably just wanna find <pause dur="short"/> if you wanna <trunc>d</trunc> to do it in April we'd have to find which weekend in April they were going</u>
<u n="113" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'm not set I haven't got me heart set on that <pause dur="short"/> just if if that's like if that's gonna be a way of getting to see people rather than Christmas time then I think it's probably worth doing so <pause dur="short"/> d'you think? Plus I like a bit of camping</u>
<u n="114" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> um yeah I think we should go <pause dur="short"/> uh probably probably the the April one time's a a good one uh</u>
<u n="115" who="S0037">it'll not be too cold though will it?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0115">uh well that it's hard to tell isn't it I mean I doubt it</u>
<u n="117" who="S0037">be rainy <pause dur="short"/> wales is always rainy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0115">uh yeah yeah yeah it can be <pause dur="short"/> it can be rainy out there</u>
<u n="119" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's part of the fun though I suppose</u>
<u n="120" who="S0115">but but with camping I suppose it <pause dur="short"/> yeah the the the wetness of it sort of <pause dur="short"/> you've got get around that by having a good tent or or whatever <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="121" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and did did I show you me waterproof trousers?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so so one of them's got a caravan so we can possibly hang hang around in their  in their  caravan</u>
<u n="123" who="S0037" trans="overlap">get warm <pause dur="short"/> I know but they've got all them dogs</u>
<u n="124" who="S0115">I know well you well uh</u>
<u n="125" who="S0037">I'd be a bit scared</u>
<u n="126" who="S0115">not sure if they've still got them</u>
<u n="127" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no but if your mam and dad's there</u>
<u n="128" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no more than two dogs in</u>
<u n="129" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh Ben won't be able to go will he? He's too old now</u>
<u n="130" who="S0115">yeah so um that's a shame actually but their dogs are probably getting old as well <pause dur="short"/> so they</u>
<u n="131" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what was he called like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or something?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and he was brown uh that was his name</u>
<u n="133" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And is that what's her second?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and</u>
<u n="135" who="S0037">what's her second name?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0115">what?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0037"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s second name</u>
<u n="138" who="S0115">surname <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0115">so he was actually yeah his name was actually <trunc>Bo</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That's what I mean <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> bashing up all the other dogs and that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> there's uh <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0037"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> musta like is your dog like Whitney?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="145" who="S0037">like The Bodyguard</u>
<u n="146" who="S0115">oh well there was uh <pause dur="short"/> there was <pause dur="short"/> what was her name with the black Labrador? Uh <pause dur="short"/> who does that belong to that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s dog the black Labrador</u>
<u n="147" who="S0037" trans="overlap">or like um <pause dur="short"/> had a stupid name <pause dur="short"/> it had like seventeen names didn't it? It was called like <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh <trunc>Luck</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm not sure about <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> but uh</u>
<u n="149" who="S0037">it had like twenty names</u>
<u n="150" who="S0115">what was it? There was Lucky but no there was <trunc>th</trunc> there was Lucky was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s one before <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="151" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> that was um <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>u</trunc> did it not not have like twenty-five middle names the dog?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0115">the they always give them a lot of middles names but um <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what his first name but anyway and then there was <pause dur="short"/> that's a black Labrador and then there was my parents' dog which is a a cross</u>
<u n="153" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0115">so yeah so we would be <trunc>m</trunc> staying on the <trunc>is</trunc> you know uh in a tent on that massive caravan site</u>
<u n="155" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but I think this time we should get like</u>
<u n="156" who="S0115" trans="overlap">in <pause dur="short"/> so hopefully we'd have to get a tent that was good enough uh to withstand all the difficult <trunc>m</trunc> surrounding wetness of Wales and uh</u>
<u n="157" who="S0037">but I think we should like invest in more like camping gadgets this time <pause dur="short"/> You know more like grill and like hot you know things for cooking</u>
<u n="158" who="S0115">yeah probably we've gotta up</u>
<u n="159" who="S0037">enter into the camping spirit</u>
<u n="160" who="S0115">up a gear you know and go to a greater greater trouble to</u>
<u n="161" who="S0037" trans="overlap">or we could just do it Ray Mears style</u>
<u n="162" who="S0115">yeah should uh</u>
<u n="163" who="S0037" trans="overlap">shoot ourselves a wild boar and</u>
<u n="164" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I dunno how um <pause dur="short"/> there are things that live around it that you could possibly</u>
<u n="165" who="S0037">get ourselves a wild boar</u>
<u n="166" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um I don't  I don't  have a gun though so</u>
<u n="167" who="S0037" trans="overlap">fashion some cutlery out of a tree stump</u>
<u n="168" who="S0115">D'you d'you uh <pause dur="short"/> how would you catch a a rabbit?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0037" trans="overlap">A wild boar? Oh with great difficulty I <pause dur="short"/> I haven't got <pause dur="short"/> I'm bit trouble catching a cold me so I don't think I'm gonna get a wild boar</u>
<u n="170" who="S0115">uh uh there won't be any wild boars but there might be a couple of rabbits or?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0037">on that programme they just shot them didn't they?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0115">um yeah that was uh</u>
<u n="173" who="S0037">maybe we'll get them</u>
<u n="174" who="S0115">you talking about the gypsy programme?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0037" trans="overlap">maybe this this weekend's turned into something quite different to just to a camping trip</u>
<u n="176" who="S0115">yeah we don't wanna sort of</u>
<u n="177" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Go back to nature</u>
<u n="178" who="S0115">to go <trunc>shoo</trunc> shooting everything</u>
<u n="179" who="S0037">Claire and Matt back to nature</u>
<u n="180" who="S0115">um so yeah but we're at <pause dur="short"/> sort of Ray Mears style might be  might be  good <pause dur="short"/> could could get a <trunc>st</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> d'you wanna get a portable gas stove or something?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0037" trans="overlap">D'you remember that Ray Mears? Yeah I think so <pause dur="short"/> d'you remember that Ray Mears thing?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh <pause dur="short"/> which one?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0037" trans="overlap">somebody must <pause dur="short"/> I bet <trunc>s</trunc> I know somebody who's got one we can borrow</u>
<u n="184" who="S0115">D'you know one the one when Ray Mears did a roast hog or something?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0037">yeah and he spent like Ray <trunc>Me</trunc> he spent so long making like a brush for his dressing not for his roast things</u>
<u n="186" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> he put well he put the pig on the uh <pause dur="short"/> on a <trunc>sp</trunc> he made a spit roast out of some pieces of wood which is easy to do</u>
<u n="187" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's right <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah stick essentially</u>
<u n="188" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh two stick holders or they're called andirons or are they?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0037">are they really? Have you just made that up?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they're things  they're things  that hold the stick</u>
<u n="191" who="S0037" trans="overlap">how on earth do you know that?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0115">they put <pause dur="short"/> ah it was a pub quiz question a while ago</u>
<u n="193" who="S0037">andirons?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0115">they're the things on the uh</u>
<u n="195" who="S0037">what pub quiz was that?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0115">the things you put on a fire and they have like a hand thing like that and they're sort of like</u>
<u n="197" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> ah yeah like they rest the <trunc>st</trunc> the stick the spit stick in?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0115" trans="overlap">something like that anyway yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know if they're always called andirons or if that isn't just the iron version <pause dur="short"/> they he made two side sticks to hold it up and then</u>
<u n="199" who="S0037">uhuh</u>
<u n="200" who="S0115">sorry two ones that rest hold it up and then the <trunc>s</trunc> the spit across the top</u>
<u n="201" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0115">and he put his pig on the and he made a fire underneath</u>
<u n="203" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0115">then he  then he  <trunc>p</trunc> he set that going then he he thought he'd make a brush to brush the pig with</u>
<u n="205" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No what was he brushing on it?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but while  but while  he was making the brush</u>
<u n="207" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he was putting like honey <pause dur="short"/> he'd been like ferreting around in like a bee's nest or something</u>
<u n="208" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he got uh he well he had these he had his glaze you know to put but while he was  while he was  uh <pause dur="short"/> he the pig was basically roasting on the spit and he was spending about an hour maybe about an hour making this this wooden brush just to brush the pig like</u>
<u n="209" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it'd been like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0115">meanwhile the pig's totally burnt <pause dur="short"/> and it  and it  he's he's got no sort of no glazing on it <pause dur="short"/> he could of just used his hands to put it on</u>
<u n="211" who="S0037" trans="overlap">aw <pause dur="short"/> cos you're supposed to turn it round and he was just like</u>
<u n="212" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah he was just spent all his time doing uh</u>
<u n="213" who="S0037">aw silly Ray Mears</u>
<u n="214" who="S0115">doing his uh with a wooden brush which didn't even work and it wasn't a proper brush it was just like a stick with like some holes in the end of it</u>
<u n="215" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
</body>
</text>
