<text id="SNRQ">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:02:14</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-08</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0018 S0170</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Birmingham</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Jobs, learning languages, babies</topics>
		<activity>Friends (ex-colleagues) talking about jobs, learning languages and babies.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, requesting, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0018">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Hertfordshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years, 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Advanced; French -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0170">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Stourbridge, West Midlands</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birmingham</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>25 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Beginner; Polish -- Beginner</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0018">thank you <pause dur="short"/> so what you know you were telling me about the jobs that you were looking at in the <anon type="place"/> newspaper</u>
<u n="2" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0018">what kind of jobs they are coming up there?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0170">oh it's a lot of admin sales marketing that kind of thing</u>
<u n="5" who="S0018">for what kind of companies? Did they specify?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0170">no <pause dur="short"/> I for in <anon type="place"/> I don't it's not very big town <pause dur="short"/> so it's em <pause dur="short"/> there's a lot of solicitors <pause dur="short"/> yeah but there were quite a few solicitors that were looking for admin <pause dur="short"/> but I don't think that's my sort of thing</u>
<u n="7" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> definitely <pause dur="short"/> I mean if it was an admin in a really interesting exciting company</u>
<u n="8" who="S0170">mm mm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0018">or something it would the you could <trunc>prob</trunc> you could probably deal with the the boredom of the admin tasks cos it's an exciting context <pause dur="short"/> but then if you're talking about an insurance company</u>
<u n="10" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0018">or a firm that makes hangers <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0170">no</u>
<u n="13" who="S0018">and what's the pay? Do they advertise the pay in jobs like that?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0170">fifteen sixteen thousand</u>
<u n="15" who="S0018">for full time hours?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0170">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> that's not very good <pause dur="short"/> it's all like <anon type="place"/> way <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think I need to look maybe Express and Mail those kind of papers or on online as well</u>
<u n="17" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0170">did you ever look on Monster Monster Jobs?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0018">monster Jobs? I did in Spain <pause dur="short"/> but I haven't looked at it here cos you have to sift through so much</u>
<u n="20" who="S0170">that's what I'm thinking I don't have time with him <pause dur="short"/> I I need to find well you know quickly what I want</u>
<u n="21" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> would you I mean could you set up job alerts? For them to?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0170">mm <pause dur="short"/> I did with the NHS I was looking for em speech therapy language assistant</u>
<u n="23" who="S0018">oh really?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0170">but it's really low pay <pause dur="short"/> but once you've done that for a couple of years you can do that plus the course at the same time you can become a speech therapist through it</u>
<u n="25" who="S0018">oh wow <pause dur="short"/> that's em</u>
<u n="26" who="S0170">it's really hard to do to get in to do it</u>
<u n="27" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I want to find something that's not too far away <pause dur="short"/> I found one in Wolverhampton <pause dur="short"/> I did apply for that that was last year <pause dur="short"/> but I didn't get</u>
<u n="29" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0170">shortlisted so</u>
<u n="31" who="S0018">so what you'd start off as an assistant speech therapist?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0170">and whilst you're doing that do a course</u>
<u n="35" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0170">and then you can become a speech therapist or there's a one year course but it's in Essex or London</u>
<event desc="sound of baby crying"/>
<u n="37" who="S0018">eh huh <pause dur="short"/> oh what's wrong?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0170">you'll have it with your relevant degree and then you can do a one year sort of like fast track to be a speech therapist</u>
<u n="39" who="S0018">fantastic</u>
<u n="40" who="S0170">I was interested in it but I'm not sure it's just</u>
<u n="41" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0170">now I've got little <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="43" who="S0018">and what do they class as a relevant degree?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0170">well something with <trunc>lang</trunc> well languages <pause dur="short"/> linguistics em <pause dur="short"/> they didn't really list it what what it was but I think linguistics was a main one</u>
<u n="45" who="S0018">what did you study?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0170">linguistics and Spanish</u>
<u n="47" who="S0018">oh really?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> that sounds really interesting <pause dur="short"/> when you're a speech therapist what em is that working with the NHS?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they that so they they've got their</u>
<u n="51" who="S0018">so yeah tell me about speech therapy <pause dur="short"/> is it  is it  quite em a demanding course?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0170">I think so <pause dur="short"/> I mean I read about the modules a bit and it's quite an intense one year course</u>
<u n="53" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0170">because you have to learn about everything but and I think you have to specialise <pause dur="short"/> I wanted to either do em speech therapy for people who have had brain injuries or children</u>
<u n="55" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0170">so but then to do the speech therapy em <trunc>a</trunc> assistant you had to have some experience of working with children</u>
<u n="57" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="58" who="S0170">before so <pause dur="short"/> I didn't have that</u>
<u n="59" who="S0018">oh don't you? Have you not taught kids?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0170">I taught for two weeks one Easter <pause dur="short"/> but em I haven't done it more than that <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="61" who="S0018">and doesn't having your own kid?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0170">well now I have</u>
<u n="63" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0170">now I have and I'll see how his language develops <pause dur="short"/> well I've heard cos he'll be hearing cos he's hearing Polish and English that he'll take <trunc>l</trunc> longer to start speaking</u>
<u n="65" who="S0018">yeah I heard that <pause dur="short"/> cos I did em psycholinguistics in my degree and wrote wrote a paper about the bilingual lexicon <pause dur="short"/> and yeah I heard that that they develop they still develop the two language systems you know like natives?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0018">but they do take a little longer</u>
<u n="68" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos you can imagine it's a lot to take in isn't it? It takes long enough when you're learning one language</u>
<u n="69" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0170">let alone two <pause dur="short"/> em my friend who was from Quebec</u>
<u n="71" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0170">in Canada <pause dur="short"/> so she spoke like French and I think her mum was eh German <pause dur="short"/> so in her house she heard English German and <trunc>F</trunc> French and she said she used to say sentences in a mixture of all three languages <pause dur="short"/> cos she knew something like cup she only knew it in French <pause dur="short"/> so she'd say the whole sentence in English but the French word for cup and she didn't know what it was in in English</u>
<u n="73" who="S0018">I miss speaking Spanglish <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> most of my friends in Spain were em English speakers and Spanish speakers <pause dur="short"/> so you could always mix up the two languages in a sentence <pause dur="short"/> cos some expressions or some words</u>
<u n="74" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0018">different languages have better ways of <trunc>sa</trunc> expressing it <pause dur="short"/> so it's it's weird not using eh Spanglish</u>
<u n="76" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0170">my thing was I put English grammar <pause dur="short"/> we use the English grammar but with Spanish words <pause dur="short"/> sometimes I didn't know and you know you'd be like what?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0018">so when did you learn Spanish?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0170">just doing the degree I think that was my mistake <pause dur="short"/> I thought well but <anon type="place"/> Uni offered it as an intensive <pause dur="short"/> but it wasn't really that intensive it was like six hours a week</u>
<u n="80" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="81" who="S0170">and then you were supposed to finish your degree the same level as someone who's done GCSE plus A level</u>
<u n="82" who="S0018">blimey</u>
<u n="83" who="S0170">so</u>
<u n="84" who="S0018">that's eh that's a lot</u>
<u n="85" who="S0170">and it was then we were  we were  put together then after the first year with people who had done GCSE A-level plus the first year</u>
<u n="86" who="S0018">crikey</u>
<u n="87" who="S0170">and then <pause dur="short"/> intensive</u>
<u n="88" who="S0018">and did you spend time in Spain as part of your degree?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was in Granada</u>
<u n="90" who="S0018">oh lovely</u>
<u n="91" who="S0170">for nine months and I thought I understood some Spanish but when I went to Granada I didn't understand anyone</u>
<u n="92" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0170">except my landlord and he was an English teacher <pause dur="short"/> and he spoke really slowly and everything <pause dur="short"/> my friend I know how she did it <pause dur="short"/> she didn't speak a word <pause dur="short"/> she was from Germany</u>
<u n="94" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0170"> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> and she phoned up places not speaking any Spanish trying to find a place to live <pause dur="short"/> how would how you know what do you say to them on the phone? Cos I wouldn't have done it</u>
<u n="96" who="S0018">it is so much more difficult on the phone as well isn't it cos?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0170">yeah we did have when I was when em and luckily I was with eh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she spoke very good Spanish <pause dur="short"/> she's Italian <pause dur="short"/> she she learnt really quickly and em she would speak to people on the phone and arrange but sometimes they wouldn't want eh non Spanish</u>
<u n="98" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="99" who="S0170">there were certain areas that we phoned and they would say no sorry</u>
<u n="100" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0170">we want Spanish speakers <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0018">I guess they didn't want people who would be only there for like nine months or something</u>
<u n="103" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0170">and <pause dur="short"/> hey</u>
<u n="106" who="S0018">have you been back to Granada's since you lived there?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0170">no I haven't <pause dur="short"/> I want to I want to go with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and show him where I lived and everything <pause dur="short"/> I was really lucky we found a lovely apartment in em</u>
<u n="108" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="109" who="S0170">and it was like a the traditional part</u>
<u n="110" who="S0018">whereabouts is that? I know Granada a little bit em yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0170">it's up by it's not far from The</u>
<u n="112" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="113" who="S0170">so it is really close and like that's on top of the hill and it's down the side</u>
<u n="114" who="S0018">ah lovely where all the little white houses are</u>
<u n="115" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0018">with the patios and aw</u>
<u n="117" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0018">that is</u>
<u n="119" who="S0170">but we did <pause dur="short"/> we had one of the <trunc>ol</trunc> apartments where you know you got the square hole in the middle and</u>
<u n="120" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="121" who="S0170">and it's quite dark</u>
<u n="122" who="S0018">I like them though</u>
<u n="123" who="S0170">but it's lovely</u>
<u n="124" who="S0018">nice</u>
<u n="125" who="S0170">very traditional Spanish</u>
<u n="126" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> and did you go to uni while you were there?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0170">I did yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think that's why my Spanish is very em passive knowledge I</u>
<u n="128" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0170">I can watch Spanish films <pause dur="short"/> I can hear people speak and I can understand but trying to put sentences and express myself</u>
<u n="130" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's difficult isn't it? If you don't practice actually producing it it's it's a lot more difficult to <pause dur="short"/> cos you learn a lot of words through <trunc>li</trunc></u>
<u n="131" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0018">hearing them don't you?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0018">but you you don't your brain doesn't actually automatically throw them out until you've actually used them</u>
<u n="135" who="S0170">welI I read Spanish and I say em like I understand that story so I don't understand then why I don't know it when I try and speak <pause dur="short"/> it's really weird I and I just really</u>
<u n="136" who="S0018">I think there's some theory that says you have to use a word seven plus or minus two times before your brain can produce it</u>
<u n="137" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0018">so you can  you can  recognise it but you have to actually <trunc>produc</trunc> produce it <pause dur="short"/> you know a <trunc>ce</trunc> a certain amount of times before <trunc>y</trunc> you know it's integrated into your vocabulary <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0170">mm <pause dur="short"/> but the accent as well when I went to Granada it's <pause dur="short"/> they say it's like a Brummie accent here <pause dur="short"/> people make fun of the the accent from down south in Spain and and when I came back here and spoke with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> eh boyfriend</u>
<u n="140" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="141" who="S0170">he said oh you sound like you're from Granada</u>
<u n="142" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0018">is he from the north?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0170">I think so <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0170">no <pause dur="short"/> madrid</u>
<u n="147" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="148" who="S0170">he's from Madrid</u>
<u n="149" who="S0018">well in Granada do they speak with like if they say gracias do they say gracias or <trunc>gr</trunc>?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0170">mm <pause dur="short"/> and they cut the end off of everything</u>
<u n="151" who="S0018">eh <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> it's similar like</u>
<u n="152" who="S0170">gracia</u>
<u n="153" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> similar in Murcia</u>
<u n="154" who="S0170">yeah they don't have the Ss on the end <pause dur="short"/> it's like como esta?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0018">but did you practice it a lot or did you like em have a lot of Spanish friends and speak with them or was it a more Erasmus students sticking together?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0170">more Erasmus students <pause dur="short"/> not not so much but we were in the faculty of em of translation and interpretation <pause dur="short"/> well not you know the translation part</u>
<u n="157" who="S0018">yes</u>
<u n="158" who="S0170">you know translation em part and a lot of the students wanted to practice their English with you</u>
<u n="159" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="160" who="S0170">but they said this university was like the equivalent of Oxford and they were you could tell it was  it was  very good</u>
<u n="161" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0170">university and their English was very good</u>
<u n="163" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="164" who="S0170">with no accents some of the younger students</u>
<u n="165" who="S0018">well they learn it from such a young age over there don't they?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0170">and and you can imagine they like the equivalent of the like rich students <pause dur="short"/> they've probably been sent to England every summer and and they they speak English incredibly well <pause dur="short"/> so they just used to practice with us <vocal desc="laugh"/> with me <pause dur="short"/> another English guy there we always used to get people wanting to to talk with us in English and em <trunc>h</trunc> he was the same he didn't improve his Spanish <pause dur="short"/> he was quite good before but he was there with his family and that was different</u>
<u n="167" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> and did you live with the Italian girl?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0170">I lived with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's from Italy and another girl from Poland</u>
<u n="169" who="S0018">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> so you spoke English at home?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0170">yeah but we we tried sometimes to speak in Spanish</u>
<u n="171" who="S0018">it's really unnatural though isn't it? It's difficult <pause dur="short"/> no I was lucky when I went to Spain because I was apart from Lisa who's em bilingual cos her father's Spanish and her mother's English <pause dur="short"/> all my friends over there were Spanish <pause dur="short"/> so I had to start producing it and</u>
<u n="172" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0018">and I <trunc>wa</trunc> I was lucky in that respect is that I became fluent in about six months <pause dur="short"/> I knew nothing when I went there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="174" who="S0170">it is <pause dur="short"/> I things like having to order and by the end I mean I could do all things like I would things I had to do quite often ordering bombones</u>
<u n="175" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0170">things like that or having having to eh I went to the dentist and had to explain in in Spanish what what was wrong and <pause dur="short"/> you know and and things like that <pause dur="short"/> my Spanish was a lot <trunc>be</trunc> my Spanish was a hell of a lot better than when I went I would say</u>
<u n="177" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="178" who="S0170">I was a beginner when I went <pause dur="short"/> I didn't understand anything</u>
<u n="179" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> but it's the yeah the communication likely you were able to communicate in a shop <pause dur="short"/> it's the thing that probably comes first isn't it?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0018">is you're interacting in society were your  were your  classes in Spanish?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0170">they were <pause dur="short"/> they were well and this is the funny thing <pause dur="short"/> because it was the translation and I had to take a language <pause dur="short"/> so I learned Italian</u>
<u n="183" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0170">I ended  I ended  up giving a presentation in Italian oh <pause dur="short"/> giving a presentation in Italian when I was there to learn Spanish</u>
<u n="185" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="186" who="S0170">and I sort of three six nine nine hours a week I did Italian</u>
<u n="187" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="188" who="S0170">and it was either Italian French or German I had  I had  to take that fitted in into my timetable</u>
<u n="189" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="190" who="S0170">and I did a translation from Spanish to English science and technology <pause dur="short"/> I did translation of newspapers articles and stuff</u>
<u n="191" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0170">but I couldn't do it the other way because my Spanish wasn't good enough</u>
<u n="193" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="194" who="S0170">so I was just taking it the higher level</u>
<u n="195" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0170">modules of <trunc>transla</trunc> because for them that was a higher level translation started with English to Spanish</u>
<u n="197" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0170">and then Spanish to English <pause dur="short"/> so I was in like</u>
<u n="199" who="S0018">yeah I did a <pause dur="short"/> a translation course em at International House in Barcelona and oh yeah it was  it was  really interesting the teacher was really good but <pause dur="short"/> I found it really difficult to to translate <pause dur="short"/> I don't know cos when you're used to speaking other languages and learning them when you're abroad</u>
<u n="200" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0018">you're not necessarily translating <pause dur="short"/> you're not really developing the skill of translating <pause dur="short"/> cos if you learn it through immersion you have kind of a separate system in your head</u>
<u n="202" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0018">so I found it quite difficult to to I don't know sometimes English would just sound <pause dur="short"/> when I translated it into English it just didn't sound English <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I didn't have that capability of being able to</u>
<u n="204" who="S0170" trans="overlap">yeah I had to  yeah I had to change it I did one module of theory and of translation and that was quite interesting</u>
<u n="205" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0170">but can you imagine like sitting in lectures and I was please don't ask me a question <pause dur="short"/> please don't ask me a question</u>
<u n="207" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0170">for the first semester I didn't understand <trunc>any</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc> what the hell they were going on about <pause dur="short"/> and I just wanted to not go <pause dur="short"/> I thought no no I've got to go <pause dur="short"/> I've got to go <pause dur="short"/> And I'm glad I did because I think that helped me learn <pause dur="short"/> but at first you're just sitting there just listening to them blah blah blah blah blah blah and some of the lecturers are really it's a proper lecturing</u>
<u n="209" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0170">there was an older guy we did em Spanish History and em he was just like la la la la la la <pause dur="short"/> the whole</u>
<u n="211" who="S0018">monotone <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0170">yeah he just and he had like his notes in front of him and turn the page la la la la la <pause dur="short"/> it was <trunc>re</trunc> it was awful and then he'd ask questions at the end and it was like</u>
<u n="213" who="S0018">head down don't pick me</u>
<u n="214" who="S0170">please don't pick me</u>
<u n="215" who="S0018">what were your classes lectures?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0170">pardon?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0018">were all your classes lectures format?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0170">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> I mean the translation ones they were really good</u>
<u n="219" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="220" who="S0170">but the translation from Spanish to English the science one it was taught by an English guy</u>
<u n="221" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="222" who="S0170">who did the lesson in English</u>
<u n="223" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0170">and eh so that was  that was  I mean cos then he would always use me as the the person to explain things</u>
<u n="225" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="226" who="S0170">to the some of the students</u>
<u n="227" who="S0018">did they set up any language exchanges for you?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0170">yeah they did and I had an <unclear/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0018">oh good</u>
<u n="230" who="S0170">I had em I did with one girl called eh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> and eh she was really nice <pause dur="short"/> and another girl called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and we ended up going to Morocco together which was good</u>
<u n="231" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="232" who="S0170">because everyone else was with Erasmus students</u>
<u n="233" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0170">and I had with me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0170">and she was talking constantly in Spanish with me</u>
<u n="237" who="S0018">fantastic <pause dur="short"/> while you were in Morocco speaking French too no?</u>
<u n="238" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0018">you had a right hotch potch of languages <pause dur="short"/> spanish eh Italian at home</u>
<u n="240" who="S0170">oh I know <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> it was <trunc>ju</trunc> it was just so funny that I couldn't believe that I'd gone to Spain and ended up my main exam was a presentation in Italian</u>
<u n="241" who="S0018">my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> he came over to <anon type="place"/> University to do the Erasmus and he was living in a house full of Italian people</u>
<u n="242" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0018">and his English actually improved quite a lot when he was there but he learned fluent fluent Italian <vocal desc="laugh"/> when there as well</u>
<u n="244" who="S0170">I think <trunc>I</trunc> Italian and Spanish was <trunc>com</trunc> it complicates thing because they're so similar</u>
<u n="245" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="246" who="S0170">really similar that some sometimes you I'd be <trunc>prono</trunc> pronouncing things like the Italians would <pause dur="short"/> and in my I had an intensive Spanish class as well at the language centre</u>
<u n="247" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="248" who="S0170">which was good <pause dur="short"/> I really really enjoyed that <pause dur="short"/> cos they did it <trunc>Es</trunc> how we teach ESOL here</u>
<u n="249" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="250" who="S0170">which it all like at university it was very dry</u>
<u n="251" who="S0018">yeah more like studying it as opposed to learning how to use it</u>
<u n="252" who="S0170">yeah and then I but I really enjoyed those classes <pause dur="short"/> but all my classmates were Italian except for em well the German girl and I was like sometimes I didn't understand when they spoke Spanish because <pause dur="short"/> and the teacher said you know why because they're not speaking Spanish to me they're speaking Italian</u>
<u n="253" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0170">and they're just hoping that it's <trunc>Span</trunc></u>
<u n="255" who="S0018">but it is it's so similar <pause dur="short"/> I think sometimes it might be more difficult to learn a language that is similar to yours because you know it it comes so naturally to you</u>
<u n="256" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0018">to say something a certain way as if it's completely different <pause dur="short"/> maybe it's easier to remember <pause dur="short"/> but no when I I think I went to India about seven years after I'd started living in Spain?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="259" who="S0018">and I hung out with a couple of Italian people and I was surprised that I could understand pretty much everything that they were talking about</u>
<u n="260" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0018">because I spoke Spanish</u>
<u n="262" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0018">and I spoke Spanish to them they understood and they'd speak Italian back to me and and I'd understand</u>
<u n="264" who="S0170">and French helps as well if you've got French and Spanish then you can understand pretty much everything</u>
<u n="265" who="S0018">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="266" who="S0170">Cos there's a lot of crossover between them <pause dur="short"/> if it's not similar to Spanish then it's similar to French</u>
<u n="267" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but no saying that all the Erasmus students <pause dur="short"/> the em the ones who did <trunc>ha</trunc> get English friends they made fantastic progress but I remember we were living in in the first year with some I think they were Chinese maybe? Em and they just stayed together in their little social groups all the time and</u>
<u n="268" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0018">it was funny <pause dur="short"/> at six o'clock all the Chinese people would walk across the quad there was like em all the the accommodation was around <trunc>out</trunc> a grassy quad and they'd all be there carrying their woks and their their ingredients over to someone's <pause dur="short"/> they appointed someone's house every night to go and eat together in <pause dur="short"/> but they'd just stick together all the time and they didn't learn at all</u>
<u n="270" who="S0170">yeah that's like the <unclear/> students <pause dur="short"/> they're the ones we had in the summer isn't it?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I'm em friends on Facebook with quite a few of the students we had</u>
<u n="272" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="273" who="S0018">mm last summer not the ones from the summer before</u>
<u n="274" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="275" who="S0018">but and I thought because they were  they were  art students they were all doing oh you know from the eh mine were fashion and</u>
<u n="276" who="S0170">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> I had one fashion</u>
<u n="277" who="S0018">interior design <pause dur="short"/> and they I got the feeling that they'd make more of an effort to actually integrate and meet people and <trunc>s</trunc> communicate</u>
<u n="278" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="279" who="S0018">in English more than the students we'd had the years before who were doing business and stuff</u>
<u n="280" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0018">but</u>
<u n="282" who="S0170">it was hard over the summer though who who did they have to integrate</u>
<u n="283" who="S0018">but they haven't</u>
<u n="284" who="S0170">no</u>
<u n="285" who="S0018">they've all joined the Chinese church and all of their social activities revolve around the Chinese church</u>
<u n="286" who="S0170">really?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I think the only English they're getting is em at university</u>
<u n="288" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="289" who="S0018">they haven't you know made any English-speaking friends</u>
<u n="290" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0018">and all their status updates are in Chinese and it it's just such a shame cos</u>
<u n="292" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0018">I understand during the presessional course</u>
<u n="294" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="295" who="S0018">you know they stick together cos it's a new a totally different situation for them</u>
<u n="296" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0018">it would be comforting to to have you know Chinese around them but they</u>
<u n="298" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0018">it seems like they're doing it all the time <pause dur="short"/> it's a shame</u>
<u n="300" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there are a few people I mean there's I don't know if you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <trunc>they</trunc> they've em integrated well I think</u>
<u n="301" who="S0018">have they?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0170">they're they're coming on really well</u>
<u n="303" who="S0018">oh super</u>
<u n="304" who="S0170">they are but <trunc>the</trunc> they're Taiwanese and not Chinese</u>
<u n="305" who="S0018">ah <pause dur="short"/> yeah actually the Taiwanese students I heard they already had a better level of spoken English?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="307" who="S0018">their written ability wasn't great but do do they speak English</u>
<u n="308" who="S0170">yes</u>
<u n="309" who="S0018">more in Taiwan?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0170">they must do <pause dur="short"/> I don't know why why it was but they didn't need the visa did they? So maybe they're from</u>
<u n="311" who="S0018">eh <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="312" who="S0170">one or two had had been here before</u>
<u n="313" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="314" who="S0170">and maybe for like summer or something <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="315" who="S0018">and what are they doing? Are they em meeting up with their course mates and stuff and speaking English?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0170">yeah they're just like writing things on Facebook in English and they have they seem to have friends from other nationalities <pause dur="short"/> maybe not just English but maybe <trunc>Eras</trunc> I don't know if they were European students who are their friends and stuff <pause dur="short"/> that's encouraged them to use English</u>
<u n="317" who="S0018">that's good</u>
<u n="318" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0018">that's fantastic <pause dur="short"/> no I reckon when they do the presessional that they shouldn't all be put together in a hall of residence <pause dur="short"/> it's it kind of creates a ghetto doesn't it?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0018">and it sets them up with bad habits from the start <pause dur="short"/> I think if they  if they  had a home stay for the five or ten weeks and a presessional</u>
<u n="322" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="323" who="S0018">and actually integrated into life in a family and kinda got a bit more exposed to the culture and embraced living in a different country</u>
<u n="324" who="S0170" trans="overlap">yeah that's and and separate them when don't let them choose the same roommates for a whole year</u>
<u n="325" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0170">and get to separate and</u>
<u n="327" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0170">but the the people who have moved out it's like they were eh one <trunc>coup</trunc> they were one couple and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and another one <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> they've all <trunc>mo</trunc> they all moved out when they had that opportunity to move out</u>
<u n="329" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="330" who="S0170">and they they're the ones who are doing better</u>
<u n="331" who="S0018">yeah it's not surprising isn't it?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="333" who="S0018">that's the thing it was so difficult to improve their marks over the ten weeks of the course</u>
<u n="334" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="335" who="S0018">Cos you know</u>
<u n="336" who="S0170">you're just speaking with well just in the class with us but then</u>
<u n="337" who="S0018">and even then they weren't particularly forthcoming in speaking in English <pause dur="short"/> actually I I think by the end I think they've been trained to</u>
<u n="338" who="S0170">I'm pretty good for the first couple of weeks they spoke nothing but English</u>
<u n="339" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="340" who="S0170">and then it's slowly slid into</u>
<u n="341" who="S0018">as their social life <pause dur="short"/> because they didn't really know each other before did they? I think they became more socially em active with each other they started slipping into Chinese more <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I guess it's typical</u>
<u n="342" who="S0170">I don't know it is hard learning a language <pause dur="short"/> it's not an easy thing especially when you  when you when you  start when you're older <pause dur="short"/> I mean I I learnt French at school but I it was a large class of thirty or so students <pause dur="short"/> I didn't think I really knew French but I still remember some phrases but I I was definitely not fluent or anything in it</u>
<u n="343" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0170">and apart from that I've never studied a language and then I suddenly started Spanish</u>
<u n="345" who="S0018">but it must have been easier for you to learn a bit of Spanish because your brain was used to learning French?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0018">I think just the the skill of of being able to memorise words and spot patterns even if you can't speak it fluently it's definitely</u>
<u n="348" who="S0170">I don't know it's how how how easy it was to learn Italian</u>
<u n="349" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="350" who="S0170">not even just cos of the similarities but it was it just is easier the more you use that part of the brain</u>
<u n="351" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0170">I think it does get easier to <trunc>remem</trunc> remember words and everything</u>
<u n="353" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="354" who="S0170">but it was funny cos every time I wanted to think of a Spanish word I think of the Italian word</u>
<u n="355" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0170">or <pause dur="short"/> even now like I'm learning a bit of Polish and I'm trying to think of the Polish word I think of the Spanish word <pause dur="short"/> and it's like oh</u>
<u n="357" who="S0018">are you going to classes for Polish or?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0170">no <pause dur="short"/> I'm just trying to learn from home with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and his son</u>
<u n="359" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="360" who="S0170">his son's a better teacher than <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is</u>
<u n="361" who="S0018">was he brought up bilingual? His son?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0170">no no no no <pause dur="short"/> he just learned English since he's been here in eh in England</u>
<u n="363" who="S0018">oh really?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0170">but he came here when he was about three</u>
<u n="365" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="366" who="S0170">so yeah he's he speaks like Polish at home</u>
<u n="367" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="368" who="S0170">but at school he's speaking English and he laughs at his Dad</u>
<u n="369" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="370" who="S0170">I speak better English than you</u>
<u n="371" who="S0018">do he have a little accent when he speaks English?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0170">no <pause dur="short"/> he sounds like a Brummie</u>
<u n="373" who="S0018">oh really?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> crikey <pause dur="short"/> but he didn't start learning till he was three?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="377" who="S0018">I guess that's in that sensitive period for learning</u>
<u n="378" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="379" who="S0018">learning the accent and stuff</u>
<u n="380" who="S0170">mm <pause dur="short"/> but he can't he can of course Polish is his first language but he can't write in Polish</u>
<u n="381" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="382" who="S0170">he can write in English <pause dur="short"/> he was sending messages to his em his aunty and I said why are you writing messages to her in English? I said eh are you not going to write it in Polish? And he <trunc>j</trunc> tried and he couldn't spell the words</u>
<u n="383" who="S0018">oh <pause dur="short"/> is it phonetic?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0170">it is <pause dur="short"/> but there are a few sounds that em you have to learn <pause dur="short"/> majority of it is is phonetic but there are like the shhh chhh chhh</u>
<u n="385" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="386" who="S0170">kind of sounds that you have to learn those</u>
<u n="387" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="388" who="S0170">it's the same in English isn't it when they learn phonetically there were certain sounds you just have to to learn</u>
<u n="389" who="S0018">does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> help you? Do you speak a bit of Polish when you're together?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0170">not really <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> she's surprised at times when I'm with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and she's like oh you <trunc>und</trunc> you understand <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>a</trunc> again I understand</u>
<u n="391" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="392" who="S0170">more but I can say a a little bit</u>
<u n="393" who="S0018">is it similar to Spanish at all?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0170">no</u>
<u n="395" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="396" who="S0170">oh there's one thing  is the same and <trunc>play</trunc> playa is plaga</u>
<u n="397" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="398" who="S0170">in Polish is plaga</u>
<u n="399" who="S0018">what are the roots of the Polish language then are they similar to German or?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0170">it's like Slavic language</u>
<u n="401" who="S0018">eh okay</u>
<u n="402" who="S0170">there's no similarity to German</u>
<u n="403" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="404" who="S0170">there's a few Latin words in there</u>
<u n="405" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="406" who="S0170">but eh no it's mainly Slavic</u>
<u n="407" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="408" who="S0170">then it's like it's just like shhh khhh shhhhk and lots of like those kind of sounds</u>
<u n="409" who="S0018">that's like Czech</u>
<u n="410" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0018">probably</u>
<u n="412" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0018">I lived in Prague for a couple of months eh doing the teacher training</u>
<u n="414" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="415" who="S0018">and oh it was so difficult to learn pick up words just cos there's they seem so alien</u>
<u n="416" who="S0170">I know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says <unclear/> I think I'm saying it how he said it to me and he says like no no no and he keeps saying it <pause dur="short"/> I'm like I'm saying it like that <pause dur="short"/> he said you're not <pause dur="short"/> it's like a because you know like <foreign lang="pol"/> is like thank you but you just say it <foreign lang="pol"/> and then one is little pig</u>
<u n="417" who="S0018">no</u>
<u n="418" who="S0170">and one is thank you <pause dur="short"/> careful when you say that little pig little pig</u>
<u n="419" who="S0018">that's like Chinese though isn't em cos it's tonal <pause dur="short"/> if you say  If you say  one word with a certain intonation it means god and if you say it with a different intonation it means I don't know I can't remember if it's eleven or something like that <pause dur="short"/> hello <vocal desc="laugh"/>Yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I'll be learning any more languages</u>
<u n="420" who="S0170">no <pause dur="short"/> I'd like to if I go somewhere to learn a few words so I could just be polite</u>
<u n="421" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="422" who="S0170">but to learn a whole new language <pause dur="short"/> I might I think I'll learn Polish because I'll want to understand when he's speaking with his dad and</u>
<u n="423" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0170">even if I just understand it rather than speak it</u>
<u n="425" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0170">and with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s family cos they're coming over at Easter</u>
<u n="427" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="428" who="S0170">and when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s not there</u>
<u n="429" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="430" who="S0170">he was at work the last time they came and I ended up like saying something really embarrassing <pause dur="short"/> yeah cos I think I told you <trunc>w</trunc> well I said this when I was with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> I said like little <foreign lang="pol"/></u>
<u n="431" who="S0018">oh yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0170"><foreign lang="pol"/> Come come and eh but in hodge podge in in Polish and it's like how you would speak to a child child <pause dur="short"/> a little little baby</u>
<u n="433" who="S0018">I'm sure he found it endearing as opposed to insulting though</u>
<u n="434" who="S0170">yeah things like that I'd I'd like to be able to just communicate a little bit with his family</u>
<u n="435" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="436" who="S0170">Cos I know on Skype it's like I just say hello how are you <foreign lang="pol"/> and that's about it really</u>
<u n="437" who="S0018">but you understand more or less the the thread of the conversation when they're speaking?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0170">yeah cos there are words that I understand now like I know work I know car I know airplane I know  I know  words</u>
<u n="439" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="440" who="S0170">but their grammar is so hard</u>
<u n="441" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0018">does it have a lot of tenses or is it?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0170">it's em not tenses <pause dur="short"/> I forgot what they call it when it's one word em it's a  it's a  verb like in Spanish where you change it fully to the person</u>
<u n="445" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="446" who="S0170">like <foreign lang="pol"/> and depending on I am you are</u>
<u n="447" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="448" who="S0170">there's those things <pause dur="short"/> but also you change it depending accusative</u>
<u n="449" who="S0018">oh the cases</u>
<u n="450" who="S0170">yeah the case that's it the cases</u>
<u n="451" who="S0018">is that called declining or something? Declining the verb <pause dur="short"/> oh I yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos I studied Latin for a year</u>
<u n="452" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="453" who="S0018">at school and remember</u>
<u n="454" who="S0170">it's that sort of cases <pause dur="short"/> god</u>
<u n="455" who="S0018">oh really? Nightmare</u>
<u n="456" who="S0170">there are eight cases</u>
<u n="457" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="458" who="S0170">so it changes <pause dur="short"/> cos I know like I'm sure he said something about <trunc>wor</trunc> work cos it's <foreign lang="pol"/> and it's <foreign lang="pol"/> and so I'm knowing it's about work but I'm not sure who it's talking about his work or their work or</u>
<u n="459" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0170">I don't know the endings of the verbs and that</u>
<u n="461" who="S0018">that's so complicated <pause dur="short"/> so does every different conjugation in every different tense have eight possibilities depending on the case?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0018">but that just makes</u>
<u n="464" who="S0170">what is it German has eight cases and this one has seven</u>
<u n="465" who="S0018">for a lot <pause dur="short"/> but still that's a lot a mighty load of endings to remember</u>
<u n="466" who="S0170">it is <pause dur="short"/> cos like I'll say like em <trunc>l</trunc> little <pause dur="short"/> but that you in Spanish like <foreign lang="pol"/> or <foreign lang="pol"/> depending on male or masculine or feminine</u>
<u n="467" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="468" who="S0170">and then he says something else and it's like well why have you changed it for that?</u>
<u n="469" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0018">yeah I remember the I I didn't  I didn't  even get my head around the concepts of the different cases <pause dur="short"/> I think when I was I think I was only twelve when I'd studied Latin</u>
<u n="471" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="472" who="S0018">but is it stuff like genitive accusative dative?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0170">mm hm <pause dur="short"/> yeah those things <pause dur="short"/> I mean I don't even I don't understand it totally</u>
<u n="474" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="475" who="S0170">so I like trying to learn it <pause dur="short"/> it would be really hard</u>
<u n="476" who="S0018">have you a teach yourself book?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0170">I <trunc>ha</trunc> there is <pause dur="short"/> I have got a work book and a textbook <pause dur="short"/> I think I need help with it I don't think</u>
<u n="478" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="479" who="S0170">it's all in em Polish so I just <pause dur="short"/> and I don't want like learning a language like that</u>
<u n="480" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="481" who="S0170">either</u>
<u n="482" who="S0018">but you might find because you're hearing a lot of it em if you get a a teach yourself book and just start to become aware of all the different endings and all the different you know pick up some more vocabulary <pause dur="short"/> maybe you'll start thinking when you <trunc>he</trunc> listening to eh huh that would be that word</u>
<u n="483" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0018">with that ending</u>
<u n="485" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think I'll learn better I think I'm an oral learner rather than a</u>
<u n="486" who="S0018">uh-huh <pause dur="short"/> ah no I'm a visual learner <pause dur="short"/> I need to see it written down before I <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0170" trans="overlap">are you? No that's not how I learn best I think watching films in Spanish and being in the classroom just listening  just listening</u>
<u n="488" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="489" who="S0170">it helped me a lot</u>
<u n="490" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I remember a phase that that I went through I think it was about three months after I I <trunc>st</trunc> I lived in Spain? Em and I could <trunc>ju</trunc> I could just put together sentences and express pretty much a lot of basic things and have conversations socially</u>
<u n="491" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="492" who="S0018">but because I could put together a sentence quite easily em then people would think oh she speaks Spanish they'd just go brrrrr back <pause dur="short"/> so I developed this em defence mechanism of just not letting other people reply just speaking speaking speaking and not giving them a little space to <trunc>re</trunc> respond <vocal desc="laugh"/> Cos as soon as they'll something and I'll be like I don't know what you've just said sorry <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and when you've learnt it you've learnt you say this then they say that then you say this and then they say that and then you say it and they say something completely different and it's like em</u>
<u n="494" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0018">one tiny word can throw you <pause dur="short"/> no I em before I went to Spain I I got a BBC teach yourself Spanish book</u>
<u n="496" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="497" who="S0018">and it was it wasn't it was all communicative in that every at the beginning of every chapter there was a little dialogue</u>
<u n="498" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="499" who="S0018">and then afterwards it picked apart of the dialogue in terms of vocabulary and the different little grammar bits that we use but as chunks not</u>
<u n="500" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0018">okay we're gonna learn the present tense <pause dur="short"/> no it was what was used in that dialogue</u>
<u n="502" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0018">was explained <pause dur="short"/> and I thought that was a fantastic way of of learning <pause dur="short"/> it helped me a lot</u>
<u n="504" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0018">to to be able to recognise a lot of speech <pause dur="short"/> obviously producing it was more difficult after but</u>
<u n="506" who="S0170">mm <pause dur="short"/> I remember being in in Spain somebody coming up to me and I'm thinking I understand what they're saying but they're not speaking <event desc="sound of sneezing"/></u>
<u n="507" who="S0018">oh bless you</u>
<u n="508" who="S0170">bless you <pause dur="short"/> they're not speaking Spanish to me and then I realise they were Italian</u>
<u n="509" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="510" who="S0170">and I didn't see it and I was studying Italian at the time and that was really bizarre because I don't <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know what to reply <pause dur="short"/> I understood what they'd asked me but I wasn't sure how to reply cos I like that's not Spanish but for a second I was a bit frightened that someone has come up to me in Spain and spoke to me not in Spanish but just in Italian and I was a bit confused</u>
<u n="511" who="S0018"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I had that when I went to em I went to em I went to Monaco with eh two Spanish friends and an English friend and I was the only one who spoke French <pause dur="short"/> and the two Spanish friends didn't speak much English</u>
<u n="512" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="513" who="S0018">so we were  we were  pretty much operating in Spanish apart from me and the English girl we were talking English to each other</u>
<u n="514" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0018">but everything any kind of interaction with the French world had to come through me <pause dur="short"/> so she'd say it to me in English and I had to translate and then the Spanish guys would speak to me in Spanish and I had to translate that into French and there was a moment when just my head and exploding <pause dur="short"/> especially because it was culturally as well I was interpreting <pause dur="short"/> because em the two guys from eh Murcia they we were at breakfast and they wanted to order toast with tomato on</u>
<u n="516" who="S0170">oh no</u>
<u n="517" who="S0018">I said yeah but look in <trunc>Fr</trunc> we're in France you can have croissant you can have pain au chocolat you can have anything sweet and pastry like but toast with tomato on is not part of their culture <pause dur="short"/> hello what do you mean? Everyone's got toast <pause dur="short"/> surely they've got some tomatoes <pause dur="short"/> I was like they don't know how to do it</u>
<u n="518" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="519" who="S0170"><foreign lang="spa"/></u>
<u n="520" who="S0018">then again I remember in the first month I think I was in Spain I ordered toast with tomato on and I thought it was gonna come in slices of tomato and when it came with just yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0170">like the tomato paste on</u>
<u n="522" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos they just squeeze out the juice and grate a bit of the flesh into it</u>
<u n="523" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="524" who="S0018">and add olive oil and I was like where is the tomato? I ordered tomatoes and they were like it's there on it and I felt very put out</u>
<u n="525" who="S0170"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I remember ordering tea with milk <pause dur="short"/> just getting a <trunc>h</trunc> a cup of hot milk with a tea bag in it</u>
<u n="526" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="527" who="S0170">so I had to soon learn to say can I have eh tea with milk separate</u>
<u n="528" who="S0018">cold milk on the side <pause dur="short"/><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="529" who="S0170">yes my friend was laughing she was <trunc>I</trunc> she was Italian she was laughing at me <pause dur="short"/> another Italian girl I my friend and we went we travelled round a little bit <pause dur="short"/> and she just laughed at me because of my face when I was given this tea with milk with a tea bag in it <pause dur="short"/> I was so disappointed cos I like my tea in the morning <pause dur="short"/> I could cope with coffee I don't mind <pause dur="short"/> it was such strong coffee wasn't it?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0018">yeah no I always had em decaf in a sachet</u>
<u n="531" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="532" who="S0018">and just a cup of hot milk and I'd just sprinkle a bit of decaf coffee and <pause dur="short"/> cos yeah they make it so strong</u>
<u n="533" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0018">then again when I was in France I used to have em le petit noir like a tiny little cup of really intense coffee <pause dur="short"/> and when I was like eighteen nineteen I could quite happily drink three or four a day but when I don't know what when I was about twenty-one twenty-two I just developed this complete my body couldn't take caffeine <pause dur="short"/> I think maybe I'd drunk too much in France <pause dur="short"/> em yeah it was just ah</u>
<u n="535" who="S0170">I'm the same I never used to like coffee and then I worked in eh Costa Coffee and having it there I just tried it a few times and actually that's it's alright <pause dur="short"/> now I like to drink a lot of it and have a café au lait <pause dur="short"/> with a croissant <pause dur="short"/> ooh yes</u>
<u n="536" who="S0018">yum yum yum yum <pause dur="short"/> yeah I hated olives before I went to Spain and then it was cos when you visit people's houses they always want to give you things to eat and drink and you know it's from their  from their  earth <pause dur="short"/> olives <pause dur="short"/> how can you not like olives? It used to be like a personal insult so I'd have to eat olives and then I actually developed quite a taste for them which is good cos they're nice and healthy</u>
<u n="537" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="538" who="S0018">but I never managed to develop a taste for seafood</u>
<u n="539" who="S0170">oh it does <pause dur="short"/> oh I love it <pause dur="short"/> oh octopus</u>
<u n="540" who="S0018">urgh</u>
<u n="541" who="S0170">calamari <pause dur="short"/> oh I love it love it love it</u>
<u n="542" who="S0018">disgusting</u>
<u n="543" who="S0170">I remember eh ordering some I was like I didn't recognise anything on the menu <pause dur="short"/> everywhere you go it different dishes and different parts and you don't know what it doesn't say what was in each just the name of the dish <pause dur="short"/> so I was I wanted seafood it was my birthday and I want seafood I'm gonna treat myself</u>
<u n="544" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="545" who="S0170">and I got this whole big it looked like a round squid <pause dur="short"/> a whole one and everyone was looking at me cos he said it's like calamari</u>
<u n="546" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="547" who="S0170">cos I said what is  what is  that? Like and he was explaining and what's that like and he was explaining and that one is like calamari <pause dur="short"/> I though okay that's the one then</u>
<u n="548" who="S0018">are those the little small rings?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="550" who="S0018">they <trunc>l</trunc> look like onion rings?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="552" who="S0018">they do those well in Granada don't they?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0170">mm and you have them sometimes with free with the as tapas part of the</u>
<u n="554" who="S0018">eh the first time I visited Granada we arrived at the the bus station I think?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0018">and got off the bus after a five hour rather worrying trip around all these very thin country roads on a mountain and worried that the bus was going to drop off so we went straight to the bar when we got off the bus and I just ordered a little beer <pause dur="short"/> and it came with like a a ham sandwich</u>
<u n="557" who="S0170">oh yeah</u>
<u n="558" who="S0018">and I was like no we didn't ask for that no it's alright it's free eat it <pause dur="short"/> yey</u>
<u n="559" who="S0170">that's great <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> That's why I'm thinking my my other half will love it in Granada <pause dur="short"/> you just you order a drink and gain food <pause dur="short"/> my dad actually got to the point where he said eh how do you ask he phoned me up not bring <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Cos he my dad was great like that he'd just go off and go to places by himself and try and speak a little bit of the language <pause dur="short"/> cos I went to uni and em I phoned him oh dad I've finished where are you? I'm in the hairdresser <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="560" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="561" who="S0170">he went to have his hair cut I mean not many people would go and do that would they? If you don't speak the language <pause dur="short"/> and just I was okay I took my guide book with me and just you know tried to say the sentence <pause dur="short"/> you know short back and sides</u>
<u n="562" who="S0018">my mum's quite my mum's the same but my dad is completely not <pause dur="short"/> I remember we were in this em we were in Majorca I went over to visited them when they were on holiday there <pause dur="short"/> and we'd stopped off at a little restaurant on the motorway <pause dur="short"/> so it wasn't even like a little restaurant for tourists it was for truckers and they probably didn't even speak Spanish cos it was all Majorcan Catalan</u>
<u n="563" who="S0170">uh-huh</u>
<u n="564" who="S0018">and there's my dad in the middle of the restaurant <pause dur="short"/> Eh excuse me excuse <trunc>m</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> Dad shhh I can translate for you? And everyone's like looking around who is that linguistic imperialist over there who will only speak English? But my mum well she came over to Murcia when we just got a cat and the cat was a bit ill <pause dur="short"/> em so while I was at work she'd gone to the chemists</u>
<u n="565" who="S0170">eh hm</u>
<u n="566" who="S0018">with no Spanish whatsoever <pause dur="short"/> she wanted to get some ointment for the cat's eye</u>
<u n="567" who="S0170">uh-huh</u>
<u n="568" who="S0018">and she managed to communicate to the the chemist em that she needed ointment for the eye and then she said em it's for a cat meow meow <pause dur="short"/> so she was just standing there going meow meow at them <vocal desc="laugh"/> And they must have thought what? In the end they realised that she was asking for medicine for a cat <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="569" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0170">yeah it is funny</u>
<u n="571" who="S0018">crazy <pause dur="short"/> crazy <pause dur="short"/> crazy <pause dur="short"/> crazy <pause dur="short"/> I found it <pause dur="short"/> did you have a nice lunch <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? Has he eaten well?</u>
<u n="572" who="S0170">yeah he has actually <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so that's good <pause dur="short"/> so he doesn't seem too bad today with the injections he <pause dur="short"/> I think get in there with Calpol early</u>
<u n="573" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0170">it seems to stop the em the symptoms</u>
<u n="575" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> did they say that he might have some specific symptoms?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0170">yeah they say for a few of the injections especially the ones with a live em virus</u>
<u n="577" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="578" who="S0170">that he can <pause dur="short"/> I mean the MMR thing that's why it was so controversial is that they can have</u>
<u n="579" who="S0018">is that the super bug thing?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0170">no it's the eh mumps measles and rubella</u>
<u n="581" who="S0018">oh okay</u>
<u n="582" who="S0170">and the injection having it all together em he can have the <pause dur="short"/> well he might never have he he might never get the the any of those things</u>
<u n="583" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="584" who="S0170">but if em he has the injection he could possibly get one of the you know like mumps or something</u>
<u n="585" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="586" who="S0170">and he could be really ill and even have em convulsions</u>
<u n="587" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="588" who="S0170">I mean it's a one in so many one in a million that it could happen to</u>
<u n="589" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="590" who="S0170">but there is a small chance that it is just as dangerous as him getting the actual disease</u>
<u n="591" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="592" who="S0170">I mean he's <unclear/> but you've just got to take all of these things to consideration</u>
<u n="593" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="594" who="S0170">I think that's the most that was the most dangerous one</u>
<u n="595" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="596" who="S0170">the MMR one <pause dur="short"/> that's why some people choose not to give it to their children</u>
<u n="597" who="S0018">right</u>
<u n="598" who="S0170">Cos it can cause problems if their their brain can swell and cause brain damage and things like that <pause dur="short"/> I've read about</u>
<u n="599" who="S0018">lordy</u>
<u n="600" who="S0170">and it must be horrible if and autism as well</u>
<u n="601" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="602" who="S0170">so it must be terrible if you do give your child the injection and you know and he was one of the ones that</u>
<u n="603" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="604" who="S0170">did have autism <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="605" who="S0018">do you need a towel or something?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0170">I</u>
<u n="607" who="S0018">where's your bag? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> which one? This one?</u>
<u n="608" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="609" who="S0018">that's the one <pause dur="short"/> what are we looking for? Baby wipes</u>
<u n="610" who="S0170">mm no we got like a little muslin cloth <pause dur="short"/> muslin</u>
<u n="611" who="S0018">let's see <pause dur="short"/> oh here it is <pause dur="short"/> oh no no that's a baby wipe</u>
<u n="612" who="S0170" trans="overlap">oh that's a wipe I'll use a wipe</u>
<u n="613" who="S0018">oh gosh sorry</u>
<u n="614" who="S0170">no it's okay <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Maybe I've left it in the car <pause dur="short"/> eeh <pause dur="short"/> a baby wipe will do <pause dur="short"/> ooh dear</u>
<u n="615" who="S0018">no he seems fine</u>
<u n="616" who="S0170">he does</u>
<u n="617" who="S0018">survived his traumatic experience <pause dur="short"/> how many times did they inject him?</u>
<u n="618" who="S0170">twice in one leg and once on other</u>
<u n="619" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="620" who="S0170">like that leg and chht that one</u>
<u n="621" who="S0018">did he  Did he  scream every time they did it?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0170">he was smiling at the nurse and then suddenly she like chhk and he was waaaaaa not a little <trunc>ru</trunc> not a little eh grumble it was a real what have you do to me? What have you done I thought you looked nice <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="623" who="S0018">how dare you? You were smiling at me and then you hurt me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="624" who="S0170">but I I did before I held him like this way and looking at him and I'm thinking well maybe he thinks it's me</u>
<u n="625" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="626" who="S0018">yeah face the nurse face the nurse</u>
<u n="627" who="S0170">it's her she did it</u>
<u n="628" who="S0018">aw <pause dur="short"/> and does he usually sleep after a feed or?</u>
<u n="629" who="S0170">sometimes</u>
<u n="630" who="S0018">does he get like energetic?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0170">it's because he's somewhere new and em he seems to be quite like oh what's that what's that? And he gets excited <pause dur="short"/> but when I was with Camilla and em the lady <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and he just he was sitting like this and he just went bumm <pause dur="short"/> he he'd stopped himself sleeping for so long he fight he'd fought it for so long then he em he was just bumm but he doesn't do that very much <pause dur="short"/> usually I have to feed him to sleep or rock him to sleep or something <pause dur="short"/> but he'll get tired he'll just go</u>
<u n="632" who="S0018">do you notice does do babies normally get burped after a feed?</u>
<u n="633" who="S0170">with breastfeeding not so much no</u>
<u n="634" who="S0018">eh okay</u>
<u n="635" who="S0170">it's not like with bottles where they can get a lot of air</u>
<u n="636" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="637" who="S0170">breastfeeding they tend to not need it so much <pause dur="short"/> you can just sit him up like that and being upright it will tend to</u>
<u n="638" who="S0018">it will come out</u>
<u n="639" who="S0170">come out yeah <pause dur="short"/> need out</u>
<u n="640" who="S0018">burpy burp burp</u>
<u n="641" who="S0170">yeah he's not really a windy baby are you? Cos some some babies have it worse and they just need every stop burped stop burped</u>
<u n="642" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="643" who="S0170">but with bottles it's a lot worse</u>
<u n="644" who="S0018">I guess you get a lot more air going in don't you?</u>
<u n="645" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="646" who="S0018">he seems so placid though</u>
<u n="647" who="S0170">he is</u>
<u n="648" who="S0018">how does he compare to the babies of the other mums that you know?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0170">em one or two like they can be a bit manic <pause dur="short"/> but I'm alright <pause dur="short"/> em <pause dur="short"/> but he's alright until he gets hungry or tired and then he'll be a little bit waaaa</u>
<u n="650" who="S0018">do you recognise what he <trunc>w</trunc> well if he's crying to do recognise what kind of cry it is?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I try now I think to I think well now he must be getting hungry he will get hungry soon <pause dur="short"/> so I feed him now just before he gets to that stage and then he kind of does less crying so <pause dur="short"/> I just sort of</u>
<u n="652" who="S0018">and if he's in pain? Just can you tell?</u>
<u n="653" who="S0170">yeah because you can't stop him crying with a toy or something</u>
<u n="654" who="S0018">ah</u>
<u n="655" who="S0170">so I just know it if you can't console him then must be something wrong <pause dur="short"/> and he had that once with the second injection and he was just inconsolable</u>
<u n="656" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="657" who="S0170">I just had to carry him around in a <trunc>sl</trunc> in a sling just with me and I took him to the chemist like it was about mm seven o'clock at night in the winter and so it was quite cold and dark and just had him in my sling running up to the chemist what can I do? He's not stopped crying for two hours</u>
<u n="658" who="S0018">oh no</u>
<u n="659" who="S0170">they said Calpol <pause dur="short"/> it is it's wonderful wonderful stuff isn't it? Magic Calpol <pause dur="short"/> I don't like to give him too many medicines and stuff</u>
<u n="660" who="S0018">no <pause dur="short"/> but I mean if it's going to stop him suffering so much <pause dur="short"/> it's not gin is it?</u>
<u n="661" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="662" who="S0170">no</u>
<u n="663" who="S0018">that's what they use to dose up the babies in Victorian times <pause dur="short"/> stop and give it a whiskey bit of gin <pause dur="short"/> and does he he sleep through the night well?</u>
<u n="664" who="S0170">no because he's breastfeeding <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>you</trunc> They digest it really quickly</u>
<u n="665" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="666" who="S0170">and they don't last as long cos em bottle fed babies <pause dur="short"/> bottle fed babies can be very placid because it's like what was it a nurse said</u>
<u n="667" who="S0018">do you want me to pull the curtain over?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0170">it's like <pause dur="short"/> what's ah that's better</u>
<u n="669" who="S0018">there you go</u>
<u n="670" who="S0170">it's like giving them a a Sunday dinner</u>
<u n="671" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="672" who="S0170">every time you feed them whereas breastfeeding they take how much they want <pause dur="short"/> if they want a drink if they want a snack if they want a three course meal <pause dur="short"/> they choose and they take what they need and with a bottle you just kind of fill them up cos it says you know you've got to be seven ounces so go go come on you've got to be seven ounces <pause dur="short"/> so you you you know sometimes you fill them up too much</u>
<u n="673" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="674" who="S0170">and then they're em very quiet and that's why and it takes a while to digest it</u>
<u n="675" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="676" who="S0170">but with breast milk it can be digested within when they're younger an hour and they're hungry again <pause dur="short"/> so but their stomachs are like so small that they can't take very much</u>
<u n="677" who="S0018">how many times do you have to get up in the night to feed him?</u>
<u n="678" who="S0170">last night was a bad night <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="679" who="S0018">oh dear</u>
<u n="680" who="S0170">we woke up quite a few times didn't we? But the night before he slept all the way through</u>
<u n="681" who="S0018">how bizarre</u>
<u n="682" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="683" who="S0018">very weird <pause dur="short"/> does he sleep eh in the same room as you at the moment?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0170">yeah he does sometimes sleeps in bed with me <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="685" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="686" who="S0170">especially when he's waking up so often <pause dur="short"/> cos it's just easier to feed him</u>
<u n="687" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="688" who="S0170">and then go back straight to sleep again</u>
<u n="689" who="S0018">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="690" who="S0170">so I can get up get him out and</u>
<u n="691" who="S0018">do you find it quite easy to get back to sleep after?</u>
<u n="692" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm getting very good at it <pause dur="short"/> I didn't I use to really bad at <pause dur="short"/> if someone disturbed me it would make me crazy and I couldn't get back to sleep for ages now <pause dur="short"/> I don't sometimes I don't even know I've woken I I remember it a little bit I'm sure I fed him cos he's in bed with me</u>
<u n="693" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="694" who="S0170">Cos I put him to sleep in his bed</u>
<u n="695" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="696" who="S0170">and then he wakes up a few times and he'll end up staying with me <pause dur="short"/> so he's in the bed with me but I don't remember really <pause dur="short"/> it's like half? Half asleep feeding sometimes</u>
<u n="697" who="S0018">then again I guess I believe we've got in built mechanisms to cope with that no?</u>
<u n="698" who="S0170">yeah you just get you get used to it</u>
<u n="699" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="700" who="S0170">you don't probably wake up like half asleep feeding and then it's easier to get back to sleep <pause dur="short"/> if you wake up that's it then</u>
<u n="701" who="S0018">is does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wake up as well?</u>
<u n="702" who="S0170">sometimes <pause dur="short"/> but I try and get him like he cos he'll be  he'll be  like this he'll be moving and you can hear him moving and I think I'm not even deep sleeping cos I wake up</u>
<u n="703" who="S0018">mm</u>
<u n="704" who="S0170">when I just hear him moving</u>
<u n="705" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="706" who="S0170">aha here's the time for food <pause dur="short"/> I just get to him before he he gets to crying stage</u>
<u n="707" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="708" who="S0170">because then that crying stage is harder to</u>
<u n="709" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="710" who="S0170">calm them down and</u>
<u n="711" who="S0018">and when he starts drinking bottles are you gonna share the getting up in the middle of the night?</u>
<u n="712" who="S0170">oh yes definitely <pause dur="short"/> at weekends</u>
<u n="713" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="714" who="S0018">you're like right I've carried him for nine months and I've got  I've got  up to breastfeed him for six months and it's your turn</u>
<u n="715" who="S0170">well I tend to with definitely with nappies and stuff and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does bathing doesn't he? It's daddy time <pause dur="short"/> so he can have time to bond with him and Daddy baths you</u>
<u n="716" who="S0018">oh</u>
<u n="717" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> except when he's on late shift <pause dur="short"/> and then there's time they have together and <pause dur="short"/> at first he was just he always I would give him to him and he started crying <pause dur="short"/> so he always wanted me but now he's really good he's really good with him</u>
<u n="718" who="S0018">Good</u>
<u n="719" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can't imagine being with someone who refused to change nappies or anything <pause dur="short"/> welI I don't know if I would be I wouldn't</u>
<u n="720" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="721" who="S0170">having a kid with someone who refused to change any nappies or do anything</u>
<u n="722" who="S0018">is he working week during the week or at weekends too?</u>
<u n="723" who="S0170">yeah no he sometimes does an extra for the weekend cos I'm not getting very much at the moment so he's going to take <pause dur="short"/> ooh you know in the other bag there's a blue blue cloth</u>
<u n="724" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="725" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0018">and what's his late shift timetable like?</u>
<u n="727" who="S0170">late's two till ten and it's that one week six till two <pause dur="short"/> one week two till ten so</u>
<u n="728" who="S0018">oh he's spat it out again <pause dur="short"/> well at least he gets to spend time with him in the morning no then?</u>
<u n="729" who="S0170">yeah well I mean like</u>
<u n="730" who="S0018">can you get a lie in?</u>
<u n="731" who="S0170">sometimes yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah but <pause dur="short"/> then he tries to get his things done doesn't he in the morning sometimes so</u>
<u n="732" who="S0018">so are you going to work over the summer? Do you think?</u>
<u n="733" who="S0170">yeah well I'm gonna have to work but I'm getting some maternity allowance until end of May</u>
<u n="734" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="735" who="S0170">in the first week of June</u>
<u n="736" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="737" who="S0170">so I'm I'm now looking for something <pause dur="short"/> either I'm probably gonna start before the end of maternity allowance</u>
<u n="738" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="739" who="S0170">so I'm earning some proper money</u>
<u n="740" who="S0018">what about the Chinese students? Are you going to do that again?</u>
<u n="741" who="S0170">I think I'll send a message to see but <trunc>na</trunc> there's nothing nice about em where am I gonna  where am I gonna  put him?</u>
<u n="742" who="S0018">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> you were talking last time they have a childcare at the university though don't they?</u>
<u n="743" who="S0170">yeah they do <pause dur="short"/> I mean I can ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about that</u>
<u n="744" who="S0018">it was funny I think after was it before I spoke to you or after I spoke to you? I saw an article in the newspaper about in Denmark <pause dur="short"/> how the government pays for childcare</u>
<u n="745" who="S0170">do they?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0018">and how much easier it makes going back to work after</u>
<u n="747" who="S0170">well it would I mean even if it was just like partly subsidized or something I don't mind paying but when it's like three hundred pound a week <pause dur="short"/> three hundred pound no it's not three hundred pound a week <pause dur="short"/> some places it's about fifty pound a day</u>
<u n="748" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's horrendous isn't it?</u>
<u n="749" who="S0170">but weekly then maybe two hundred <pause dur="short"/> one fifty to two hundred and unless you're earning a pretty decent wage that's the fair whack of it isn't it?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="751" who="S0170">and then you just feel like but I want to to to <trunc>p</trunc> put him somewhere <pause dur="short"/> I don't want to just warehouse him <pause dur="short"/> cos it my sister said she's in em social policy warehousing or greenhousing? I don't want to just stick him somewhere where it's just he's there and so I've got somewhere for him I want him to be somewhere where they can help him develop and</u>
<u n="752" who="S0018">what about  What about  Polish grandma? Does she not fancy coming over for?</u>
<u n="753" who="S0170">no <pause dur="short"/> she's working over there</u>
<u n="754" who="S0018">really?</u>
<u n="755" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="756" who="S0018">still works?</u>
<u n="757" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="758" who="S0018">yeah well the course this year this summer is either ten weeks or six weeks <pause dur="short"/> they're not doing a five week course</u>
<u n="759" who="S0170">oh</u>
<u n="760" who="S0018">it's six weeks this year <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="761" who="S0170">I mean no I'd like to I mean I have to I meant to already do this but I forget things</u>
<u n="762" who="S0018">mummy brain</u>
<u n="763" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I need to send an email to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> five would be nice</u>
<u n="764" who="S0018">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> that would be good</u>
<u n="765" who="S0170">didn't he say something to you about going to China or to?</u>
<u n="766" who="S0018">yeah well apparently em <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s going to Taiwan <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did you meet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="767" who="S0170">sounds <trunc>f</trunc> her name sounds familiar</u>
<u n="768" who="S0018">em I think they were working at the other campus but em</u>
<u n="769" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="770" who="S0018">em <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s going to Thailand and was there a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well?</u>
<u n="771" who="S0170">yes <pause dur="short"/> there was yeah</u>
<u n="772" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> him and another girl I can't remember her name they're going to China to two different universities but em I think demand was less than they had expected <pause dur="short"/> so Steve's only sending one person to each university</u>
<u n="773" who="S0170">oh okay</u>
<u n="774" who="S0018">and I'd ask I asked him to put my name on the list but I think I was other people had asked him before</u>
<u n="775" who="S0170">oh right okay</u>
<u n="776" who="S0018">em so I've not been contacted about that but to be honest if it's to go somewhere alone</u>
<u n="777" who="S0170">mm <pause dur="short"/> you don't really fancy it</u>
<u n="778" who="S0018">I'd do it cos it's good money but it's I mean you've got to deal with the course over there</u>
<u n="779" who="S0170">mm hm</u>
<u n="780" who="S0018">is completely generated by you</u>
<u n="781" who="S0170">oh okay</u>
<u n="782" who="S0018">there's no guidelines no materials no access to photocopiers</u>
<u n="783" who="S0170">oh my god</u>
<u n="784" who="S0018">if you're in China most of the websites that you use like</u>
<u n="785" who="S0170">are blocked</u>
<u n="786" who="S0018">are blocked <pause dur="short"/> em so it's it would be such eh an intense difficult working environment <pause dur="short"/> in a foreign country where you don't speak the language</u>
<u n="787" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="788" who="S0018">I'm quite happy not to do it in a way <vocal desc="laugh"/> If it was offered to me I'd take it and I'd take the challenge but if there aren't enough students well I'm not going to get too upset about it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="789" who="S0170">I'd go to Hong Kong cos I've got a friend there but that's about it really <pause dur="short"/> I I'd love to got to Hong Kong <pause dur="short"/> take me to see my friend</u>
<u n="790" who="S0018">that would be so cool <pause dur="short"/> even Taiwan <pause dur="short"/> taiwan would be</u>
<u n="791" who="S0170">yeah</u>
<u n="792" who="S0018">good <pause dur="short"/> cos it seems a bit better organised in the uni there <pause dur="short"/> but no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is going to Thailand and she's just like there's <trunc>noth</trunc> I've got to train the teachers there as well how to teach</u>
<u n="793" who="S0170">really?</u>
<u n="794" who="S0018">academic English and</u>
<u n="795" who="S0170">she's going to Thailand</u>
<u n="796" who="S0018">I know <pause dur="short"/> but apparently they haven't got any rooms set up yet <pause dur="short"/> she hasn't got accommodation organised <pause dur="short"/> I think it's going to be typical organisation eh em I lack of organisation and</u>
<u n="797" who="S0170">how did people get in these in managerial jobs if they can't organise?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0018">I know <pause dur="short"/> it's</u>
<u n="799" who="S0170">it's terrible</u>
<u n="800" who="S0018">crazy but</u>
<u n="801" who="S0170">I had a really good boss at the one college <pause dur="short"/> she was <trunc>sh</trunc> she's organised to a fault you know she organises within an inch of her life you know and then</u>
<u n="802" who="S0018">contingency plans and everything</u>
<u n="803" who="S0170">there's another <trunc>man</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> another manager who does the evening classes I ended up running the eh exams <pause dur="short"/> I I organised it because he would just turn up five minutes before <pause dur="short"/> so I had all the rooms organised had the recording equipment <pause dur="short"/> we had decided who was going to go in each room and em well I mean it was a bit stressful and I'm not getting paid to do it</u>
<u n="804" who="S0018">tell me about it</u>
<u n="805" who="S0170">but even then she was terrible</u>
<u n="806" who="S0018">do you remember the the level testing?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="808" who="S0018">last summer and were you there the summer before?</u>
<u n="809" who="S0170">no</u>
<u n="810" who="S0018">no last summer was your first summer <pause dur="short"/> well the summer before it was just a nightmare because all of a sudden at nine o'clock in the morning like three hundred four hundred Chinese students descended on the building with no organisation no one had told them where to go apart from the foyer</u>
<u n="811" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="812" who="S0018">there were about fifteen teachers who didn't know what rooms they were in who haven't got the materials already cos the materials hadn't been photocopied until like eight thirty and it was just a complete organisational nightmare because it hadn't been organised</u>
<u n="813" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="814" who="S0018">so in the end that's you know</u>
<u n="815" who="S0170">you did the the numbers?</u>
<u n="816" who="S0018">this year it was really organised and all that took was printing out a few numbers wasn't it?</u>
<u n="817" who="S0170">yeah I know that's much better cos everyone knew that they had that room and that was the room they were going to and no arguments</u>
<u n="818" who="S0018">but again yeah it's like <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't our responsibility to do that but it made our life <trunc>al</trunc> our lives a lot easier</u>
<u n="819" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a good job that you knew what it was going to be like</u>
<u n="820" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="821" who="S0170">so you were there to sort it out</u>
<u n="822" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="823" who="S0018">it was quite fun actually meeting everyone <pause dur="short"/> meeting and greeting them and actually having an organised here you go to this room you go to that room as opposed to where we go? Eh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> Ah ah <pause dur="short"/> it was fun <pause dur="short"/> what are you laughing about?  What are you laughing about?</u>
<u n="824" who="S0170">mm <pause dur="short"/> everything don't you? I think he's quite sociable</u>
<u n="825" who="S0018">yeah</u>
<u n="826" who="S0170">he likes being there and if I put him over on the side he'll start crying and when he's here he's quite happy to just sit and listen and</u>
<u n="827" who="S0018">he makes a lot of eye contact actually</u>
<u n="828" who="S0170">mm</u>
<u n="829" who="S0018">he's quite regularly looking up at you or looking up at me and</u>
<u n="830" who="S0170">well apparently that's that's how they're at this age they're memorizing faces</u>
<u n="831" who="S0018">uh-huh</u>
<u n="832" who="S0170">and their favourite people</u>
<u n="833" who="S0018">mm <pause dur="short"/> look at that little smile <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="834" who="S0170">here you go</u>
<u n="835" who="S0018">what do you think he's tickled by when he's smiling? Why do you think he's smiling?</u>
<u n="836" who="S0170">he's smiling cos he thinks that <trunc>y</trunc> you're you're saying it in a nice way an upbeat way he thinks I think she's saying something nice and she's saying it to me <pause dur="short"/> so they're they're just learning to to to eh interact</u>
<u n="837" who="S0018">mm hm</u>
<u n="838" who="S0170">and to</u>
<u n="839" who="S0018">aw</u>
<u n="840" who="S0170">smiles are not just eh if you said something like urgh <pause dur="short"/> he probably wouldn't he wouldn't smile but</u>
<u n="841" who="S0018">so was the nurse like right I'm just going to give you a lovely little injection and hurt your leg and he was like yey</u>
<u n="842" who="S0170">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like you would say have you done a big poo? Have you done a big poo? And he's like I think it's just the way you say it</u>
<u n="843" who="S0018">aw <pause dur="short"/> are you getting hungry?</u>
<u n="844" who="S0170">A bit yeah</u>
<u n="845" who="S0018">yeah <pause dur="short"/> shall we have some lunch?</u>
<u n="846" who="S0170">yeah</u>
</body>
</text>
