<text id="SNWS">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:33:39</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-25</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0618 S0619</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Campervan journey from Tarnow to Białka Tatrzańska, Poland – part 2.</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Living with hippies in Poland, the trip to Białka Tatrzańska, friends, physical characteristics, religion, health &amp; exercise, friends. </topics>
		<activity>Two friends talking about various topics (see 9 above) while driving in a campervan from Tarnow to Białka Tatrzańska, Poland – part 2.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0618">
				<exactage>42</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge/Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months on and off</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>unemployed/ Some part-time private TEFL teacher/ Semi-retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0619">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury, Lancashire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Nort West: Lancs, Greater Manchester</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Tarnow</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Poland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>nearly 4 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher of English as a foreign Language</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0618">yeah I think it's more manageable in terms of file size erm there was one that was a hundred and thirty-two megabytes the other day and it was just too big</u>
<u n="2" who="S0619">aha <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0618"><vocal desc="cough"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but anyway so yeah <unclear/> ah not too much further up here then you turn right</u>
<u n="4" who="S0619">aha</u>
<u n="5" who="S0618">and then <anon type="place"/> is a bit like <anon type="place"/> where we were</u>
<u n="6" who="S0619">aha</u>
<u n="7" who="S0618">with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the other day just like erm it's got a smallish</u>
<u n="8" who="S0619" trans="overlap">smallish place</u>
<u n="9" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah a small square in the middle with parking all around a few shops you know? the butcher the baker the candlestick maker all around in a square and that's it</u>
<u n="10" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="11" who="S0618">and otherwise it's just sort of a thoroughfare for other places <unclear/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0618">and <unclear/> is quite similar to that and then for the <anon type="place"/> you branch off and go another I don't know ten fifteen minutes up on a lot of single track windy roads and you end up it's about a thousand metres above sea level so hopefully you won't be too hot in the summer erm and it's stunning</u>
<u n="14" who="S0619">sounds nice</u>
<u n="15" who="S0618">absolutely stunning and then the bit that I'll be staying in will be <anon type="place"/> like a little log cabin and you've got an orchard behind you where you can see woodpeckers even in September October</u>
<u n="16" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0618">still see woodpeckers saw erm the great spotted saw a male and a female and I saw a green woodpecker and they have jays and they have all sorts of cute little birds as well thirteen cats I think something like six dogs</u>
<u n="18" who="S0619">do they have wi-fi?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0618">they don't have wi-fi</u>
<u n="20" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> unless you're near the main house</u>
<u n="22" who="S0619">aha</u>
<u n="23" who="S0618" trans="overlap">so you can go to the main house and get wi-fi and then in theory the log cabin has an Ethernet cable but I took my computer one time and plugged it in and didn't work so</u>
<u n="24" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="25" who="S0618">and then erm it's got a little wood burner which is why I'm not living there now <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm so yeah I think April time is or May time is sufficient it's got a wood burner and that's the only heating er water is alright the shower has a boiler where you don't touch a thing don't change the temperature do nothing and you should get warm water</u>
<u n="26" who="S0619">right erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's funny</u>
<u n="27" who="S0618">yeah it is and then you sort of look out there's like a bit of a clearing and they've got horses and cows and ducks and hens and they sort of are in the clearing bit and then you've got some more trees and then over the top of the trees where the sun rises you get this beautiful view of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0619">nice</u>
<u n="29" who="S0618">and you've got all the jaggedy mountains that look really sort of red and orange with the sunrise and it's just beautiful <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0619">very nice</u>
<u n="31" who="S0618">mm so I'm looking forward to that oh and they've got thirteen beehives and I really want to learn everything there is to know about bees</u>
<u n="32" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah no no no <unclear/> post me some honey</u>
<u n="33" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0619">well I'll come and get it myself</u>
<u n="35" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0619">no I'm looking forward to a relaxing couple of days wherever we are going anyway</u>
<u n="37" who="S0618">what? now?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0619">in <anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah I'm really looking forward to the spa I love feeling the heat in my bones</u>
<u n="40" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0618">you know?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0619">yeah and it you need it at this time of year</u>
<u n="43" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah and I love a wet heat that you get from the steam rooms</u>
<u n="44" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah I've been considering I've not been doing it I don't think it's fair to but having like evening showers as well</u>
<u n="45" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0619">just because I mean to get you know warmth in my bones my feet especially</u>
<u n="47" who="S0618">mm <pause dur="long"/> has your flat been cold?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0619">ah well I've had the heating on</u>
<u n="49" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0619">ah on and off depending on where I am and what I'm doing but <trunc>aga</trunc> I keep waking up in the middle of the night really hot and having to turn it off when I go for a wee at about four</u>
<u n="51" who="S0618">ah okay <pause dur="short"/> you can't change it someway so do you just have a timer?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0619" trans="overlap">it's it's not on a timer</u>
<u n="53" who="S0618">ah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0619" trans="overlap">but it's a little bit it's either too sensitive or not sensitive at all in that it's either on really hot</u>
<u n="55" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="56" who="S0619">or it's not on at all</u>
<u n="57" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0619">yeah and like even if you put it on two it stays cold and if you put it on three or four then it's really hot it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear>you'd roast</unclear>?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0619">yeah ah it's been a real problem</u>
<u n="61" who="S0618">I've found that I can be toasty in the living room because it's you know it's a big enough room and it's got two radiators in it and then I go up to bed it's fucking freezing</u>
<u n="62" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0618">cos it's you know a big-sized room with just four windows no curtains</u>
<u n="64" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0618">and yeah I <trunc>thi</trunc> I think just that volume of glass makes it really really cold and so I just take a hot water bottle up and have two blankets wear a fleece and when I get up for my first middle of the night wee I take my fleece off and I'm fine for the rest of the night sometimes kick a blanket off</u>
<u n="66" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no <unclear/> quite snug</u>
<u n="67" who="S0618">good <pause dur="short"/> I don't mind taking the floor tonight by the way seeing as erm I'm probably more used to it I've got a couple of foam things in like the top here that I can put on the floor and then I've got the double sleeping bag that lives in the van then my double duvet and two blankets <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I can kind of make a bit of a camp bed thing of sleeping on stuff</u>
<u n="68" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0618">erm and then stuff on the top so I don't mind</u>
<u n="70" who="S0619">no I don't mind doing that</u>
<u n="71" who="S0618">and then I gather then there are just three single beds for three single people but I didn't really like the idea of four people spreading out on three beds pushed together <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="73" who="S0618">little bit close not that I don't like you all cos of course I do but you know?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no I'm the same I just can't sleep with other people around</u>
<u n="75" who="S0618" trans="overlap">nah me either</u>
<u n="76" who="S0619">I don't think I'll sleep very well anyway so it doesn't matter if I'm on the floor <pause dur="short"/> or not so I don't think I'll sleep much ah we'll see <pause dur="long"/> it's been quite a long holiday already there's another week</u>
<u n="77" who="S0618">it's great isn't it?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0619">to go yeah we've done so much but it's been erm like as I said before as I've said before I've really enjoyed doing daytime things and having nights to yourself</u>
<u n="79" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I suppose that's <unclear/> more natural yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0618">cos when the you've got sunlight you know technically you're active and then oh lots of flashing lights</u>
<u n="82" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah oh my goodness me</u>
<u n="83" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="84" who="S0619">I think what is that?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0618">oh my god cop cars one two three four five six</u>
<u n="86" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="87" who="S0618">that's a raid that is seven oh my god that's that's a raid that's not an accident</u>
<u n="88" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yes <unclear/> loads of</u>
<u n="89" who="S0618">wow</u>
<u n="90" who="S0619">detectivey-type cars</u>
<u n="91" who="S0618">yeah undercover cars seem to have a lot of those undercover cars in Poland</u>
<u n="92" who="S0619">do you think?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah I quite often see one that's pulled somebody over it's a like a plain clothes car <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah well when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got done for jaywalking</u>
<u n="95" who="S0618">yeah oh that was yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0619" trans="overlap">that was an undercover car</u>
<u n="97" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0619">I thought I think they were really police and <unclear/> just some guys pushing their luck</u>
<u n="99" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I know yeah that crossed my mind but he said it was all very official and they had badges and paperwork and <unclear/></u>
<u n="100" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah documents yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0618">and they gave him a <trunc>re</trunc> receipt that looked official <vocal desc="laugh"/> so yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it would be real cos you know they could be pulling over a Polish person and there's nothing about he his <unclear/> foreigner</u>
<u n="102" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah he his face yeah yeah I think he's just kind of having a look in his eye <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="104" who="S0619">have you spoken to him?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0618">yeah we've corresponded a little bit on WhatsApp and erm done a few WhatsApp recorded voice messages</u>
<u n="106" who="S0619">he's a huge fan</u>
<u n="107" who="S0618">he is I quite like it so yeah it's good he's met a nice lady I can't remember her name <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or something like that</u>
<u n="108" who="S0619">aha</u>
<u n="109" who="S0618">but no and he's sharing a flat</u>
<u n="110" who="S0619" trans="overlap">like net met nicely</u>
<u n="111" who="S0618">as in net met</u>
<u n="112" who="S0619"><unclear>how nice</unclear></u>
<u n="113" who="S0618">as in having a relationship with</u>
<u n="114" who="S0619">he doesn't mess around does he? Jesus</u>
<u n="115" who="S0618" trans="overlap">no he doesn't it's like right up here where are the single ladies? <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah he's funny like that isn't he? but he he does seem to be a guy who does seem to function better as part of a a team than on his own</u>
<u n="116" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0618">erm but he's living in a house with I think four men so oh wouldn't want to sit on that toilet seat</u>
<u n="118" who="S0619">no</u>
<u n="119" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0619">wouldn't fancy that at all</u>
<u n="121" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0619">and I think he lived with four men in <trunc>L</trunc>London or he lived with a few guys</u>
<u n="123" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="short"/> these guys love to cook and he loves to cook</u>
<u n="124" who="S0619">good for him</u>
<u n="125" who="S0618" trans="overlap">erm I think they're teaching him about Italian cuisine so he'll be thoroughly enjoying that erm and on his first night he went straight from the airport into the forest by a lake for an all-night party and booked his accommodation at six in the morning and yeah that was sort of his welcome to Italy</u>
<u n="126" who="S0619">good for him he's landed just lands on his feet doesn't he?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah he does but you know hats off to him he puts himself out there he says right this is what I want now so I'm going to go and get it and I think that's marvellous I think it's very good to actually know what you want</u>
<u n="128" who="S0619">mm mm yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0618" trans="overlap">and and then to go and get it</u>
<u n="130" who="S0619">yes I think a lot of people just simply don't</u>
<u n="131" who="S0618" trans="overlap">so yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0619">often know what they want</u>
<u n="133" who="S0618">yeah <pause dur="long"/> I've been looking for this petrol station but I fear we've now passed it so</u>
<u n="134" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0618">erm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0619">cross your legs</u>
<u n="137" who="S0618">well I know <pause dur="short"/> but we should after the turn for <anon type="place"/> I would imagine we'll start getting a bit more into skiing tourist town where they have a lot of bars and restaurants where the skiers go</u>
<u n="138" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0618">of an evening so shouldn't be a problem <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0619">I've never done sort of <foreign lang="fre">apres</foreign> ski-type parties they look fun</u>
<u n="141" who="S0618" trans="overlap">it's just it's just drinking beer isn't it?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0618">and eating fondue I don't know does it involve exactly</u>
<u n="144" who="S0619">exactly that</u>
<u n="145" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="146" who="S0619">just drinking and dancing <pause dur="short"/> looks fun all of these people have got their skis and their snowboards</u>
<u n="147" who="S0618">yay <pause dur="short"/> but not us</u>
<u n="148" who="S0619">no I hope <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s well she doesn't have to have done all these things I hope she's got the helmet that I've been wearing <unclear/> if not</u>
<u n="149" who="S0618"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> popped round this morning to pick up her helmet and goggles so erm I said to her</u>
<u n="150" who="S0619" trans="overlap">tiny heads united</u>
<u n="151" who="S0618">I know yeah and her little fifty-four inch head and proud and I funny thing is my brother is the other way round he has a massive head</u>
<u n="152" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0618">a huge head so when we both had motorcycles I had trouble finding a <unclear/> small enough and he had trouble finding one big enough</u>
<u n="154" who="S0619"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s brother's really really tall and she's</u>
<u n="155" who="S0618">she's tiny</u>
<u n="156" who="S0619" trans="overlap">she's tiny tiny</u>
<u n="157" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0619">yeah and her brother was at this party as well I think he's gay erm and he was sort of saying to me oh I'm not very religious but my sister and my mother are</u>
<u n="159" who="S0618">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s quite religious is she?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0618">oh I wasn't aware of that</u>
<u n="162" who="S0619">I think lots of well I don't know it depends how you define religious</u>
<u n="163" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0619">and if you know going to church every Sunday makes you</u>
<u n="165" who="S0618">no it doesn't</u>
<u n="166" who="S0619">religious</u>
<u n="167" who="S0618">it doesn't in my little bit of Northern Ireland where the whole community went to church <unclear/> religious so</u>
<u n="168" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah exactly <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0618">but yeah I think that it's a more community thing and it's yeah well mind you <vocal desc="laugh"/> my friend sort of swears oh Jesus Mary mother of god saint Patrick fuck</u>
<u n="170" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0618">so as you know that makes you religious well I don't know yeah perhaps there's something to it but actually no they would light a candle for people or say a prayer for people but</u>
<u n="172" who="S0619">aha</u>
<u n="173" who="S0618">then if you say do you believe in god? do you believe in afterlife? do you believe you're a sinner? do you believe Jesus died to save you?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0618">then the answer is invariably no</u>
<u n="176" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> his sins are being forgiven oh yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0618">I'm no sinner that's what pisses me off what more of a disempowering control mechanism</u>
<u n="178" who="S0619">aha</u>
<u n="179" who="S0618">for humanity can you possibly have by saying you're shit and you know you are? you were born that way</u>
<u n="180" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0618">and you have to repent and you've got so much to make up for I think bollocks isn't it much nicer to say to a baby and a small child you know you are a gift you are love incarnate you are perfection itself</u>
<u n="182" who="S0619" trans="overlap">that's nice</u>
<u n="183" who="S0618">you are beauty you are the light of this world you are god incarnate if you want to use those terms how much more of a you know positive smiley happy woohoo</u>
<u n="184" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0618">kind of an upbringing are people going to have with that? but anyway to each their own</u>
<u n="186" who="S0619">to each their own indeed <pause dur="short"/> it's not for me <unclear>mother</unclear> has fallen out with me because I refused to go to church on Christmas Day</u>
<u n="187" who="S0618">wow</u>
<u n="188" who="S0619">ah even on Christmas Day and it was because I was very hungover but</u>
<u n="189" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0619">and I just thought I don't go at any other time of year why should I go just cos it was Christmas?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0619">erm I don't really I don't know I should probably have done it for her but</u>
<u n="193" who="S0618">yeah but that's</u>
<u n="194" who="S0619" trans="overlap">she felt that strongly</u>
<u n="195" who="S0618">that's a really shit reason to do something</u>
<u n="196" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0618">because you're no longer standing in your own truth you're sacrificing a part of yourself for somebody else's happiness</u>
<u n="198" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="199" who="S0618">I would wonder I mean your mum sounds to me like an intelligent woman I would think if you phrased it to her in those terms</u>
<u n="200" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0618">she would probably think oh shit oh sorry about that</u>
<u n="202" who="S0619">yeah true and we've talked about it before we've talked about religion and how I can't do it anymore don't want to do it it's not right I don't not only do I not believe in it but I actively disagree with the majority of it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0619">wrong</u>
<u n="205" who="S0618">me too I actively disagree I think anything that subjugates humanity or puts humans down</u>
<u n="206" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0618">is just so wrong <pause dur="short"/> I mean people are beautiful people are you know people are love and light in my mind</u>
<u n="208" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0618">people are wonderful we are an aspect of the divine we are the divine expressing itself and learning about itself</u>
<u n="210" who="S0619">is that man just selling jam out of the back of his car?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0618">ah you maybe you don't know this because you don't come to my house much erm but there's a man who sits in a little put-you-up tent type thing selling fire extinguishers by the side of the road between <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> and he's there most days he he just and when the weather's not as bad he sits in his little fold-out chair</u>
<u n="212" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0618">like you'd take to a summer picnic sort of chair drinking his tea out of his flask waiting for a customer for a fire extinguisher</u>
<u n="214" who="S0619">that's so nice</u>
<u n="215" who="S0618">isn't that amazing?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0619">who <trunc>wo</trunc> ever would want to buy a fire extinguisher?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0618">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/> just in case you happened to be</u>
<u n="218" who="S0619">on fire</u>
<u n="219" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0619">thank god you're here</u>
<u n="221" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> maybe it's a Polish thing maybe they have to have somebody every five miles selling fire extinguishers just in case a vehicle is on fire I don't know</u>
<u n="222" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="223" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0619">outside <anon type="place"/> there's someone who sits and sells bits and pieces apples or potatoes or whatever they can find</u>
<u n="225" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0619">and er near Zenith as well there's people who sit outside and sell stuff</u>
<u n="227" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0619">good old Zenith it's a great little supermarket that</u>
<u n="229" who="S0618">it is I really like it you've got everything there</u>
<u n="230" who="S0619">yeah it's better than the Tesco</u>
<u n="231" who="S0618" trans="overlap">and I <trunc>kno</trunc> fabulous eco range</u>
<u n="232" who="S0619">yeah really good</u>
<u n="233" who="S0618">of environmentally-friendly and organic products have you seen how cheap the the the coconut oil is?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0619">yeah it is cheap</u>
<u n="235" who="S0618">oh my god yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0619" trans="overlap">way cheaper than England</u>
<u n="237" who="S0618">yeah and the Himalayan sea salt</u>
<u n="238" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0618">and it's weird you can't buy or you can't easily buy a tin of beans you can't buy</u>
<u n="240" who="S0619">you can't easily buy a tin of beans I find it fine and easy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0618" trans="overlap">well I can't no I can't fucking find them I know you know where they are and I just yeah they hide them when they see me coming but yeah or a tin of soup or you know certain convenience things that you would expect would be sold internationally but they're just not but you can get Himalayan sea salt and coconut oil easily</u>
<u n="242" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0618">you can get spirulina easily chia seeds easily</u>
<u n="244" who="S0619">and they I don't see or consider Polish people to be especially erm <pause dur="short"/> what's the word? ah health-conscious</u>
<u n="245" who="S0618">no</u>
<u n="246" who="S0619">I think it's a lot more visible in England er people are far more healthy I mean lots of people are the exact opposite but you know?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I was just wondering if you get that because of the polarity?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0619">yes possibly but you know there's sort of a Holland and Barrett everywhere</u>
<u n="249" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="250" who="S0619">lots of people are obsessed with fitness I see far more joggers in England than here</u>
<u n="251" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0619">and I've spoken to students about this before</u>
<u n="253" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it is cold</u>
<u n="254" who="S0619">no but I mean all year round and I've spoken to students about it before and they said erm</u>
<u n="255" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="256" who="S0619">it's just not it's becoming a thing</u>
<u n="257" who="S0618">oh it is becoming a thing?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah yeah in the most student <unclear/> called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he was a</u>
<u n="259" who="S0618">what a great name</u>
<u n="260" who="S0619">head of logistics at er this <unclear/> factory er and he said you know a couple of years ago you would never see anyone running in the streets they'd be sort of stared at</u>
<u n="261" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0619">erm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0618">where's the fire?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0619">well <unclear/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0618" trans="overlap">if it was the extinguisher man <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0619">er but now it's becoming more popular <pause dur="short"/> lot of meatheads in the gym and that lots of big guys</u>
<u n="269" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="270" who="S0619">no girls <vocal desc="laugh"/> don't think girls exercise Polish women exercise very much</u>
<u n="271" who="S0618">no?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0619">not running really not</u>
<u n="273" who="S0618"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> runs <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> runs</u>
<u n="274" who="S0619"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> runs <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> runs yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0618">mm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0619">don't know I suppose a lot of them don't have time when I talk to the core groups about exercise they're just saying oh we don't have time</u>
<u n="277" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="278" who="S0619">we <unclear/> sort of cleaning the house or cooking</u>
<u n="279" who="S0618" trans="overlap">we work fifteen hours a day yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0619">eh well this is inconvenient</u>
<u n="281" who="S0618">I know I'm not quite sure why we have a queue of traffic I hope it's not all the way to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0619">I know can we just see what's potentially there?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0618">yeah erm no you can't cos cos I'm not well I'm not connected to the internet</u>
<u n="284" who="S0619" trans="overlap">no you can't</u>
<u n="285" who="S0618">so it won't tell you about any traffic jams <trunc>a</trunc></u>
<u n="286" who="S0619">no I'm just trying to zoom out and see</u>
<u n="287" who="S0618" trans="overlap">and now since we've stopped I think oh I really need a wee now which is a bit of a bugger I mean if it comes to it we can have a pee in the van erm I'll just have to empty it but it's not a problem so according to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s satnav we've got thirty minutes and forty-two kilometres to go erm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="289" who="S0618"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> isn't expecting us for an hour or a little bit under an hour</u>
<u n="290" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0618">so we can stop and get a coffee somewhere?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0619">yeah we let's just see what happens with this</u>
<u n="293" who="S0618" trans="overlap">erm yeah it's a bit annoying though <unclear/> irksome</u>
<u n="294" who="S0619" trans="overlap">let's just see not if there is any sort of traffic things but if there's like a town or I don't know junctions or type things coming up what do you see?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0618" trans="overlap">so zooming in ah zooming out ah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0619">try and work out why</u>
<u n="297" who="S0618">yeah keep an eye on the things at the side of the road cos cos when you've got a coffee shop coming up they quite often do have billboards</u>
<u n="298" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0618">but it doesn't look like there is a town by the side of the road ah that could be ah no that's just random houses I think</u>
<u n="300" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0618">erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> Siberia</u>
<u n="302" who="S0619">Siberia</u>
<u n="303" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we might get a coffee in Siberia</u>
<u n="304" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Siberia</u>
<u n="305" who="S0618">erm that probably looks favourite <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0619"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0618">a little <foreign lang="fre">en francais</foreign></u>
<u n="308" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> little bit French</u>
<u n="309" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh look and there's a knife and fork symbol oh and a P for parking</u>
<u n="310" who="S0619">oh good that's good</u>
<u n="311" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh right we're going there so parking area add as waypoint please</u>
<u n="312" who="S0619">good</u>
<u n="313" who="S0618">okay so we've added it as a waypoint start and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> won't tell us how far it is to waypoint but I don't think it's that far</u>
<u n="314" who="S0619">well we'll see how this</u>
<u n="315" who="S0618">that's probably a Maccy D's or something</u>
<u n="316" who="S0619">er anything's better than nothing though</u>
<u n="317" who="S0618">indeed actually it's really not that far at all by the looks of this</u>
<u n="318" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh good</u>
<u n="319" who="S0618">if we were driving I would say two minutes or or less so</u>
<u n="320" who="S0619"><trunc>e</trunc> probably not so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah look at this car number plate it ah it looks like it says potty or something</u>
<u n="322" who="S0619">oh yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0618">I like all the fours</u>
<u n="324" who="S0619">four four four four <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0618">so we are moving oh that's good</u>
<u n="326" who="S0619"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0618">okay so I'm just visualising a massive lorry that had missed its turn and needed to do like a <trunc>f</trunc> a seven-point manoeuvre</u>
<u n="328" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="329" who="S0618">in the middle of the road so all of the traffic had to stop while the lorry did the manoeuvre and now the lorry is moving and it's on its way so the traffic may now flow completely freely so there's my creative visualisation</u>
<u n="330" who="S0619">good I'm thinking about it too</u>
<u n="331" who="S0618">yeah and we're moving see this is brilliant now it'll take a little while to get up to speed cos you've got people like me in big vans who can't really accelerate that quickly but yeah we're going and it's all good <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0619">good</u>
<u n="333" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0619">good good good</u>
<u n="335" who="S0618">yes well glad we sorted that out</u>
<u n="336" who="S0619">otherwise we'd have a yellow snow situation</u>
<u n="337" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you would yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0619"><vocal desc="yawn"/> I wonder what that says <unclear/> well <foreign lang="pol">zdrowie</foreign> is health</u>
<u n="339" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> but yeah healthy slippers shop</u>
<u n="340" who="S0619">healthy slippers</u>
<u n="341" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0619">I have brought my slippers they were five zloty and they're awful</u>
<u n="343" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I have as well</u>
<u n="344" who="S0619">absolutely vile bought them last year in <anon type="place"/> and they're just the ugliest they remind me of something like my grandma would wear</u>
<u n="345" who="S0618">why did you buy ugly slippers?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0619">cos I just couldn't find any anywhere <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0618">aw</u>
<u n="348" who="S0619">plus and I didn't want to spend a lot of money</u>
<u n="349" who="S0618">haven't you seen the lady that stands outside in?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0619" trans="overlap">outside yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0618">oh my god</u>
<u n="352" who="S0619">I know I'm tempted <unclear/></u>
<u n="353" who="S0618" trans="overlap">I think older Polish women must have loads of secret layers of fat</u>
<u n="354" who="S0619"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0618">or just be wrapped up in hot water bottles</u>
<u n="356" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="357" who="S0618">cos they stand outside in like minus fifteen degrees Celsius <unclear/></u>
<u n="358" who="S0619" trans="overlap">well I suppose they've had like eighty years to get used to the weather</u>
<u n="359" who="S0618">yeah they maybe have</u>
<u n="360" who="S0619">erm oh we are really near good good good</u>
<u n="361" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> we are that see just yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0619">I saw the court man in the middle of town the other day</u>
<u n="363" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0619">he's like <unclear/> across the street</u>
<u n="365" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0619">I was like oh Jesus I was on the phone</u>
<u n="367" who="S0618">did you babble away at each other and not understand what the other was saying?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0619" trans="overlap">he just no thankfully I was on the phone to this woman who the hell was that? <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh it was just a man</u>
<u n="369" who="S0618">I had lots of kisses off of my neighbour this morning it was lovely this is nice</u>
<u n="370" who="S0619">ah that's nice</u>
<u n="371" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah she got me out of the shower to give me cake she's</u>
<u n="372" who="S0619">what kind of cake was it?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0618">oh there's a bit looks like a <unclear/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0619">aha</u>
<u n="375" who="S0618">and there's a bit that looks like something else with sliced almonds and desiccated coconut</u>
<u n="376" who="S0619" trans="overlap">nice</u>
<u n="377" who="S0618">but she's amazing and she bought me this erm thing the other day which I described it to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she said it's called a roulade</u>
<u n="378" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="379" who="S0618">but it's I thought roulade was just like cake with creamy stuff in</u>
<u n="380" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="381" who="S0618">erm I used to have a Polish friend in England who makes roulade at Christmas she makes chocolate roulade and and a jam roulade anyway</u>
<u n="382" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0618">this was more like a sweet bread</u>
<u n="384" who="S0619">aha</u>
<u n="385" who="S0618">with chocolate rolled through it</u>
<u n="386" who="S0619">oh nice</u>
<u n="387" who="S0618">it's nice anyway I think she's a bit worried about me not eating or something bringing me cake but anyway so she got me out of the shower at</u>
<u n="388" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0618">quarter past eight</u>
<u n="390" who="S0619">people I don't know whether people worry that you don't eat or whether it's just a custom to ply people with food</u>
<u n="391" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0619">my neighbour last year they used to you know he lived alone but whenever he went to his sister's house for lunch or whatever he would always come back with a bag of food for me</u>
<u n="393" who="S0618">ah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0619">and leave it outside my door</u>
<u n="395" who="S0618">that's sweet</u>
<u n="396" who="S0619" trans="overlap">when I wasn't in yeah just go home to like a jar of coleslaw and sausage</u>
<u n="397" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0619">thanks <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="399" who="S0618">look that's where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is living up there on the high mountains up there</u>
<u n="400" who="S0619" trans="overlap">very nice oh nice</u>
<u n="401" who="S0618">so that's where I will be living</u>
<u n="402" who="S0619" trans="overlap">excellent excellent have we gone</u>
<u n="403" who="S0618">in no time</u>
<u n="404" who="S0619">past the turn for there yet?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0618">yeah I think we must have done because I erm I don't recognise this hill and this turn I think I'd have normally turned off by now <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0619">oh oh oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0618">oh that looks like that lorry must need to turn round again <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0619">maybe this is just traffic lights or something</u>
<u n="409" who="S0618">ah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0619">I don't know a while</u>
<u n="411" who="S0618">oh no that's the lorry look it turned round</u>
<u n="412" who="S0619">yeah it did good for them good good good</u>
<u n="413" who="S0618">oh isn't this beautiful though? getting to look out across the valley</u>
<u n="414" who="S0619">yeah nice</u>
<u n="415" who="S0618">on a clear day you could probably see <anon type="place"/> from here <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="416" who="S0619">it's beautiful</u>
<u n="417" who="S0618">it really is</u>
<u n="418" who="S0619">absolutely</u>
<u n="419" who="S0618">mm and I like the drive to the <anon type="place"/> as well cos there's erm a road you go up that's got a little bit of a hairpin bend</u>
<u n="420" who="S0619">mm</u>
<u n="421" who="S0618">but as you come round this hairpin bend this just vista of valleys and mountains opens up before you really really lovely and there was snow-peaked mountains back in September and October as well</u>
<u n="422" who="S0619">goodness me</u>
<u n="423" who="S0618" trans="overlap">so so pretty <pause dur="short"/> oh mind you we had snow in <anon type="place"/> in October</u>
<u n="424" who="S0619">we did but only for a day</u>
<u n="425" who="S0618" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0619">we had snow last year in April so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0618">oh wow in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah in <anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="429" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="430" who="S0619">it was my birthday</u>
<u n="431" who="S0618">my gosh</u>
<u n="432" who="S0619">it was Easter Monday and I opened the window</u>
<u n="433" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0619">oh the curtains and it was snowing I was like fuck I'm going back to bed</u>
<u n="435" who="S0618"><vocal desc="laugh"/> don't blame you</u>
<u n="436" who="S0619">that was like that was the worst time of living in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0618">yeah?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0619" trans="overlap">when it was Easter so nothing was open for like four days</u>
<u n="439" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah forever yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0619">er and it was my birthday and I was just alone</u>
<u n="441" who="S0618">ah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0619">yeah I know it's really sad erm</u>
<u n="443" who="S0618">that's not going to happen this year</u>
<u n="444" who="S0619">that's not going to happen this year</u>
<u n="445" who="S0618">I was so grateful to you throwing a party for me for my birthday in December</u>
<u n="446" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="447" who="S0618">yeah it was great but no I was really touched by that thank you very kind</u>
<u n="448" who="S0619" trans="overlap">oh you're very welcome any any any excuse for a <trunc>pa</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="449" who="S0618">well in December <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0618">now oh no</u>
<u n="452" who="S0619">I know I don't plan on having any parties until June</u>
<u n="453" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0619">for the sake of our neighbours I'm still getting really the most <unclear/> off them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah uh oh</u>
<u n="456" who="S0619"><unclear/> anyone sometimes if I open the door and hear that there's voices I wait for them to go cos I just don't want to see them cos I know that they hate me</u>
<u n="457" who="S0618" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="458" who="S0619">and it's not me I'm not a loud party-throwing person</u>
<u n="459" who="S0618">I know it's all whatever</u>
<u n="460" who="S0619">but I've been tarred with the brush</u>
<u n="461" who="S0618">maybe you need to give them a bit of sober <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> go out and greet them cheerily wish them a pleasant morning</u>
<u n="462" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's it's true it's true</u>
<u n="463" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="464" who="S0619">I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is just going to keep his head down</u>
<u n="465" who="S0618">yeah?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0619">yes I don't think he's a party person</u>
<u n="467" who="S0618">mm doesn't strike me as a partier</u>
<u n="468" who="S0619" trans="overlap">he doesn't really he doesn't well I think that's not true I think he probably is but he's not a an active</u>
<u n="469" who="S0618">mm</u>
<u n="470" who="S0619">he's a passive party person he'll go if it's <trunc>invi</trunc> if you know if he's invited but he won't throw one himself</u>
<u n="471" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah but he won't throw one yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0619">which is fair enough and I don't think he speaks to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> very much</u>
<u n="473" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0619">all his friends are in <anon type="place"/> so he didn't go there I mean they're more than welcome to come here but I think a lot of his friends were girls so that rules them out of coming and staying I suppose</u>
<u n="475" who="S0618" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="476" who="S0619">don't know <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="477" who="S0618">yeah I sort of miss erm I want to say dinner parties but that sounds a bit formal</u>
<u n="478" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="479" who="S0618">informal dinner parties yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0619" trans="overlap">eating together</u>
<u n="481" who="S0618">where people just a bit like we did the other day really</u>
<u n="482" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0618">turn up with food everybody does a bit and everybody shares and then fuck off early in bed by ten perfect</u>
<u n="484" who="S0619">yes</u>
<u n="485" who="S0618">yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0619">yes yes yes <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> in bed by ten that could be the name of my autobiography</u>
<u n="487" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u> <pause dur="short"/>
<u n="488" who="S0618">oh wood sculptures</u>
<u n="489" who="S0619">beautiful</u>
<u n="490" who="S0618"><unclear/> sculptures</u>
<u n="491" who="S0619" trans="overlap">absolutely great <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0618">so apparently seven hundred and fifty metres to restaurant</u>
<u n="493" who="S0619" trans="overlap">ah it's not looking <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0618">well I suppose we are fairly rural so</u>
<u n="495" who="S0619">yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0618">but erm actually maybe that's what's causing the slower traffic is with things pulling in and out of the restaurant</u>
<u n="497" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah maybe yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0618">well I'm calling it a restaurant it's just a knife and fork</u>
<u n="499" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> knife and fork on a thing</u>
<u n="500" who="S0618">on a satnav picture yeah I must ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I get the impression <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't clean her own car I was going to ask her where she goes seems a little ironic to me that anywhere you go in in the United Kingdom you can find somebody eastern European who</u>
<u n="501" who="S0619">clean your car</u>
<u n="502" who="S0618" trans="overlap">clean your car efficiently and effectively for not too much money yet in Poland it's kind of impossible erm I mean I don't mind cleaning the van myself but I maybe need somebody and I know you offered thank you to put coins in the thing to keep the water flowing</u>
<u n="503" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0618">but also to read the instructions cos these things you know usually have a soap function</u>
<u n="505" who="S0619" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="506" who="S0618">now where is parking? here we are I can pull in here can't I? yes</u>
<u n="507" who="S0619" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="508" who="S0618">I just need to make sure there's nothing coming behind so I pull in after this car ah out the way</u>
<event desc="sound of banging"/>
<u n="509" who="S0618">okay and we're here</u>
<u n="510" who="S0619">and we're here</u>
<u n="511" who="S0618">so if I reverse oh shit I hope we're going to get up that again <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="512" who="S0619">we will <unclear/></u>
<u n="513" who="S0618" trans="overlap">if I reverse in here yeah exactly well said erm then we're pointing downwards</u>
<u n="514" who="S0619" trans="overlap"><unclear/> get a bit of oomph up right would you like to go to</u>
<u n="515" who="S0618" trans="overlap">the winter tyres are fabulous</u>
<u n="516" who="S0619"><unclear/> something? or</u>
<u n="517" who="S0618">er what's that place? that looks more like I don't know <unclear/> that's beer</u>
<u n="518" who="S0619">mm mm</u>
<u n="519" who="S0618"><unclear/> bar I think that's the bar and I think that's restaurant up there so let's go up the steps</u>
<u n="520" who="S0619">that looks nice yes</u>
<u n="521" who="S0618">if your gym legs will cope with it</u>
<u n="522" who="S0619">I</u>
<u n="523" who="S0618">oh I'm a bit close to that car <unclear/> carpark and I'm making a right mess of</u>
<u n="524" who="S0619">in the gym there's shitloads of stairs it's awful the weights room's downstairs and the you know the reception's upstairs but to get into the building you've got to go up the stairs <vocal desc="laugh"/> so it's like you know an arc of stairs it's awful</u>
<u n="525" who="S0618" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="526" who="S0619">just not very nice</u>
<u n="527" who="S0618">okay so goodbye</u>
<u n="528" who="S0619">bye</u>
<u n="529" who="S0618">bye</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
