<text id="SP2X">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:59:54</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-03-25</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0326 S0381 S0382</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>classics, planes, recordings, Paris, Essex, travel plans, regret, university, France, sea food, Cavafy, reception theory, philosophy, wine </topics>
		<activity>Father, son and step-mother talk over dinner at home </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, announcing, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0326">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>12</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0381">
				<exactage>45</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>American</nat>
				<birthplace></birthplace>
				<birthcountry>USA</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>American/British</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Academic</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0382">
				<exactage>63</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Oxford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/US</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Professional</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>50 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Academic</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0382">so is it like an automatic transcription programme or something?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0326">probably I don't know</u>
<u n="3" who="S0382">so if I say phenomenological complexity <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> how is your paper on cognitive phenomenological?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0381" trans="overlap">oh my god I had this thought about consciousness today</u>
<u n="5" who="S0382">oh scary</u>
<u n="6" who="S0381">on my run</u>
<u n="7" who="S0382">oh</u>
<u n="8" who="S0381">and it it's relation to existence</u>
<u n="9" who="S0382">oh</u>
<u n="10" who="S0381">well it was started off thinking about erm Descartes' <trunc>cogi</trunc>cogito so you know he has this I think therefore I am right?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0382">no I am having a conscious experience therefore I am</u>
<u n="12" who="S0381">okay</u>
<u n="13" who="S0382">that's my translation</u>
<u n="14" who="S0381" trans="overlap">so you can't if if and if you think of it as some sort of deduction right? okay let's just think of it as a deduction the existence claim has to be contained in the I think claim</u>
<u n="15" who="S0382">correct</u>
<u n="16" who="S0381">so there has to be sort of this affirmation of existence or</u>
<u n="17" who="S0382">correct</u>
<u n="18" who="S0381">I don't know I thought that was sort of I've never</u>
<u n="19" who="S0382" trans="overlap">but no this is this is old old news because there's been a huge debate about whether it is a whether it's a syllogism or a deduction</u>
<u n="20" who="S0381">yeah yeah I know that I that's why I was saying take it as a syllogism but then that made me think of Brentano cos the way he explicates the aware</u>
<u n="21" who="S0382">damn</u>
<u n="22" who="S0381">I know I had a good sort of the way the way he explicates the awareness of awareness claim part of it is he thinks involves a judgement but judgement is either to affirm or deny the existence of something so contained in consciousness is an affirmation of existence</u>
<u n="23" who="S0382">oh well I think that's like I think that's like</u>
<u n="24" who="S0381" trans="overlap">and I thought wow he probably got that from Descartes</u>
<u n="25" who="S0382">well Descartes had a sort of struggle about whether it was a syllogism or not but</u>
<u n="26" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0382">that <trunc>co</trunc> that fits with something we were talking about before which was <pause dur="short"/> that in the mere awareness of awareness there is the judgement that it is in some sense and then you have to think about whether animals are doing that</u>
<u n="28" who="S0381">yeah I mean that's the hard</u>
<u n="29" who="S0382">how who where did that come up?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0381">anyway that was a good part of my run</u>
<u n="31" who="S0382" trans="overlap">anyway <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that was very deep no I think that</u>
<u n="32" who="S0381">but it made me think about you know how you have this</u>
<u n="33" who="S0382">me?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0381">self-sprung</u>
<u n="35" who="S0382">oh yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0381">stuff and I thought oh well maybe there's something I don't know something about that existence somehow</u>
<u n="37" who="S0382" trans="overlap">my latest paper is <unclear>cooked</unclear> I think it might be true but everyone's going to think it's crazy</u>
<u n="38" who="S0381">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="39" who="S0382">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0381">I just wanted to cos I totally forgot I was thinking of telling you about this and then I forgot when I got home cos you were having the crisis about the skip</u>
<u n="41" who="S0382">that's our new crisis today skips</u>
<u n="42" who="S0326">where's the skip?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0381">it's the thing that you</u>
<u n="44" who="S0382" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0326">yeah but where where do you got it? where do you put it?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0382">it's got to be out there but you have to buy parking suspension and then that costs</u>
<u n="47" who="S0326">everybody else in your neighbourhood uses it</u>
<u n="48" who="S0381">yeah I mean they already use our garbage we're already the neighbourhood recycling centre</u>
<u n="49" who="S0382" trans="overlap">yeah they in our in our echo recycle bin they keep dropping we usually find some old fish and chips</u>
<u n="50" who="S0381">well you know what though? I've noticed lately that they've only been putting recyclable items in there</u>
<u n="51" who="S0382">no a little bit of</u>
<u n="52" who="S0381">because I've taken them out the things that aren't recyclable and put them on the corner there</u>
<u n="53" who="S0382">you have? oh</u>
<u n="54" who="S0381">yes</u>
<u n="55" who="S0382">vigilante? yeah although we have we have at least</u>
<u n="56" who="S0381">because otherwise the recycle people have to do that right?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0382">yeah they do so some <trunc>be</trunc><trunc>be</trunc> very popular pub was closed in <anon type="place"/> road so some of the clientele are now coming here so we're getting quite a lot of noise at night but it's alright I kinda like it I kind of there's at least one domestic every day</u>
<u n="58" who="S0381">oh my god we saw a really bad one</u>
<u n="59" who="S0382">oh yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0326">yeah but that's the same you know cos <anon type="place"/> road sort of off two main roads</u>
<u n="61" who="S0382">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0381">oh</u>
<u n="63" who="S0326">couples coming down there to go and have have their <trunc>sh</trunc> fights</u>
<u n="64" who="S0381">oh off the main road</u>
<u n="65" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0382">yeah that's right I think they feel it's the kind of stage set out there and there aren't many people around so they have them there</u>
<u n="67" who="S0381">yeah we saw a really terrible one</u>
<u n="68" who="S0382">oh I think has <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> been here since then? maybe not no</u>
<u n="69" who="S0381">they had a fight they were screaming and the husband was running out the door and then running back to the door and screaming at her and they he came out around the corner and then this Muslim no</u>
<u n="70" who="S0382">Somali kind of guy</u>
<u n="71" who="S0381">Somali guy was coming round the corner</u>
<u n="72" who="S0382">coming back with his shopping</u>
<u n="73" who="S0381">and the husband just started punching him and I was watching out the window cos I'm nosy but I don't know what to do</u>
<u n="74" who="S0382">yeah he was just letting out his anger at his but his domestic was like</u>
<u n="75" who="S0381" trans="overlap">but the <trunc>am</trunc> the ambulance did come so the police did</u>
<u n="76" who="S0382">that was bad that's not a domestic that was just a piece of</u>
<u n="77" who="S0381">a domestic gone bad</u>
<u n="78" who="S0382">the guy was</u>
<u n="79" who="S0381">he lost it</u>
<u n="80" who="S0382">wow it was horrid <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> so when are you going off to Italy?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0326">April about the twelfth?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0382">oh after after Easter?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0382">yeah so we're meant to be coming back on on Easter Sunday there's the you know there's the usual erm <anon type="place"/> thing happening but we can't go what?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0326">I don't know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just looked at me</u>
<u n="86" who="S0382">well weirdly <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/> yet</u>
<u n="87" who="S0326">yeah where is that? is that in America or something?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0382">might have been yeah so are you staying in <anon type="place"/> right?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0381">er I'm wondering if did you guys get invited to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s wedding? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> one of the cousins</u>
<u n="90" who="S0326">I don't think so</u>
<u n="91" who="S0382"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cousin</u>
<u n="92" who="S0326">I don't think so</u>
<u n="93" who="S0382">she's not so big now</u>
<u n="94" who="S0381">they're all skinny actually they're all skinny</u>
<u n="95" who="S0382">they are it's the new cousins</u>
<u n="96" who="S0381">the new cousins</u>
<u n="97" who="S0382">no they're not though <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> isn't skinny</u>
<u n="98" who="S0381">oh that's true</u>
<u n="99" who="S0326">can I get another beer?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0381">yeah there's one</u>
<u n="101" who="S0382">hey oh what you? you want the loo? or beer yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0381">it's on the</u>
<u n="103" who="S0382">great cos</u>
<u n="104" who="S0381">on the <trunc>do</trunc> no you were right on the door</u>
<u n="105" who="S0382">yeah <unclear/> have you seen the telly yet?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0381">we just thought oh we don't need to go in there and that's where the beer is</u>
<u n="107" who="S0326">after all can you sell that?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0382">yeah but I think it's some years old I think I don't know whether they're kind of decaying or not</u>
<u n="109" who="S0326">I think you could set up a fairly good business of selling things that people like that are valuable but that people can't be bothered to sell</u>
<u n="110" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0382">so what would be the?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0326">so you like sell that and you take <trunc>twenty</trunc> you get I give you twenty percent or something</u>
<u n="113" who="S0382">people can be bothered to sell though because they can they can all do Ebay and</u>
<u n="114" who="S0381">okay <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's your turn to check the sausages</u>
<u n="115" who="S0382">I have no idea it's kind of impressive but yeah okay you want me to swizzle them?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0326">bottle opener</u>
<u n="117" who="S0381">oh</u>
<u n="118" who="S0382" trans="overlap">ah oh it's all happening it's all looking good how long have they been in?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0381">erm I don't know thirty minutes or</u>
<u n="120" who="S0382">they look mostly done</u>
<u n="121" who="S0381">where is the bottle opener?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0382">I put erm it's probably still on the table</u>
<u n="123" who="S0381">no I don't I feel like I oh here it is</u>
<u n="124" who="S0382">there's the cork</u>
<u n="125" who="S0381"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can open it with a knife</u>
<u n="126" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I already did it I already did it what happened to this knife? stabbed someone</u>
<u n="127" who="S0382">no</u>
<u n="128" who="S0381">oh yeah your dad broke it</u>
<u n="129" who="S0382">I was trying to prize something I'm really really upset I love those knives that's</u>
<u n="130" who="S0326">still it's still pretty functionable</u>
<u n="131" who="S0382">yeah yeah it's just erm it is so can you do you ever cook in <anon type="place"/> cook stuff for yourself?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0326">I don't really like to I don't really like using the shared kitchen you know? I do I eat it in my room and it's kind of just like I I I like just sort of make things I don't really need to use the cooking stuff for</u>
<u n="133" who="S0381">you can do you have a hot plate?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0326">yeah it's a whole fully functioning kitchen like down the hallway</u>
<u n="135" who="S0381">oh yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0382">I had I was a veggie all my time at <anon type="place"/> I basically ate brown rice soy sauce lettuce peanuts cheese</u>
<u n="137" who="S0381">did you eat vegetables?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0382">probably not much I don't know</u>
<u n="139" who="S0381">isn't that funny you don't eat vegetables when you were younger</u>
<u n="140" who="S0382">I mustn't have but I never ate in my own college once not one time</u>
<u n="141" who="S0381">that is so annoying <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0382">so cos I was a scholar after a year I got a scholarship I had to go in and read say the prayer sometimes</u>
<u n="143" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0382">so I would go in I'd march in put on my gown and say I said it in this ridiculously exaggerated Italian accent</u>
<u n="145" who="S0381">oh my god</u>
<u n="146" who="S0382"><foreign lang="lat">domino deus</foreign> or <unclear/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0381" trans="overlap">in Latin?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0382">and then I just walked out yeah it was in Latin yeah but</u>
<u n="149" who="S0326"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0381">do they still do that?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0326">when when I I had to go to a half-way dinner erm a couple of weeks ago and I had like it's was a formal dinner and things like that they do some speech in Latin before you eat</u>
<u n="152" who="S0381">that's probably the prayer</u>
<u n="153" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0382">I don't know erm <foreign lang="lat"/> see if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can translate <foreign lang="lat">gratius tibi agimus domino deus</foreign></u>
<u n="155" who="S0381">wait say it again</u>
<u n="156" who="S0326">we give we give thanks to erm</u>
<u n="157" who="S0382"><foreign lang="lat">domino deus proheset universi stoni duis</foreign></u>
<u n="158" who="S0326">I need to see it's hard just to do it</u>
<u n="159" who="S0382">I know <foreign lang="lat">prohis et de universi</foreign></u>
<u n="160" who="S0326">in return for this</u>
<u n="161" who="S0382"><foreign lang="lat"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0326">this gift of university study</u>
<u n="163" who="S0382">no no no</u>
<u n="164" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0382">for this and all your gifts to did I get that right?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0381" trans="overlap">oh does that mean universe is that the universe word?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0382" trans="overlap"><foreign lang="lat"/> I'm probably very wrong</u>
<u n="168" who="S0326">which we receive we receive cos which we receive at your</u>
<u n="169" who="S0382">but this must be this must be after I'm doing the afterwards one yeah which out of your</u>
<u n="170" who="S0381">oh did you march in after the dinner and?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0382">no no I only had to do it before no I'm just doing the one I don't know how that went</u>
<u n="173" who="S0381">did you ever get that picture of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0382">yeah I got it yeah yeah is your rice ready?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0381">yeah it's kind of crunchy</u>
<u n="176" who="S0382">oh dear</u>
<u n="177" who="S0381">I don't know why</u>
<u n="178" who="S0382">did you not put enough water? how much did you put?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0381">I put one-and-a-half</u>
<u n="180" who="S0382">no but what is the just tell me your math</u>
<u n="181" who="S0381">four fifty babe</u>
<u n="182" who="S0382">four fifty no we can't help but we told you about this ever since we started taking the piss out of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for saying babes we've been saying it ever since we can't stop</u>
<u n="183" who="S0326">it's fine to say it it's fine</u>
<u n="184" who="S0382">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0381">no actually it's okay</u>
<u n="186" who="S0382">it's okay yeah no no yeah I mean</u>
<u n="187" who="S0326">I don't eat a lot of like sort of I quite like sardines and stuff you know?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0381">well that's good</u>
<u n="189" who="S0326">er</u>
<u n="190" who="S0382">ah <unclear/> like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> always oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> rang me I think I sent it to you all didn't I? yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0326">what else do I eat? I always I can like sort of it's <trunc>re</trunc> I eat really cheap there I go into Sainsbury's and spend like twelve quid and that's enough food for a week</u>
<u n="192" who="S0382">yeah no I I did too I think but yeah hard boiled and sardines hard boiled eggs and <trunc>pro</trunc> sardines</u>
<u n="193" who="S0326">and like once or twice a week I'll eat in hall</u>
<u n="194" who="S0382">how much does it cost for? in hall?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0326">it's about</u>
<u n="196" who="S0382">three quid or three fifty</u>
<u n="197" who="S0326">I mean it's they're <trunc>try</trunc> it's not they're trying to get it cheaper like my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> if you remember he did a boycott of hall it was actually really successful he managed to like cook sort of pasta bake and like pizza for like the two like hundred people and did it in the bar while the hall was running and like no one went to the hall obviously cos it was like two pounds</u>
<u n="198" who="S0381">wow</u>
<u n="199" who="S0326">so who wants a meal like for two pounds? which is probably affordable</u>
<u n="200" who="S0381">wow that's enterprising of him</u>
<u n="201" who="S0382" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0326">but the thing is also that you everybody in everybody in <anon type="place"/> pays a a catering fee anyway and</u>
<u n="203" who="S0382">oh</u>
<u n="204" who="S0326">lots of people don't even use use the canteen</u>
<u n="205" who="S0382">right</u>
<u n="206" who="S0326">and it's like a hundred and forty pounds a term</u>
<u n="207" who="S0382">right</u>
<u n="208" who="S0326">and you're like well what's that? that's like if you add it all up it's a lot</u>
<u n="209" who="S0382">yeah good point yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0326">erm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0382">so he did the</u>
<u n="212" who="S0326">he did pay it yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0382">what he just did it by sort of massive use of microwaves or?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0326">well I think he got like a lot of people sort of got involved and helped and they used like lots of <trunc>col</trunc> college for students in college kitchens</u>
<u n="215" who="S0382">so you had a kind of what do you call them in America? a bake out or a bake off</u>
<u n="216" who="S0381" trans="overlap">wow protest bake off</u>
<u n="217" who="S0382">you had a I kind of I saw the I just remembered I've had a <trunc>fla</trunc> I've had a <trunc>fla</trunc> memory flash the first microwave I ever saw was in <anon type="place"/> bar</u>
<u n="218" who="S0381">really? what year was that?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0382">probably nineteen seventy-two</u>
<u n="220" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0382">they'd just invented them or something yeah I think only only places like restaurants had them or</u>
<u n="222" who="S0381">I didn't grow up with a microwave</u>
<u n="223" who="S0382">no no well my mum hasn't got one yet</u>
<u n="224" who="S0326">I went to a really strange <trunc>pa</trunc> place the other week I went there by accident sort of it was in the basement of the Science Museum and it's sort of where they kind of have all the exhibits of sort of the Hoover throughout time the toaster</u>
<u n="225" who="S0382">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0381">yeah yeah yeah quite fun actually</u>
<u n="227" who="S0326">but it's it's it's feels like some sort of train station in from Tokyo in the nineties or something it's like it's super super weird and there's like I mean it's hard to explain you have to see it</u>
<u n="228" who="S0382">yeah it's part of the museum is it?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0326">yeah but it's like also it's kind of mixed with the it where they used to <trunc>ha</trunc> I suppose when it was like schools went there for <trunc>lu</trunc> holidays and have their lunch there but I don't think they use it for that anymore</u>
<u n="230" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0326">and it's just like sort of weird colours and they've done all these weird things like it's kind of like a horror museum like a horror like things jump out of like</u>
<u n="232" who="S0381"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0326">they had like a cooker attached to the ceiling and it's not sort of this thing would hop out of it</u>
<u n="234" who="S0381">woah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0382">a cuckoo?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0326">a <trunc>ca</trunc> a cooker</u>
<u n="237" who="S0381">a cooker</u>
<u n="238" who="S0382">a cooker</u>
<u n="239" who="S0326">and like there's all these like weird things going on like noises you can like watch adverts through and this is <unclear/> telephones from the like fifties</u>
<u n="240" who="S0381">oh yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0382">well I think yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0326">and it's not</u>
<u n="243" who="S0381"><unclear/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0382">yeah yeah apparently I'm the model of</u>
<u n="245" who="S0326">and there's no one there you know?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0381">these might</u>
<u n="247" who="S0382" trans="overlap">yeah there's lots of those interactive things in in the national <trunc>na</trunc> yeah I think they're good <unclear/></u>
<u n="248" who="S0381">right mm those look pretty cooked</u>
<u n="249" who="S0382">do they? yeah do you want to go on to the oh those are</u>
<u n="250" who="S0381">those are definitely cooked</u>
<u n="251" who="S0382">yeah we're good</u>
<u n="252" who="S0381">so we'll turn this off I we should try the peas though</u>
<u n="253" who="S0382">try the peas okay</u>
<u n="254" who="S0381">the rice is definitely done</u>
<u n="255" who="S0382">so where is that Science Museum? like down Downing Street or something?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0326">High Street Kensington</u>
<u n="257" who="S0382">oh I thought oh in London</u>
<u n="258" who="S0326">in London yeah where did you think I was talking about?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0382">yeah no I was just saying they have all those sort of things in London now thinking you were in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0326">no but it's so it's like a massive</u>
<u n="261" who="S0381" trans="overlap">I'm just going to use this plate done?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0382">do you want to put a blob of butter in it?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0381">yeah that's what I was just about to do</u>
<u n="264" who="S0382">yeah I know that but it's got a massive extension now <pause dur="short"/> that's all our bread I'll just see if there's some</u>
<u n="265" who="S0381">there's there's got to be another bread</u>
<u n="266" who="S0382"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0381">so you think the peas are done?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0382">yeah well they'll do they're not great I don't know if it's</u>
<u n="269" who="S0381">I think it would be on just use the pot</u>
<u n="270" who="S0382">jeepers all kind of stuff in here I don't think there is any bread</u>
<u n="271" who="S0381">oh no</u>
<u n="272" who="S0382">nope</u>
<u n="273" who="S0381">oh my god</u>
<u n="274" who="S0382">oh my</u>
<u n="275" who="S0381">we went through that bread fast it seems like</u>
<u n="276" who="S0382">we're out of bread we've just got nasty bagels oh I need bread</u>
<u n="277" who="S0381">this is the I'm not sure how much to do <unclear/> go for a second meal</u>
<u n="278" who="S0382">yeah you've got</u>
<u n="279" who="S0326">I don't really I'm just going to eat a tiny bit of the fish seeing as I caught it</u>
<u n="280" who="S0381">well you you can start with that and if you want more</u>
<u n="281" who="S0382">that's pretty amazing though so how far out did you go?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0326">not far cos it's sort of like it's a bit kind of quite a big tidal river saltwater</u>
<u n="283" who="S0382">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0326">and it's another sort of</u>
<u n="285" who="S0382">which what was the river called? which one is it?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0326">no idea</u>
<u n="287" who="S0382">I had to learn them all when I was a kid there was the Ouse and the Stour and the I have to check it is your computer on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0381">no it's all the way upstairs</u>
<u n="289" who="S0326">I can do it on my phone probably <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0382">the Orwell is it Orwell? I know Orwell George Orwell took his name from some place in around there his pen name Orwell cos his real name was Blair Eric Blair <pause dur="long"/> let's hope the <unclear/> is nice who knows maybe it's weird it's organic anyway</u>
<u n="291" who="S0326">well it says the river <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0382">oh oh</u>
<u n="293" who="S0326">so basically if you see this</u>
<u n="294" who="S0382">oh <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0326">this is <anon type="place"/> island here</u>
<u n="296" who="S0382">mm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0326">this is where we were fishing</u>
<u n="298" who="S0382">mm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0326">this is the river but it's basically open sea kind of</u>
<u n="300" who="S0382">go go in so I can see where it is in that's the bulge of East Anglia right?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0326">whoops</u>
<u n="302" who="S0382">oh look it's still is it still recording?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0326">yeah erm where did maps go?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0382">yeah yeah okay yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0326">so it's sort of that</u>
<u n="306" who="S0382">right over there</u>
<u n="307" who="S0381">oh</u>
<u n="308" who="S0382">what's the town at the end?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0326"><trunc>se</trunc> er</u>
<u n="310" who="S0382">cool where of <anon type="place"/> it's spelt like that</u>
<u n="311" who="S0381">I don't know if you should let them</u>
<u n="312" who="S0382">oh there's <anon type="place"/> where we get <anon type="place"/> salt from</u>
<u n="313" who="S0381">oh</u>
<u n="314" who="S0382">whoo hoo cool</u>
<u n="315" who="S0326"><anon type="place"/> is cool cos it's like it's in Essex but it's sort of bit oh it's a bit <trunc>wil</trunc> like</u>
<u n="316" who="S0382">quite strange</u>
<u n="317" who="S0326">weird very few people live there and</u>
<u n="318" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0382">you know they're erm there are still people descended from the Dutch who who took flight from the Mongols in the thirteenth century because there's fear of</u>
<u n="320" who="S0381">new salt <unclear/> will you pass that salt?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0382">the <unclear/> is really nice</u>
<u n="322" who="S0381">thanks</u>
<u n="323" who="S0382">it seems to me</u>
<u n="324" who="S0381">I haven't tried it yet</u>
<u n="325" who="S0382">it's better than that</u>
<u n="326" who="S0381" trans="overlap">let's see</u>
<u n="327" who="S0382">we must do it again sometime</u>
<u n="328" who="S0381">what?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0382">the nipping over to France</u>
<u n="330" who="S0381">yeah that was pretty fun actually</u>
<u n="331" who="S0326">did you go on the train?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0381">we drove</u>
<u n="333" who="S0382">we went on the car train</u>
<u n="334" who="S0381">tunnel</u>
<u n="335" who="S0382">which we did once with you</u>
<u n="336" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0326">more than once I think</u>
<u n="338" who="S0382">yeah?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0381">we went on the ferry I remember going on the ferry and I remember going on the tunnel but</u>
<u n="340" who="S0382">several times on the ferry</u>
<u n="341" who="S0326">maybe I <trunc>wa</trunc> I went to Paris quite often on the bus</u>
<u n="342" who="S0381">yeah on and you went on the tunnel</u>
<u n="343" who="S0382" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0326">I think I might have gone I think I went on both</u>
<u n="345" who="S0381">yeah so how long did you er stay in Paris this time?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0326">erm from Thursday till Monday so not a long just a weekend</u>
<u n="347" who="S0381">and did you stay in a hotel or with friends?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0326">we stayed in erm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0382">oh don't tell me in er this amazing apartment</u>
<u n="350" who="S0381" trans="overlap">yeah it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0326">well I stayed in an apartment in in the Marais</u>
<u n="352" who="S0382">cool oh yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0326">erm which <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s friend's apartment</u>
<u n="354" who="S0382">that's cool in the troisieme arrondissement</u>
<u n="355" who="S0381">so do you sort of speak French I mean cos you went through the?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0326">I used to be a lot better</u>
<u n="357" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0326">it's <trunc>str</trunc> it's strange cos sort of I can kind of in theory I can but in practice I just really like feel embarrassed</u>
<u n="359" who="S0381">to to speak</u>
<u n="360" who="S0326">to try even try really</u>
<u n="361" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0326">I'd rather like seem like a I don't know I</u>
<u n="363" who="S0382">well it's amazing</u>
<u n="364" who="S0381">yeah maybe it's even worse to try</u>
<u n="365" who="S0382">it's really hard if you don't</u>
<u n="366" who="S0381" trans="overlap">they're sort of more ruthless than if you just</u>
<u n="367" who="S0382">if you haven't had that sort of basic and you're just sitting in a classroom and hearing it wash over you gives you a kind of basic <unclear/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0381" trans="overlap">yeah but he did do that</u>
<u n="369" who="S0382">I know I know but it's much harder to</u>
<u n="370" who="S0381" trans="overlap">with those lessons yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0382">to achieve kind of critical</u>
<u n="372" who="S0326">yeah especially in Paris and stuff</u>
<u n="373" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0382">and the French speak English much more than they used to and are probably hanging out with English people</u>
<u n="375" who="S0381">does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> speak French?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0382">no</u>
<u n="377" who="S0381">so have you <trunc>sp</trunc> talked to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at all?</u>
<u n="378" who="S0326">I saw him briefly a few times but yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0381">is he recovering from his break up?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0326">probably I don't know</u>
<u n="381" who="S0382">mm?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0326">probably</u>
<u n="383" who="S0382">oh so he's been back a few times?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0326">mm he was back last weekend but I didn't I barely saw him</u>
<u n="385" who="S0381">yeah he told us he was coming back but so that's when you said something about</u>
<u n="386" who="S0382" trans="overlap">oh you thought he meant for good?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0381">yeah I thought it was his Easter break too but I don't think <anon type="place"/> has that long Easter break like <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0382">he probably has a school week</u>
<u n="389" who="S0326">he is finished like I think he's pretty much finished most of his sort of lectures and stuff</u>
<u n="390" who="S0381">whoo</u>
<u n="391" who="S0382">what?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0381">hot mustard</u>
<u n="393" who="S0382">oh</u>
<u n="394" who="S0381">is really hot</u>
<u n="395" who="S0382"><unclear/> on</u>
<u n="396" who="S0381"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0382">yeah so so you don't know if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got a girlfriend or not?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0326">no I don't I mean like I doubt it</u>
<u n="399" who="S0382">I know his best friend is a girl but so maybe it's sort of</u>
<u n="400" who="S0381">god last time we saw him he was in pretty bad shape</u>
<u n="401" who="S0382">was he?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0381">he had a really bad hangover cos he was hanging out with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="403" who="S0382">oh god</u>
<u n="404" who="S0326">you saw him after that as well?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0381">she's a bad influence no yeah he just came why did he come by? he forgot something it was the <trunc>m</trunc> it was the day after your dad's birthday party and he had gone out with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0326">yeah I heard about that</u>
<u n="407" who="S0381"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he was I I have never seen <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> look like that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0382">binges hey oh well mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0381">no I don't know if it was binge or if he just</u>
<u n="410" who="S0382">kept going</u>
<u n="411" who="S0381">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0382">yeah it was really really uncool to drink at all when I was at uni</u>
<u n="413" who="S0381">I didn't like drinking either</u>
<u n="414" who="S0382">when I was eighteen but I mean we got a bit we kind of got into it near the end but relatively mildly alcohol was like street people and <unclear/> not turned on so what about summer what are you planning?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0381">oh yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0382">are you going to get some money?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0381">are you going to apply to summer travelling grant or?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0326">I'm going to go to probably go to Greece for a bit erm</u>
<u n="419" who="S0381">god you have like</u>
<u n="420" who="S0382" trans="overlap"><unclear/> interesting</u>
<u n="421" who="S0381">a pretty amazing life</u>
<u n="422" who="S0382">well part of it is like I mean you know in America?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0381">yeah you just don't do that</u>
<u n="424" who="S0382">going to Greece is like going from Colorado to Tennessee or something</u>
<u n="425" who="S0381">oh yeah that's true that's the way things are here</u>
<u n="426" who="S0326">but actually I <trunc>wo</trunc> I wondered that cos erm my friends in London who live with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> they just closed down their restaurant and they're thinking of things to do next and they might open a go try and open a bar in Austin</u>
<u n="427" who="S0381">oh really?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0326">they're all going to go there in the summer</u>
<u n="429" who="S0381">you can come visit us next year cos we're going to have a big house</u>
<u n="430" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0382">yeah yeah yeah yeah you must</u>
<u n="432" who="S0381">so we were hoping people will come to visit</u>
<u n="433" who="S0382">definitely <pause dur="long"/> yeah maybe they maybe we can get all of you coming I don't know when <unclear/> is</u>
<u n="434" who="S0326">March</u>
<u n="435" who="S0381">March</u>
<u n="436" who="S0382">oh it doesn't <unclear/></u>
<u n="437" who="S0381">it was just ending or it's going on or</u>
<u n="438" who="S0382">really?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0381">yeah I read about it</u>
<u n="440" who="S0382">does it get <trunc>bo</trunc> does it actually fall in the in the UK?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0381">well he would be on break</u>
<u n="442" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="443" who="S0381">maybe not quite</u>
<u n="444" who="S0326">just the end</u>
<u n="445" who="S0382">is it now <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0381">yeah just I think it's either just finished or</u>
<u n="447" who="S0382">oh I didn't know anyway cos now I know that Austin is number two city for gays in America San Francisco</u>
<u n="448" who="S0381">just gays or?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0382">it has the third highest percentage <pause dur="short"/> of resident people who identify as gay <unclear/> nice this wine</u>
<u n="450" who="S0381">it is good where did you get it? did you get it from a wine shop?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0326">there's this thing in <anon type="place"/> it's called <anon type="place"/> wines they probably have one in <anon type="place"/> too</u>
<u n="452" who="S0382">it's really I</u>
<u n="453" who="S0326">I mean it might if you take the bottle it's like five fifty to fill it up</u>
<u n="454" who="S0381">oh really?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0326">and the bottle is like three quid if you don't</u>
<u n="456" who="S0382">oh well that's not cheap</u>
<u n="457" who="S0381" trans="overlap">well that's a good idea so we can take it</u>
<u n="458" who="S0326" trans="overlap">five fifty?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0382">five fifty for a bottle of wine I mean that's fine but it's not cheap</u>
<u n="460" who="S0326" trans="overlap">five pounds fifty?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0381">even even <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is drinking better wine than we are</u>
<u n="462" who="S0382" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="463" who="S0326">five pounds fifty is really cheap</u>
<u n="464" who="S0382">it's pretty well yeah it's not but</u>
<u n="465" who="S0326" trans="overlap">you can't even get a bottle of wine in an off-licence that isn't Echo Falls for five quid</u>
<u n="466" who="S0382">probably true I'd say <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> we've been we're kind of cheap <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0326">but even so like even like I don't like there's I know the secret off-licence brands that if you can buy it are cheap but they're still like six pounds you know? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0381"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="469" who="S0382">you know when we go to Sainsbury's?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0326">that's probably less though than a full bottle I think</u>
<u n="471" who="S0382">erm no it <trunc>sh</trunc> it's probably I'm sure it's refilled</u>
<u n="472" who="S0381">have some salad</u>
<u n="473" who="S0382">you know sometimes you go to Sainsbury's and there's some two pounds off and it's <trunc>of</trunc></u>
<u n="474" who="S0381">we used to drink really cheap wine from Sainsbury's like two pounds a bottle <unclear/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0382">I don't remember</u>
<u n="476" who="S0381">we went we just in France we bought ninety-six bottles of wine</u>
<u n="477" who="S0382">that's right <pause dur="short"/> that was fun</u>
<u n="478" who="S0381">it was fun</u>
<u n="479" who="S0382">fun quite but the most expensive one we bought was like six fifty I think <pause dur="short"/> also</u>
<u n="480" who="S0326">well when I went to Paris all I did was</u>
<u n="481" who="S0382" trans="overlap">babe are you still itching all the time?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0326">mm not really</u>
<u n="483" who="S0382">mm <pause dur="short"/> so yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0326" trans="overlap">what I do in Paris is go to the best restaurants in Paris</u>
<u n="485" who="S0382">mm</u>
<u n="486" who="S0326">oh can you? yeah</u>
<u n="487" who="S0381">such a good idea</u>
<u n="488" who="S0326">cos er me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went to visit our friend from New York who's like a big time chef dude and he's just friends with all the all the <trunc>ga</trunc> all the chefs and they all <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0382">I don't think I've ever been to a posh restaurant</u>
<u n="490" who="S0381" trans="overlap">so nice</u>
<u n="491" who="S0326">and they don't well they don't even like you don't have to order anything you just sit there</u>
<u n="492" who="S0381">yeah and they just bring you food</u>
<u n="493" who="S0326">for like hours</u>
<u n="494" who="S0381"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0382">how do we get in on this?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0381">oh</u>
<u n="497" who="S0382">one day <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="498" who="S0381">you have to erm</u>
<u n="499" who="S0382">give us a bell</u>
<u n="500" who="S0381">we have we're not foodies so we have to be hooked in</u>
<u n="501" who="S0382" trans="overlap">no we're not no but</u>
<u n="502" who="S0381">or pay money</u>
<u n="503" who="S0326">I'm not a foodie either I don't I don't know what half the stuff they bring me is</u>
<u n="504" who="S0381">yeah it's probably a good thing</u>
<u n="505" who="S0382" trans="overlap">it's probably like grilled testicles and</u>
<u n="506" who="S0326">yeah I know I was I said I was I was eating I had never eaten it before but it was that thing sweetbread</u>
<u n="507" who="S0382">yeah brain</u>
<u n="508" who="S0381">what is that?</u>
<u n="509" who="S0326">yeah it's brain or something and anyway I was like to my friend I said is this pork or octopus?</u>
<u n="510" who="S0381">mm</u>
<u n="511" who="S0326">cos it looks like it's looks like an octopus tastes a bit like fatty pork</u>
<u n="512" who="S0382">not that I ate a lot of that when I was a kid cos</u>
<u n="513" who="S0381">you did?</u>
<u n="514" who="S0382">well it was we were it was cheap it was really cheap</u>
<u n="515" who="S0326">I thought it was like this bit</u>
<u n="516" who="S0382">no the you can the sweetbread is the brain that's all</u>
<u n="517" who="S0326">I thought it was like a bit in the neck</u>
<u n="518" who="S0382">no but I told I was giving some</u>
<u n="519" who="S0381">ah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0382">they're made of meat consciousness is meat</u>
<u n="521" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0382">or something</u>
<u n="523" who="S0381">you should tell your American students that because</u>
<u n="524" who="S0382">I did tell some audience the other day I cos I'm trying to tell them</u>
<u n="525" who="S0381">that would be a <unclear/> they would be grossed out</u>
<u n="526" who="S0382">actually it was perfectly nice if you dice it up and fry it with garlic mm</u>
<u n="527" who="S0381">there's lot there's a lot more food <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="528" who="S0382">I know he wants another <unclear/> right?</u>
<u n="529" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0381">the <unclear/> was good</u>
<u n="531" who="S0326">and more rice rice and beans</u>
<u n="532" who="S0382">it was good but there was only five so one for him and</u>
<u n="533" who="S0381">that's fine</u>
<u n="534" who="S0382">two-thirds for us</u>
<u n="535" who="S0381">there were only five in there?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0382">yeah should have bought more I just didn't know</u>
<u n="537" who="S0381">we did did we only buy one pack?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0382">I bought two packs but I only unfroze one cos we were having the others</u>
<u n="539" who="S0381">oh</u>
<u n="540" who="S0382">okay yeah we need rice do you want some more rice?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0326">yes please</u>
<u n="542" who="S0382">actually you know what I should swizzle the rice with <unclear/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0381">mm</u>
<u n="544" who="S0382">so hang on not too much cos it's</u>
<u n="545" who="S0326"><unclear>I'll have</unclear> another glass of wine then</u>
<u n="546" who="S0381">there are glasses over there <pause dur="long"/> be careful</u>
<u n="547" who="S0382">what?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0381">nothing <pause dur="short"/> yeah this is good</u>
<u n="549" who="S0382">it is it's really it's really it's not bullshit it's not</u>
<u n="550" who="S0381">mm</u>
<u n="551" who="S0382">yeah no there was a movement I remember back in the eighties or nineties this is like <unclear/> rice</u>
<u n="552" who="S0381">yeah I'll have some</u>
<u n="553" who="S0382">where they thought they'd set up these shops with these big steel vats with wine in and then people would just come in and fill up like that</u>
<u n="554" who="S0326">that's exactly what that is that shop is though</u>
<u n="555" who="S0382">was it steel vats?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="557" who="S0381">we should go there</u>
<u n="558" who="S0382">yeah well there you are so somebody has imported the concept</u>
<u n="559" who="S0381">just take this to the <anon type="place"/> wines and</u>
<u n="560" who="S0382">yeah but</u>
<u n="561" who="S0381">have it</u>
<u n="562" who="S0382">cheaper to have a booze cruise</u>
<u n="563" who="S0381">I know</u>
<u n="564" who="S0382">yeah you get the slightest <unclear/> on your principles</u>
<u n="565" who="S0381">now we can have a</u>
<u n="566" who="S0382">there's more English ones too</u>
<u n="567" who="S0326" trans="overlap">ninety-six bottles of wine</u>
<u n="568" who="S0381">oh wait so what are you going to do for the summer?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0326">erm I don't know go to Greece with</u>
<u n="570" who="S0382" trans="overlap">Greece</u>
<u n="571" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0326"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants to buy somewhere</u>
<u n="573" who="S0382">wow</u>
<u n="574" who="S0381">she wants to buy a house in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0326">or something yeah but</u>
<u n="576" who="S0382">good grief</u>
<u n="577" who="S0381">god I wonder if</u>
<u n="578" who="S0326">so she's looking at it and she thinks she can get it for the amount of money</u>
<u n="579" who="S0382">two a penny</u>
<u n="580" who="S0381">yeah very good time</u>
<u n="581" who="S0382">cos she hasn't really it's not really an investment for her she just wants to have somewhere to go but you can get she has like a bigger sort of like bar on the beach has a pool table and stuff and it's like seven thousand</u>
<u n="582" who="S0382">quid? jeez</u>
<u n="583" who="S0326">euros yeah</u>
<u n="584" who="S0382">euros</u>
<u n="585" who="S0381">I wonder though you know what? I wonder what's going to happen if they leave the eurozone it'll probably get even cheaper</u>
<u n="586" who="S0382" trans="overlap">it doesn't matter no maybe not necessarily</u>
<u n="587" who="S0381">really?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0382">I mean that's so cheap it's ridiculous</u>
<u n="589" who="S0381">yeah sure</u>
<u n="590" who="S0326">I think Athens is going to be like Berlin or something cos when I was there just for one say last summer it just seemed really sort of cool and like happy</u>
<u n="591" who="S0382">cool</u>
<u n="592" who="S0326">a lot of young people there</u>
<u n="593" who="S0382">hey babe what about this? did you heat this up?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0381">no I forgot</u>
<u n="595" who="S0382">well would you like a normal sausage <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="596" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="597" who="S0381">I'll have half a one my nose is burning what about the peas? shall we have some more peas?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0382">want more peas? yeah you do peas you're the pea <unclear/> yeah it's a it's a it's a funny <trunc>co</trunc> it's always a dream to have a house abroad</u>
<u n="599" who="S0381">so but the thing is how do you</u>
<u n="600" who="S0382">but sometimes</u>
<u n="601" who="S0381">you have to get one that you could shut down really safely you know while you're not there right?</u>
<u n="602" who="S0382" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="603" who="S0326">yeah but I mean it's not I don't know if it's like gonna have to be that sort of</u>
<u n="604" who="S0381" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> peas?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0326">yes please lots of people go sort of they get their house abroad and they put a lot of stuff that they really care about in there and stuff you can like make in really nice you know luxury and like</u>
<u n="606" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="607" who="S0382">yeah maybe not that</u>
<u n="608" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="609" who="S0382">but they only the key thing there is you've got to have some local</u>
<u n="610" who="S0381">that kind of</u>
<u n="611" who="S0382">who can maybe kind of live there when you're not there and deal with all the <trunc>elect</trunc> you know you've got all the electricity utilities and difficult stuff like that yeah wow <pause dur="long"/> wonder what's going to happen to Greece okay so Greece but what else? aren't you going to go to where would? you know I was trying to think what I was going where I was I would want to go to <anon type="place"/> and places like that in Turkey</u>
<u n="612" who="S0381" trans="overlap">or at least</u>
<u n="613" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="614" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0382">I mean we went far from there when we were in Turkey but</u>
<u n="616" who="S0326">it's quite hard when you can't drive</u>
<u n="617" who="S0381">oh yeah you need to get your licence</u>
<u n="618" who="S0326">yeah like <unclear/> to get a car and like</u>
<u n="619" who="S0381">yeah and just it's pretty can <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> drive or does she not? maybe you should do your licence together</u>
<u n="620" who="S0382">it's fun driving</u>
<u n="621" who="S0381">you should maybe you should try to do that this summer</u>
<u n="622" who="S0326">yeah probably</u>
<u n="623" who="S0381">just read the book</u>
<u n="624" who="S0382"><unclear/></u>
<u n="625" who="S0381">basically and then</u>
<u n="626" who="S0382">what you really need does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have a car?</u>
<u n="627" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="628" who="S0382">no because that's the way that's how I did it I just had a girlfriend with a car <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="629" who="S0381" trans="overlap">no but you can rent a car</u>
<u n="630" who="S0326">her flatmate might buy one</u>
<u n="631" who="S0382">what? buy a car?</u>
<u n="632" who="S0326">yeah cos he just sold his restaurant so he's like</u>
<u n="633" who="S0382">who did?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0326">like her flatmate her friends</u>
<u n="635" who="S0382">oh</u>
<u n="636" who="S0326">she she lives with this couple that like ran a restaurant in <anon type="place"/> for the last six years and have had enough and sold it</u>
<u n="637" who="S0382">what are they going to do now?</u>
<u n="638" who="S0326">open a bar in Austin or something</u>
<u n="639" who="S0381">so did they sell it as with the name and all the?</u>
<u n="640" who="S0326">no they just sold their lease and like it's sort of <trunc>so</trunc> the amount people are willing to sort of pay for like just a lease round there is really crazy</u>
<u n="641" who="S0381">and it's in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="642" who="S0326">yeah <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="643" who="S0382">do you know how hot Austin is?</u>
<u n="644" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="645" who="S0381">it's frigging hot in the summer</u>
<u n="646" who="S0326">he's <trunc>ma</trunc> he's Australian though the guy</u>
<u n="647" who="S0382">oh</u>
<u n="648" who="S0381">oh so he's</u>
<u n="649" who="S0382">there's quite a lot of Aussies in Austin yeah there's one really what's that place we liked? the French Bakery or something what's it called?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0381">yeah it's not the French Bakery but something like it</u>
<u n="651" who="S0382">it was just called something like</u>
<u n="652" who="S0381">yeah it was very simple</u>
<u n="653" who="S0382">it's really nice it's basically a big bread shop but it has a restaurant as well last time we went they gave us this massive <trunc>r</trunc>rye loaf</u>
<u n="654" who="S0381">mm for free</u>
<u n="655" who="S0382" trans="overlap">for free cos it was the end of the day</u>
<u n="656" who="S0381">it was good too</u>
<u n="657" who="S0382">it was really good it was really <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> yeah I don't know</u>
<u n="658" who="S0381">okay Greece and</u>
<u n="659" who="S0326">I don't know it's quite a long way away I probably oh actually I'm going to Portugal I forgot</u>
<u n="660" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="661" who="S0381">when?</u>
<u n="662" who="S0326">like straight after straight <trunc>af</trunc>like twenty-second of June so at the start</u>
<u n="663" who="S0381">oh right after</u>
<u n="664" who="S0382" trans="overlap">oh you went there before didn't you? with you</u>
<u n="665" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="666" who="S0381">where in Portugal?</u>
<u n="667" who="S0326">some place like an hour away from Lisbon</u>
<u n="668" who="S0382">it's called <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="669" who="S0326">it might be that somewhere kind of cool and old style like <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0382">well</u>
<u n="671" who="S0381">we're going to Japan that's our big</u>
<u n="672" who="S0382">yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0326">I want I want to go there</u>
<u n="674" who="S0382">that's work though</u>
<u n="675" who="S0381">yeah I know but at least I want to go there</u>
<u n="676" who="S0326" trans="overlap">when are you going?</u>
<u n="677" who="S0381">erm erm</u>
<u n="678" who="S0382" trans="overlap">end of May</u>
<u n="679" who="S0381" trans="overlap">May yeah end of May</u>
<u n="680" who="S0326">cos my friend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just found a ticket on the internet for three hundred pounds return</u>
<u n="681" who="S0381">to Japan?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0326">yeah London</u>
<u n="683" who="S0382">wow</u>
<u n="684" who="S0381">what airline?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0326">like weird ones you know like with stops?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0382">oh yeah</u>
<u n="687" who="S0326">that's how you get around</u>
<u n="688" who="S0382">yeah yeah why not?</u>
<u n="689" who="S0381">yeah I'm post that I just want I mean that's a lot of stops he probably has to make</u>
<u n="690" who="S0326">I think it's actually just like one in each city</u>
<u n="691" who="S0381">oh okay</u>
<u n="692" who="S0326">I can't remember maybe like one in the in the Far East</u>
<u n="693" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0326">but I <trunc>wa</trunc> I was going to try and go with him but he's going before I finish school</u>
<u n="695" who="S0381">I mean that really is a different <trunc>ga</trunc> a different thing you know you can't read a word</u>
<u n="696" who="S0326">yeah but they do have a lot some lots of signs have English on them</u>
<u n="697" who="S0381">yeah they do</u>
<u n="698" who="S0382" trans="overlap">yeah it probably says Coca-Cola in</u>
<u n="699" who="S0381">where is he going in do you know?</u>
<u n="700" who="S0326">well he's learnt Japanese like on the computer for a bit he's like has like really interested in the culture</u>
<u n="701" who="S0381">we need to get a book because apparently getting around Tokyo is a nightmare because of the way their streets are</u>
<u n="702" who="S0382" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <unclear/> numbers or something all the numbered</u>
<u n="703" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="704" who="S0382">there's some weird thing about</u>
<u n="705" who="S0381">it's some like they're numbered according to</u>
<u n="706" who="S0382">when they were built</u>
<u n="707" who="S0381">when they were built and so</u>
<u n="708" who="S0326">there's a restaurant where you can fish your own fish before you eat it</u>
<u n="709" who="S0382">what? you you can</u>
<u n="710" who="S0326">you sit there like at a sort of bar or something with a</u>
<u n="711" who="S0382">oh you don't just point and say I want that one</u>
<u n="712" who="S0381">shit so do you like fishy fish? do you like that?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0326">I kind of like all fish</u>
<u n="714" who="S0382" trans="overlap">I like fish but I don't</u>
<u n="715" who="S0326">what's a fishy fish?</u>
<u n="716" who="S0381">like</u>
<u n="717" who="S0382">well you know the fish that's sort of</u>
<u n="718" who="S0381">what was that fish we had?</u>
<u n="719" who="S0382">a fishy fish I just meant you know it's like the difference between white fish which is really not</u>
<u n="720" who="S0326">what like kippers and stuff?</u>
<u n="721" who="S0382">yeah kippers</u>
<u n="722" who="S0381">no I wasn't kippers they're not I mean what was that fish we had that</u>
<u n="723" who="S0382">that was that was</u>
<u n="724" who="S0381">in in Antwerp?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0382">that was erm pickled mackerel it was</u>
<u n="726" who="S0381">the <trunc>sa</trunc></u>
<u n="727" who="S0382">yeah</u>
<u n="728" who="S0381">er</u>
<u n="729" who="S0382">yeah it just wasn't well done I think actually I don't think it was</u>
<u n="730" who="S0381">oh oh</u>
<u n="731" who="S0326">it sounds good to me</u>
<u n="732" who="S0381">I thought we both we looked at each other we both had the same reaction thank god it was</u>
<u n="733" who="S0382">yeah well I'm a real wimp you know I don't like shellfish and</u>
<u n="734" who="S0381">oysters</u>
<u n="735" who="S0382">sea <trunc>ur</trunc> sea urchins like fishy fish</u>
<u n="736" who="S0326">that's the place that place in Essex we went to is famous for oysters that's what people go there to do</u>
<u n="737" who="S0382">I don't like the chewy or is that mussels?</u>
<u n="738" who="S0381">I don't like it's kind of slimy</u>
<u n="739" who="S0326">you don't chew oysters</u>
<u n="740" who="S0381">no just like they go right down your throat</u>
<u n="741" who="S0382">what do you do?</u>
<u n="742" who="S0326">if you're chewing it you do that's like it's really disgusting if you chew it obviously</u>
<u n="743" who="S0381" trans="overlap">it's an oyster shooter</u>
<u n="744" who="S0382">so what is what is the taste but then there's no taste is there?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0326">no no there is you just you swallow it and then it's like get</u>
<u n="746" who="S0381">it slides down your throat</u>
<u n="747" who="S0326">and it's like getting hit in the face with a wave or something but refreshing you know?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0381">I've only done it once I can't remember</u>
<u n="749" who="S0382">done what once?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0381">an oyster shooter</u>
<u n="751" who="S0326">shooter <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="752" who="S0381">that's what they call them we say oyster shooter I was at some</u>
<u n="753" who="S0382" trans="overlap">in the United States</u>
<u n="754" who="S0381">yeah at a Boxing Day party and they had oyster shooters I swear that's what they called them and you just</u>
<u n="755" who="S0326">in the shell?</u>
<u n="756" who="S0382" trans="overlap">what is it though?</u>
<u n="757" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="758" who="S0326">yeah that's you kind of</u>
<u n="759" who="S0381" trans="overlap">it was disgusting</u>
<u n="760" who="S0326">just you spray lemon on it and Tabasco and pepper</u>
<u n="761" who="S0382">is it still alive or something?</u>
<u n="762" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="763" who="S0381">no god that would be really something</u>
<u n="764" who="S0382">well that was really nice</u>
<u n="765" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="766" who="S0382">you're meant to have a merguez cruise go and stock up on organic you know</u>
<u n="767" who="S0381" trans="overlap">yeah just have a have a meat cruise you know</u>
<u n="768" who="S0382">yeah if you get a day return it probably pays for itself if you buy two <trunc>da</trunc></u>
<u n="769" who="S0381">or you could just spend the night</u>
<u n="770" who="S0382">yeah you could <pause dur="short"/> yeah you could but I mean if you really were trying to maximise the profit you'd do a day return and just like</u>
<u n="771" who="S0381" trans="overlap">yeah true and where would we go?</u>
<u n="772" who="S0382">well I my my theory</u>
<u n="773" who="S0381">that place we went?</u>
<u n="774" who="S0382">my theory is that you get away from Calais</u>
<u n="775" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="776" who="S0382">because Calais is just designed to sell stuff</u>
<u n="777" who="S0381">yeah we only had to drive an hour away we were already</u>
<u n="778" who="S0382">yeah indeed that's right</u>
<u n="779" who="S0381">ah</u>
<u n="780" who="S0382">ah that was good</u>
<u n="781" who="S0381"><unclear/> good cook</u>
<u n="782" who="S0382">oh I moved it</u>
<u n="783" who="S0326">can I have another bit of bread or?</u>
<u n="784" who="S0382">yeah you can you can have our final oh what is happening tomorrow? oh we'll get the car if it doesn't blow up again four hundred quid on the car five hundred quid on the skip</u>
<u n="785" who="S0326">the skip is expensive</u>
<u n="786" who="S0326">that's insane</u>
<u n="787" who="S0382">well the thing is I've I've got a permit for four weeks</u>
<u n="788" who="S0381">oh</u>
<u n="789" who="S0382">but <anon type="place"/>'s <trunc>ru</trunc>running some <trunc>sche</trunc> I don't I don't think it's as expensive in other boroughs</u>
<u n="790" who="S0381">mm</u>
<u n="791" who="S0382">I don't suppose it's expensive in <anon type="place"/> for example</u>
<u n="792" who="S0326">all every single council is running schemes they're all corrupt and like crooked because they had to make this money because the government have pulled it out from under their feet a bit</u>
<u n="793" who="S0381">oh really?</u>
<u n="794" who="S0326">so they're really just like selling off everything and like</u>
<u n="795" who="S0381">oh maybe like that's why they</u>
<u n="796" who="S0326">the long-term repercussions of stripping those councils of their money is going to be like it's going to bad because</u>
<u n="797" who="S0381">well they want to become their own governments but we saw that cities want to become their own governments</u>
<u n="798" who="S0326">but not sort of boroughs</u>
<u n="799" who="S0381">no</u>
<u n="800" who="S0382" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah this is like well well London boroughs of course have got more people in them than most cities but yeah I doubt it's so</u>
<u n="801" who="S0381">it's true</u>
<u n="802" who="S0382">and it looks like the kind of surge in interest in cricket is dropping away now</u>
<u n="803" who="S0381">well we haven't been watching it</u>
<u n="804" who="S0326">that's cos that's cos England are so crap</u>
<u n="805" who="S0382">it's just hysteria</u>
<u n="806" who="S0381">who did they lose to? Sri Lanka?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0326">no Bangladesh</u>
<u n="808" who="S0381">mm well good for Bangladesh and what happened to them did they?</u>
<u n="809" who="S0326">they got knocked out</u>
<u n="810" who="S0382">they were knocked out</u>
<u n="811" who="S0326">in the in a tournament that's basically designed to make it impossible for that to happen</u>
<u n="812" who="S0381">so was has the final been played?</u>
<u n="813" who="S0382">no</u>
<u n="814" who="S0381">is it's Australia versus New Zealand?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0382">no I think there's still some</u>
<u n="816" who="S0326">New Zealand's in the final and Australia play India tonight for the other final spot</u>
<u n="817" who="S0381">oh I hope India wins</u>
<u n="818" who="S0326">no I hope Australia wins</u>
<u n="819" who="S0381">right mm</u>
<u n="820" who="S0326">and then they're gonna lose in the final</u>
<u n="821" who="S0382">oh yeah</u>
<u n="822" who="S0381">yeah I'd I'd like to see New Zealand win</u>
<u n="823" who="S0382">New Zealand oh yeah you know the pleasure that would give the New Zealanders would be like worth everything</u>
<u n="824" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="825" who="S0382">it's such a shame I kind of knew that would happen</u>
<u n="826" who="S0381">what?</u>
<u n="827" who="S0382">we got to the top and then</u>
<u n="828" who="S0326">the thing about it is that it's not even the team it's just sort of people like there's like people in sort of the executive positions in the ECB this guy Paul Downton who fired Pietersen and like had all these sort of big ideas but he's totally removed from</u>
<u n="829" who="S0382">it's exactly</u>
<u n="830" who="S0381">oh yeah</u>
<u n="831" who="S0382">it's like the health service the police and universities</u>
<u n="832" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah and trains</u>
<u n="833" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="834" who="S0382">layers and layers of</u>
<u n="835" who="S0381">removed bureaucrats</u>
<u n="836" who="S0382" trans="overlap">of admin yeah cost and they all have you know like SUVs you know and all the bull old it's disgusting it's like with the decline and fall of the Roman empire</u>
<u n="837" who="S0381">who is it?</u>
<u n="838" who="S0326">I read a really good piece about problems in universities today</u>
<u n="839" who="S0382">oh</u>
<u n="840" who="S0326">I can't remember who wrote it <trunc>Ma</trunc>Marina something</u>
<u n="841" who="S0382">Marina Warner yeah in the LRB I was reading that yeah I she's okay</u>
<u n="842" who="S0326">I thought it was a good piece anyway</u>
<u n="843" who="S0382">it was a good piece I read most of it</u>
<u n="844" who="S0381">what was she saying? what's the problem?</u>
<u n="845" who="S0382">just described how how grotesque it is and she's always been a freelance but she's been working in I think Essex and these guys just come along telling you what to do and</u>
<u n="846" who="S0326">well everything has sort of become <trunc>mid</trunc> everyone everything now is expected to be business models</u>
<u n="847" who="S0381">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="848" who="S0382">that's right and I've seen programmes on the NHS how they've done that and on the police they've applied this model that doesn't work</u>
<u n="849" who="S0381">the business model</u>
<u n="850" who="S0382">all these all these institutions had their own perfectly reasonable things that worked and they've all been fucked by bureaucrats in Whitehall</u>
<u n="851" who="S0381">Whitehall</u>
<u n="852" who="S0382">well we say Whitehall it's kind of the generic term for</u>
<u n="853" who="S0381">for government?</u>
<u n="854" who="S0382">yeah I mean <trunc>wa</trunc> it's like DC</u>
<u n="855" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="856" who="S0382">no there have been a series but there might be how come you saw that online?</u>
<u n="857" who="S0326">I just picked it up today when I was <trunc>wa</trunc> I was went to the library today but just before I wanted to kill some time so and I saw it on the</u>
<u n="858" who="S0382">Marina Warner god bit of a slag no she's she's nice but she's very sort of she's always written about she was Martin Amis' girlfriend once and then do you remember a time she suddenly started coming to <anon type="place"/> road because she was having</u>
<u n="859" who="S0381" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you want some more? no I don't remember</u>
<u n="860" who="S0382">she took up with some guy at the end of <anon type="place"/> road don't you remember? oh you</u>
<u n="861" who="S0381">no I don't must have not been me</u>
<u n="862" who="S0382">well I interviewed her</u>
<u n="863" who="S0381">I remember there was someone that came and took a bench</u>
<u n="864" who="S0382" trans="overlap">some some sweetheart no no that was</u>
<u n="865" who="S0381">was that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>' wife</u>
<u n="866" who="S0382">that was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>' wife that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would know hey big treat do you want a chocolate pop from France?</u>
<u n="867" who="S0326">er maybe</u>
<u n="868" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="869" who="S0382">er it doesn't have <unclear/> but it goes to the posh workshop</u>
<u n="870" who="S0381">yeah he's sort of</u>
<u n="871" who="S0382">he's like moved out of my range there's a vanilla one or have you got something classier?</u>
<u n="872" who="S0381">no</u>
<u n="873" who="S0382">oh we have we've got</u>
<u n="874" who="S0381">the fancy chocolate pop</u>
<u n="875" who="S0382">have we got one left?</u>
<u n="876" who="S0381">I don't know I don't know we ate the vanilla ones</u>
<u n="877" who="S0326">were they the GU ones or something?</u>
<u n="878" who="S0381">I don't know</u>
<u n="879" who="S0326">I don't really like those</u>
<u n="880" who="S0382">wow that's alright <unclear/> Danone Danette</u>
<u n="881" who="S0326">six Danette seven</u>
<u n="882" who="S0382">erm yeah we ate the <unclear/> ones it's true oh well oh we got a <trunc>bu</trunc>b how do you think your brownies are holding up?</u>
<u n="883" who="S0381">I don't know they've been in there for a while</u>
<u n="884" who="S0382">I bet they are</u>
<u n="885" who="S0381">and they're sort of semi-burnt ones aren't they?</u>
<u n="886" who="S0382">oh are these the crusts? why don't we</u>
<u n="887" who="S0381">yeah they're the crust I just want to try it</u>
<u n="888" who="S0382" trans="overlap">why don't we get them out of the freezer cos you can eat them out the freezer</u>
<u n="889" who="S0381">let's just see yeah it's pretty dry <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="890" who="S0382">aren't there some more in the freezer like?</u>
<u n="891" who="S0381">there's a yeah</u>
<u n="892" who="S0382">would you like a brownie section?</u>
<u n="893" who="S0381">actually it's</u>
<u n="894" who="S0382">would you like to find it?</u>
<u n="895" who="S0381">it's not bad try it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="896" who="S0382">not bad</u>
<u n="897" who="S0326">I bet there's a good brownie recipe in in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s book</u>
<u n="898" who="S0381">I'll have to try it</u>
<u n="899" who="S0326">with like salt sea salt</u>
<u n="900" who="S0382" trans="overlap">this is what?</u>
<u n="901" who="S0326">I think they have like sea salt on the top</u>
<u n="902" who="S0382">ah</u>
<u n="903" who="S0381">yeah I looked through it there are a lot of yummy things are you going to eat the one out of the freezer?</u>
<u n="904" who="S0382">well erm not really I mean I thought we were going to eat this <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> made this <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> made this for my birthday</u>
<u n="905" who="S0381">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s probably eaten all of them</u>
<u n="906" who="S0326">I don't actually I don't really eat eat any of any of the cakes</u>
<u n="907" who="S0382">so what are you going to do when you grow up <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="908" who="S0326">I don't know</u>
<u n="909" who="S0381">when you grow up?</u>
<u n="910" who="S0382">I mean</u>
<u n="911" who="S0381">he's only he's only finishing his second year you know</u>
<u n="912" who="S0382">I know but <unclear/> I was</u>
<u n="913" who="S0326">you can't start asking him that</u>
<u n="914" who="S0382">I just went on to graduate cos it was two years' free money I didn't have any further motive</u>
<u n="915" who="S0381">but it's not it's not like that anymore</u>
<u n="916" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="917" who="S0382">oh</u>
<u n="918" who="S0381">you don't they're not just throwing money at people to go to graduate school</u>
<u n="919" who="S0326">who want to do classics</u>
<u n="920" who="S0381">no</u>
<u n="921" who="S0382">these are frozen I think I think you'll find that you can just bite it but be careful yeah mm yeah great and I might have it with what are you going to have?</u>
<u n="922" who="S0381">yeah I might have I want vanilla</u>
<u n="923" who="S0382">mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="924" who="S0381">no</u>
<u n="925" who="S0326">er</u>
<u n="926" who="S0382">so which restaurant have you been to one of these posh restaurants in Paris yet?</u>
<u n="927" who="S0326">me?</u>
<u n="928" who="S0382">mm</u>
<u n="929" who="S0381">he's been to all of them</u>
<u n="930" who="S0326">that's what I was doing when I was there</u>
<u n="931" who="S0382">so tell me the name oh I see</u>
<u n="932" who="S0326">erm Chateaubriand was one</u>
<u n="933" who="S0382">probably <unclear/></u>
<u n="934" who="S0326">erm</u>
<u n="935" who="S0382">mm</u>
<u n="936" who="S0326">Bat Baratin</u>
<u n="937" who="S0382">what?</u>
<u n="938" who="S0326">Baratin Baratin B A R A T I N</u>
<u n="939" who="S0381">this is too frozen</u>
<u n="940" who="S0382">maybe these are the new ones what is the place kind of an incredibly famous old one?</u>
<u n="941" who="S0326">I don't think le Baratin I think that's only <trunc>fa</trunc> like famous in new famously rather</u>
<u n="942" who="S0382">right</u>
<u n="943" who="S0326">cos the woman in there is this really like sort this tall sort of Spanish woman who like smokes in her own restaurant and she's there all the time and it's been there for like fifty years cooking and in the last like ten years it's become like in all the like ten best restaurants ever or whatever</u>
<u n="944" who="S0382">cool wow it's delicious I'm going to finish that <pause dur="short"/> I can't really remember the the name it's like where Proust <unclear/> or something</u>
<u n="945" who="S0326">those ones don't exist anymore though what's the famous one?</u>
<u n="946" who="S0382">some of them do</u>
<u n="947" who="S0326">what's that one? that erm</u>
<u n="948" who="S0382">le le La Tour d'Argent was one of them the Silver Dart</u>
<u n="949" who="S0381">and that's still there?</u>
<u n="950" who="S0382">well I should think so</u>
<u n="951" who="S0326">what's the one where they sort of had it took it's everybody's sauce they got so many ashtrays stolen from them they tried they took the name off the ashtrays to see if it would stop and it didn't</u>
<u n="952" who="S0382">that's right that's right I think that <trunc>mi</trunc> was that a cafe or a restaurant?</u>
<u n="953" who="S0326">I think it was a sort of restaurant thinking in my head it begins with M</u>
<u n="954" who="S0382">I can't remember <pause dur="long"/> mm very difficult to mark down the keyboard</u>
<u n="955" who="S0381">mm</u>
<u n="956" who="S0382">there's one I'm just not remembering there's de la Tour d'Argent and one other</u>
<u n="957" who="S0381">yeah but you're just</u>
<u n="958" who="S0326">La Maitre</u>
<u n="959" who="S0382">mm?</u>
<u n="960" who="S0326">La Martre?</u>
<u n="961" who="S0382">tomato?</u>
<u n="962" who="S0326">Clematre?</u>
<u n="963" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="964" who="S0382">no no no mm</u>
<u n="965" who="S0381">he didn't go to that many restaurants though</u>
<u n="966" who="S0326">I was only there for three days four days</u>
<u n="967" who="S0382">right</u>
<u n="968" who="S0326">but it was the same when we were in New York with this guy he took us like to some crazy one <pause dur="short"/> cos he has one one of the crazy ones himself there</u>
<u n="969" who="S0381">really?</u>
<u n="970" who="S0382">what about Noma in Copenhagen you've got to go there</u>
<u n="971" who="S0381">oh yeah that's a fancy one</u>
<u n="972" who="S0382">Noma it's number one in the world at the moment or it was it's that sort of cooking nettles on the roadside</u>
<u n="973" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="974" who="S0381" trans="overlap">yeah it's all local</u>
<u n="975" who="S0382">yeah</u>
<u n="976" who="S0381">so are you interested in the restaurant business and food and stuff?</u>
<u n="977" who="S0382">he's not</u>
<u n="978" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="979" who="S0381">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="980" who="S0326">well it'd be good I mean sort of good for things if like if you could do it's like food writing and stuff cos it's just like it's fun and there's good freebies</u>
<u n="981" who="S0381" trans="overlap">oh right yeah you could do that</u>
<u n="982" who="S0382" trans="overlap">he already wrote</u>
<u n="983" who="S0326">I already did it</u>
<u n="984" who="S0382">in Berlin</u>
<u n="985" who="S0326">I didn't know anything at that at that point</u>
<u n="986" who="S0381" trans="overlap">oh that's right you did it</u>
<u n="987" who="S0382">that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="988" who="S0381">was he a restaurant critic?</u>
<u n="989" who="S0382">he used to have his own restaurant</u>
<u n="990" who="S0381">really? he's really successful actually</u>
<u n="991" who="S0382">mm my god does he want to be famous</u>
<u n="992" who="S0381">really?</u>
<u n="993" who="S0382">mm he's desperate to be famous</u>
<u n="994" who="S0381">mm oh I think he's succeeded</u>
<u n="995" who="S0382">yeah he has <pause dur="short"/> I remember he came to sit when I was teaching in <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/> he was drawing little cartoons for the New Statesmen he's developed a kind of character this kind of totally depressed lump of</u>
<u n="996" who="S0381">himself</u>
<u n="997" who="S0382">he wanted me to try and get one in a few <unclear/></u>
<u n="998" who="S0381">they don't put cartoons in it really</u>
<u n="999" who="S0382">no they could have but I think it was called Slump the character mm do you think those would be good too?</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0381">yeah so does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like cooking in general or she just sort of knows her baking?</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0326">mm she doesn't like she <trunc>do</trunc> I think so yeah a little bit but not that much</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0382">oh look it</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0381">her book is really good actually the erm the story part sort of description and</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0382">oh you've been reading have you?</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0381">yeah I've been reading it</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0382">I knew what you were doing up there</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0381">I read through it</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0382">I got to <unclear/> stop doing that I'm working</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0381" trans="overlap">I was looking for recipes</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0382">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="1011" who="S0326">yeah yeah I think I mean she I don't really like know that I don't really know much of her even her cakes</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0381">yeah you haven't god <pause dur="short"/> maybe she doesn't eat them either</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0326">she has like one bite probably you know she's like really quite thin</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0382">I can see that</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0326">obviously she does like I think for her the baking is sort of more just a like to see what she can do now</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0382">yeah</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0326">rather than like cos it's very sort the way things look and she lots of <trunc>maga</trunc> she does lots of a photoshoots with cakes but people no one's eating them really</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0381">right right</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0382">what happens to them?</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0326">they sort of have do some photos and then someone like puts their foot through it and they take a photo of that and they put it on the cover</u>
<u n="1022" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1023" who="S0326">I can <trunc>fi</trunc> find her</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0382">you should eat them</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0381">I'm sure a lot of people take bites and</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0382">well they should go and give them to the the poor</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0381">yeah put them on the street somebody would eat it</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0326">this is <trunc>ha</trunc> what <unclear/></u>
<u n="1029" who="S0381">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0326">erm which is like where she sells them</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0381">she has a lot of fancy cakes</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0326">they're show cakes and I guess she has lots of I think she only really bakes if someone wants a wedding cake or a or as a commission cake</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0381">yeah damn they are sort of artistic looking</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0382" trans="overlap">show me</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0381">her book isn't like this it's very you know you sort of straightforward recipes look at these</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0382">wow blimey <pause dur="short"/> tea party that's funny Christ how do I go back? just that</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0381">I don't know</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0382">oh I lost it oh it's still recording does does does em</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0381" trans="overlap">you're getting a lot of good hours on this</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0382">does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s thing record too?</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0326">they all do all Iphones</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0382">mm mm how do you record? is it like erm</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0381">I have no idea</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0382">what it's called the button?</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0326">it's an app called Voice Memos</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0382">oh <pause dur="long"/> mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1047" who="S0381">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have you guys always had Polish builders when you had work done?</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0326">no but when like erm when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> moved she had a Polish guy who had like sort of set up he was sort of leader of lots of like had like a whole crew of</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0381">yeah old people</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0326" trans="overlap">lots and lots and lots of guys he kind of went round in a nice car like sorting everybody out</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0381">oh wow</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0326">they were working but they I guess they sort of arrived from Poland and he gives them the job</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0381">yeah right</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0326">and they were just sort of like I remember cos I was doing stuff like packing up the boxes and helping out while they were doing the real work</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0326">and sort of like they were like always sweating with the effort of what they were doing and they were like super super strong</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0382">they were a kind of crack team</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0382">well these guys seem okay</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0381">I think yeah they seem pretty energetic and they <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1061" who="S0382">well they haven't got that <unclear/> it's funny so the Polish in a way they they they sort of just they sort of <unclear/> it's almost like what we think of as Mediterranean</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0381">yeah they sound like they're fighting</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0382">no well</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0381">they're constantly yelling at each other</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0382">no not to me maybe cos it's more like</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0381">maybe I</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0382">more like French or something</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0381">I took <unclear/> on my <unclear/></u>
<u n="1069" who="S0382">no I don't mealy-mouthed English people</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0381">yeah so are we done with this this?</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0382">woah</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0381"><unclear/> done <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1073" who="S0382">it's been <unclear>open</unclear> a long time <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1074" who="S0381">no</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0382">woah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1076" who="S0381">I put a teeny bit of olive oil</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0382">oh you did?</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0382">okay <pause dur="long"/> they've just decided that all that protein diet stuff is bullshit you know like</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0381">I don't know I think that it isn't I mean it is if you want to lose weight if you just eat protein and no</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0382">I can't believe <unclear/></u>
<u n="1082" who="S0381">and you don't eat any carbs you're gonna lose weight</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0382">it's like <unclear/> the</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0382">yeah what was it meant to do? it was meant to?</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0381">so you could lose weight</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0382">oh <pause dur="long"/> so <anon type="place"/> town I think I think we're going I don't think we're as classy as <anon type="place"/> now</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0381">no</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0382">so we aren't <trunc>get</trunc> we've got</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0381"><anon type="place"/> town</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0326" trans="overlap">no the the thing about <anon type="place"/> town that's really charming cos I <trunc>do</trunc> it hasn't really changed since like I can imagine it being the same similar in the fifties</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0381" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0382">so you know where we've got a Tesco an Iceland a Poundland</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0326">we have all that in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1096" who="S0382" trans="overlap">a Lidl's the new one is a Lidl</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0326">we have all of that</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0382">you do? yeah</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0381" trans="overlap">you have a Lidl's too</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0382">we have a new shop opened at the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1102" who="S0326">that's like yeah that's funny cos like when when all the Woolworth's closed down you could tell what an area was like by what replaced it <pause dur="short"/> we've got an Iceland in <anon type="place"/> a Waitrose in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1103" who="S0382">bloody Waitrose</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0382">that's funny yeah no we we are now way out</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0381">we have a few trendy coffee shops that's for sure</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0382">yeah everywhere has those now</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0381">I think I don't</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0382">are they trendy or?</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0381">yeah they kind of are sort of you know fancy</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0382">yeah so our pizza there was a Pizza Express that closed down <vocal desc="misc"/> still not <unclear/></u>
<u n="1113" who="S0326" trans="overlap">there was never pizza there was never <trunc>piz</trunc> one of those in</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0382">in</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0326">in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1116" who="S0381">that's really erm what is it?</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0382">quite</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0381">corporate</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0326">there's no sort of there's still no sort of Pret a Mangers or Starbucks</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0381" trans="overlap">we have a Nando's</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0326">there's a Nando's but that's cos</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0382">yeah no so it's very very <unclear/></u>
<u n="1123" who="S0326" trans="overlap">Nando's came out from places like <anon type="place"/> rather than into them</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0382">right as soon as you go down to <anon type="place"/> you've got Marks and Spencer's Waitrose</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0381" trans="overlap">oh yeah Waitrose Starbucks</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0382">Starbucks</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0381">Nero's <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if there's Starbucks</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0382" trans="overlap">and what was the one?</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0381">I don't know if there's Starbucks but</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0382">Pret a Manger the whole lot</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0381">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0382">and even a Whole Foods one on <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1133" who="S0381" trans="overlap">oh I like Whole Foods but that's on <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1134" who="S0382">yeah no where my mum lived in the war</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0381">that's really there's not much on that street though</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0382">no so it's I think that's it and so that that will always be there and <anon type="place"/> town will never be able to break free but I I actually I'm happy because</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0381" trans="overlap">you know what's weird there's no one sort of decent clothes shop</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0382">no they haven't</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0381">they're not doing that you can't even buy a pair of underwear on this</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0382" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0326">but the thing is I think in London if you want to buy clothes you just you go <trunc>s</trunc> further afield</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0326">it's not kind of a</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0382">well it yeah you're not gonna is there even a Gap on?</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0381">there's a Gap on <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1146" who="S0382" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> high street yeah so everything is there and it's it's</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0381">yeah yeah that's too far though</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0382">so there's no way that you're gonna need a whole</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0381">that's true</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0382">new set of them</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0381">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0382">for <anon type="place"/> town is actually protected</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0381">yeah that's true it's never going to change always going to be like</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0382">very ethnic</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0381">they we have a lot of erm Muslims <pause dur="short"/> muslim ladies that go to the gym in their full gear</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0382" trans="overlap">yeah I think everywhere probably oh yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1157" who="S0381" trans="overlap"><unclear/> you know they gym they have they're they're fully protected you know on the exercise bike</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0382">yeah I I'm I'm ambivalent about that cos on the one hand I</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0381">must be really I don't know</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0382">it's okay that they</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0381">not that comfortable</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0382">keep their traditions and on the other hand the deep foundation of those traditions is not good it's sexist there's no and it's kind of it's difficult</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0326">all the girls in my school in <anon type="place"/> were always like I like it cos I can just wear whatever I want underneath it and you're like</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0382">did you I would have thought that even your time there would have been more people doing it</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0381">wearing the headscarf and stuff?</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0382">from your first year to your last year</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0326">what do you mean more people doing it?</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0382">well because nobody nobody did it twenty years ago</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0381">you mean wearing a headscarf?</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0326" trans="overlap">well I only start my school only started</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0382">that's true no</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0381">no he means in the time that you</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0382">in the time you were there</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0381">were there by the time you were finished were there more people wearing headscarfs and?</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0326">I can't I wasn't keeping count</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0382">no no because nobody did it before and it's so it's got <trunc>no</trunc> nothing Islam does not require it it's just it just became a kind of statement of identity and what did you just never <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0381">you turn out to</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0382"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1179" who="S0381">no I didn't mean to put it away</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1181" who="S0381">take the brownies away</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0382">it's like make you feel less bad</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0382">yeah what else? nothing really here we all are stacked up in this room</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0381">it's not bad actually I mean</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0382">we got a TV</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0381">it's a little cramped</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0326">what that watch the TV still?</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0381">that's isn't that the TV we bought when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> broke the TV?</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0382">probably yes</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0326">I didn't break the TV</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0381">you did</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0326">was it that massive huge one?</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0381">you knocked it over don't you remember?</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0326" trans="overlap">it needed to get it needed to get broken though it was so old</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0382">it was a big old</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0326">try and put that on there</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0382">a big old-fashioned one</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0381">no I think we got one from your mum</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0382">it had still had a a cathode ray tube</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0381">yeah you're right that we needed a new one</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0382">no it was really good erm <pause dur="long"/> we could see if the</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0381">we could see what's happening with the plane crash</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0382">we could</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0381">my new obsession</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0382">so when have you got to have? when are you having supper with?</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0381">when's your fish?</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0326">erm probably about ten</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0381">oh that's late</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0382">oh very very Spanish but you should have <trunc>ea</trunc> so when did you catch it? what day?</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0326">yesterday</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0382">okay okay that's fine and is there anything special about in <trunc>la</trunc>b I mean <trunc>col</trunc> not are they do they taste different?</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0326">I don't know I mean it looked really like erm they look really good</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0382">they look really beautiful yeah how big do they get when they're full-grown?</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0326">those are full-grown</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0382">I thought cod were massive</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0381" trans="overlap">they look pretty big</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0326">but they're <trunc>di</trunc> that's different species of cod</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0381">oh okay</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0326">but yeah cod and you don't get cod see when you get fish and chips that's a whole cod</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0381">oh really?</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0326">that's like the size of a <trunc>c</trunc> like a sort of</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0382">no</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0326">a little cod yeah</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0382">it's a fillet it's a fillet</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0326">not of not of like it's a fillet but of the <trunc>s</trunc> of like the kind of catch off the coast of England</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0382">I see</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0326">I mean they're a bit bigger than that it's true but it's not I think people think they're like as big as salmon and tuna but they're not like around England they are in sort of the Arctic</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0382">I see so they really rebounded?</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0382">that's cool</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0381">oh my god it looks like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got that job at the University of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1233" who="S0382">oh my god doesn't surprise me</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0381">yeah it's really good for him</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0382">jeez that's incredible <pause dur="short"/> oh well he's had it</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0381">this is really weird they have they they this is our placement record and they're listing the school but not the names</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0382">weird why?</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0381">I don't know</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0382">are you still how long are you recording? how many hours worth are you getting out of us?</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0326">one-and-a-half</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0382">one-and-a-half are we done are we done our hour-and-a-half?</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0326">well it's still going</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0381">he's got he's got an hour-and-a-half so far</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0382">oh I see well <unclear/> alright so I'm going to turn this on</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0381" trans="overlap">what if you started recording the TV? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1246" who="S0382">what?</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0381">what if you just start recording the TV?</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0382">oh yeah that's</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0326" trans="overlap">well it's very obviously</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0382">what?</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0326">that it's not natural oh no</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0381">yeah cos you can hear</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0326" trans="overlap">if you turn the TV on I'll turn it off</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0382">alright well maybe not that</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0381" trans="overlap">you can hear the like the laugh track you can hear the <trunc>la</trunc> a laugh track</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0326">yeah you can't really do it</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0381">I need to get my glasses</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0326">you can't really do it in a bar or in a you know sort of or even if someone plays music it <trunc>di</trunc> it's a bit tricky</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0382" trans="overlap">yeah sure what are you getting?</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0381">my glasses</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0382">yeah get get me a <trunc>la</trunc> a machine</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0381">okay</u>
<event desc="0381 leaves"/>
<u n="1263" who="S0382"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> woah isn't that cool? look at that jeez I didn't know I've never seen his complete poems</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0326">never seen what?</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0382">I've never seen his complete poems I didn't know he wrote so much</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0326">well it's not it's kind you know that guy Daniel Mendelsohn?</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0382">yeah oh Daniel</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0326">it's more about him than about Cavafy really</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0382">oh my god</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1271" who="S0382">oh god</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0326">but it's good it's enough to really really</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0382">he is a wanker Daniel Mendelsohn</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0326">no it's a it's a good piece of work though</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0382">yeah but he's a wanker <pause dur="short"/> he was really he was I had an argument with him in the letters column he was he he accused Eleanor Winghurst of being <unclear/> sort of a gay brother and that's erm</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0326">gay brother</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0382">no I don't like I don't like <trunc>dan</trunc> don't like Daniel Mendelsohn I'm afraid I like Ed Ed Mendelsohn who does <unclear/> but I don't like Daniel he's probably going to be the next editor of the New York Review but you said it's funny you said that cos it's mostly about him why did you say that?</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0326">cos I know like <trunc>Ca</trunc> I mean it's very like when you saw the size of it it's so heavy it's like really</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0382">why do you say it's mostly about Daniel Mendelsohn?</u>
<u n="1280" who="S0326">cos that's cos I there's never really been anything sort of like that about Cavafy before so er at least in English</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0382">yeah but so why is it about Daniel Mendelsohn?</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0326">because sort it's sort of it it it would have been a good it would have been sufficient if it was half the size you know but this is</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0382">cos everyone says he's a complete egomaniac</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0326">yeah but I think he's you know I I think he's a good you know good interesting <trunc>ma</trunc> like writes interesting material</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0382" trans="overlap">doesn't mean he isn't doesn't mean he isn't good at the job</u>
<u n="1286" who="S0326">good scholar</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0382">well he totally falsely accused me of being <unclear>absolutist</unclear> so I wrote one saying no he isn't and <unclear/></u>
<u n="1288" who="S0381"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1289" who="S0326">so I'm thinking of something to do a dissertation on and I can't think</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0381">oh my god how long does it have to be?</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0326">not long like ten thousand</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0382">erm</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0381">mm what what what do you like? do you like</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I'm quite interested in I'm quite interested in like reception you know like</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0382">oh my god</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0381">what? what? reception?</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0382" trans="overlap">it's this trendy kind of</u>
<u n="1298" who="S0381">what's that?</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0382">well they're very into it in classics for sort of</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0326">well it's not it's they're into it in classics <trunc>be</trunc>be</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0382" trans="overlap"><unclear/> reception theory</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0326">because it <trunc>me</trunc> it only <trunc>real</trunc> <trunc>rea</trunc> reason why you would study it</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0382">but what how would you define it? as this like media response or something?</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0326">well it's what I it's what reading a text makes me think about you know cos I'm not from Greece and Rome</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0381">oh so you're like what did he intend or what's the?</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0326">no not necessarily what you know like it's sort of</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0382">no on the contrary what do I feel?</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0381">oh what does the audience take from this?</u>
<u n="1309" who="S0326">no but it's <trunc>behin</trunc> but it's beneath that cos you you <trunc>can</trunc> you have to be strict with yourself</u>
<u n="1310" who="S0382">yeah I actually</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0326">what did Cavafy does with that stuff is just so interesting I think</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0382"><trunc>Ca</trunc>ca he does?</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0381">who?</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0326">all all his poems about sort of <trunc>Alexa</trunc> er Anthony and and Alexandria</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0382">right</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0326">you know he cos he obviously had a real he was engaged with them all the all the time and it shaped the way he worked I'll tell you what I'm I'm not interested in reception of other people from the classics rather that like</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0382">yeah I mean</u>
<u n="1319" who="S0326">I'm interested in Cavafy so I'm interested in how he responds to it</u>
<u n="1320" who="S0382">right</u>
<u n="1321" who="S0326">rather than</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0382">yeah I mean in one way it's complete erm</u>
<u n="1323" who="S0326">and like you know writers <trunc>A</trunc> like Anne Carson</u>
<u n="1324" who="S0382">erm yeah I</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0326">who is like I think like <trunc>fa</trunc> my favourite writer</u>
<u n="1326" who="S0382">oh</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0381">who?</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0326">Anne Carson</u>
<u n="1329" who="S0382">who is she?</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0381">I don't know I haven't read any of her</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0326">a poet and and a classicist</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0381">wow</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0382">right yeah I mean there was a there was a movement and I don't know when where they talked about the intentional fallacy</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0382">and that was meant to be the fallacy of trying to recover the author's intentions</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0381" trans="overlap">mm Roland Barthes</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0382">and this was thought to be a really bad idea but actually I'm not I was sort of quite old-fashioned about that and then then Philip Larkin said when I write a poem erm I like to make a slot machine into which the reader I'm almost quoting him inserts depending on his attention</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0382">his picture is he really gets out exactly what he felt so that's the classic old picture</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0381">oh so the reader gets exactly what Philip Larkin felt</u>
<u n="1341" who="S0382" trans="overlap">what you do you want yeah yeah whereas the extreme reader response people say we don't give a fuck what the author meant it's just what I feel when I read it</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0381">yeah but that's so weird because</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0382">that's the two extremes right erm</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1345" who="S0326">there's <trunc>al</trunc> there's also it's a way it's not just responding when they're sort of reading but when people make sort of another really good poem was Alice Oswald and people <trunc>re</trunc>respond in in their own art</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0382">yeah that's is that part of what you want to do your dissertation on?</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0326" trans="overlap">well I don't know that's like what I'm interested in rather than</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0382">yeah no I think well that's</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0326">it's like if you read sort of the Alice Oswald one is really good to look at cos it's <trunc>s</trunc> it's sort of the Iliad it's a translation of the Iliad but it's</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0382">whose is it?</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0326">Alice Oswald called Memorial</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0382">oh is it the Cavafy translation?</u>
<u n="1353" who="S0326">kind of yeah but it's it's basically every sort of it's every single death in the Iliad</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0382">oh I've heard of this it's really</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0326">sort of one on top of the other</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0382">this rings a bell</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0326">and all the similes are repeated sort of verbatim twice</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0382">oh that's erm oh yeah</u>
<u n="1359" who="S0326">and like sort of <unclear/></u>
<u n="1360" who="S0382">have you told me about it?</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0326">maybe but it's like really <trunc>so</trunc><trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="1362" who="S0382">Alice Oswald</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0326">sort of such good what I think about it it's such good sort of contemporary writing and poetry that makes it and it stems from people who are sort of deeply involved in the classics</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0382">right</u>
<u n="1365" who="S0326">that's why I think it's interesting</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0381">mm so what it what it causes yeah?</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0326" trans="overlap">like what is it about the what is it about the classics that <trunc>ma</trunc> makes people feel like that?</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0382" trans="overlap">she's pretty cool Alice Alice Oswald she is pretty cool</u>
<u n="1369" who="S0326">and that's the same with Anne Carson</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0382">woah she is cool erm yeah so it's like</u>
<u n="1371" who="S0381">and do you think that there's something particular about the classics or is it some kind of just conveying a human?</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0326" trans="overlap">well I think it I I I don't think it can't even just with something as simple as the way someone uses language I don't think that I don't I can't see how I can't see how it cannot sort of affect the way you use English as a writer if you've really properly learnt Latin and Greek</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0381" trans="overlap">mm right</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0326">and like done translating</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0382">maybe she was at <anon type="place"/> when I was teaching there</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0381">right</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0382">erm cool</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0326">and sort of cos <trunc>al</trunc>also to to to be engaged in the classics sort of requires you to be sort of engaged in it's like your imagination has to be <unclear/> awake sort of the whole time to do it it's</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0381">mm</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0326">you're trying to it's all the all you really have is books and it's not really things that kind of are strictly cerebral either you want to sort of be aware in a more immediate sense</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0381">yeah right</u>
<u n="1383" who="S0326">and then you like have your like imagination engaged and sort of to erm linguistic faculties engaged</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0381">right</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0326">all the time as a a classicist</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0382">I think there's something translated</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0381">but that that's going to be true I mean that's going to be true for any translation that you're doing</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0381">so <trunc>wha</trunc>what you one question is is what is particular about you know sort of Greek for example that's shaping their thought that's?</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0326" trans="overlap">root languages</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0381">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0382">mm</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0381">I mean it's an interesting question just in general about the relationship between language and thought so erm Hungarian for example has a really weird grammatical structure so their thinking process is supposed to be especially great for mathematics for example</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0326">right</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0382">yeah</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0381">which is kind of a but that is an interesting that's an interesting question in itself that's got to be part of it</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0326">yeah but then</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0381">part of the</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0326">yeah but then</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0381">how did Greek</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0382">is this you're talking about Hungarian?</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0382">yeah I was talking to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about that she said yeah well actually they were all Jewish anyway so</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0381">yeah but</u>
<u n="1406" who="S0382">she suggested that it's because of that</u>
<u n="1407" who="S0381">pff oh</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0382">she's Jewish herself but she was sort of saying well it's not the genius of the Hungarian language it's just that</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0381">well if there's if there's one <trunc>exam</trunc> if there's like sort of</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0382">I think it I</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0381">I mean I guess if they're all Jewish then that would be sort of a question</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0382">they're not all but mostly yeah that could go that</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0326" trans="overlap">like Hungarian Hungarian chess champions</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0381">right</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0382">it is yeah that's right it is it could be true cos apparently</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0326">Russian <unclear/></u>
<u n="1417" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0382">apparently Hungarian is uniquely free in kind of word order or something</u>
<u n="1419" who="S0381">is it what is it related to any other language I mean?</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0382">yeah it's related to Finnish and it's a <trunc>pa</trunc> it's a member of Finno-Ugric language group has it's completely weird</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0381">anyway I think that would be <trunc>in</trunc></u>
<u n="1422" who="S0382">it's not at all like Romance languages or Semitic languages</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0382">anyway</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0381">sounds like a good question I mean you don't I don't know</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I've got a friend in <anon type="place"/> from Hungary she struggles with English I think</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0326">in in Hungary you know I I thought it was I found it interesting she asked people from like who learn different languages what how animals talk in that language an English frogs say ribbit ribbit ribbit</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0381">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0326">and in Hungarian they go ra ca ca</u>
<u n="1431" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1432" who="S0381">that does kind of sound like a</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0326">ra ca ca ra ca ca</u>
<u n="1434" who="S0382">yeah and in in Aristophanes they go croax croax or something don't they somehow</u>
<u n="1435" who="S0381">that is so funny but both sound but ribbit does that? yeah they kind of go <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1436" who="S0382" trans="overlap">exactly the same in America</u>
<u n="1437" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1438" who="S0382">well cos frogs do different things don't they?</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1440" who="S0382">I bet you that this Alice her her surname must her maiden name must be different she took her husband's name yeah she must she must have been doing classics when I was teaching</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0326">that that and they should if you should get a chance to read to read Anne Carson</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0382">yeah I will I like <unclear>recommendations</unclear></u>
<u n="1443" who="S0381">do you ever read the sort of a Greek sentence and think erm that's something some thought particular to that language that you wouldn't really think in English or it strikes you as or maybe just lose that in translation? I don't know</u>
<u n="1444" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I think that well if you're doing I mean I <trunc>u</trunc> I think you get it when you read like someone like Plato in Greek it's really like there's so much sort of joke almost jokes in Greek</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0381">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0326">that you can't get in translation</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0381">ah yeah yeah that's good jokes yeah good example</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0382">well actually it's funny I feel partly feel the opposite where I what I loved about Aristophanes is he's just bloody fun in the idea that you can laugh</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0381">that a human can translate</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0382">you can laugh across two-and-a-half thousand years is I find that really moving</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0326">it's not that funny though I this Aristophanes</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0382">well it is pretty funny</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0326">I actually just wrote an essay about Aristophanes about <trunc>whe</trunc> what is Aristophanes er er serious about Athens?</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0382">well I haven't read enough but I just think there are things</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0326">yeah I really like the jokes about farting</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0382">exactly exactly but that's cool people are laughing about that in</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0326">there is a that's the thing that's not the funniest stuff in Aristophanes</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0382">yeah but also the women saying well we won't let our men have sex with us unless they stop fighting</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1460" who="S0382">that's funny</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0381">unless they stop fighting?</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0326">the funniest</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0381">or stop farting?</u>
<u n="1464" who="S0382">fighting</u>
<u n="1465" who="S0381">oh</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0326">I think the funniest things in Aristophanes is the is the things that we can't find funny</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0381">oh</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0326">cos we're not there</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0382">so my <trunc>ha</trunc> my reception we're not there</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0381" trans="overlap">your reception is fucked up</u>
<u n="1471" who="S0382">so what? give me an example</u>
<u n="1472" who="S0326">well it's hard to explain like it's sort of she talks about all this like nuanced stuff you know how the funniest things are the things that kind of dip under</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0382">oh yeah that's true that's true so</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0326">you know when you I <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="1475" who="S0382">I see this all</u>
<u n="1476" who="S0326">I did the supervision with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he starts talking about all this shit about Freud how laughter is epistemologically free and when you're like when you're really laughing and you really know what you're laughing about</u>
<u n="1477" who="S0382">yes you do you know what triggered it?</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0326">yeah but you know when you're you're like <trunc>wa</trunc> you <trunc>we</trunc> you know it you're just sort of walking down the street and start laughing</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0382">oh well that sounds like sort of mystical illumination</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0326">no you well I I</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0382">well that's different</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0326">you know I you don't you don't always know you're laughing uncontrollably</u>
<u n="1483" who="S0381">yeah I haven't done that for a long time</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0382" trans="overlap">yeah but it's usually something sets you off</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0381">then but then you start laughing and then you're just like I don't know why I'm laughing and you're like laughing</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0382">oh</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0326">he said there are two he said there were two people who were famous for never having laughed it Plato and Jesus</u>
<u n="1488" who="S0381"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1489" who="S0326">and maybe the next one is</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0382">two people famous for doing what?</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0326">for never having really laughed</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0382">oh no no I've laughed</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0381">Plato Jesus and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1494" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1495" who="S0382">no I've laughed a lot that's stupid I know people who don't have a sense of humour there are people</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0326">but that's the point of being a a sort of the thing about epistemology these are the two figures that you would not expect to be epistemologically free ever</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0382">so and you mean so and they didn't laugh so that proves that's</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0326">not it's not obviously it's not a proof it's just a sort of sort</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0381">observations</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0382">we don't know about we don't know about Jesus</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0326">obviously we don't no one knows that</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0381"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we're never going to know that</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0382" trans="overlap">cos you know you know all we ever got from about Jesus was all the kind of</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0381">yeah it's true we don't what do we know about Jesus <trunc>se</trunc> sort of</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0382">well yeah we just get the we get the story afterwards and</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0381">he must have been a pretty serious guy though I mean</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0382">I don't know I don't know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got no sense of humour</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0381"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has no sense of humour</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0382">he he knows what's funny he can tell stories he can tell jokes well but he doesn't himself naturally spontaneously laugh I mean he does he's not like some people who can't even get</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0382">but most you know I when I watch often on telly I watch things I don't know why it's funny cos I don't know it's some TV person I don't know what the reference is erm but most of the there's there's a lot of theorising about what what humour is it's really it's really hard one of the things we know is the kind of incongruity sort of when the when the posh when the really pound posh person sits on the banana skin and that's part of it</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0326">yeah and I mean British people have a particular sense of humour which is</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0382">oh we do</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0326">yeah very strange to Americans</u>
<u n="1515" who="S0382">yeah</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0326">you're silly</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0382">yeah yeah we do silly</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0381">like really stupid silly that Americans just</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0382">they they do though they do in those TV programmes</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0326">like Bill and Ted</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0382">more and more</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0381">yeah Bill and Ted yeah that's true but that's <trunc>e</trunc> but that's different even from</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0326" trans="overlap">Wayne's World <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1524" who="S0381">it's hard to yeah it's hard to</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0382">it's very hard to talk about</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0381">it's <trunc>ta</trunc></u>
<u n="1527" who="S0326">also it's really interesting about Aristophanes in sort of context of the Greater Dionysian and it's sort of state sponsored state sanctions all like this act of sort of being in a citizen is to laugh at this thing if you don't laugh you're not one of us</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0382">oh my god</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0381">yeah that's hard</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0326">so I didn't I was a bit sort of deadly serious</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0382">oh my god</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0326">undertones</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0382">I mean no but tell me I'm <trunc>re</trunc> I'm really quite ignorant so you mean his plays were put on as part of these?</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0326">well yeah it's kind of to understand any sort of Greek drama you really have to understand the context that they're performed in which is a really like grand public ceremony put on by the state where you have all these rituals before</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0382">always?</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0326">yeah there's two main ones the Lenaia which is just just it's before the before the weather's alright to sail so it's just Greeks and the Great Dionysia which is sort of the whole Greek world</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0382">the Great?</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0326">Dionysia</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0382">Dionysia</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0326">and then you have you know you have things like at the Great Dionysia you have a sort of parade of the war orphans of that year you have all the <trunc>sp</trunc> you have lots of sacrifices</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0382">right</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0326">parade the tributes from the Empire and then you watch some fucking Euripides</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0382" trans="overlap">I had no idea but Euripides is not funny is it?</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0326">yeah but I know but but you went in and then you did that for four days and you do one day of of comedy at the end</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0382" trans="overlap">it's tragedy <pause dur="short"/> sort sort of regimental</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0381" trans="overlap">it's all very rigid it's sort of</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0326">it's you have to</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0381">time for comedy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1550" who="S0326">it's sort of the idea as citizen as</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0382">catharsis</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0326">as spectator you got it's a performance of roles and and the and the</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0382" trans="overlap">was was it always like that? couldn't you just go to the theatre or something?</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0326">no that was when you watched it</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0381" trans="overlap">there was no side off Broadway</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0382">jeez I am so ignorant</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0326">there was no sort of there was no no sort of theatre as a there's no theatre as a as a erm leisure activity</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0382">that's it</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0326">when just a sole entertainment</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0382">what a <unclear>baloney</unclear> so you mean all <trunc>Ar</trunc> I mean Aristophanes Aristophanes is quite subversive quite often</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0326">that's the thing that's why it that's why it's</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0381">oh so he had a way of being humorous maybe in that context</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0382" trans="overlap">so he's <unclear/></u>
<u n="1564" who="S0326">yeah <pause dur="short"/> people talk about tragedy and comedy as the way of sort of problematising myth and sort of preconceived truths about what it is to be Athenian and Greek</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0382">yeah but aren't they? <trunc>b</trunc> you one begins to think that's over theorising it but</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0326">yeah but if you look at</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0381" trans="overlap">well <trunc>do</trunc> is it?</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0326" trans="overlap">you know like plays like sort of the Ion and stuff they all kind of almost like sort of Greek <trunc>auto</trunc> I Athenian autochthony</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0381"><trunc>auto</trunc> are you I hope you're still recording this cos it cos this is good stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1570" who="S0382" trans="overlap">yeah it's gonna be your your phone is going to break down it's like autochthonous shit</u>
<u n="1571" who="S0381" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> is there evidence I mean in other texts of humour that's not sort of this?</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0326">well that's the thing there's there's there's satire plays</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0381">but they're they're not part of this whole parade of</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0326" trans="overlap">they're <unclear/> to</u>
<u n="1575" who="S0381">is there any non-parade humour?</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0326">non what?</u>
<u n="1577" who="S0382" trans="overlap">jeez</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0381">like sort of this that's not part of this state-sanctioned erm I don't know</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0382" trans="overlap">I need a I think I need a one O one on this I need a book about</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0326">I mean there there might be there's probably like sort of things like they had in Rome like sort of pantomime and stuff that were going on but not really like grand like things like Aristophanes and Euripides are sort of really just like not you don't you only get that at these at these festivals</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0381" trans="overlap">even yeah <pause dur="short"/> so he had to be probably be really subtle if he wanted to slip some actual humour</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0326" trans="overlap">well that's the thing this is this theatre this stage was sort of one place where you can be subversive cos it was sort of so heavily contained that it was alright to be</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0381">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0326">that's part of democracy sort of testing itself</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0381">right</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0326">that's how people like to look at it</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0382">so I'm just reading about it then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> knows all this the central event was the Pompeii procession in which the phallus were carried by the phallus bearers</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0326">that sounds like that sounds ridiculous but to us</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0382" trans="overlap">were they like huge</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0381">the phalli</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0382">the <trunc>pha</trunc> okay</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0326">it seems very funny like it's their you know long male they're tied on everyone's walking around them</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0382">how big are they like?</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0326">three foot long</u>
<u n="1595" who="S0381"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1596" who="S0382">that's pretty cool I think the Muslims should take that up sorry shouldn't have said that</u>
<u n="1597" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1598" who="S0382">er and then come the girls carrying baskets and then come the <foreign lang="gre"/> carrying bowls of bread and some wow that's so cool I had no idea</u>
<u n="1599" who="S0381">so do you have to pick a a particular advisor for your dissertation?</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0326">yeah probably</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0382">well yeah I mean it's</u>
<u n="1602" who="S0326">I can't I want to do one I want to do one <trunc>lit</trunc> like so sort of literature-based with a like philosopher philosophy angle</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0381">mm</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0382">right Aristophanes parodied the rural Dionysia in</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0326">in in Arcadians that's one I did the that's one of my set texts this year</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0382">oh cool</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0326">which I did the essay on</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0382">go well <unclear/></u>
<u n="1609" who="S0381">I know I cannot I cannot keep up with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s classics education</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0382" trans="overlap">and we know I know I knew what the word tragedy means goat song so they say</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0326">yeah and then <trunc>a</trunc> somebody has <trunc>ma</trunc> has a joke cos he had <unclear/> quite some time <trunc>trou</trunc>troubadour</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0382">which means?</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0326">which is erm from the <trunc>bo</trunc> sort of the leaves at the bottom of the wine bottles are the <trunc>tre</trunc><trunc>tre</trunc></u>
<u n="1614" who="S0382">trellis oh the faeces?</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0381">oh right right</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0326">basically it's like a wine song but it takes obviously pun on it and it's in the Arcanes there is a really good bit with Euripides in it sort of borrowing costumes from his plays and he's like he kind of points to how contrived tragedy is as a sort of <unclear/></u>
<u n="1617" who="S0382">so is the comedy that he started from four eight seven BC that's when we first started having comedy as well as tragedies is there one there? mm <pause dur="short"/> wow well well well yeah I mean at the same time you don't want to say it's all context because I mean there are just the words and the meanings of the words and things <unclear/></u>
<u n="1618" who="S0381">yeah I mean that's what's wrong with it</u>
<u n="1619" who="S0382">can be beautiful or funny</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0381">right</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0382">on their own as it were but so and you just have to balance appreciating context and</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0326">yeah I mean there's either and then there's like there's been a symposium and they afterwards they go on about us sort of what they and then quote bits of the play</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0382">in the symposium?</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0326"><unclear/> it's a kind of culture of sort of going to the theatre and then</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0382">right</u>
<u n="1626" who="S0326">at the at the symposium reciting it cos they had those kind of memories</u>
<u n="1627" who="S0382">yeah because you didn't have</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0326">and you then you take it out of the civic arena and appreciate it which isn't like I haven't really read any of the <unclear/> about that</u>
<u n="1629" who="S0381">but that would be that's a kind of interesting question</u>
<u n="1630" who="S0382">how much poetry was there written independently of?</u>
<u n="1631" who="S0326">well all the lyric</u>
<u n="1632" who="S0382">yeah quite so they're just they have they're not so so context-bound in the same way except that they sit in the literary traditions in <unclear/> of course what what did you say I? you said I'm not doing that what were you</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0381">I said I can't keep up with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s classics education</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0382">no no but I am kind of but I'm actually just really know nothing about this probably cos I stopped learning Latin Greek when I was fourteen or fifteen <unclear/> fourteen <vocal desc="yawn"/> mm</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0326">anyway I thought Cavafy was a sort of like old sort of sort of thing that Anne Carson and Alice Oswald</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0382">I definitely want to check that out</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0381">I'll have to look up this person</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0382">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0326">there's also <trunc>u</trunc> cos then I started getting <trunc>in</trunc>interested in just in like Alexandria and there's this writer there's like these books about Alexandria</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0382">ah yeah yeah the cryptology before <unclear/></u>
<u n="1641" who="S0326">cos he's a <trunc>ne</trunc> he's a <trunc>ne</trunc> he's an he always talk er sort of refers to him sort of secretly calls him the old man of the city it's actually Cavafy</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0382">who's this?</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0326">erm <unclear/> historical</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0382">oh right right right in <trunc>h</trunc> Daniel refers to him yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0326">I like that book except when he's <trunc>si</trunc> like cos there's too much of him being like philosophical about London</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0382">he he is a bit poncey</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0382">he's a bit</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0326">he's a bit what he's really good at though is sort of just describing characters for like a page</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0382">mm wow</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0326">and they're really sort of <trunc>intr</trunc> that's like takes it so it sounds totally different convincingly</u>
<u n="1652" who="S0382">god yeah I haven't</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0381">can I see that?</u>
<u n="1654" who="S0382">I read a number of I used to love his brother cos his brother was a natural history writer his the family the Durrell family moved to Corfu when</u>
<u n="1655" who="S0381">oh really?</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0382">when Gerald Durrell was a kid and he was just amazing that this English family and he wrote a lovely book called My Family and Other Animals about being transplanted out of grey old England to Corfu at the age of nine <vocal desc="yawn"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's worth reading the tretraudy tetrology <trunc>tetr</trunc> whatever <pause dur="short"/> what does what's the person called The Alexandria Quartet?</u>
<u n="1657" who="S0326">so that's the first one</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0382">what?</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0326">that's the first one</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0382">is it?</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0326">Justine</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0382">Justine Justine was name Marquis de Sade's girl <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1663" who="S0326">I'm thinking what's the best thing to read for Anne Carson first is</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0382">the first of what?</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0326">Anne Carson</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0382">what to read first?</u>
<u n="1667" who="S0381">oh is this a library book that you checked out yeah?</u>
<u n="1668" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1669" who="S0381">which is? oh that</u>
<u n="1670" who="S0326">that's something else</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0382">yeah it would be nice I would like it it would be nice if the Greek <unclear/></u>
<u n="1672" who="S0326">yeah I want the Greek too</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0382">yeah</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0326">he sort of like in the introduction saying really interesting things</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0382">are these his translations as well?</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0326">yeah they're not that good but they're really like you get a sense of cos he does one thing at sort of like expense and then <trunc>rhy</trunc>rhymes nicely in English he does in Greek they had a they had sort of two modes of two sort of languages in Greek sort of an official one of</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0382">yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="1678" who="S0326">which borrowed a lot on classical <trunc>re</trunc> lots of classic Greek words and the vernacular one and Calafy was</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0382">still?</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0326">well that's</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0382">well that's like Arab like Arab countries yeah</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0326">and then Cavafy sort of shifts between like those two to you know to indicate points</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0381">mm</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0326">so he uses lots of like awkward words that's just an indication</u>
<u n="1685" who="S0382">oh I see</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0381">was that unusual to shift between the two?</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0326">I think Cavafy might have started it he's sort of a modernist and like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1688" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0382">cool have you ever heard of erm Pessoa? Fernando Pessoa? he's one of my he is so weird he has they're not they're not pseudonyms he calls them heteronyms and they're kind of he's this Portuguese weirdo</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0381">oh my god I remember you reading reading his poetry or</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0382">yeah I read a lot of it because he's he's kind of a very episodic person in in</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0381">what's his name again?</u>
<u n="1693" who="S0382">Pessoa which just means person in Portuguese when you were I think early on when they you and I were <unclear/> we went down to this old cafe where you used to have do you remember that amazing</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0381">oh my god yes</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0382">amazing old</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0381">we snuck away from you guys</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0382">yeah we snuck away and then said oh coffee and just get these little espressos and it's just like</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0381">yeah yeah I remember that</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0382">three old guys in suits at eight o'clock in the morning well you should check out a check out Pessoa before you go to Portugal erm one of his one of his <trunc>perso</trunc>personae one is very into sort of classical stuff and then one of them is one of them is kind of you into just rural simple things and and his own person is kind of he was saying oh I feel like nothing and there's nothing it's all nothing</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0381">his own person</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0382">what? after what?</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0381">did you say his own person?</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0382">yeah I think he writes if you the poems he writes under his own name are the least good ones</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0381" trans="overlap">that that yeah I'm glad you related that to what we were talking about cos when you first mentioned it I thought wow that's a real lateral jump</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0382">no it's just</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0381">but then you</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0382">no I'll tell you what it was I was just looking at I started reading a poem in here and it somehow reminded me of Pessoa</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0382">maybe partly <pause dur="long"/> I'm reading a book at the moment called The Swerve <unclear/> almond have you done Lucretius?</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0326">yeah a bit</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0381">what's the book the best book to begin with to your favourite author?</u>
<u n="1712" who="S0326">I only read one and I can't even remember which number it was</u>
<u n="1713" who="S0381"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1714" who="S0326">probably I think it might be I think one three and four are famous</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0382">Lucretius? he's basically right I mean he got a lot of stuff right</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0326">is that the guy that said you shouldn't fear death? no no</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0382">yeah no he did say that</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0326">yeah that's the bit I read</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0382">erm death is nothing</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0326" trans="overlap">you shouldn't fear death</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0381">you shouldn't fear death cos you won't be here</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0326">yeah Ian Ian McEwan wrote to me he says he's pretty into that but he was he got that from Epicurus</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0381">oh right yeah that's not I'm thinking of Epicurus</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0326">although it's actually an interesting question how much it is he is a sort of <unclear/> but Epicurus doesn't really think the <unclear/> should write poetry and there's lots of things like we only the only evidence we have for it is Lucretius</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0381">why doesn't he think people should write poetry?</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0382" trans="overlap">oh and like <unclear/></u>
<u n="1727" who="S0326" trans="overlap">can't remember I don't know</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0382">oh</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0381">cos it's annoying poetry is annoying</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0326" trans="overlap">you don't get you don't get you don't get The Swerve anywhere else</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0382">oh? no you know The Swerve</u>
<u n="1732" who="S0326" trans="overlap">I think</u>
<u n="1733" who="S0382">like all the atoms have all the atoms are like going along in straight lines none of them ever bump into each other so how does how did the world begin and?</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0381">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0382">and at one point one of them went</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so that's how you get erm</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0382" trans="overlap">it swerved</u>
<u n="1738" who="S0381">no electrons are collapsing</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0382">that's how you get everything yeah</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0382">but then some people think that's how you get free will and blah blah blah</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0381">oh The Swerve?</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1744" who="S0382">cool</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0326">and once one does it once then it's like chaos</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0382">yeah and then everything ran off</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0326">it all swerves in and parallels lines</u>
<u n="1748" who="S0381">why would you think that they're all going in straight lines to begin with?</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0326">I don't know er very good question but yeah so that could be literary and</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0381" trans="overlap">I mean like</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0326" trans="overlap">well the question is</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0381">it could easily</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0326">I think I mean I was like I sort of cos like I think it all sort of comes from like Epicureans and the Stoics arguing about things like how can you how can you know a certain thing?</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0326">like you can just say well you you can if you see it therefore it's there</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1757" who="S0326">and the Stoics were like well no</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0382">no</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0326">they're like well if you see something from a distance or like a stick in the water it's like a swerve man</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0381"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1761" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's like a first principle that they don't have to argue for I guess</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0381">right yeah but</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0326">yeah but it makes sense going backwards I guess in their arguments</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0382">I don't know what you could do <vocal desc="yawn"/> I mean everyone says you know Plato is like great literature and well anyway</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0381">it is it is actually I think</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0382">yeah it is but erm it's</u>
<u n="1768" who="S0381">maybe it's not the best of that I mean</u>
<u n="1769" who="S0382">well it's not you might think that wasn't literary enough</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0381">oh well there</u>
<u n="1771" who="S0382">you want something literary but with an philosophical side</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0326" trans="overlap">it's like there's there's a girl in the year above and her her dissertation on sort of like regret in Seneca</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0382">oh oh yeah</u>
<u n="1774" who="S0381">that sounds like a good one</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0382">that's a good one</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0382">Seneca is so rich</u>
<u n="1778" who="S0381">regret is a good topic too</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0382">or Plutarch what?</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0381">regret is a good topic I think</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0382">I've got a huge great fat book called Regret so when I was at <anon type="place"/> and I had my heavy old glass table and I had this pile of books and I collected them from the <unclear/> over the years there was Regret Shame erm Idolatry</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0381">well apparently they did a lot of interviews of old people recently and what they regret is not what they did but what they didn't do</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0382" trans="overlap">oh yes yeah you said that years ago you said</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0326" trans="overlap"><unclear>I'll be back</unclear></u>
<u n="1785" who="S0381">yeah where are you going?</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0326">beer somewhere?</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0381">beer yeah</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0382" trans="overlap">oh yeah so I thought you that was you when I I first kind of first met you you thought that that's what people would</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0381">yeah and then</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0382">I don't think I regret what I mean I</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0381">you don't regret what you do</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0382">no I don't think I</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0381">maybe you're not do you regret anything?</u>
<u n="1794" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1795" who="S0381">that may answer that question</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0382" trans="overlap">well you know the famous French <foreign lang="fre">je ne regrette rien</foreign></u>
<u n="1797" who="S0381">what's that?</u>
<u n="1798" who="S0382">that's the great the most famous French song ever by Edith Piaf I won't sing it</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0381">oh</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0382">you know <foreign lang="fre">non rien je ne regrette rien</foreign></u>
<u n="1801" who="S0381">I don't think it's true that you I do regret some of the things I've done I think</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0382" trans="overlap">you know she says</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0381">I dunno</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0382">erm well it's really</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0326" trans="overlap">well I think if you think about old people like now that when they were young it was like all you couldn't do anything</u>
<u n="1806" who="S0381"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah it's true that's a good point</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0326">you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0382">compared to</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0381">like it's not as restrictive now</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0382" trans="overlap">so you were</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0326">they have lived their whole life sort of trying to behave properly and they're way much more</u>
<u n="1812" who="S0382" trans="overlap">well oh so now you don't have to bother</u>
<u n="1813" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0381">no I don't I bet you don't I bet I think that's a good point there <trunc>de</trunc> there <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc> there isn't as much</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0382">no there's been a there's been a sort of shattering increase of opportunity not just <unclear/></u>
<u n="1816" who="S0381" trans="overlap">yeah but also sort of I mean that's what the sixties were about right?</u>
<u n="1817" who="S0382">yeah</u>
<u n="1818" who="S0381">think about the difference between the fifties and the sixties</u>
<u n="1819" who="S0382">yeah that's incredible</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0381">and now anything goes anything</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0382">no but you see the thing about so you know I you know there was really particularly bad time when I went round and er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0381">having a hard time</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0382">had left and it was erm you know he was sobbing and I just felt</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0381">regret?</u>
<u n="1825" who="S0382">so terrible and yeah and but do I regret it? I it's difficult I can't really make sense of regret because it's so locked in with the cause</u>
<u n="1826" who="S0381">yeah it's hard that's why I was to say</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0382" trans="overlap">the whole pattern of your life it's cos you think if I hadn't done that well then that wouldn't have happened there wouldn't be <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for example you see? and things like that so</u>
<u n="1828" who="S0381" trans="overlap">It's hard to say I think that's why people I think that's why people don't regret what they did do it cos they realise that</u>
<u n="1829" who="S0382">it's all locked in</u>
<u n="1830" who="S0381">it's all you can't sort of subtract some piece and say</u>
<u n="1831" who="S0382">well here's a I've just read a good one so this guy yeah the guy who <trunc>wri</trunc>wrote the book called The Swerve is called Steven Greenblatt he's a Shakespeare scholar he said he went off to boarding school for and then a few days later he his mother died suddenly she was only thirty-three and he said I spent the rest of my life regretting I didn't get one last hour</u>
<u n="1832" who="S0381">oh</u>
<u n="1833" who="S0382">one hour to talk to her now that's</u>
<u n="1834" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1835" who="S0382">that's pretty powerful</u>
<u n="1836" who="S0381">yeah and that's also something that's</u>
<u n="1837" who="S0382">and so</u>
<u n="1838" who="S0381">it's it's an isolated something you can isolate like you can</u>
<u n="1839" who="S0382">yeah it's a very sort of pure case</u>
<u n="1840" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1841" who="S0382">so you've got that kind of case</u>
<u n="1842" who="S0381">yeah and I can see that I think a lot of</u>
<u n="1843" who="S0326" trans="overlap">what <trunc>re</trunc>regret because he himself went to boarding school?</u>
<u n="1844" who="S0382">no just just he just regrets</u>
<u n="1845" who="S0381">not having one</u>
<u n="1846" who="S0382">he couldn't say goodbye he couldn't have</u>
<u n="1847" who="S0326">but that's nothing to <trunc>re</trunc> I mean it's it's just to be bitter about</u>
<u n="1848" who="S0382" trans="overlap">oh well er no wait wait wait regret doesn't there's remorse which is when you feel bad about something</u>
<u n="1849" who="S0381">yeah it's not that</u>
<u n="1850" who="S0382">you can regret things that and have got no moral so like you might have met so-and-so</u>
<u n="1851" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1852" who="S0382">but they were going to come but they didn't so you can regret something completely morally neutral is that?</u>
<u n="1853" who="S0381">that's true</u>
<u n="1854" who="S0326">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1855" who="S0381">that's true</u>
<u n="1856" who="S0382">yeah so there's a big difference between</u>
<u n="1857" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1858" who="S0382">regret and remorse so</u>
<u n="1859" who="S0381">but I <trunc>do</trunc> I</u>
<u n="1860" who="S0382" trans="overlap">but these these are things like you know I they might regret oh I never went scuba diving or something</u>
<u n="1861" who="S0381">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1862" who="S0382">yeah</u>
<u n="1863" who="S0381">but I think you know sort of when I think about sometimes I worry that I'm going to regret not doing X</u>
<u n="1864" who="S0382">do you? I never</u>
<u n="1865" who="S0381">yeah I'm going to regret not talking to my mum more</u>
<u n="1866" who="S0326" trans="overlap">yeah and that's the that's the reason that and you and then you do it</u>
<u n="1867" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1868" who="S0382">it then</u>
<u n="1869" who="S0381">it motivates me to do it</u>
<u n="1870" who="S0326">kind of like when <unclear/> tonight when I went to sort of Dusseldorf and I <trunc>we</trunc> when I was offered well I might I'll probably be like if tomorrow I'm just <trunc>a</trunc> bored at home like I might as well go to Dusseldorf</u>
<u n="1871" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1872" who="S0382">but I can't it's not really the best motive is it?</u>
<u n="1873" who="S0381">no it's not no I think it's not</u>
<u n="1874" who="S0382" trans="overlap">you ought to be doing it because it's good to do or</u>
<u n="1875" who="S0381" trans="overlap">no it's but I but I think I <trunc>be</trunc> I <trunc>re</trunc> I I'm worried I'm going to regret it because I know it's good to do but I'm being lazy or it's difficult or it's you know?</u>
<u n="1876" who="S0382">yeah that's</u>
<u n="1877" who="S0381">and but I know it's the I it would be a good thing</u>
<u n="1878" who="S0382" trans="overlap">that's I don't I don't have that I just don't have it I'm not thinking well I should do this because I know that in future I will wish that I had done it no</u>
<u n="1879" who="S0326">I that's why I did that my <trunc>p</trunc> my grade eight piano exam cos I wasn't going to do it and then two days before I was like I'll regret it if I don't</u>
<u n="1880" who="S0382">yeah that's yeah that's not I'm going to look back fifty years later and</u>
<u n="1881" who="S0381">yeah he might have though</u>
<u n="1882" who="S0326">it doesn't make any difference though like anybody you know</u>
<u n="1883" who="S0382">no it makes</u>
<u n="1884" who="S0381">he might say oh that what is it? I don't know I just know I have that thought</u>
<u n="1885" who="S0326">I think actually when I do things I don't really want to do is cos I think I'll regret it if I don't</u>
<u n="1886" who="S0381">yeah <pause dur="long"/> it's not I it's not that I don't want to do it but okay there yeah there's a slightly I don't want to do it it's hard</u>
<u n="1887" who="S0326" trans="overlap">it's like it's stuff you want to do but it's hard yeah</u>
<u n="1888" who="S0381">there's something it's partly unpleasant or difficult or effort or maybe you're just not as lazy?</u>
<u n="1889" who="S0382">well here's a yeah I this is</u>
<u n="1890" who="S0381" trans="overlap">plus you don't have the same this is this like a one area I have you don't have this area with your parents</u>
<u n="1891" who="S0382" trans="overlap">embarrassing but I have do you want to hear my embarrassing what?</u>
<u n="1892" who="S0381">you I mean your mum's not like losing it slowly so that you know that there's this sort of time period</u>
<u n="1893" who="S0382" trans="overlap">I don't no I don't but</u>
<u n="1894" who="S0381">of course she is rather old</u>
<u n="1895" who="S0382">who? but it's I'm suspicious of the motive of wanting to do it so that it will have happened</u>
<u n="1896" who="S0381">no just cos I know that I like talking to my mum and that da da da da you know</u>
<u n="1897" who="S0382">but your mum is really already is not really there in the same way</u>
<u n="1898" who="S0381">no but she's still there like somewhat there</u>
<u n="1899" who="S0382" trans="overlap">that's very that's very weird talking to people whose parents have gone further and they're obviously very</u>
<u n="1900" who="S0381" trans="overlap">yeah I don't know what</u>
<u n="1901" who="S0382">they they always they take up a sort of defensive dismissiveness because they it's very obviously very upsetting you know they say oh she didn't know who I was and</u>
<u n="1902" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1903" who="S0382">erm and they they have to it's like doctors</u>
<u n="1904" who="S0381">yeah that's the only way you</u>
<u n="1905" who="S0382">doctors have to you know when they're in their first year of</u>
<u n="1906" who="S0381">you can't really display your true emotions cos it would be too awful like you're just in casual conversation you can't sort of start blathering</u>
<u n="1907" who="S0382" trans="overlap">yeah but I think I think it's</u>
<u n="1908" who="S0381">so you sort of must do something</u>
<u n="1909" who="S0382">right yeah but <pause dur="long"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="1910" who="S0326">but that that would be a good sort of theme like the regret like some some sort of theme <unclear/></u>
<u n="1911" who="S0382">yeah a kind of erm</u>
<u n="1912" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1913" who="S0382">as it were a <trunc>mor</trunc></u>
<u n="1914" who="S0326">I can I can think quite easily for like Rome like you can quite easily like sort of youth in <unclear/> and things like that</u>
<u n="1915" who="S0382">what <trunc>yo</trunc></u>
<u n="1916" who="S0326">like youth or like</u>
<u n="1917" who="S0382">oh you mean carpe diem or something that theme? what?</u>
<u n="1918" who="S0326">well just like sort of in the longer poems like <unclear/> stuff and</u>
<u n="1919" who="S0382">I don't know</u>
<u n="1920" who="S0326">but it would you know <unclear/> but I can't really understand the Greek</u>
<u n="1921" who="S0382">right</u>
<u n="1922" who="S0326">and you get you never get such consistent <unclear/></u>
<u n="1923" who="S0382">what about Plutarch?</u>
<u n="1924" who="S0326">never read that</u>
<u n="1925" who="S0382">just as just as interesting as Seneca really Seneca got I mean have I got the dates right? didn't he get most of it from Plutarch anyway? erm</u>
<u n="1926" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1927" who="S0382">yeah now that seems to be a good good idea to look at <pause dur="long"/> yeah and you could always read Cicero cos he'll tell you nice clear language what so-and-so said</u>
<u n="1928" who="S0381" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1929" who="S0326">yeah I know cos I did <trunc>Se</trunc>Seneca this year and is it cos it's also it's also their reception within classics so how it</u>
<u n="1930" who="S0382">reception</u>
<u n="1931" who="S0326">or no or receiving other texts like how was Seneca <trunc>rec</trunc></u>
<u n="1932" who="S0382">oh</u>
<u n="1933" who="S0326">when he writes <unclear>Medea</unclear> how does he receive <trunc>Euri</trunc> how does he respond to Euripedes' <unclear>Medea</unclear>? they're kind of intertextual relationships</u>
<u n="1934" who="S0382">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1935" who="S0326">which can't be ignored</u>
<u n="1936" who="S0382">yeah it's just always going on all the time really I mean how do we receive Shakespeare? now there's just loads of stuff we're just not getting at all</u>
<u n="1937" who="S0326">but yeah but it's but it's if someone's people if someone's thing about Seneca and Euripides is that they're writing the same play in different language</u>
<u n="1938" who="S0382">you reckon? Seneca and Euripides?</u>
<u n="1939" who="S0326">well cos they both wrote in <unclear>Medea</unclear></u>
<u n="1940" who="S0381" trans="overlap">what is that?</u>
<u n="1941" who="S0382">oh I see oh yeah but I don't think of Seneca as mainly a a playwright or I was thinking mainly of his letters and stuff it's true it's true though yeah</u>
<u n="1942" who="S0381">so is that an actual</u>
<u n="1943" who="S0382">a play?</u>
<u n="1944" who="S0381">no the term reception is that sort of a theoretical term in classics or literary theory I've never heard it before</u>
<u n="1945" who="S0382" trans="overlap">oh yeah oh god yes literary theory mate you lived with a literary theory person</u>
<u n="1946" who="S0381">yeah she just like lost it and dropped out of academics</u>
<u n="1947" who="S0382">she got so tangled up with the French people</u>
<u n="1948" who="S0381" trans="overlap">she got so freaked <pause dur="short"/> no I think what did her in is she taught this course on erm Deleuze and what's the other guy's name?</u>
<u n="1949" who="S0382">Derrida</u>
<u n="1950" who="S0381">Derrida and</u>
<u n="1951" who="S0382">Deleuze and Guattari</u>
<u n="1952" who="S0381" trans="overlap">a third year</u>
<u n="1953" who="S0382">oh</u>
<u n="1954" who="S0381">and she just</u>
<u n="1955" who="S0382" trans="overlap">well I think flipped</u>
<u n="1956" who="S0381">she did she went off the deep end <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know what was in those books</u>
<u n="1957" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1958" who="S0382">no it's true I mean in one sense it's trivial that every person receives a different meaning from the</u>
<u n="1959" who="S0381">well there has to be like a lot of overlap though</u>
<u n="1960" who="S0382">I hope so yeah I I kind of like I like the sense that I can I another human being of the same species is talking to me across the centuries</u>
<u n="1961" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="1962" who="S0382">erm but a lot of people</u>
<u n="1963" who="S0326" trans="overlap">that's the point that's the reason why it was when when Seneca writes a <unclear>Medea</unclear> it's because someone spoke across the centuries</u>
<u n="1964" who="S0382">yeah sure but some people don't like that they're sort of super relativists and they say well you can it's just your reaction and you have no idea what they've</u>
<u n="1965" who="S0381" trans="overlap">I wonder if that's kind of fallen out of fashion?</u>
<u n="1966" who="S0382">and it doesn't matter I don't know actually</u>
<u n="1967" who="S0381">I don't either</u>
<u n="1968" who="S0382">I don't know</u>
<u n="1969" who="S0326">especially cos do you know that <trunc>per</trunc> Statius you ever hear of him?</u>
<u n="1970" who="S0382">I've heard</u>
<u n="1971" who="S0326">cos he wrote a poem sort of <pause dur="short"/> called the Achilleid which is he sets out to sort of write the whole story of Achilles' life</u>
<u n="1972" who="S0382">yeah</u>
<u n="1973" who="S0326">and he does like sort of Achilles as a child and doing cross-dressing</u>
<u n="1974" who="S0382">really?</u>
<u n="1975" who="S0381">Achilles?</u>
<u n="1976" who="S0326">yeah in <unclear/> when he's trying to get out when Thetis is trying to stop him going to the war she hides him in a harem</u>
<u n="1977" who="S0382">oh that's right yeah</u>
<u n="1978" who="S0381">oh okay</u>
<u n="1979" who="S0326">and then he like cos he wasn't just <unclear/> see he's trying to do all sorts of</u>
<u n="1980" who="S0382" trans="overlap">how but she why is she worried cos she knows about the heel?</u>
<u n="1981" who="S0326">she knows that he's going to die</u>
<u n="1982" who="S0382">oh she knows he's going to die cos she held him by the heel?</u>
<u n="1983" who="S0326">yeah and that's interesting cos the thing is Thetis doesn't want if if it could as well be called the Thetis tale or something so both the Thetis and Statius know what's going to happen to Achilles but they're both sort of trying to delay it</u>
<u n="1984" who="S0382">cos Statius is the author</u>
<u n="1985" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="1986" who="S0382">and she's the mother</u>
<u n="1987" who="S0326">yeah he's a writer <unclear/> the tradition he doesn't want to he wants to write his own epic he doesn't want to be</u>
<u n="1988" who="S0382">right</u>
<u n="1989" who="S0326">and then there's sort of it it stops and it's just as when just when he's erm on his way to Troy the poem stops people don't know if he did that deliberately</u>
<u n="1990" who="S0382">just on his say it again?</u>
<u n="1991" who="S0326">on his way to Troy and like when they get back into sort of epic general like</u>
<u n="1992" who="S0382">I see <pause dur="short"/> I see</u>
<u n="1993" who="S0326">I'm interested in sort of that like sense of belatedness</u>
<u n="1994" who="S0382">yeah</u>
<u n="1995" who="S0326">like trying to combat it</u>
<u n="1996" who="S0382">er what you want to</u>
<u n="1997" who="S0326">try to sort of <trunc>co</trunc> like how can Statius sort of carve himself out of it and like you know?</u>
<u n="1998" who="S0382">right but you don't know whether he stopped playing because</u>
<u n="1999" who="S0326">I think he did definitely did</u>
<u n="2000" who="S0381"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm putting this in the freezer now cos sealing it is not enough to prevent me from</u>
<u n="2001" who="S0382">no wow well so it's all it's all so rich there's so much life in it</u>
<u n="2002" who="S0381">that's true there's so much to think about <pause dur="long"/> I need to pee</u>
<u n="2003" who="S0382">you can pee in there</u>
<u n="2004" who="S0381" trans="overlap">nobody else has to pee I've already peed once so I'm not going in the other room</u>
<u n="2005" who="S0382" trans="overlap">and me</u>
<event desc="0381 leaves"/>
<u n="2006" who="S0382">oh there's a big oh it's Seneca who's like really <trunc>po</trunc>popular at the moment</u>
<u n="2007" who="S0326">cos he I've got a module on <unclear/>well it's about Neronian literature which is Seneca Lucan and the other one</u>
<u n="2008" who="S0382" trans="overlap">yeah oh yeah</u>
<u n="2009" who="S0326">which I think is really interesting</u>
<u n="2010" who="S0382">when is Tibullus? is he?</u>
<u n="2011" who="S0326">I'm not sure when he he's not really on it though</u>
<u n="2012" who="S0382">Lucan who is?</u>
<u n="2013" who="S0326">Lucan's sort of like he's like sort of like it's also interesting how he reacts to epic cos he he really wants to like tear it apart</u>
<u n="2014" who="S0382">right</u>
<u n="2015" who="S0326">and till right at the end he <unclear/> doesn't like</u>
<u n="2016" who="S0382">that's right</u>
<u n="2017" who="S0326">he's like very angry</u>
<u n="2018" who="S0382">there's also this guy called Callinicus? did you come across him at all?</u>
<u n="2019" who="S0326">only sort of cos that's why I try and cos he's like what people talk about Alexandria</u>
<u n="2020" who="S0382">oh cos he's he's interesting cos he's like he's basically a postmodernist</u>
<u n="2021" who="S0326">yeah that that's why that's what sort of people like <unclear>Citalis</unclear> and stuff they were all doing by <unclear/> that's what they're they're also inspired by Callinicus</u>
<u n="2022" who="S0382">oh right so I like to say when someone says you know who is I just say well actually is Callinicus was a postmodernist</u>
<u n="2023" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2024" who="S0382">he's sort of already gone kind of meta and he's sort of aware of language</u>
<u n="2025" who="S0326">yeah that's that's what that's what I really am interested in I think</u>
<u n="2026" who="S0382">yeah well that well yeah that's different from I mean that's fascinating</u>
<u n="2027" who="S0326">but that's <trunc>co</trunc><trunc>ca</trunc> the only post like post <trunc>li</trunc> modern or post-literary or post-meta because they're receiving it</u>
<u n="2028" who="S0382">oh okay</u>
<u n="2029" who="S0326">that's part of their reception</u>
<u n="2030" who="S0382">yeah it's true yeah I think it must happen maybe it happens in every tradition that yeah</u>
<u n="2031" who="S0326">it's just <trunc>me</trunc> I mean it's a thing it's it's I mean it's it's kind of interesting like erm kind of the <unclear/> that expresses against influence thing it's just this kind of quite quite clever thing where someone says exist</u>
<u n="2032" who="S0382">a recent person?</u>
<u n="2033" who="S0326">I think like eighties or something X in the first</u>
<u n="2034" who="S0382">oh</u>
<u n="2035" who="S0326">so there's not really</u>
<u n="2036" who="S0382">you mean the anxiety of influence?</u>
<u n="2037" who="S0326">no no no not that it's kind of when it's when someone says when X the idea of like X influencing Y is really just kind of belies the sophistication of that relationship</u>
<u n="2038" who="S0382">yeah I think well</u>
<u n="2039" who="S0326">cos if you then cos if you flip it round sort of saying Y remodelled X or Y parodied X or Y <trunc>tr</trunc> you know travestied X or Y</u>
<u n="2040" who="S0382">yeah</u>
<u n="2041" who="S0326">that that's still a relationship of influence but it's not so straightforward</u>
<u n="2042" who="S0382">no</u>
<u n="2043" who="S0326">that's what I talk about when I talk about how Roman art relates to Greek art it's not really just copying it's an improvement</u>
<u n="2044" who="S0382">well sometimes but wait sometimes it starts off like that because you can see sometimes a poet starts off oh yeah they had a really good I was what's a good example? where they're just kind of totally in the in the grip of someone else and then they break through oh yeah I was reading about Beckett Beckett was like enslaved to Joyce and it was in the yeah I was reading it just like week in New York Review so that's one classic story that a poet or author on one hand is enslaved just worships X and and then they start to break free and stuff that seems to be a real story</u>
<u n="2045" who="S0326">mm</u>
<u n="2046" who="S0382">that happens erm but you're right in general that the whole idea of influence is you know complicated because rejection as it were violent rejection is a form of influence just as much as</u>
<u n="2047" who="S0326">yeah</u>
<u n="2048" who="S0382">trying to copy trying to imitate or emulate or yeah well well but it's yeah so that's but that's a different that's a that's a different kind of interest from isn't that from wanting to sort of pursue a philosophical theme in a literary framework?</u>
<u n="2049" who="S0326">yeah I suppose so</u>
<u n="2050" who="S0382">maybe you could do them all together</u>
<u n="2051" who="S0326">I mean that's what I how I really like to do</u>
<u n="2052" who="S0382">images of regret now what do I regret?</u>
<u n="2053" who="S0326">cos you could look at <unclear/></u>
<u n="2054" who="S0382">I'll tell you something I regret</u>
<u n="2055" who="S0381">what?</u>
<u n="2056" who="S0382">so when I was in Israel I was being like really</u>
<u n="2057" who="S0381">pious</u>
<u n="2058" who="S0382">pious yeah and I met this girl from the Bronx</u>
<u n="2059" who="S0381">oh</u>
<u n="2060" who="S0382">in Jerusalem and she I don't know why I mean she just was really into me</u>
<u n="2061" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2062" who="S0381">I don't either</u>
<u n="2063" who="S0382">really really into me</u>
<u n="2064" who="S0381">probably really annoying</u>
<u n="2065" who="S0382" trans="overlap">but I just sort of thought what?</u>
<u n="2066" who="S0381">you were probably <trunc>we</trunc> <trunc>we</trunc></u>
<u n="2067" who="S0382">and she was really cute</u>
<u n="2068" who="S0381">and you were sort of oh I can't have sex because</u>
<u n="2069" who="S0382">yeah exactly but you see then then I went back to <anon type="place"/> and then she I gave her my address and then my parents forced me to go on holiday I was seventeen to go on holiday to France and I came back she called she called round at our house and</u>
<u n="2070" who="S0381">wow</u>
<u n="2071" who="S0382">I wasn't there</u>
<u n="2072" who="S0381" trans="overlap">what? how do you know she <trunc>cam</trunc>?</u>
<u n="2073" who="S0382" trans="overlap">I <trunc>sho</trunc> what?</u>
<u n="2074" who="S0381">how do you know she came by the house?</u>
<u n="2075" who="S0382">because because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the woman who used to clean answered</u>
<u n="2076" who="S0381">oh</u>
<u n="2077" who="S0382">so I regret that</u>
<u n="2078" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2079" who="S0381">that's very deep</u>
<u n="2080" who="S0382">very deep very deep</u>
<u n="2081" who="S0381">you're blushing</u>
<u n="2082" who="S0382">am I?</u>
<u n="2083" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what was her name?</u>
<u n="2084" who="S0382"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I can't even remember she she was called sort of Blienstein or something she said I'm the only one in the Bronx prom book</u>
<u n="2085" who="S0381">well yeah next time I drink too much</u>
<u n="2086" who="S0382">next time</u>
<u n="2087" who="S0381">I'll confess to who I</u>
<u n="2088" who="S0382">well babe I haven't drunk too much</u>
<u n="2089" who="S0381" trans="overlap">I'm just kidding I'm kidding talk talk talk</u>
<u n="2090" who="S0382">I do not want another one</u>
<u n="2091" who="S0381">maybe we should open another bottle of wine and have a teeny bit right now because tomorrow night</u>
<u n="2092" who="S0382">that's very subtle reasoning babe erm</u>
<u n="2093" who="S0381">that was actually really</u>
<u n="2094" who="S0382">no it was</u>
<u n="2095" who="S0381">that was pretty good</u>
<u n="2096" who="S0382" trans="overlap">it was really nice and it was I mean actually I think</u>
<u n="2097" who="S0381">I think you should just get a cheap one because</u>
<u n="2098" who="S0382">I think they're making a profit those people but it's erm it's exactly the model that a nice</u>
<u n="2099" who="S0381">god I'm tired I'm <trunc>ti</trunc> oh yeah cos I woke up so early</u>
<u n="2100" who="S0382">you want tea? I just have to</u>
<u n="2101" who="S0381">yeah because I mean</u>
<u n="2102" who="S0382">the screw top because</u>
<u n="2103" who="S0381">we might not finish it by tomorrow night I mean</u>
<u n="2104" who="S0382">what's so terrible about tomorrow? oh Thursday</u>
<u n="2105" who="S0381">cos we're going to be leaving on Friday also we need to I think we should just hire a car</u>
<u n="2106" who="S0382">well hiring a car means I'm getting a bit worried about all these expenses that I'm not properly <unclear/> now I've failed to to get the bill for my breakdown cover and is that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s or?</u>
<u n="2107" who="S0381">yeah he didn't drink it he went back I can't get this I can never do these</u>
<u n="2108" who="S0382">it's awfully serious sweet</u>
<u n="2109" who="S0381">yeah it's very intellectual</u>
<u n="2110" who="S0382">I mean I think</u>
<u n="2111" who="S0381">oh he's recording us so</u>
<u n="2112" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2113" who="S0382">ah oh</u>
<u n="2114" who="S0381">I almost fell down the stairs <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="2115" who="S0382">so how?</u>
<u n="2116" who="S0381"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we just started <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we just started talking about you and then we realised that we were being recorded</u>
<u n="2117" who="S0326"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2118" who="S0382">is it still recording?</u>
<u n="2119" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="2120" who="S0382">oh my god no it's not oh I won't say anything now</u>
<u n="2121" who="S0326">it's probably got a bit to go actually in a minute</u>
<u n="2122" who="S0381">so can you just send I mean do they ever reject what you send as being you know sort of unsuitable?</u>
<u n="2123" who="S0326">no</u>
<u n="2124" who="S0381">so you're just going to send that two hours</u>
<u n="2125" who="S0382">I think by definition it can't be unsuitable by definition because you're just trying to</u>
<u n="2126" who="S0326">I think they're just looking for patterns</u>
<u n="2127" who="S0382">sweep the language you wonder are they trying to get a picture of the language?</u>
<u n="2128" who="S0326">well I <trunc>so</trunc> I had an email from them erm last weekend it was like their status and it was like sort of three hundred out of a thousand hours three million out of ten million words transcribed which is what they're going for</u>
<u n="2129" who="S0381">wow</u>
<u n="2130" who="S0382">so it's like English as she is spoken today?</u>
<u n="2131" who="S0381">yeah</u>
<u n="2132" who="S0382">this is the truth</u>
<u n="2133" who="S0381">well especially looking at the <unclear/></u>
<u n="2134" who="S0382">well no they're not</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
