<text id="SP3Q">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:59:58</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-10</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0529 S0530</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Flatmate/close friend’s bedroom in university halls, Lancaster University</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Mental health, missing university seminars, university stress, the lottery, wealth</topics>
		<activity>Two flatmates talking together about mental health issues and worries</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0529">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Falmouth</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cornish/Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Falmouth</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation></occupation>
				<socgrade>unknown</socgrade>
				<nssec>unknown</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0530">
				<exactage>19</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Liverpool</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cheshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Chester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>19</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0530">why not hide from the world?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0529"><unclear>so what is it though?</unclear></u>
<u n="3" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0529">it's too bright though <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> looks like</u>
<u n="5" who="S0530">I know</u>
<u n="6" who="S0530" whoConfidence="low">oh <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> what are we going to do with you <unclear>little zapper?</unclear></u>
<u n="7" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> it's something <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0530">no it is like <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="long"/> <trunc>i</trunc> er <pause dur="short"/> babe have you got have you got any appointments soon with the counsellor person?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0529">on Friday yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0530">Friday <pause dur="short"/> me too <pause dur="short"/> what time are you going?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0530">erm <pause dur="short"/> three o'clock <pause dur="short"/> oh okay mine's half nine in the morning</u>
<u n="13" who="S0529">oh god <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> it's so early</u>
<u n="14" who="S0530">yeah just before my <pause dur="short"/> how long are you there for for your first <pause dur="short"/> appointment? <pause dur="short"/> I'm with this <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> person or <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or someone</u>
<u n="15" who="S0529">yeah I think I've got her <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="16" who="S0530">is that the <trunc>f</trunc> weird woman?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0529">she's not weird she's just</u>
<u n="18" who="S0530">the clinical woman?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0529">well just cos I'm a bit you know I'm a bit of a <pause dur="short"/> difficult person to work with so I'm sure she'll be alright with you <pause dur="short"/> cos you're actually like <pause dur="short"/> cooperating so</u>
<u n="20" who="S0530" trans="overlap">is she young or is she old?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0529">erm</u>
<u n="22" who="S0530">or like middle aged?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0529">I dunno how old she is really like</u>
<u n="24" who="S0530">older than forty?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0529">no</u>
<u n="26" who="S0530">oh no?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0529" trans="overlap">no I wouldn't say so <pause dur="short"/> I would say younger than forty</u>
<u n="28" who="S0530">okay</u>
<u n="29" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0530">that's not too bad <pause dur="short"/> I'm just imagining like a fifty-five year old</u>
<u n="31" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I mean it might be a different person but I I don't really know <unclear>what they're called</unclear></u>
<u n="32" who="S0530" trans="overlap">I think it is <pause dur="short"/> it yeah <pause dur="short"/> how long does each one last?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0529">erm I'm trying to think how long <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was on for I think it was like <pause dur="short"/> my first appointment <pause dur="short"/> was about <pause dur="short"/> half an hour maybe</u>
<u n="34" who="S0530">okay</u>
<u n="35" who="S0529">yeah cos I did <pause dur="short"/> the first thing I did I did on computer</u>
<u n="36" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0529">you have to do that <pause dur="short"/> and then she takes through that <pause dur="short"/> and then you talk about <pause dur="short"/> your probs <pause dur="short"/> and then it usually <trunc>hav</trunc> lasts like <unclear>not long though</unclear> so like twenty-five to half an hour I'd say</u>
<u n="38" who="S0530" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> so I'll be able to go to my lecture at eleven then?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah definitely yeah it won't <vocal desc="laugh"/> it won't take that long</u>
<u n="40" who="S0530" trans="overlap">god I was gonna say cos I was like mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0530">cos sometimes initial assessments take like an hour <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="43" who="S0529">no I don't think it will</u>
<u n="44" who="S0530">I don't think it will</u>
<u n="45" who="S0529">well even if it does you still have time to like</u>
<u n="46" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> to run up</u>
<u n="47" who="S0529">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0530">anyway I'm fine let's talk about</u>
<u n="49" who="S0529">no no I didn't mean it I didn't mean I wasn't silence <trunc>b</trunc>because</u>
<u n="50" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no? <pause dur="short"/> no no no no <pause dur="short"/> I mean as in like</u>
<u n="51" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I just like I don't know what to fucking say to be honest like</u>
<u n="52" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> hashtag <unclear>relational</unclear></u>
<u n="53" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I'd rather talk about you to be honest</u>
<u n="54" who="S0530">hey then if we talk about me it's gonna ignore all of your shit and then</u>
<u n="55" who="S0529">I don't care I wanna ignore all my shit</u>
<u n="56" who="S0530" trans="overlap">it's not gonna happen <pause dur="short"/> no that's <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>oi</unclear></u>
<u n="58" who="S0530">you shouldn't ignore the shit because purely you want to</u>
<u n="59" who="S0529" trans="overlap">no but I also care about what <trunc>y</trunc> what's going on in your life as well <pause dur="short"/> I do give a shit</u>
<u n="60" who="S0530" trans="overlap">I <pause dur="short"/> I care more about you</u>
<u n="61" who="S0529">well <pause dur="short"/> that's <pause dur="short"/> stupid of you</u>
<u n="62" who="S0530">why?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0529">because</u>
<u n="64" who="S0530">it's stupid of you to care more about me</u>
<u n="65" who="S0529"><vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah but you're not a lost cause</u>
<u n="66" who="S0530">I'm not a lost</u>
<u n="67" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0530">I thought I was a lost cause for like</u>
<u n="69" who="S0529" trans="overlap">you're not you're not a lost cause</u>
<u n="70" who="S0530">I don't think you are a lost cause</u>
<u n="71" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0530">despite it you've felt like this for a long time doesn't mean you're <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> a lost cause it doesn't mean that <trunc>y</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> you know you can be experiencing something for a long time and feeling a certain way but it doesn't mean you should <pause dur="short"/> well you feel more inclined to give up but</u>
<u n="73" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0530">you know?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0530">cos I guess I guess it is easier if say like <pause dur="short"/> it's been like a sudden slide <pause dur="short"/> but with you it hasn't really has it? like you've felt like this for a while</u>
<u n="77" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0530">and you've had a lot of time <trunc>f</trunc> like to yourself which is gonna make it kind of more difficult <pause dur="short"/> to get back <trunc>int</trunc> like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> like for you now like <pause dur="short"/> the abnormal is normal</u>
<u n="79" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0530">so like not doing is the norm <pause dur="short"/> which isn't your fault at all</u>
<u n="81" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>I know what you mean</unclear></u>
<u n="82" who="S0530">because <pause dur="short"/> literally like <pause dur="short"/> I've been there and it's</u>
<u n="83" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0530">horrible because you can't do anything <pause dur="short"/> like even if you try</u>
<u n="85" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I know I I'm really wanted to like <pause dur="short"/> kill myself earlier <pause dur="short"/> like honestly <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0530">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0529">but it just <pause dur="short"/> it's just so stupid as well like there's just no reason to think like that</u>
<u n="88" who="S0530" trans="overlap">it's not stupid</u>
<u n="89" who="S0529">cos I mean I do think like that and it's fine cos I don't</u>
<u n="90" who="S0530" trans="overlap">cos it affects it it all affects your brain yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0529" whoConfidence="low">I know</u>
<u n="92" who="S0529">it really does it must do because it's just like <trunc>n</trunc> there's no logical reason for you to be thinking like that otherwise <pause dur="short"/> you know? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0530">cos if you think about it like <pause dur="short"/> you know? <pause dur="short"/> it's <pause dur="short"/> it's an impairment</u>
<u n="94" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0530">it's a disability like <pause dur="short"/> it's <pause dur="short"/> stops you from functioning normally and <pause dur="short"/> not normally but you know what I mean it it stops you from functioning as you would be if you were healthy</u>
<u n="96" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0530">you know? <pause dur="short"/> and that's hard <pause dur="short"/> it's not to say that you can't be healthy again but like <pause dur="short"/> this isn't how it's gonna be <pause dur="short"/> for ever and ever <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> to actually get rid of it <pause dur="short"/> well not get rid of it but to be able to control it and get into like a stage where you can cope with it <pause dur="short"/> or even see it as maybe less <pause dur="short"/> powerful than it is <pause dur="short"/> you know? <pause dur="short"/> like I know it's quite like typical to say oh yeah you just have to beat it I'm not that kind of person that's like <pause dur="short"/> you have to push past this</u>
<u n="98" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0530">and you have to keep trying <pause dur="short"/> but <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>then</unclear> like <pause dur="short"/> the more you let it kind of <pause dur="short"/> the thing is like <pause dur="short"/> it it makes you think that it's you that doesn't wanna do anything</u>
<u n="100" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0530">which is really horrible isn't it because like?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0529">I feel like it's my fault and I don't know whether that is true or not</u>
<u n="103" who="S0530" trans="overlap">it's not your fault</u>
<u n="104" who="S0529">like I really don't any more <pause dur="short"/> like the way my family were like like talking to me it sounded <pause dur="short"/> as though it was my fault <pause dur="short"/> and then I felt really awful about it and that's when I was like</u>
<u n="105" who="S0530">I mean from the outside <pause dur="short"/> people do think <pause dur="short"/> well people can think it's your fault because <pause dur="short"/> the symptoms of it are just like <pause dur="short"/> you don't want to do things</u>
<u n="106" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I think it is</u>
<u n="107" who="S0530">but it's how is it your how is your fault that you feel like this?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0529">I don't know because this is just how I am like I've just this is just my personality now it's not even <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't even feel like it's <pause dur="short"/> you know there's something wrong with my brain it's just the way I am</u>
<u n="109" who="S0530">I think you can be a cynical person</u>
<u n="110" who="S0529"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0530">and be able to get out of bed and be able to feel able to do things I don't think <pause dur="short"/> there's correlation that much correlation there I think <pause dur="short"/> you can be somebody that <pause dur="short"/> like it's not I don't <trunc>i</trunc> I don't think it's just because you might have a negative view of things</u>
<u n="112" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0530">like it might help <trunc>sometime</trunc> like it might've contributed to it but I'm I'm certain that <pause dur="short"/> just because like you're maybe not as like <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> you've got such <pause dur="short"/> like a spiritual outlook of the world some people have <pause dur="short"/> you know? <pause dur="short"/> it doesn't it doesn't mean that like <pause dur="short"/> you know? <pause dur="short"/> cos it's not it's not part of your personality to be <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> constantly like upset and constantly worried <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> outside factors contribute to that <pause dur="short"/> it's not just like oh I'm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so I'm like this <pause dur="short"/> it's not <pause dur="short"/> and I know <trunc>h</trunc>how it just it just feels permanent and it sucks but it's not <pause dur="short"/> I mean <trunc>u</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> like you've said that over summer you didn't feel very good <pause dur="short"/> like when you were at home <pause dur="short"/> like did <trunc>y</trunc> did it feel <pause dur="short"/> it <trunc>di</trunc> obviously didn't feel very good but did it feel like less stressful than this because you didn't actually have responsibility then or <pause dur="short"/> were your family onto you so it was pretty hard?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0529">I mean it was stressful in a different way like it was</u>
<u n="115" who="S0530">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0529">erm the stakes are a lot higher <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0530">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0529">you know if I get <pause dur="short"/> if if things fall apart here then like that's just really bad because</u>
<u n="119" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0529">you know there's a lot of money involved here and there are a lot of serious</u>
<u n="121" who="S0530" trans="overlap">oh god <pause dur="short"/> there's definitely a lot of money</u>
<u n="122" who="S0529" trans="overlap">important things involved here <pause dur="short"/> like that would be affected if I decided to fuck things up which I have done <pause dur="short"/> but whereas at home it was like if I <pause dur="short"/> if I like acted out or something the only thing that would <pause dur="short"/> affect would be like my family</u>
<u n="123" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0529">and that did upset me but it didn't <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>w</trunc> no it did stress me out but like like <trunc>who</trunc> like in a different way like <pause dur="short"/> yeah I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I just feel like I'm gonna feel like this wherever I go <vocal desc="laugh"/> really <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and I'm always gonna have the same pressure from my family</u>
<u n="125" who="S0530">do they want you to do really well or do they just want you to do stuff all the time?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0529"><vocal desc="sigh"/> I don't I don't even know any more</u>
<u n="127" who="S0530" trans="overlap">is that what?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0529">they want me to do well up here cos they think I can</u>
<u n="129" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0529">they think I have it in me and I really don't <pause dur="short"/> it's not <unclear>there</unclear></u>
<u n="131" who="S0530">it isn't <unclear>fair</unclear></u>
<u n="132" who="S0529">it <pause dur="short"/> cos</u>
<u n="133" who="S0530" trans="overlap">cos it's not that you're not capable of getting <pause dur="short"/> good grades that you're not smart it's because right now you're not in the right position to be able to apply yourself</u>
<u n="134" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0530">that isn't <pause dur="short"/> it's not fair and it's not that is not your fault</u>
<u n="136" who="S0529"><vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0530">and maybe when you actually start getting like proper regular help <pause dur="short"/> and let it kick in a bit</u>
<u n="138" who="S0529">no but that's just not happening here it's just not happening it's like I</u>
<u n="139" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0529"><vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> if I made another appointment it would take a week at least</u>
<u n="141" who="S0530">to actually? <pause dur="short"/> are they not like <unclear>putting</unclear> regular slots in or anything like that?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0529" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="143" who="S0530">why?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0529">well cos <trunc>o</trunc>on on Friday I went to like the acute <pause dur="short"/> kind of thing because <pause dur="short"/> that's the only way you can get a faster appointment at the doctor's <pause dur="short"/> so I did that and I went to see a nurse <pause dur="short"/> and then she <pause dur="short"/> made me <trunc>appoi</trunc> an appointment for yesterday which I obviously missed</u>
<u n="145" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="146" who="S0529">and that's the problem like <pause dur="short"/> and I haven't called them back because I don't have any signal and I haven't been outside but if I were to call them back they would tell me like this is when the next appointment's available <pause dur="short"/> or you'd have to go through the <pause dur="short"/> acute team again</u>
<u n="147" who="S0530">oh my god</u>
<u n="148" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and <pause dur="short"/> back to where you came from and it's just</u>
<u n="149" who="S0530">that's crazy</u>
<u n="150" who="S0529" trans="overlap">it's just straight back to square one and it's really frustrating <pause dur="short"/> and they don't give you like <pause dur="short"/> repeat appointments like all the time <pause dur="short"/> and the counselling appointment's like once every Friday</u>
<u n="151" who="S0530" trans="overlap">oh god</u>
<u n="152" who="S0529">and it's like why would you put it at the end of the week you know? it's just fucking stupid <pause dur="short"/> I get one appointment every week <pause dur="short"/> and it's on Friday <pause dur="short"/> and it's with a woman who wants me to</u>
<u n="153" who="S0530">leave?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0529">to leave</u>
<u n="155" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0529">and also like <pause dur="short"/> do CBT like try things during the week that I just can't cope with most of the time because I'm too worried about everything else and it's just not helpful</u>
<u n="157" who="S0530" trans="overlap">what's the sort of thing she asks you to do?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0529"><vocal desc="sigh"/> I don't know so even like difficult stuff it's just basic things like getting out of bed and <pause dur="short"/> eating properly and going for walks <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> and it's just not helpful at the minute</u>
<u n="159" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0529">it's not what I want</u>
<u n="161" who="S0530">I think <pause dur="short"/> a bad of it <pause dur="short"/> well the part of that's probably <pause dur="short"/> really hard is that like it feels <pause dur="short"/> like there's too much now to actually control</u>
<u n="162" who="S0529">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it feels really out of my hands</u>
<u n="163" who="S0530" trans="overlap">like <pause dur="short"/> those <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>u</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0529">I feel like I've messed it up way too much I really have done a really good job of fucking stuff up for myself so far</u>
<u n="165" who="S0530">and it can still be</u>
<u n="166" who="S0529">I don't think it can</u>
<u n="167" who="S0530">I think it can</u>
<u n="168" who="S0529">I <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0530">I think it <trunc>feel</trunc> cos it's going on <pause dur="short"/> in your life and because it affects you <trunc>most</trunc> like more than anybody <pause dur="short"/> and because <pause dur="short"/> obviously you're stressed you're stressed and you're anxious about everything that <trunc>s</trunc> you're not done or <trunc>n</trunc> things that you've done <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> from looking at it from the outside I'm sure a lot of students have been in this situation <pause dur="short"/> you've not committed any crimes</u>
<u n="170" who="S0529"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0530">you've not gone to your lectures because you felt depressed <pause dur="short"/> you've not handed in assignments because <trunc>you</trunc> not functioned <pause dur="short"/> you've <trunc>n</trunc> you've not been able to function or to do the work <pause dur="short"/> and if you think about it that's it <pause dur="short"/> like I know that's big it's important <pause dur="short"/> but it's not as many <pause dur="short"/> individual problems as you think <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> it's not like <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure the lecturers here will've had experience with students like that like these are common problems</u>
<u n="172" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0530">they're horrible problems but they're common</u>
<u n="174" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0530">erm I'm sure a degree level student <pause dur="short"/> particularly at their first time away <pause dur="short"/> it's usually like the worst like the first time you go to university if you have any problems you'll have them in your first year</u>
<u n="176" who="S0529">well that's the point of first year isn't it?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="178" who="S0529">to be <unclear/> and to adjust</u>
<u n="179" who="S0530" trans="overlap">exactly <pause dur="short"/> like you can fuck up in first year a little bit</u>
<u n="180" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear><vocal desc="sigh"/></unclear></u>
<u n="181" who="S0530">like obviously you've gotta get the forty percent pass mark but I think it allows you a bit of leeway to like <pause dur="short"/> and I know it's not just missing assignments and missing someone else's problem it's actually when like <pause dur="short"/> sitting down doing the work and</u>
<u n="182" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0530"><unclear>then</unclear> actually thinking about it</u>
<u n="184" who="S0529">and I have this intense fear of just <pause dur="short"/> doing it wrong and <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and getting feedback and <pause dur="short"/> then reading my work and</u>
<u n="185" who="S0530">I know</u>
<u n="186" who="S0529">thinking it's awful because I just that's what I think like every time I read anything I've ever written I hate it</u>
<u n="187" who="S0530">have has it always felt like that?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>and I just</unclear> can't stand it it's always felt like that yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've always felt like that about reading stuff that I've written</u>
<u n="189" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0529">that I can't read my own essays I can't do it</u>
<u n="191" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no same <pause dur="short"/> I hate looking back at them</u>
<u n="192" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I've never actually read one <pause dur="short"/> all the way through <pause dur="short"/> I just hope that I've spelt everything right I do spell check I don't <pause dur="short"/> read through it because I can't</u>
<u n="193" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0529">I physically like I <pause dur="short"/> my body seizes up <pause dur="short"/> like I get <pause dur="short"/> I get like really <pause dur="short"/> tense</u>
<u n="195" who="S0530">tense yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and I can't look at it <pause dur="short"/> and then like when I get feedback I just <pause dur="short"/> I just get like a cold sweat and I can't look at it and it's just not good <pause dur="short"/> cos <pause dur="short"/> you know you need feedback and <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> I just don't wanna do it wrong <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0530">mm cos it it <trunc>def</trunc> it definitely does sound like that like</u>
<u n="198" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>know what</unclear> I mean? I don't think I can do it right</u>
<u n="199" who="S0530">you would well not been good enough for it</u>
<u n="200" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0530">like cos in my head I feel like I'm not good enough but also I've got this other expectation of you can't <pause dur="short"/> you can't do it badly you have to do it well</u>
<u n="202" who="S0529" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0530">the good thing is though like</u>
<u n="204" who="S0529"><unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="205" who="S0530">I know I've been saying this all along but <pause dur="short"/> being first year at uni it's no necessarily about <pause dur="short"/> excelling academically</u>
<u n="206" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0530">it's <pause dur="short"/> getting your life together <pause dur="short"/> and getting <pause dur="short"/> starting a new life basically and having you know? <pause dur="short"/> having such like kind of <trunc>l</trunc>learning a new way of living <pause dur="short"/> which <pause dur="short"/> is the biggest thing <pause dur="short"/> the most important thing about first year like focus on your studies like <pause dur="short"/> if you wanna <pause dur="short"/> aim for <pause dur="short"/> a really high grade in your second and third year just work really hard but <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>fir</trunc>first year is about just getting used to the experience and getting to know people and <pause dur="short"/> joining stuff and just <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's supposedly why it's like not everyone has a load of fun <trunc>n</trunc> at uni in first year <pause dur="short"/> but that's probably why they say like you'll have the time of your life because it's just</u>
<u n="208" who="S0530" whoConfidence="low"><trunc>sh</trunc></u>
<u n="209" who="S0530">a new <pause dur="short"/> experience and it's not <pause dur="short"/> in the first year <pause dur="short"/> completely academically centred <pause dur="short"/> even though at <anon type="place"/> because we have a big amount of subjects <pause dur="short"/> it feels like it it's</u>
<u n="210" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0530">cos we have quite a lot of contact like do you feel like you've got quite a lot of contact hours?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0530">so <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure that's like added stress as well because it feels like you're in all the time</u>
<u n="214" who="S0529">and then you also have all the group stuff as well <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>so</unclear></u>
<u n="215" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0529">it feels like contact hours to me cos you have to go with your group</u>
<u n="217" who="S0530" trans="overlap">I mean it <trunc>soun</trunc> it sounds like that might be a big part of it</u>
<u n="218" who="S0529">oh that is annoying yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0530" trans="overlap">the worry about the <pause dur="short"/> presentations and the crap</u>
<u n="220" who="S0529"><unclear><vocal desc="sigh"/></unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0529">but I mean there's no way around that I can't just stamp my feet and be like I don't wanna do it I can't <pause dur="short"/> I don't wanna be in groups you can't do that here like you have to do it</u>
<u n="223" who="S0530">is this gonna be every week for the whole year?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0529">I don't know I don't I think so</u>
<u n="225" who="S0530" trans="overlap">or at the moment because <pause dur="short"/> it's very strange that</u>
<u n="226" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0530">like you'd expect maybe a few times in the year but not every week I mean that is a big ask</u>
<u n="228" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly <pause dur="short"/> it is <pause dur="short"/> I just I just wish I'd not chosen this degree <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0530">I mean <pause dur="short"/> in terms of choosing a degree <pause dur="short"/> like I totally see where you're coming from now because <pause dur="short"/> obviously it doesn't have to be the most like <pause dur="short"/> if you if you don't really feel that inspired <trunc>the</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> by anything you still have to I think to an extent be able to want to face it <pause dur="short"/> you know? and</u>
<u n="230" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0530">with English you don't seem to feel like that like you don't even wanna do it</u>
<u n="232" who="S0529">no</u>
<u n="233" who="S0530">like do you think there's <pause dur="short"/> not even anything you're interested in but is there anything you could find maybe more accessible <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="234" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0530">as in like you'd maybe oh yeah I <trunc>tr</trunc> could try and write an essay on that or I could try I could I'd actually go to a lecture and be <pause dur="short"/> like I'd take some of that in kind of thing like <pause dur="short"/> because I'm sure there are</u>
<u n="236" who="S0529">well this is what I thought English would be <pause dur="short"/> I I hoped that I would <pause dur="short"/> you know <unclear>get my</unclear> interests <unclear>back</unclear></u>
<u n="237" who="S0530" trans="overlap">be your that'd be your subject yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah that I would be able to <pause dur="short"/> kind of tap into what I liked about it at A level and be like oh yeah this is interesting and I can do this like</u>
<u n="239" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0529">but it just hasn't happened yet <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and there isn't another subject that I can think of that would <pause dur="short"/> that would be accessible</u>
<u n="241" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="242" who="S0529">for me <pause dur="short"/> I just don't know</u>
<u n="243" who="S0530">does your mind <unclear>like</unclear>?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and I can't <unclear>say I like</unclear> humanities</u>
<u n="245" who="S0530">oh yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0529">and there's nothing else is there? <pause dur="short"/> sorry what were you saying?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0530">does your mind feel a bit like foggy <trunc>l</trunc> that's why you</u>
<u n="248" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0530">can't learn?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0530">because <pause dur="short"/> often <pause dur="short"/> if you get the right medication <pause dur="short"/> which <pause dur="short"/> my problem was the fogginess <pause dur="short"/> it can clear it can help like it can make your brain like untangle a bit like</u>
<u n="252" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0530">and I think actually medication might help you <pause dur="short"/> in that way like honestly you've gotta do the stuff yourself which sucks and it's hard and it's horrible but <pause dur="short"/> it actually makes it slightly easier</u>
<u n="254" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0530">like you're you're driving through a mist rather than like a thick fog <pause dur="short"/> if you get me?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0530">like it's still obviously there but it's not as like <pause dur="short"/> impairing <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="258" who="S0529">I'm so glad you get the fog thing cos I</u>
<u n="259" who="S0530">yeah oh my god</u>
<u n="260" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I say that to my sister and my mum and they're like and they just don't get it</u>
<u n="261" who="S0530">no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="262" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="263" who="S0530">but it it it feels like you've just been <trunc>s</trunc> like <pause dur="short"/> imagine a car that's been just sat in a field in fog for like</u>
<u n="264" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0530">forty years</u>
<u n="266" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0530">that is how I feel</u>
<u n="268" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0530" trans="overlap">quite a lot of the time</u>
<u n="270" who="S0529">I get that as well</u>
<u n="271" who="S0530" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and it's really hard when you wanna try and do work or write essays because you can't really look <pause dur="short"/> outside of your <trunc>h</trunc>head</u>
<u n="272" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0530">and it's horrible and oh <pause dur="short"/> but yeah <pause dur="short"/> what did who were who were you on the phone to? <unclear>then er</unclear> your mum or your sister or everyone?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0529">I was on <vocal desc="sigh"/> I was on the phone to my sister at first</u>
<u n="275" who="S0530">okay</u>
<u n="276" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and then <pause dur="short"/> we had a bit of a yeah like</u>
<u n="277" who="S0530" trans="overlap">a little row?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0529">well not really it was just more of me like just no knowing what to say to her any more <pause dur="short"/> and so I just sort of said right I'm gonna go now and <pause dur="short"/> then she rang my apparently like really upset and crying <pause dur="short"/> and then my mum Whatsapped me saying like <pause dur="short"/> your sister's just <pause dur="short"/> you know rung me like really upset <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> and she rang me from work</u>
<u n="279" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="280" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and like <pause dur="short"/> kind of just <pause dur="short"/> sort of had a go at me and then I hung up on her <pause dur="short"/> and yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and that was it really <pause dur="short"/> yeah so it wasn't very nice but <pause dur="short"/> it was kinda my fault to be honest <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0530">it's not your fault</u>
<u n="282" who="S0529" trans="overlap">that's why I feel bad about it</u>
<u n="283" who="S0530">because</u>
<u n="284" who="S0529">you know like these conversations?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0530" trans="overlap">you you have people that love and that's not your fault <pause dur="short"/> that's why they're upset</u>
<u n="286" who="S0529"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0530">you've not done anything to them <pause dur="short"/> it's just because they're concerned about you and it makes you feel guilty</u>
<u n="288" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0530">but you haven't actually done anything wrong <pause dur="short"/> it's because they love you</u>
<u n="290" who="S0529"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0530">and it's because they care and they want you to have the best time and they want the best view <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0529">I really wish I could just try for them like if I'm not trying for myself</u>
<u n="293" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0529">I wish I could do it for them but I just don't feel like <pause dur="short"/> I can even do that</u>
<u n="295" who="S0530">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos you just <pause dur="short"/> I dunno you just don't feel like you have the energy do you? it's not</u>
<u n="296" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh yeah</unclear> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0530">do you know how I found? <pause dur="short"/> like it feels a bit like? <pause dur="short"/> you know <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> is it the right word like receptors like <pause dur="short"/> when <pause dur="short"/> you know you have like something that like you know when you touch something? <pause dur="short"/> like you burn yourself you pull away really fast?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah pain receptors</u>
<u n="299" who="S0530">I feel like <pause dur="short"/> with everything like kind of thing not obviously with pain cos I probably like <pause dur="short"/> pull myself away just as fast but in terms of like life my life <pause dur="short"/> when I'm depressed it's like that a bit like it's but it's very slow it's not <pause dur="short"/> yeah like fast it's</u>
<u n="300" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0530">very like my reactions are very kinda like <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="302" who="S0529">yeah I get that</u>
<u n="303" who="S0530"><unclear>go down</unclear></u>
<u n="304" who="S0529">yeah like sometimes when I might do just <pause dur="short"/> sabotage stuff to myself I just watch myself doing it like coming from outside of</u>
<u n="305" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="306" who="S0529">myself <pause dur="short"/> and just kind of think <pause dur="short"/> this is what you're doing and you're not stopping it and I just let it carry on</u>
<u n="307" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="308" who="S0529">I just like it's not like I like <trunc>t</trunc> sabotaging myself</u>
<u n="309" who="S0530">no</u>
<u n="310" who="S0529">it's just I have like no feeling about it <pause dur="short"/> I just feel a bit kind of <pause dur="short"/> distant from it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="312" who="S0529">and I just watch it happen <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then that's when I panic</u>
<u n="313" who="S0530">mm?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0529">after that <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0530">it's just a killer isn't it? like it's horrible</u>
<u n="316" who="S0529">yeah <pause dur="short"/> could be worse</u>
<u n="317" who="S0530">well don't say that because it's gonna be worse for everyone <trunc>some</trunc> there's gonna be someone out there it's worse for</u>
<u n="318" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0530">like don't don't compare</u>
<u n="320" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> me <vocal desc="laugh"/> being allowed to suffer <pause dur="short"/> you've won like the prize for being allowed to suffer <pause dur="short"/> I've found someone finally <pause dur="short"/> everyone else isn't allowed cos their problems <unclear>as big as this</unclear> one person</u>
<u n="321" who="S0530" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="322" who="S0529">that's how that's what it's like</u>
<u n="323" who="S0530">I know <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="324" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> ah <pause dur="long"/> it's just horrible cos it's makes me feel so selfish and self absorbed</u>
<u n="325" who="S0530" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="326" who="S0529">and just <pause dur="short"/> everything is about yourself <pause dur="short"/> because you just can't get out of it like you can't</u>
<u n="327" who="S0530">I don't think you're self absorbed like even if you were it wouldn't be</u>
<u n="328" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="329" who="S0530">it would be part of the illness but I don't think that's your problem I think you just don't care about anything including yourself</u>
<u n="330" who="S0529">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean that's true as well like <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I'm constantly in my head but also don't <pause dur="short"/> care a <trunc>sh</trunc> like I don't give a shit about myself like</u>
<u n="331" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="332" who="S0529">well as well like if <pause dur="short"/> I had the choice I would just</u>
<u n="333" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0529">I don't leave myself to kind of rot away in my room <vocal desc="laugh"/> and not give a shit like</u>
<u n="335" who="S0530" trans="overlap">I mean <pause dur="short"/> you get to that point where your mind isn't really like your <pause dur="short"/> kind of</u>
<u n="336" who="S0529">no <pause dur="short"/> it's not even mine any more</u>
<u n="337" who="S0530" trans="overlap">function it's</u>
<u n="338" who="S0529">no</u>
<u n="339" who="S0530">more of your cage you know?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="341" who="S0530">it's not the <pause dur="short"/> thing that makes you get up and do things it's the thing that kinda keeps you in one place</u>
<u n="342" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0530">and <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's hard</u>
<u n="344" who="S0529">and it's weird cos most of the time I was like well not most of the time but some of the time I'm completely normal and</u>
<u n="345" who="S0529"><unclear/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0530">exactly like that</u>
<u n="347" who="S0529" trans="overlap">think <pause dur="short"/> doesn't it?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0530">it does feel like you're a fraud <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0530">that you're not <pause dur="short"/> just because it's not <pause dur="short"/> you know full time every minute of the every day <pause dur="short"/> just because you can have some maybe some <pause dur="short"/> higher points and then some really low points it doesn't undermine the low points okay?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0529">I'm sorry if it makes it difficult to talk about with you cos <unclear/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> I I mean I'm I'm happy talking about it like it doesn't make me feel like lower</u>
<u n="353" who="S0529" trans="overlap">cos I know that my friend doesn't cos she's had it before and she just doesn't like talking about it any more</u>
<u n="354" who="S0530">I mean I can it actually is a relief to me that you can relate to everything that I'm saying</u>
<u n="355" who="S0529">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0530">because</u>
<u n="357" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><trunc>s</trunc> me too</u>
<u n="358" who="S0530">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's horrible when it happens and when it gets <unclear>bad <trunc>sh</trunc></unclear> like <pause dur="short"/> I mean for me it's only been the last week <pause dur="short"/> that things have actually lifted a bit</u>
<u n="359" who="S0529">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'm so glad <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0530" trans="overlap">and I felt able to do thing <trunc>u</trunc><trunc>u</trunc> more and I was actually surprised at how quickly it was</u>
<u n="361" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0530">and I've been <pause dur="short"/> I've been</u>
<u n="363" who="S0529">do you think it's the med? <pause dur="short"/> partly?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0530">no</u>
<u n="365" who="S0529">oh that's good <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0530">I obviously I think <pause dur="short"/> in a way <pause dur="short"/> meds are gonna have an influence</u>
<u n="367" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0530">they <trunc>al</trunc> they always are but I think that it's because <pause dur="short"/> I literally have said to myself <pause dur="short"/> I think my moment was when I was just not being able to do my work and I was just like <pause dur="short"/> nothing can be worse by just <pause dur="short"/> than like the way I am now like</u>
<u n="369" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0530"><trunc>noth</trunc> like even trying my work and failing everything and getting a really bad grade and hating myself for it</u>
<u n="371" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0530">it cannot be worse by <pause dur="short"/> than having to tell my seminar tutor that I can't do the work</u>
<u n="373" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0530">and feel even more of a failure because I'll never know what I actually would've got in the <pause dur="short"/> assignment <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I just hope that regularly <pause dur="short"/> doing work will exercise my brain and</u>
<u n="375" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="376" who="S0530">train it to work again</u>
<u n="377" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0530">like see it as <pause dur="short"/> kind of growth rather than like <pause dur="short"/> something that'll burn me out <pause dur="short"/> and not pushing myself too hard as well because <pause dur="short"/> you know you've gotta be gentle <pause dur="short"/> like you've gotta be firm but you've gotta be gentle</u>
<u n="379" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>I think that is</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> it's a good way of looking at it</u>
<u n="380" who="S0530">it is because there's I think there's a danger of like making yourself do too much</u>
<u n="381" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0530">but also too little as well like you can <trunc>alway</trunc> you can never really tell what <pause dur="short"/> cos you've gotta get a balance in on it and I think that is hard especially at uni because <pause dur="short"/> there is no well except me <pause dur="short"/> and people in the flat there is nobody telling you <pause dur="short"/> what to do here</u>
<u n="383" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="384" who="S0530">which and I think independence when you're depressed can be the most damaging thing you know? <pause dur="short"/> like obviously there are people like emailing you and shit but it's not direct nobody's coming and hammering on your door and saying <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> get out of bed you know? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I am worried they're gonna start doing that</u>
<u n="386" who="S0530">oh wow</u>
<u n="387" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's why I used to worry about last year</u>
<u n="388" who="S0530">come all the where to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="389" who="S0529" trans="overlap">that they would actually just come to my room and start like <pause dur="short"/> telling me off <unclear>for it right in front of</unclear> my face <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> emails are scary though I hate emails</u>
<u n="390" who="S0530">they are <pause dur="short"/> they really are</u>
<u n="391" who="S0529" trans="overlap">cos they just expect you to keep up with your email account every day and it's like I don't <pause dur="short"/> like checking it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0530">I always get really scared like <pause dur="short"/> if I've missed something or <pause dur="short"/> like well</u>
<u n="393" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah like you know I said that my physics thing wasn't on my timetable my seminar?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0529">it turns out they sent an email round yesterday saying that oh it is actually on I don't know why it's not on the <pause dur="short"/> not on your timetable</u>
<u n="396" who="S0530" trans="overlap">what the physics?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0529">the physics seminar</u>
<u n="398" who="S0530">I was thinking that</u>
<u n="399" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and I didn't get that email until like today</u>
<u n="400" who="S0530">oh well you shouldn't've known well</u>
<u n="401" who="S0529" trans="overlap">cos I hadn't looked <pause dur="short"/> and it was already too late so <pause dur="short"/> I mean to be honest I probably wouldn't gone anyway cos I haven't been to <unclear>one</unclear> of them and <pause dur="short"/> so you know <vocal desc="laugh"/> like <pause dur="short"/> you know what I'm like but <pause dur="short"/> that wasn't really my fault that one</u>
<u n="402" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="403" who="S0529">but it's just a pain now cos I'm I've got another absence and <pause dur="short"/> if I do actually end up staying here I'm not gonna get the grand that I need <pause dur="short"/> next year</u>
<u n="404" who="S0530">are you sure you need attendance for that?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I expect so <pause dur="short"/> that's usually what they <pause dur="short"/> work with like that's what they <pause dur="short"/> measure it <pause dur="short"/> by</u>
<u n="406" who="S0530">what were you gonna use the grand for like accommodation or food for this year just for this year?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0529" trans="overlap">well just everything it was just for like <pause dur="short"/> it it was just we just factored it into everything we didn't like put it aside <pause dur="short"/> it was just part of the money we'd get</u>
<u n="408" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0529"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="410" who="S0530">that sucks</u>
<u n="411" who="S0529">yeah so if I don't get that I'm gonna be so fucked <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> but I mean that's <unclear/> anyway</u>
<u n="412" who="S0530" trans="overlap">is there any way you can get? <pause dur="short"/> like do they charge for? <pause dur="short"/> you know <anon type="place"/> you're with <anon type="place"/> aren't you?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0529"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0530">oh you're in <anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0529">well no my my student account's with <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="416" who="S0530">okay</u>
<u n="417" who="S0529">I've got an overdraft</u>
<u n="418" who="S0530">do they charge interest for overdraft?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0529" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="420" who="S0530">no?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0529">no I would be able to use my overdraft but I'd have to pay it off at the end and it would <unclear>not <pause dur="short"/> be</unclear> it's just</u>
<u n="422" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="423" who="S0529">yeah I don't know I suppose I could use my overdraft dip in dip into that</u>
<u n="424" who="S0530" trans="overlap">is it the same with all banks then like all banks?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0529">yeah they don't charge interest with student accounts usually</u>
<u n="426" who="S0530" trans="overlap">student banks? <pause dur="short"/> really?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0530">that's really I thought they did</u>
<u n="429" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and I get I get fourteen hundred overdraft which is pretty decent</u>
<u n="430" who="S0530" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="431" who="S0529">so <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna get an <unclear>I</unclear></u>
<u n="432" who="S0530" trans="overlap">is this for Coop then?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0529">yeah Coop <unclear>yeah</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> do you not get interest <pause dur="short"/> erm overdraft?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0530">I've not got a student bank account I've just got a normal one</u>
<u n="435" who="S0529">have you not?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0529">oh my god why not?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0530" trans="overlap">so I have cos my parents were like don't get a student account</u>
<u n="439" who="S0529" trans="overlap">we should've done though cos you get you get an overdraft and it's completely free</u>
<u n="440" who="S0530">and how long can you have the overdraft for?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0529">well it's for this year and then it gets it <pause dur="short"/> erm they give you more next year you get two grand next year</u>
<u n="442" who="S0530">so I can have one grand overdraft this year?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0529">I get fourteen hundred overdraft</u>
<u n="444" who="S0530">wow</u>
<u n="445" who="S0529">on my current account and</u>
<u n="446" who="S0530">okay</u>
<u n="447" who="S0529">most accounts do that <pause dur="short"/> even <unclear/></u>
<u n="448" who="S0530" trans="overlap">fourteen grand?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0529">well no not fourteen grand like one thousand four hundred</u>
<u n="450" who="S0530" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="451" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0530">wow okay</u>
<u n="453" who="S0529">perhaps they get fourteen grand imagine</u>
<u n="454" who="S0530" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> and then it's so you get you'd have to pay it back over next</u>
<u n="455" who="S0529">well you have to</u>
<u n="456" who="S0530" trans="overlap">three years or <pause dur="short"/> by next year?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0529" trans="overlap">when you're in your overdraft you just pay <pause dur="short"/> the overdraft back you don't like <pause dur="short"/> you don't have to like pay it back as debt it's just money that you don't have and you pay it back <unclear>over time</unclear> as you go</u>
<u n="458" who="S0530" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> well <trunc>I</trunc>I'll <trunc>ch</trunc> convert my account then</u>
<u n="459" who="S0529" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> but then at the end of the year if you are in overdraft most students are</u>
<u n="460" who="S0530" trans="overlap">sorted <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0529">then you just pay it off next year or get a job over summer and that's <unclear>if you can pay their account</unclear></u>
<u n="462" who="S0530" trans="overlap">oh okay so there's no like deadline to the end of this year you have to pay it or something?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0529" trans="overlap">no no no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> and then there's no interest and what they do if you go over it if you go over your overdraft which is so impossible cos you've got fourteen hundred quid <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> they tell you <pause dur="short"/> that you've gone over and they give you a chance to pay it back</u>
<u n="464" who="S0530">okay</u>
<u n="465" who="S0529" trans="overlap">like what you've gone over and it's usually only a couple of quid anyway</u>
<u n="466" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0529">and then they don't charge you</u>
<u n="468" who="S0530"><unclear>okay</unclear></u>
<u n="469" who="S0529">so it's like really good</u>
<u n="470" who="S0530" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0529">to get an overdraft like it's really <pause dur="short"/> essential <pause dur="short"/> cos it just gives you a kind of like <pause dur="short"/> safety belt if you do <pause dur="short"/> have to</u>
<u n="472" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="473" who="S0529">have trouble with like paying <unclear>rent or</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="474" who="S0529">I can't believe you don't have an overdraft</u>
<u n="475" who="S0530">no cos my parents are like don't even bother with overdrafts and student accounts but I was like okay <pause dur="short"/> but I like</u>
<u n="476" who="S0529" trans="overlap">really? <pause dur="short"/> I mean yeah they're they're kind of scary cos like <pause dur="short"/> if you do go into your overdraft it's a bit scary cos it goes red and it looks like oh my god like I'm I'm in debt but you're not <pause dur="short"/> it's like everybody</u>
<u n="477" who="S0530" trans="overlap">it's just yeah</u>
<u n="478" who="S0529">dips into their overdraft</u>
<u n="479" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0529">it's just <pause dur="short"/> part of being a student really <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0530">I'll definitely make that on my agenda then to</u>
<u n="482" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0530">convert it because if my thingy comes through I'll need it <pause dur="short"/> if er</u>
<u n="484" who="S0529">yeah I didn't think about it you could use that yeah definitely</u>
<u n="485" who="S0530" trans="overlap">might be able to do it <unclear>through there</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> cos it's one thousand two hundred and <pause dur="short"/> thirty or something yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah to like use it for your <pause dur="short"/> accommodation as well</u>
<u n="487" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="488" who="S0529">no it's definitely a good idea and then you just pay it back over summer <pause dur="short"/> when you get a job</u>
<u n="489" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="490" who="S0529">and it takes like not very long usually</u>
<u n="491" who="S0530">okay</u>
<u n="492" who="S0529">to pay it back</u>
<u n="493" who="S0530">wow <pause dur="short"/> but what if you didn't pay it back over summer?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0529">well then you just have <pause dur="short"/> overdraft next year</u>
<u n="495" who="S0530">and overdraft then</u>
<u n="496" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and it will just roll over <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0530">okay</u>
<u n="498" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>but</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure what would</u>
<u n="499" who="S0530" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> yeah cos I don't yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0529">well no no cos I think my sister's actually in overdraft and you just kind of stay in overdraft until you pay it off <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="501" who="S0530">that's cool</u>
<u n="502" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0530" trans="overlap">that's fair enough then</u>
<u n="504" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I mean it's yeah it's fair enough like it's if you don't pay it back you just don't <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> they don't like come after you like</u>
<u n="505" who="S0530">I'll look on the <anon type="place"/> how much overdraft you can get</u>
<u n="506" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="507" who="S0530">if it's one thousand four hundred <pause dur="short"/> then that's not not too bad</u>
<u n="508" who="S0529" trans="overlap">let's have a look</u>
<u n="509" who="S0530">let's see</u>
<u n="510" who="S0529">you're <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0530">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos I tried looking I think before cos I was actually looking into getting a student account being like</u>
<u n="512" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0530">screw you know what screw your parents</u>
<u n="514" who="S0529" trans="overlap">what I got mine last year cos you get a free <pause dur="short"/> train ticket you get a free like railcard</u>
<u n="515" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's cool</u>
<u n="516" who="S0529">but it's just easier cos what I do I just pay myself a hundred pounds a week <pause dur="short"/> like from my account to my</u>
<u n="517" who="S0530">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0529">like my building society so I know exactly how much money I can spend a week</u>
<u n="519" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's cool</u>
<u n="520" who="S0529" trans="overlap">then I don't end up spending over</u>
<u n="521" who="S0530">right</u>
<u n="522" who="S0529" trans="overlap">upgrade existing account <pause dur="short"/> oh no I <trunc>d</trunc> I just want information really</u>
<u n="523" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="524" who="S0529">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah what does it say in here? <pause dur="short"/> when you open a student account with this <unclear>firm</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>get one now</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> an interest free overdraft here we go <pause dur="short"/> you can apply for up to five hundred in term one and up to <trunc>thu</trunc> two thousand after that</u>
<u n="525" who="S0530">up to two thousand?</u>
<u n="526" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh so you only get a <pause dur="short"/> you only get five hundred in the first year then? that's weird</u>
<u n="527" who="S0530">term one</u>
<u n="528" who="S0529">yeah that isn't that? doesn't that mean year?</u>
<u n="529" who="S0530">I thought it meant <pause dur="short"/> oh term does that mean the?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0529">I'm not sure <trunc>h</trunc> what that means actually maybe it does mean <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what it means</u>
<u n="531" who="S0530" trans="overlap">cos I I think cos your loan</u>
<u n="532" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0530">it <pause dur="short"/> your <trunc>f</trunc> in your first term you have to pay your loan back <pause dur="short"/> and you're sometimes in overdraft but it's not <pause dur="short"/> as much usually the first instalment isn't as much</u>
<u n="534" who="S0529" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh right</u>
<u n="535" who="S0530">it is <trunc>i</trunc> ironically it is here but</u>
<u n="536" who="S0529">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="537" who="S0530">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I think it does actually mean term one <pause dur="short"/> but it would've said year one otherwise</u>
<u n="538" who="S0529">yeah to keep the overdraft you have pay at least seven hundred fifty every six months <pause dur="short"/> and make at least three debit transactions each month but you you do that anyway like</u>
<u n="539" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0529">just by having <pause dur="short"/> just by like using the bank account</u>
<u n="541" who="S0530">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah with student finance you do get seven hundred and fifty every</u>
<u n="542" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0530">three months <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="544" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="545" who="S0530">and how do you undo your student account like how do you stop it being a student account? do you just like change it back?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0529">erm I think you just have to ring them up <pause dur="short"/> and just ask them if you could like <pause dur="short"/> change it</u>
<u n="547" who="S0530" trans="overlap">change it back <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="548" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/> how that would work really <pause dur="short"/> but I mean you could get <pause dur="short"/> a student account <pause dur="short"/> like it's pretty easy to do <pause dur="short"/> and you don't have to pay for it</u>
<u n="549" who="S0530" trans="overlap"><trunc>s</trunc>separate to your other account?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0529">like separate that's what I've got <pause dur="short"/> and it's</u>
<u n="551" who="S0530">okay</u>
<u n="552" who="S0529">quite good because it means that it's like separate so all your student money is separate and you just pay yourself what you get</u>
<u n="553" who="S0530">okay</u>
<u n="554" who="S0529">like your allowance and then the rest of it's all just in another account and you don't have to worry about it <pause dur="short"/> it just gets paid by like</u>
<u n="555" who="S0530" trans="overlap">that's really good</u>
<u n="556" who="S0529">like automatically like you set up automatic payments to the like the uni and to</u>
<u n="557" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="558" who="S0529">student finance and whatever</u>
<u n="559" who="S0530">that's cool</u>
<u n="560" who="S0529">and if you did that you might get more overdraft</u>
<u n="561" who="S0530">do some people have it all in the same one?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0529">I mean yeah yeah some people do yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="564" who="S0529">I dunno cos <pause dur="short"/> I've got mine in separate but</u>
<u n="565" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah you've got yours in separate I'm sure that's a good way of doing it actually like</u>
<u n="566" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I'm sure <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure people have</u>
<u n="567" who="S0530">the way you're doing it</u>
<u n="568" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I'm sure people do have it in <pause dur="short"/> let's look at like the best student <pause dur="short"/> bank accounts <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0530">so you have to apply for an overdraft then?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0529">erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah but it's not like a big</u>
<u n="571" who="S0530">okay</u>
<u n="572" who="S0529" trans="overlap">a big kind of thing like it's really easy to get <pause dur="short"/> you just kind of <pause dur="short"/> do it <pause dur="short"/> it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="573" who="S0530">it's not like oh yeah you need this yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0529" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no no <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> two thousand for up to five years wow <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="place"/>'s supposed to be good <pause dur="short"/> a lot of people I know have got that</u>
<u n="575" who="S0530" whoConfidence="low">that's cool</u>
<u n="576" who="S0529">I mean <anon type="place"/>'s good <pause dur="short"/> I've never had any problems with it</u>
<u n="577" who="S0530">that's really cool</u>
<u n="578" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0530">yeah I will I'll change it to <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>m</trunc> I mean I like just to make things</u>
<u n="580" who="S0529">to just change it yeah</u>
<u n="581" who="S0530" trans="overlap">simpler just yeah <pause dur="short"/> just <trunc>trans</trunc></u>
<u n="582" who="S0529">yeah just sign in and muck about and see what they say</u>
<u n="583" who="S0530" trans="overlap">cos then I don't have to worry about <unclear>everything if my appeal</unclear> doesn't come through I won't have to worry about it</u>
<u n="584" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you'd have like money in there to <pause dur="short"/> pay for it</u>
<u n="585" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="586" who="S0529">until you could like pay it back yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0530">I found that the price of our <pause dur="short"/> for accommodation <unclear>of</unclear> the year it's like <pause dur="short"/> I think it's four thousand four hundred</u>
<u n="588" who="S0529">bloody hell</u>
<u n="589" who="S0530">that's what I mean so <pause dur="short"/> it's not it's it's not it could be worse I guess I I I was expecting it to be more</u>
<u n="590" who="S0529" trans="overlap">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's so much <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0530">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is <pause dur="short"/> it is a lot more than I thought it would be to be honest</u>
<u n="592" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0530">that's looks like a <pause dur="short"/> space potato</u>
<u n="594" who="S0529">it does</u>
<u n="595" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="596" who="S0529">I was wanting to go shopping today I was gonna get potatoes and mash and make like</u>
<u n="597" who="S0530" trans="overlap">oh were you?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0529">toad in the hole but I didn't go shopping in the end <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> suppose I could do it's not too late</u>
<u n="599" who="S0530">yeah it's <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>th</trunc>three o'clock</u>
<u n="600" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="601" who="S0530">I've still got my frigging <pause dur="short"/> thing to do</u>
<u n="602" who="S0529">what?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0530">my erm revision Powerpoints <pause dur="short"/> that I have to</u>
<u n="604" who="S0529" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="605" who="S0530">go through <pause dur="short"/> which is fun</u>
<u n="606" who="S0529">revision for what? have you got another exam?</u>
<u n="607" who="S0530">well basically <pause dur="short"/> I'm making <trunc>m</trunc>my <pause dur="short"/> I'm basically transferring all my revision things to my <pause dur="short"/> to Powerpoint thing</u>
<u n="608" who="S0529">oh yeah I remember you said that</u>
<u n="609" who="S0530">to print</u>
<u n="610" who="S0529">that's a good idea</u>
<u n="611" who="S0530">when I go home so I can <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="612" who="S0529">are you going home next week?</u>
<u n="613" who="S0530">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna home once before Christmas but I don't know when</u>
<u n="614" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="615" who="S0530">I might go home next week</u>
<u n="616" who="S0529" trans="overlap">there's still time <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="617" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah there is still time <pause dur="short"/> I bet you're so excited to go back</u>
<u n="618" who="S0529">go back home?</u>
<u n="619" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="620" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0530">or in a way <pause dur="short"/> like to see <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0529">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I am <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>do</trunc> I dunno I think I will be when it gets closer like if I'm actually here till Christmas I'll be excited but at the minute it just feels like</u>
<u n="623" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="624" who="S0529">mm am I actually gonna make it till then? <pause dur="short"/> I'm thinking about going to my dad's for a bit maybe just getting like some</u>
<u n="625" who="S0530">what at the <trunc>mo</trunc>? like now?</u>
<u n="626" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0529">like cos I could go this week cos I haven't got anything on <pause dur="short"/> cos it's reading week</u>
<u n="629" who="S0530" trans="overlap">you could do <pause dur="short"/> you could do</u>
<u n="630" who="S0529">but then I've gotta hand in essays and stuff so it's like</u>
<u n="631" who="S0530" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="632" who="S0529">mm</u>
<u n="633" who="S0530">no yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0529">but I dunno whether to go to the doctor's and get an <pause dur="short"/> extension <unclear>note from them</unclear> or something</u>
<u n="635" who="S0530">you could do you could do that</u>
<u n="636" who="S0529">oh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> dunno how easy it is though</u>
<u n="637" who="S0530">I mean <pause dur="short"/> if you can prove your medical <pause dur="short"/> conditions <pause dur="short"/> then <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure you can easily</u>
<u n="638" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="639" who="S0530">you can get a doctor's note <pause dur="short"/> should be pretty straightforward</u>
<u n="640" who="S0529">mm <pause dur="long"/> yeah I dunno if it would actually help going to my dad's though to be honest but <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="641" who="S0530" trans="overlap">you'd just be kind of <pause dur="short"/> still thinking about it but it would just be yeah</u>
<u n="642" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it would just be a lot of money <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> you know? <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>I'd just get a</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> break</u>
<u n="643" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="644" who="S0529">and then come back <pause dur="short"/> feel exactly the same so <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="645" who="S0530">do you feel like <pause dur="short"/> you're still waiting until you want to feel like doing it? <pause dur="short"/> almost like obviously you don't wanna do it now <pause dur="short"/> and you feel like you can't do it now <pause dur="short"/> but do you feel like <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>w</trunc> do you feel like there's a sense of like <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> I at some point <pause dur="short"/> I can't <pause dur="short"/> simply can't just feel like this for my whole life like I there will be a point where I surely <unclear>am or</unclear> suddenly like feel a bit <pause dur="short"/> different to this? <pause dur="short"/> that it feels like it's not coming kinda thing?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0529">no I don't think so but I mean I am aware that I need to make change myself</u>
<u n="647" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="648" who="S0529">like I'm not</u>
<u n="649" who="S0530">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I know you're completely aware <pause dur="short"/> but like</u>
<u n="650" who="S0529" trans="overlap">like so I understand that I have to go and seek help <pause dur="short"/> and stuff like that</u>
<u n="651" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="652" who="S0529">and I feel like I've done that to a certain extent</u>
<u n="653" who="S0530" trans="overlap">which is great <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah you've done loads of that</u>
<u n="654" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I've just kinda missed the appointment like <vocal desc="laugh"/> really unfortunate I haven't done that but <pause dur="short"/> I've got like <pause dur="short"/> an appointment with the academic advisor next week</u>
<u n="655" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="656" who="S0529">which is really annoying cos it's like this week that's everything's happening but <pause dur="short"/> I it'll still have to go to that I reckon if I'm still here then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="657" who="S0530">if you're still here then?</u>
<u n="658" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah I don't know I'm just talking in terms of like <pause dur="short"/> I don't know like present tense at the moment but erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah I <trunc>d</trunc> <vocal desc="sigh"/> I dunno like I just wanna try and write this I just don't <pause dur="short"/> know where to start and every time I try I just <pause dur="short"/> lose concentration like within five minutes</u>
<u n="659" who="S0530" trans="overlap">is this <pause dur="short"/> physics?</u>
<u n="660" who="S0529">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it's so it's so frustrating to me because it's not even the important essay</u>
<u n="661" who="S0530" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="662" who="S0529">it's just like a little <pause dur="short"/> you know? <pause dur="short"/> unimportant thing that I have to do and I just can't get it done <pause dur="short"/> because I'm so <pause dur="short"/> worked up about it and because it it feels like an insult if I were to just do it really quickly as well because like <pause dur="short"/> this is what made me leave last year <pause dur="short"/> this whole thing of not being able to do these essays is what <pause dur="short"/> pretty much made me leave <pause dur="short"/> and it just seems stupid to just be able to <pause dur="short"/> bash one out and <pause dur="short"/> that's it <pause dur="short"/> and like the whole of last year meant absolutely nothing cos I just did it <pause dur="short"/> in five minutes and I know that <trunc>g</trunc> not gonna happen because <pause dur="short"/> I don't feel like that I can't <pause dur="short"/> do it <unclear>but everyone</unclear> thinks I can <pause dur="short"/> it's not</u>
<u n="663" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="664" who="S0529">it's not an easy thing for you to do</u>
<u n="665" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="666" who="S0529">just <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and it's so stupid cos it should be <pause dur="short"/> it's not difficult <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> but I could've done this in year eleven <pause dur="short"/> like this is the sort of thing they'd set in year eleven for science</u>
<u n="667" who="S0530">but when you get out of the routine it is a lot harder like</u>
<u n="668" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="669" who="S0530"><trunc>i</trunc> like <pause dur="short"/> like maybe yourself like a few years ago might've found it like <pause dur="short"/> piss easy but it doesn't mean that it's not</u>
<u n="670" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="671" who="S0530">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="672" who="S0529">oh I dunno</u>
<u n="673" who="S0530">but I I you are hashtag relatable</u>
<u n="674" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>thanks it's</unclear></u>
<u n="675" who="S0530">you very much you are even though it's shit for you</u>
<u n="676" who="S0529" trans="overlap">me too <pause dur="short"/> no it's not it's fine I'd rather be relatable than <pause dur="short"/> no one understand what I was talking about though so <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's good</u>
<u n="677" who="S0530" trans="overlap">cos you <trunc>d</trunc> you don't <trunc>s</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> I dunno like <unclear>before me</unclear> it's strange</u>
<u n="678" who="S0529">yeah <pause dur="short"/> me too</u>
<u n="679" who="S0530">like your head is kinda like on my <unclear>words</unclear> which <pause dur="short"/> strange <pause dur="short"/> but <unclear>I mean</unclear></u>
<u n="680" who="S0529">well it just I think it just shows really that it is an illness</u>
<u n="681" who="S0530" trans="overlap">that it isn't yeah exactly it's not just like</u>
<u n="682" who="S0529" trans="overlap">you know it's not it's not in my head</u>
<u n="683" who="S0530"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> being <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> no way</u>
<u n="684" who="S0529" trans="overlap">cos it's so <trunc>coinc</trunc> it would be too coincidental for us both to feel exactly the same about this sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> without it being some <pause dur="short"/> other</u>
<u n="685" who="S0530">exactly</u>
<u n="686" who="S0529">you know?</u>
<u n="687" who="S0530">exactly</u>
<u n="688" who="S0529" trans="overlap">secondary thing happening <pause dur="short"/> which is it</u>
<u n="689" who="S0530">and a lot of symptoms of depression are symptoms of laziness and can't be arsed <unclear>but</unclear></u>
<u n="690" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="691" who="S0530">so</u>
<u n="692" who="S0529">and that's the problem</u>
<u n="693" who="S0530" trans="overlap">you know?</u>
<u n="694" who="S0529">that's like that's the massive problem with it</u>
<u n="695" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah that's why it's so stigmatised</u>
<u n="696" who="S0529">fucking ridiculous <pause dur="short"/> oh <vocal desc="sigh"/> I just hate it I really do <pause dur="short"/> I wish I was lazy you know it would be so much easier</u>
<u n="697" who="S0530">too anxious to be lazy</u>
<u n="698" who="S0529">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="699" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="700" who="S0529"><trunc>exa</trunc> it doesn't work like being depressed and anxious at the same time it doesn't work <pause dur="short"/> they just <pause dur="short"/> they completely clash and <unclear/></u>
<u n="701" who="S0530" trans="overlap">sometimes I think I'm calm but I'm not</u>
<u n="702" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="703" who="S0530" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="704" who="S0529">I'm just like bubbling under the surface all the time <pause dur="short"/> and I never I don't <pause dur="short"/> I'm not an impatient person</u>
<u n="705" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="706" who="S0529">pretty much that I don't get angry <pause dur="short"/> really <pause dur="short"/> only at myself <pause dur="short"/> I don't really like shout and like completely lose it like my mum does or anything <pause dur="short"/> I'm quite a <pause dur="short"/> patient person</u>
<u n="707" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="708" who="S0529"><vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="709" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="710" who="S0529">I don't know <vocal desc="sigh"/> just a fucking nightmare really <pause dur="short"/> I dunno why I do that do you just do that? you like go on your phone and log in and then don't do anything cos you just</u>
<u n="711" who="S0530">just to check that it's happy</u>
<u n="712" who="S0529" trans="overlap">it's kinda just like a habit it's just <vocal desc="laugh"/> like <pause dur="short"/> a weird thing that I get with my <pause dur="short"/> it's like a reflex or something</u>
<u n="713" who="S0530">sometimes you even play with your phone when you're nervous it's like</u>
<u n="714" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0530">the equivalent of <trunc>tr</trunc> like <trunc>tw</trunc> like twiddling your hair</u>
<u n="716" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I'm so awful when I'm nervous I like playing with everything like I was just <pause dur="short"/> ripping this up and <trunc>i</trunc>if they give me tissues in counselling I rip them to shreds all the way through they shouldn't give me tissues cos I just <pause dur="short"/> I just get it everywhere <vocal desc="laugh"/> like it's so bad</u>
<u n="717" who="S0530">I used to like draw grids like craaaaa</u>
<u n="718" who="S0529" trans="overlap">did you? <pause dur="short"/> that's funny</u>
<u n="719" who="S0530">and that's actually quite common actually it's not</u>
<u n="720" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="721" who="S0530">like yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0529">no I've head that one my auntie told me about that one <pause dur="short"/> that people do that when they're stressed <pause dur="short"/> I draw point coin signs like</u>
<u n="723" who="S0530" trans="overlap">if <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="724" who="S0529">money signs <pause dur="short"/> which tells a lot about me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="725" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="726" who="S0529">that's what I doodle</u>
<u n="727" who="S0530" trans="overlap">your your priorities</u>
<u n="728" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="729" who="S0530">or is that anxieties over money or?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0529" trans="overlap">money <pause dur="short"/> oh both</u>
<u n="731" who="S0530" trans="overlap">dreams of money or</u>
<u n="732" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="733" who="S0530">richness</u>
<u n="734" who="S0529">I was reading up a <pause dur="short"/> a <pause dur="short"/> there was a thing on the <unclear>Tab</unclear> about sugar daddies <pause dur="short"/> and this girl who like spent a month just <pause dur="short"/> going out for dinner with these really rich men like fifty year olds <pause dur="short"/> and they would just pay for dinner like thousands of pounds and buy her like</u>
<u n="735" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="736" who="S0529" trans="overlap">bags and perfume and all of this stuff</u>
<u n="737" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they do that</u>
<u n="738" who="S0529">and she didn't have sex with him</u>
<u n="739" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="740" who="S0529">she just</u>
<u n="741" who="S0530">that's yeah</u>
<u n="742" who="S0529" trans="overlap">has intellectual <trunc>con</trunc>conversation and I just <unclear>want</unclear></u>
<u n="743" who="S0530" trans="overlap">they just wanted company they're just lonely and they've got so much money</u>
<u n="744" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that sounds like <unclear>such</unclear> a good idea <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="745" who="S0530">like me seriously me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and</u>
<u n="746" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I wanna do that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="747" who="S0530"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> last year my friends at uni</u>
<u n="748" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="749" who="S0530">we sat in <unclear><anon type="place"/></unclear> just having this huge <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> discussion like serious discussion about how we could actually do go about doing this</u>
<u n="750" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="751" who="S0530">and <unclear>then we</unclear> were just like <pause dur="short"/> hang on we've we're all skint <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>why don't we</unclear> just do it?</u>
<u n="752" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="753" who="S0530">or like we'll just</u>
<u n="754" who="S0529">can we use that <unclear>here</unclear> like?</u>
<u n="755" who="S0530" trans="overlap">everyone <pause dur="short"/> shall we just do it?</u>
<u n="756" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="757" who="S0530">and the thing was last year like there's loads of them like near <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> because of all the big buildings</u>
<u n="758" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah I bet</u>
<u n="759" who="S0530">but here it's like</u>
<u n="760" who="S0529">yeah you wouldn't get <unclear/></u>
<u n="761" who="S0530" trans="overlap">it's <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> shit you could get the</u>
<u n="762" who="S0529">you could go to London</u>
<u n="763" who="S0530" trans="overlap">you'd get a sugar sheep</u>
<u n="764" who="S0529" trans="overlap">but they <pause dur="short"/> the thing is they pay you for like <pause dur="short"/> trips to <pause dur="short"/> other cities</u>
<u n="765" who="S0530">yeah and they can take you on like</u>
<u n="766" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>flights to get there</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="767" who="S0530">when you look on their profiles it's crazy like I'm looking for someone who I can treat and travel the world with and it's like</u>
<u n="768" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah it's ridiculous like why would <unclear>they</unclear>?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0530" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="770" who="S0529">well it's very nice of them and</u>
<u n="771" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="772" who="S0529">if I was more confident I would definitely do it like <unclear/></u>
<u n="773" who="S0530" trans="overlap">and some rich people give students loans</u>
<u n="774" who="S0529">yeah this one she said she erm he paid off her entire overdraft</u>
<u n="775" who="S0530" trans="overlap">on websites <pause dur="short"/> that's amazing</u>
<u n="776" who="S0529">just straightaway <pause dur="short"/> like he was just like give me your bank details I'll pay it off for you <pause dur="short"/> and they hadn't even met <pause dur="short"/> this was just her like chatting on the one of the like <pause dur="short"/> date line things whatever they're called</u>
<u n="777" who="S0530" trans="overlap">that's crazy</u>
<u n="778" who="S0529">I know he just paid it off</u>
<u n="779" who="S0530">you could just do that and never speak to them again as harsh as it would be</u>
<u n="780" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I know exactly and that's what she did she like she just completely cut off from everyone after a month cos she was like right my social life's kind of getting <pause dur="short"/> a bit messed up here and I'm better stop this now and she did</u>
<u n="781" who="S0530">I'm so doing this</u>
<u n="782" who="S0529">but it was just such a good month cos she had so much money <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="783" who="S0530">they buy you presents</u>
<u n="784" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and she was <unclear>and</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> I was really <pause dur="short"/> like admiring her cos she was so confident and so like not afraid of what people would think of her</u>
<u n="785" who="S0530">no</u>
<u n="786" who="S0529">like she told her family</u>
<u n="787" who="S0530" trans="overlap">I mean</u>
<u n="788" who="S0529">and it's got <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's got nothing to do with it even if she was having sex with him she shouldn't've been ashamed of it like</u>
<u n="789" who="S0530" trans="overlap">no exactly I mean you're doing them a service</u>
<u n="790" who="S0529">yeah exactly if they want it</u>
<u n="791" who="S0530" trans="overlap">like you're in control <pause dur="short"/> because it's your</u>
<u n="792" who="S0529" trans="overlap">exactly <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="793" who="S0530" trans="overlap">position like it's not</u>
<u n="794" who="S0529">and she didn't feel like ever that she was trapped into it like she felt like she <trunc>c</trunc> she could always say no</u>
<u n="795" who="S0530">opt out and mm</u>
<u n="796" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and they weren't there for sex anyway</u>
<u n="797" who="S0530">no</u>
<u n="798" who="S0529" trans="overlap">most of the time <pause dur="short"/> they just want you to talk</u>
<u n="799" who="S0530" trans="overlap">that's the thing</u>
<u n="800" who="S0529">cos they're old enough and they usually have families as well like they usually have wives and stuff they just want to like talk about their day <pause dur="short"/> and sort of</u>
<u n="801" who="S0530">that's really kinda sad isn't it?</u>
<u n="802" who="S0529" trans="overlap">it is it's really quite</u>
<u n="803" who="S0530" trans="overlap">like</u>
<u n="804" who="S0529">it's quite tragic really for them <vocal desc="laugh"/> like <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="805" who="S0530">they must be so desperate like if they're willing to spend that much on company</u>
<u n="806" who="S0529" trans="overlap">they must be quite lonely <pause dur="short"/> I know</u>
<u n="807" who="S0530">and sure <unclear>they're</unclear> rich</u>
<u n="808" who="S0529" trans="overlap">well then but money to them isn't the same thing as what it would be to us like</u>
<u n="809" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="810" who="S0529">cos it's <pause dur="short"/> cos they've just got so much of it like</u>
<u n="811" who="S0530" trans="overlap">money's probably just money like</u>
<u n="812" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="813" who="S0530">it comes and goes like the grass and the rain and</u>
<u n="814" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> imagine that</u>
<u n="815" who="S0530">trees</u>
<u n="816" who="S0529">imagine just <pause dur="short"/> money being disposable to someone</u>
<u n="817" who="S0530">yeah <pause dur="short"/> must be so strange</u>
<u n="818" who="S0529" trans="overlap">it's insane</u>
<u n="819" who="S0530">like Kardashians have is it</u>
<u n="820" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="821" who="S0530">like four hundred and eighty million?</u>
<u n="822" who="S0529"><vocal desc="misc"/> I know</u>
<u n="823" who="S0530">wow</u>
<u n="824" who="S0529">kind of admire them though cos they've done it all themselves</u>
<u n="825" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="826" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="827" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="828" who="S0529">you know why shouldn't they exploit themselves through reality <pause dur="short"/> tV if they're gonna make money off it like I would <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="829" who="S0530" trans="overlap"><unclear>cos I would</unclear></u>
<u n="830" who="S0529">hundred percent</u>
<u n="831" who="S0530">yeah I I I don't have a problem with</u>
<u n="832" who="S0529" trans="overlap">they're businesswomen</u>
<u n="833" who="S0530">Kardashians to be honest like</u>
<u n="834" who="S0529" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't</u>
<u n="835" who="S0530">I don't watch the Kardashians but like</u>
<u n="836" who="S0529">no</u>
<u n="837" who="S0530">I don't everyone's like oh I hate them I'm like I don't hate them <pause dur="short"/> nothing wrong with them</u>
<u n="838" who="S0529" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="839" who="S0530">done nothing wrong <pause dur="short"/> they're successful</u>
<u n="840" who="S0529">they're like the royal family except they've done it all themselves</u>
<u n="841" who="S0530">they really are</u>
<u n="842" who="S0529">aren't they?</u>
<u n="843" who="S0530">they are better than the royal family and that</u>
<u n="844" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos they've done it all themselves</u>
<u n="845" who="S0530" trans="overlap">in so many respects</u>
<u n="846" who="S0529" trans="overlap">they're business people like they've</u>
<u n="847" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="848" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="849" who="S0530">they're not just born into wealth you know?</u>
<u n="850" who="S0529" trans="overlap">exactly <pause dur="short"/> well I mean the <unclear>Kendall</unclear> sisters were but they're also doing stuff now aren't they? like she's a model <unclear>and she's</unclear></u>
<u n="851" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="852" who="S0529">doing something I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> yeah <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> wish I was rich</u>
<u n="853" who="S0530">me too <pause dur="short"/> be cool to be rich <pause dur="short"/> imagine just not <unclear>I</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> like <pause dur="short"/> do you know what? like <pause dur="short"/> that's the thing I <pause dur="short"/> I I never think about being rich and being like oh I <pause dur="short"/> not particularly like I'd buy this and I'd buy that not always it's more like I wouldn't have to worry about money</u>
<u n="854" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly <pause dur="short"/> and that's</u>
<u n="855" who="S0530">it's <trunc>n</trunc></u>
<u n="856" who="S0529">that's kind of good really cos that's what you want like you don't wanna <unclear>be</unclear></u>
<u n="857" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="858" who="S0529">you know really spoilt and</u>
<u n="859" who="S0530">it's just I'd like to be comfortable and not have that on my mind</u>
<u n="860" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>conceited about it</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> yeah you just don't wanna have to worry about money <pause dur="short"/> it just wouldn't be there <pause dur="short"/> and that's why people who are rich can say like oh money doesn't buy happiness but it buys like <pause dur="short"/> safety and</u>
<u n="861" who="S0530">it buys everything</u>
<u n="862" who="S0529">assurance that you're not gonna <pause dur="short"/> you know ever be in a position where</u>
<u n="863" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="864" who="S0529">you don't have enough money for things <pause dur="short"/> that you need</u>
<u n="865" who="S0530" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="866" who="S0529">and it would just yeah <pause dur="short"/> it would just leave you to <pause dur="short"/> you know go about your life doing other things and not worrying ever <pause dur="short"/> about money</u>
<u n="867" who="S0530">yeah pretty much</u>
<u n="868" who="S0529"><trunc>n</trunc> if I was rich I could just go home now and I could go and do <pause dur="short"/> I don't know a degree in <pause dur="short"/> anything I wanted and not have to <pause dur="short"/> worry about getting a job at the end of it because it would just for my enjoyment</u>
<u n="869" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="870" who="S0529">cos I'd have enough money to do <pause dur="short"/> whatever I wanted after that</u>
<u n="871" who="S0530">my god imagine that though</u>
<u n="872" who="S0529">and I wouldn't mind paying extra tax cos I'd deserve to like yeah I've got more money <pause dur="short"/> I need to contribute more <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> like <pause dur="short"/> yeah I don't think I'd be greedy about it</u>
<u n="873" who="S0530">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> neither would I really <pause dur="short"/> I mean what would you actually buy if you were rich? I don't actually know</u>
<u n="874" who="S0529">well that's the thing cos now I'm like so scared about buying anything like I don't buy very much <pause dur="short"/> other than food like here especially because I'm just worried about spending money like</u>
<u n="875" who="S0530">I'd go travelling</u>
<u n="876" who="S0529">I'd just find it so precious</u>
<u n="877" who="S0530" trans="overlap">I'd spend it on experiences like I'd like to do stuff like</u>
<u n="878" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="879" who="S0530">I know it sounds strange but like <pause dur="short"/> scuba diving and that kinda thing</u>
<u n="880" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="881" who="S0530">and just have experiences but I'd also like a home <pause dur="short"/> like a nice home <pause dur="short"/> and I'd like <pause dur="short"/> to <pause dur="short"/> make like an animal thing in my home like</u>
<u n="882" who="S0529">oh</u>
<u n="883" who="S0530">not like quite Paris Hilton's</u>
<u n="884" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>I know what you mean</unclear></u>
<u n="885" who="S0530" trans="overlap">but that is incredible <pause dur="short"/> but like</u>
<u n="886" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="887" who="S0530">have like a <pause dur="short"/> sanctuary for animals where people can come in and work and stuff and like</u>
<u n="888" who="S0529" trans="overlap">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's so cute</u>
<u n="889" who="S0530">come in and look after them and I'd <pause dur="short"/> I'd love to do stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> but yeah</u>
<u n="890" who="S0529">yeah I think I would buy my mum <pause dur="short"/> a house <pause dur="short"/> first</u>
<u n="891" who="S0530">you selfless little</u>
<u n="892" who="S0529">no but wouldn't you? no you'd buy your mum a house</u>
<u n="893" who="S0530" trans="overlap"><unclear>wow?</unclear></u>
<u n="894" who="S0529"><trunc>n</trunc> or no you might not but that's that's</u>
<u n="895" who="S0530" trans="overlap">I dunno</u>
<u n="896" who="S0529">that's like</u>
<u n="897" who="S0530">I dunno</u>
<u n="898" who="S0529">understandable</u>
<u n="899" who="S0530">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="900" who="S0529" trans="overlap">that's fine <unclear>sorry</unclear></u>
<u n="901" who="S0530" trans="overlap">I mean I I'd like to help with my family to be honest cos they have like <pause dur="short"/> financially <pause dur="short"/> have done stuff for me and I would like to give that back <pause dur="short"/> you know? <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="902" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="903" who="S0530">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> yeah I <trunc>wou</trunc></u>
<u n="904" who="S0529" trans="overlap">that sounds really annoyingly selfless but I don't think I can't think of anything else that I would do before that like that's really important to me</u>
<u n="905" who="S0530">and I suppose like with your mum as well like</u>
<u n="906" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="907" who="S0530">because <pause dur="short"/> she's had money troubles before <pause dur="short"/> that would really like <pause dur="short"/> make you think it would just be just be good</u>
<u n="908" who="S0529" trans="overlap">it would just be good cos she'd just have a house and she wouldn't have to worry about it ever again <pause dur="short"/> and I might just buy her the house we have now cos the house we have now is like really nice and</u>
<u n="909" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="910" who="S0529">it's in a good location you wouldn't get it these days <pause dur="short"/> and it's pretty cheap to buy like it's no ridiculously expensive</u>
<u n="911" who="S0530">imagine if we won the lottery</u>
<u n="912" who="S0529">oh <vocal desc="sigh"/> imagine it'd be so good</u>
<u n="913" who="S0530">like sixteen million pounds or whatever like</u>
<u n="914" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="915" who="S0530">did you know? <pause dur="short"/> fact you have more <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> you have erm more chance of dying on your way to the winning the lottery</u>
<u n="916" who="S0529">yeah I heard that once</u>
<u n="917" who="S0530" trans="overlap">than actually winning <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="918" who="S0529">I know it's so depressing</u>
<u n="919" who="S0530">it is</u>
<u n="920" who="S0529">er <vocal desc="sigh"/> the most I've ever won is like <unclear>twenty quid</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> and I think that was on a scratch card anyway so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="921" who="S0530">somebody I know in my school their family <pause dur="short"/> they they lived on like erm a council estate <pause dur="short"/> and they won a few million pounds <pause dur="short"/> they now live in quite a wealthy area of the town so it's completely changed</u>
<u n="922" who="S0529" trans="overlap">that's amazing for them <pause dur="short"/> that's brilliant</u>
<u n="923" who="S0530">it's brilliant yeah</u>
<u n="924" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="925" who="S0530">they live a completely different life now to the way they did it's</u>
<u n="926" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>now</unclear></u>
<u n="927" who="S0530">really strange <pause dur="short"/> but really good it's like</u>
<u n="928" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="929" who="S0530">couldn't've gone to anyone better to be honest</u>
<u n="930" who="S0529">what happens if the lottery like gets won by someone who's already got <pause dur="short"/> enough money <pause dur="short"/> like do they just still win it?</u>
<u n="931" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="932" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and it's just</u>
<u n="933" who="S0530">it's not they can't really take it away from them it's yeah</u>
<u n="934" who="S0529" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> no they can't really can they?</u>
<u n="935" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is <pause dur="short"/> but I don't think people that</u>
<u n="936" who="S0529" trans="overlap">luck of the draw</u>
<u n="937" who="S0530">I think it is like <pause dur="short"/> people who are in with a like <pause dur="short"/> I don't think many rich people <pause dur="short"/> enter the lottery</u>
<u n="938" who="S0529">but then they could cos they'd have the money to</u>
<u n="939" who="S0530" trans="overlap">they could</u>
<u n="940" who="S0529">you know?</u>
<u n="941" who="S0530">but I think more</u>
<u n="942" who="S0529" trans="overlap">cos that's another thing you have to pay to enter it and it's</u>
<u n="943" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="944" who="S0529">you know if you entered it a lot of times you'd have more chance <vocal desc="laugh"/> of winning in it so</u>
<u n="945" who="S0530">I <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>u</trunc> hate to image how <trunc>m</trunc> like much <pause dur="short"/> the average person spends on a lottery ticket in a lifetime without winning it's</u>
<u n="946" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> it's awful</u>
<u n="947" who="S0530" trans="overlap">horrible business <pause dur="short"/> like I actually well I recently <trunc>s</trunc> like because I'd seen the statistics I kind of got out of the habit of doing it and I'm just a bit like na <pause dur="short"/> but I used to get it</u>
<u n="948" who="S0529" trans="overlap">doing what?</u>
<u n="949" who="S0530">lottery tickets</u>
<u n="950" who="S0529">really?</u>
<u n="951" who="S0530" trans="overlap">like every now and then yeah <pause dur="short"/> just as a now and then not weekly but like oh yeah</u>
<u n="952" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I've never bought one</u>
<u n="953" who="S0530">I might do it</u>
<u n="954" who="S0529" trans="overlap">I've never actually bought one it's quite weird cos I'm so obsessed with money but I've never bought a lottery ticket or a scratch card or anything</u>
<u n="955" who="S0530" trans="overlap">I've bought a few <pause dur="short"/> scratch cards yeah</u>
<u n="956" who="S0529">I just I dunno</u>
<u n="957" who="S0530">I won like five quid but <pause dur="short"/> it's nothing that's big</u>
<u n="958" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="long"/> when does my twenty-five quid come? I need to find out about this <pause dur="short"/> it's not I don't miss it <pause dur="long"/> have you been <pause dur="short"/> I hate emails so much they're all so confusing <pause dur="short"/> what's her name?</u>
<u n="959" who="S0530"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="960" who="S0529">I know her name's so cute <pause dur="short"/> right Tuesday the third I can get this <unclear>round about</unclear> ear <pause dur="short"/> ear? here <pause dur="long"/> oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> that was <trunc>won</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> that was so funny <pause dur="short"/> did you see that on Yikyak? everyone <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>was talking about it</unclear></u>
<u n="961" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="962" who="S0529">can you see it anywhere?</u>
<u n="963" who="S0530">the what?</u>
<u n="964" who="S0529">it's like from student union <pause dur="short"/> no those are too far back it must be up here <pause dur="short"/> oh <vocal desc="sigh"/> it's so annoying <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>here we go</unclear> <pause dur="long"/> is it that? no <pause dur="short"/> aha</u>
<u n="965" who="S0530">yay</u>
<u n="966" who="S0529">yay <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> Wednesday oh god it's tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> shit <pause dur="short"/> okay I need to write this down <pause dur="short"/> <unclear><anon type="place"/></unclear> <pause dur="short"/> that's the one near <anon type="place"/> isn't it?</u>
<u n="967" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="968" who="S0529"><vocal desc="sigh"/> <unclear>so annoying</unclear> <pause dur="long"/> well good thing I checked</u>
<u n="969" who="S0530">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="970" who="S0530" whoConfidence="low">cool <pause dur="short"/> six thirty</u>
<u n="971" who="S0529">god I better not forget about this I need twenty-five quid <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="972" who="S0530">twenty-five quid</u>
<u n="973" who="S0529">yes <pause dur="short"/> I need to buy food this week <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="974" who="S0530">have you told them you can come?</u>
<u n="975" who="S0529"><trunc>i</trunc> yes I think</u>
<u n="976" who="S0530" trans="overlap">good</u>
<u n="977" who="S0529">yeah I sent them an email out so I should</u>
<u n="978" who="S0530" trans="overlap">oh good okay</u>
<u n="979" who="S0529">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="980" who="S0530">so asteroid mining may be a reality by two thousand twenty-five</u>
<u n="981" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> just so fucking boring <pause dur="short"/> why are gonna wanna read this anyway? <pause dur="short"/> I bet they don't even read them these cos these are so unimportant <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="982" who="S0530">so you could completely <trunc>sh</trunc> bullshit it then</u>
<u n="983" who="S0529" trans="overlap">oh <vocal desc="sigh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="984" who="S0530">basically</u>
<u n="985" who="S0529">well that's like the plan <pause dur="short"/> really <pause dur="short"/> just I don't wanna read through all this it's so fucking <pause dur="long"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I'm gonna go and make some food</u>
<u n="986" who="S0530">make some food</u>
<u n="987" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="988" who="S0530">I need to stop drinking Coke</u>
<u n="989" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="990" who="S0530">I'm proud of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for cutting down</u>
<u n="991" who="S0529">yes <pause dur="short"/> me too</u>
<u n="992" who="S0530">eighteen</u>
<u n="993" who="S0529">that's like almost half <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="994" who="S0530" trans="overlap">is a achievement</u>
<u n="995" who="S0529">is it? wait what what was she drinking before?</u>
<u n="996" who="S0530">erm thirty-six so it actually is half</u>
<u n="997" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is half yeah</u>
<u n="998" who="S0530" trans="overlap">she was <trunc>ea</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> she was drinking thirty-six cans of Coke</u>
<u n="999" who="S0529">well that's good that's awful</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0530" trans="overlap">a day</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0529">how on earth <unclear>she could</unclear></u>
<u n="1002" who="S0530">how is she alive?</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0529">I don't know</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0530">she must get really sleepy like tired</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0529">she must get really bad headaches like <pause dur="short"/> they give me headaches if I drink too many</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0530">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but then if you don't drink enough when you're hooked <pause dur="short"/> they give you headaches</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0530">like if <pause dur="short"/> it's must be like</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0529" trans="overlap">kind of like a drug <pause dur="short"/> really</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0530">it must feel <trunc>l</trunc> maybe their bodies like built up a tolerance like a tolerance to it</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> probably</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0530">like</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0529">oh</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0530">I think if you have it too much like</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0529">I just want a glass of Coke really <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1016" who="S0530">Coke</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0529"><unclear>my</unclear> Coke's really horrible <unclear/></u>
<u n="1018" who="S0530">oh have you still got the horrible one?</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yes I haven't drank it all yet cos it's horrible</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0530">you should actually take that back and say taste this shite</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it sometimes tastes okay and then other times it's like bleh</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0530">I can't remember what was wrong with it now it was watered down</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0529">it just and it just tastes wrong I don't know what it is <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> what do I have to eat? <pause dur="short"/> pretty much nothing</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1025" who="S0529"><vocal desc="sigh"/> <unclear>god</unclear></u>
<u n="1026" who="S0530"><unclear><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></unclear> this morning was a bit quiet and I thought he'd maybe heard what I said last night</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0529">he can't hear cos you can't hear anything although I can hear <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's got a really bad voice <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1028" who="S0530"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1029" who="S0529">I can hear <unclear/> in the kitchen</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0530" trans="overlap"><unclear>and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> he does a little</unclear> bit loud</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0530">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> maybe it wasn't <unclear/></u>
<u n="1033" who="S0529" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1034" who="S0530">I think I think he was just a bit grumpy</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0530">cos he usually is</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1038" who="S0530">so <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0529">he said he was feeling like a bit shit about the whole <unclear><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></unclear> thing so</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0530">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> bit like</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0530">he probably misses his girlfriend as well</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0529">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos she left yesterday</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0530">I think long term relationships at uni must be really like difficult</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0529">I know I dunno how everyone does it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> like she had to wait about eight weeks to see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and now she's waiting another <pause dur="short"/> four weeks till Christmas and that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="1046" who="S0530" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0529">just waits <pause dur="short"/> yeah it doesn't seem like she's actually going out or anything <pause dur="short"/> she's just like counting down the days <pause dur="short"/> yeah I can't really <unclear>remember like</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> so it's quite lucky that I don't have anyone</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0530" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0529">really <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1050" who="S0530">er <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh somebody emptied the bins that was nice of them I feel really bad because I</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah I did wanna do it <pause dur="short"/> but then I <vocal desc="laugh"/> I couldn't see where the bins were so <pause dur="short"/> I just put them like in the</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0530">yeah I tried emptying one of them the other day</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0529" trans="overlap">erm bin shed thing <pause dur="short"/> but it was pitch black so I couldn't see anything <pause dur="short"/> so I just <pause dur="short"/> I don't know where I put it like <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1054" who="S0530">no I was I tried <trunc>pu</trunc> I think I put it in the white one</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1056" who="S0530">when I went <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0529">at least the horrible rain stopped</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0530">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that is that is a positive</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0529"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1060" who="S0530">oh you've not been out have you? <pause dur="short"/> oh it's horrible and windy though</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>I dunno whether to go shopping</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> I dunno whether to go shopping cos if I do I'm gonna waste an hour like two hours just <pause dur="short"/> doing like not doing anything <pause dur="short"/> but if I go I might <pause dur="short"/> just get out</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0530">out the house for a bit</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>get some good stuff like</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> you know?</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>then</unclear> I could have some nice tea as well</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0530">yeah</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0529"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1068" who="S0530" trans="overlap">make yourself a nice meal</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0529">I might just do like an all nighter and get it done <pause dur="short"/> cos I mean I'm I'm twenty years old I can go all nighter</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0530">yes you can</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>and still survive</unclear></u>
<u n="1072" who="S0530">I felt like I was gonna do an all nighter last night then I fell asleep</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0529">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> it took me so long to get to sleep last night <pause dur="short"/> but I woke up <pause dur="short"/> with the alarm <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah I woke up at eight</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0530">did you?</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0529">yeah with the</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0530">are you kidding?</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0529">what do you call it?</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0530">you actually <trunc>d</trunc> it woke you up?</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear>I really did wake</unclear> up yeah</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0530">really good <pause dur="short"/> that is success</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0529">I know it is yeah</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0530">in itself</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0529"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I mean it took me about ten minutes to actually get out of bed but I did get out of bed and it was only like</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0530" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0529">half eight so <pause dur="short"/> I I call that <pause dur="short"/> a triumph really</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0530">that is a huge triumph</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and it will get easier every day <pause dur="short"/> cos the more I get up <trunc>ea</trunc>earlier <pause dur="short"/> you know my my sleep pattern will generally <pause dur="short"/> get better</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0530">mm <pause dur="short"/> definitely</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>so</unclear> good it's good <pause dur="long"/> I might go shopping <pause dur="short"/> put my big coat on</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0530">oh yeah you've got the hooded coat</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>so cold</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I didn't bring a scarf with me</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0530"><vocal desc="sigh"/> oh I forgot all my nice like winter wear</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've just forgotten all my clothes left them at home <pause dur="short"/> like I just didn't bring anything with me <pause dur="short"/> nice</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0530">I think</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1096" who="S0530" trans="overlap">because we came with the attitude <pause dur="short"/> that like we weren't going to stay</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0530">we were just like</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0529">did you come with that attitude as well?</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0530">a little bit</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0530">though yeah <pause dur="short"/> I came with the <trunc>a</trunc></u>
<u n="1103" who="S0529" trans="overlap">yeah I really came like that I was like right I need to make <trunc>pi</trunc> pack enough stuff so that I can get home without <pause dur="short"/> it being a massive <pause dur="short"/> fat like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1104" who="S0530">and now do you regret that a bit? thing yeah</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0529" trans="overlap">a little bit yeah because now I have no clothes <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I actually have really a nice fashion sense and you can't tell really cos I'm always wearing like black <pause dur="short"/> and big black <unclear>things</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1106" who="S0530" trans="overlap">you'll have to bring some of your stuff up after Christmas</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0529">yeah I might <pause dur="short"/> although I've only got my little suitcase so <pause dur="short"/> I won't be able to bring that much back</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0530">oh yeah oh crap</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0530">I always forget about the baggage</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0529" trans="overlap">and I wanna bring a dressing gown with me but I think what I'm gonna do is just buy one like</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0530" trans="overlap">yeah it's <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah your dressing gown?</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0529">after Christmas <pause dur="short"/> with my Christmas money</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0530">mm</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0529">and just have it up here <pause dur="short"/> and some slippers as well <pause dur="long"/> er <unclear>I've just seen some people</unclear></u>
<u n="1116" who="S0530"><shift new="singing"/> doo doo doo doo doo doo doo <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1117" who="S0529" trans="overlap"><unclear>do you want that?</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>really?</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>it's horrible?</unclear></u>
<u n="1118" who="S0530">oh is it still disgusting?</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0529">yeah <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <unclear>alright</unclear></u>
<u n="1120" who="S0530"><vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> right I'm gonna try and do this <pause dur="short"/> presentation</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0530" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1122" who="S0529"><unclear>oh I might go</unclear> on the bus <unclear>it's what I'm thinking</unclear></u>
<u n="1123" who="S0530" trans="overlap">oh yeah you actually gonna go?</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0529">yeah</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0530">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'd go</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0529"><trunc>ye</trunc></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
