<text id="SP45">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:13:20</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-16</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>4</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0652 S0653 S0654 S0655</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Home kitchen, Comberton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>About the day at Purton Green, old houses, ghosts</topics>
		<activity>Old houses and ghosts</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0652">
				<exactage>30</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace></birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur></hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Account executive at Prospect Research</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0653">
				<exactage>39</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dartford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0654">
				<exactage>7</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>1_primary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0655">
				<exactage>9</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury St Edmunds</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>1_primary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0652">have you heard from <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0655">then I'll have a vanilla like this <event desc="sound of rustling paper"/> er I'm going to put it back</u>
<u n="3" who="S0653">yep she should be coming over but erm <event desc="sound of tearing wrapper"/> she's in London today doing a singing thing so I expect she's probably quite tired so erm <pause dur="short"/> I think she will really want to come over though and see</u>
<u n="4" who="S0655" trans="overlap">if I was wearing a short-sleeved T-shirt you would see that my that <trunc>m</trunc> my skin is quite is quite bumpy on my arms</u>
<u n="5" who="S0653">your skin is quite bumpy because you're cold do you mean?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0655">yeah goosebumps</u>
<u n="7" who="S0653">goosebumps yes</u>
<u n="8" who="S0652"><unclear>you've got a T-shirt now</unclear></u>
<u n="9" who="S0655">it's it's gone now <unclear>it <trunc>w</trunc></unclear> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0653">what was the most fun part about today do you think?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0655">ice</u>
<u n="12" who="S0654" trans="overlap">going on the ice</u>
<u n="13" who="S0653" trans="overlap">cracking the ice yes in the big pond I expect</u>
<u n="14" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0653">I think I liked it best noise wise when the stones went on it it magnified</u>
<u n="16" who="S0652">mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0655">yeah those were cool and the <trunc>i</trunc> and the ice going <event desc="sound of vibrating"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0653">yes and they did look like diamonds didn't they <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0655">or crystal cos crystal is <trunc>w</trunc> kind of shiny but some <unclear>like</unclear></u>
<u n="20" who="S0654">there's this little circles on the <pause dur="short"/> which are ice and when you stamp on them they like go really sort of smaller and some looks like diamonds or</u>
<u n="21" who="S0653">lovely I liked it when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was cracking the ice standing on the ice and cracking it</u>
<u n="22" who="S0655" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0653">oh did the ice lolly fall off</u>
<u n="24" who="S0652" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="25" who="S0653">well you can have that</u>
<u n="26" who="S0655">no it's stuck it's stuck in here</u>
<u n="27" who="S0653">well you can sort of</u>
<u n="28" who="S0652">well you squeeze it from the bottom</u>
<u n="29" who="S0653">yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0655">yeah I'll have that after I've finished this part</u>
<u n="31" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="32" who="S0655"><vocal desc="laugh"/> actually I will start off with it because <event desc="sound of crunching"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0653">was it very spicy though the I can see all the chilli seeds?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0652">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0654">can I have my?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0653">your Mini Milk yes I guess so how much rice did you have?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0654">a lot I had two portions</u>
<u n="38" who="S0653"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you've eaten so much food today where are you going?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0654">to get a bowl because last time I snapped off the top and it was in my mouth it was really cold</u>
<u n="40" who="S0653">well it's an ice lolly <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0655">what do you expect?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0654">and I couldn't and I couldn't make it I was like a really big</u>
<u n="43" who="S0652">says captain this ice is cold <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0654">I had like a really big chunk and I couldn't split and I couldn't get it out</u>
<u n="45" who="S0653">alright get a bowl <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0655">I can't get this out</u>
<u n="47" who="S0654">just like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0653">so we might go and have a pub lunch tomorrow</u>
<u n="49" who="S0655">oh yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="51" who="S0652">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0653">or we could go to Ickworth House</u>
<u n="53" who="S0652">mm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0653">but not for food just to look round</u>
<u n="55" who="S0654">tidy</u>
<u n="56" who="S0653"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just come in with the bowl please <event desc="sound of bin lid"/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0652">oh dear</u>
<u n="58" who="S0653">was it easy to get to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0654">yeah I found the bin</u>
<u n="60" who="S0653">you found the bin</u>
<u n="61" who="S0654">yes</u>
<u n="62" who="S0653">well done</u>
<u n="63" who="S0655">good for her she gets to eat that</u>
<u n="64" who="S0653">if you wish to get a spoon yes did you manage to find this place quite easily as well?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0652">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="67" who="S0655">oh my gosh I'm getting goosebumps on my goosebumps</u>
<u n="68" who="S0652">well oh god there's a chill every now and then I get this horrible like coldness up my back it's horrible</u>
<u n="69" who="S0653">what here?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0652">here</u>
<u n="71" who="S0653">then what are you going to say?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0652">it's like someone stepped on my grave</u>
<u n="73" who="S0653">that it's that it's an apparition of some sort</u>
<u n="74" who="S0652">well if there was one in the picture I took of you</u>
<u n="75" who="S0653">there was a sort of glowing bit shape in one of the photographs now tell the children about when you saw a ghost when you were little</u>
<u n="76" who="S0655"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0652">which one?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0653">have you seen more than one?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0652">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0653">the monk at the end of the</u>
<u n="81" who="S0652">oh</u>
<u n="82" who="S0654">don't do that</u>
<u n="83" who="S0653">don't do that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0652">what?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0653">oh</u>
<u n="86" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I get that</u>
<u n="87" who="S0653">because we are in a house in the middle of nowhere so don't spook the children come on then</u>
<u n="88" who="S0652">but you want me to tell them a about a ghost that I've seen</u>
<u n="89" who="S0653">yes because ghosts are not they are so <unclear/></u>
<u n="90" who="S0652">but you don't want them to get scared</u>
<u n="91" who="S0653">well it's not a scary ghost is it?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0652">no it was just standing there</u>
<u n="93" who="S0653">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0652">at the end of the drive</u>
<u n="95" who="S0654">standing there</u>
<u n="96" who="S0653">what's the other ghost you've seen?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0652">mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0653">just standing just someone with a hood</u>
<u n="99" who="S0652">well we used to have the family used to have a holiday home up in the Yorkshire Dales which is very remote and it was up the side of a massive mountain and there used to be an old monastery so a monastery where lots of monks stay and that was all derelict</u>
<u n="100" who="S0655">what does derelict mean?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0652">falling apart</u>
<u n="102" who="S0653">a ruin</u>
<u n="103" who="S0652">so erm <pause dur="short"/> you had to go through about three fields and then there was in each field at the beginning and the end of a field there was a gate and you had to get out of the car and open the gate and let the car through and close the gate it was quite fun because we used to ride on the back of the car when we were young so the last gate is at the bottom of the drive and the drive was quite long to go up to the house it was about fifty metres to go up to the house and then there's a kitchen window that looks out and one time I saw this hooded figure from the window who was standing at the end of the drive and there was like no one else around so it was in the middle of nowhere and there was this hooded figure at the end of drive and I said to mummy mummy there's a man there's a man here she said what do you mean there's a man? and we looked and it was gone but there was no <pause dur="short"/> like you couldn't see anywhere else</u>
<u n="104" who="S0653">he was hiding crouching down I reckon</u>
<u n="105" who="S0652">it was not hiding</u>
<u n="106" who="S0653"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0652">that's a ghost because my then my grandma saw a ghost she woke up and she saw this figure at the foot of her bed she went <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he went aye and then my grandad was he suddenly snored next to her and she was like <vocal desc="gasp"/> and then that one disappeared as well I reckon it is the same ghost</u>
<u n="108" who="S0655">I know I know erm how ghosts can disappear so quickly</u>
<u n="109" who="S0652">because they are a figment of our imagination</u>
<u n="110" who="S0653"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yes yes</u>
<u n="111" who="S0655">no because they are non-solid they can sink through anything even if there is something solid in their way they can sink into the ground and then once the car had passed they could go up</u>
<u n="112" who="S0654">do you think <unclear/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0653">yes definitely</u>
<u n="114" who="S0652">I've seen some pretty pretty good footage in the nineteen-seventies poltergeist footage really there's no</u>
<u n="115" who="S0654">are poltergeist are poltergeists invisible?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0652">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0655">yeah they all around they could be all around us</u>
<u n="118" who="S0655">for all we know</u>
<u n="119" who="S0652">I'm going to check my Colgate toothpaste see if see if the ghost has used it</u>
<u n="120" who="S0653"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0652">mm it was definitely medieval ghost because he would be like oh this toothpaste might my stumps are so shiny</u>
<u n="122" who="S0653">I was going to say they don't they don't have any teeth anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0652">no</u>
<u n="124" who="S0653"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0655">the ghost might want to go and then all go <vocal desc="misc"/> and he will go <event desc="sound of clapping"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0653">well you see if they had a a filling in their teeth and then it just hurt and then they had to take the teeth out</u>
<u n="127" who="S0652">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0653">so you know you are going to have your filling done in a couple of weeks' time</u>
<u n="129" who="S0655">well I might but it might fall out by then</u>
<u n="130" who="S0653">well I doubt it</u>
<u n="131" who="S0652">a tooth is it a baby tooth?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0653">it is a baby tooth yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0652">crumbs</u>
<u n="134" who="S0653">I know I know</u>
<u n="135" who="S0652">a filling in a baby tooth</u>
<u n="136" who="S0653">only a tiny hole but it is not bothering you at the moment I mean I think it is pointless however I guess if it started to hurt you then it's best to prevent it isn't it the filling</u>
<u n="137" who="S0655">yeah but still it is going to hurt more than it is going to hurt me well it's going to hurt more with the filling than it is hurting me now</u>
<u n="138" who="S0653">at the moment but if it gets bigger the thing is because you can't sort of clean it properly you can get infections in the holes and all sort of things so that's why that's why the do it but some of my teeth is mostly filling anyway</u>
<u n="139" who="S0652">mm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0653">if I had lots of money I would <trunc>ca</trunc> cap them</u>
<u n="141" who="S0652">oh so would I what like veneers?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0653">no fisherman's cap they are called where you put a white or cream coating on them on the metal filling</u>
<u n="143" who="S0652">oh</u>
<u n="144" who="S0653">so it just looks like a tooth if you just bitten into your lolly stick</u>
<u n="145" who="S0654">spit it out</u>
<u n="146" who="S0653">take it out why is it still in your mouth it might have splinters</u>
<u n="147" who="S0654">idiots <unclear/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0653">why why did you bite it? <pause dur="short"/> take it out it's got splinters on the top</u>
<u n="149" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0653">you'd like veneers well I'd like I'd like my teeth whitened as well</u>
<u n="151" who="S0655">mum</u>
<u n="152" who="S0654">look you are going to get a splinter on your tongue</u>
<u n="153" who="S0655">I've got your problem solved</u>
<u n="154" who="S0653">just have massive prawn crackers instead of teeth that would look nice</u>
<u n="155" who="S0652">prawn crackety and everything you bite into would go <event desc="sound of crackling"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0653">that would be nice <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0655">I know you are</u>
<u n="158" who="S0653">perhaps I'll Tippex my teeth</u>
<u n="159" who="S0654">what does Tippex mean?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0653">Tippex is a white liquid that you put on documents if you've made a mistake</u>
<u n="161" who="S0652">but you not allowed it at school any more are you?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0653">are you not?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0652">no</u>
<u n="164" who="S0653">probably not well people in the office have it so if I've made a mistake on a document okay and it was only a tiny error and I wanted to photocopy it then rather than print out the whole document I would use the Tippex to Tippex it out and then that error would be gone so when it got photocopied you wouldn't be able to see that mistake it does smell though so lots of silly people at school used to sort of sniff it and get all excited about it and mess it up you know pour it over their text books and stuff</u>
<u n="165" who="S0655">why?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0653">because teenagers are silly sometimes</u>
<u n="167" who="S0654">if they did pour all over their text books then the teachers would go why did you put it on your text book</u>
<u n="168" who="S0653">well it kind of obviously it dries</u>
<u n="169" who="S0652">that's why it got banned</u>
<u n="170" who="S0653">I would imagine right you can eat that chicken ball if you like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because<anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is not going to eat it</u>
<u n="171" who="S0652">okay can I have another milky Mini Milk?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0653">after that if you've got room yes you two have been eating like there's no tomorrow what are you doing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0655">there's no tomorrow</u>
<u n="174" who="S0653">can you sit down please</u>
<u n="175" who="S0652">imagine if there wasn't a tomorrow</u>
<u n="176" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0652">there's today</u>
<u n="178" who="S0653">well this wouldn't be a bad place to what would happen a nuclear thing we wouldn't wake up from</u>
<u n="179" who="S0652">no as in like we we woke up and it was still dark</u>
<u n="180" who="S0653">it was today again mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0652">and all the clocks were just stop all watches were stopped everything was absolutely stopped and it was just stuck in time</u>
<u n="182" who="S0653">why does it have to be dark?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0652">because there was no tomorrow so you would get to midnight and it stop</u>
<u n="184" who="S0653">why can't it stop at like noon or something</u>
<u n="185" who="S0652">there's a little monkey climbing on me</u>
<u n="186" who="S0653">there is</u>
<u n="187" who="S0655"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0653">could you climb back onto your own chair monkey girl</u>
<u n="190" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0655">oh wait there's a banana on that chair monkey come and get it</u>
<u n="192" who="S0653">why have you both been talking about bananas and cheese all weekend?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it was</u>
<u n="194" who="S0652">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0653">what's the significance of bananas and cheese?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0654">it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not me</u>
<u n="197" who="S0655">bananas are the first random word I ever found out cheese if the newest random word I found out</u>
<u n="198" who="S0653">what do you mean that you found out? that you decided to use as a random word</u>
<u n="199" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0654">mummy can I go on my TDS?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0653">no you cannot play on your TDS</u>
<u n="202" who="S0652"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0654">why?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0653">in the end I did capitulate and she was allowed to play on it for a bit because the incessant moaning</u>
<u n="205" who="S0655">am I allowed to play on it?</u>
<u n="206" who="S0653">not at the moment</u>
<u n="207" who="S0654">what about charades?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0653">yes but at the moment <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is eating so you can come and sit down <pause dur="short"/> yes we are going to play charades</u>
<u n="209" who="S0652"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0653">we should have brought Twister really what is it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> come and sit down on your chair or we won't be playing charades</u>
<u n="212" who="S0652">I said hello little one she went hello <pause dur="short"/> big <pause dur="short"/> one <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0653"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you do look like Where's Wally <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in your PJs</u>
<u n="214" who="S0655">I'm hiding can you find me</u>
<u n="215" who="S0652">if you are American Where's Waldo</u>
<u n="216" who="S0653">is that the same thing as Where's Wally?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0652">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0653">is it?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0652">they call it Waldo instead</u>
<u n="220" who="S0653">oh</u>
<u n="221" who="S0655">that sounds like erm someone who owned <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0652">what ho Where's Waldo <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0653">good Star Wars knowledge</u>
<u n="224" who="S0652">here I'm gonna annoy yer</u>
<u n="225" who="S0653">I like these little pixie sockets</u>
<u n="226" who="S0652">no money no deal</u>
<u n="227" who="S0653">I'll just talk to myself shall I</u>
<u n="228" who="S0652">you like the little pixie sockets</u>
<u n="229" who="S0653">yeah the little baby sockets that</u>
<u n="230" who="S0652">have you taken all the plugs out and had a look?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0653">yeah they are really teeny weeny</u>
<u n="232" who="S0652">really tiny</u>
<u n="233" who="S0653">yes</u>
<u n="234" who="S0655">my name Noddy</u>
<u n="235" who="S0653">from the seventies I don't mean are the sockets in the seventies much smaller</u>
<u n="236" who="S0652">mm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0653">were they?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0655">I feel like I'm worry that if I have another main I'm going to blow up so can I please get down?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0654">there's a number of questions and you have to</u>
<u n="240" who="S0653">I suppose so and get charades ready</u>
<u n="241" who="S0655">okay I get</u>
<u n="242" who="S0653">no charades</u>
<u n="243" who="S0655"><unclear/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0653">yes</u>
<u n="245" who="S0654" trans="overlap">please can we have a game of charades we've got er cards <unclear/> and if someone gets the first one then you get two you need <unclear/> a number of things</u>
<u n="246" who="S0652">a number of things can you</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
