<text id="SP67">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:25:59</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Music, friends, gardening, weather</topics>
		<activity>ANON and ANON talking while eating dinner</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0115">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0037">are you laughing at?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0115">no just the music's funny isn't it?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0037">what is it? Is it Pendulum?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0115">Don't know <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="6" who="S0037">it sounds like that sort of thing? Ooh could you pass me the mustard? Thank you <pause dur="short"/> oh I need some more</u>
<u n="7" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah this is that's that's uh that's Oasis isn't it?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0037" trans="overlap">classic <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh I was reading something in the Guardian like that said that um Damon Albarn and um Noel Gallagher have buried their feud after like however many years it's been</u>
<u n="9" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well thought thought they'd already buried it <pause dur="short"/> I thought <pause dur="short"/> I thought you were gonna <trunc>s</trunc> I thought you were gonna say they were gonna record a song <pause dur="short"/> maybe they're gonna make a recording <trunc>s</trunc> together or something</u>
<u n="10" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no but <pause dur="short"/> did I tell you that the Beatles are gonna reform? Beetles Two Point Zero?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0115">yeah uh</u>
<u n="12" who="S0037">not the real Beatles obviously cos fifty percent are dead or whatever but</u>
<u n="13" who="S0115">right <pause dur="short"/> sean Lennon</u>
<u n="14" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no no Sean Lennon's not gonna be in it</u>
<u n="15" who="S0115">Bobby uh Harrison</u>
<u n="16" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like Pete Lennon or something <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0115">flake Harrison</u>
<u n="18" who="S0037">aha</u>
<u n="19" who="S0037">no Sean Lennon's too <pause dur="short"/> no no no <pause dur="short"/> maybe it is Sean Lennon <pause dur="short"/> um it's the <trunc>S</trunc> Zach Starkey who's the drummer <pause dur="short"/> he's too much of a good drummer to want to be in like such a sort of silly thing</u>
<u n="20" who="S0115" trans="overlap">we better find out <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="21" who="S0037">Cos he drums with like</u>
<u n="22" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah but the potential uh</u>
<u n="23" who="S0037">that my hair?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0115">the attention that he's gonna get is uh enormous cos I mean that's the world's most famous band isn't it?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0037">suppose yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0115">well</u>
<u n="27" who="S0037">and I know Gallagher would have something to say about that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0115">uhuh <pause dur="short"/> um who's the world's biggest band uh I don't know</u>
<u n="29" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="30" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> that's a good question</u>
<u n="31" who="S0037">I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> it depends how you measure it</u>
<u n="32" who="S0115">maybe U2</u>
<u n="33" who="S0037">ugh <pause dur="short"/> really don't like U2</u>
<u n="34" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> depends on like what part of the world doesn't it</u>
<u n="35" who="S0037">I was listening to a band that you probably wouldn't like but I probably <trunc>w</trunc> well I do like them um called the Cornshed Sisters <pause dur="short"/> have you heard of them?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0115">no</u>
<u n="37" who="S0037">they're a bit like you know the Unthanks that sort of <pause dur="short"/> we saw them at over the summer in the</u>
<u n="38" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well I I thought I liked that actually</u>
<u n="39" who="S0037">it's like northern sort of folk</u>
<u n="40" who="S0115">oh yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0037">girl folk I suppose you would call it</u>
<u n="42" who="S0037">you know like <pause dur="short"/> that kind of thing</u>
<u n="43" who="S0115" trans="overlap">does it have a distinctly different sound to man folk</u>
<u n="44" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well there's uhum excuse me <pause dur="short"/> no it's just girls singing instead of boys</u>
<u n="45" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0037">they're quite good</u>
<u n="47" who="S0115">the Unthanks okay</u>
<u n="48" who="S0037">so the Cornshed Sisters are like quite it's quite sort of bit Catherine Tickill-y a bit sort of uh</u>
<u n="49" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like what you'd expect I suppose innit? Is it like <trunc>Northum</trunc> Northumbrian? Is it Northumbrian folk?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no they're quite good <pause dur="short"/> found them recently <pause dur="short"/> that kind of thing <pause dur="short"/> but the one of the <trunc>p</trunc> girls in the Cowshed Sisters used to be in Kenickie <pause dur="short"/> there you go</u>
<u n="51" who="S0115">oh right <pause dur="short"/> it was uh <pause dur="short"/> I only knew one band by one song by them</u>
<u n="52" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0115">they weren't  they weren't  very big but I guess</u>
<u n="54" who="S0037" trans="overlap">not massive <pause dur="short"/> well in <anon type="place"/> they were</u>
<u n="55" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well they were very trendy <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0037">Lauren Laverne's done quite well for herself</u>
<u n="57" who="S0115">yeah um <pause dur="short"/> most famous person from the town</u>
<u n="58" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> surely not</u>
<u n="59" who="S0115"><unclear/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0037">what about um Kate Adie</u>
<u n="61" who="S0115">at the moment Kate Adie <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="62" who="S0037">or um <pause dur="short"/> one of the Hairy Bikers <pause dur="short"/> although he's from <anon type="place"/> so</u>
<u n="63" who="S0115">think it is her</u>
<u n="64" who="S0037">yeah probably is</u>
<u n="65" who="S0115">hm <pause dur="short"/> um yeah <trunc>apar</trunc> on the TV <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah so uh I guess <pause dur="short"/> I never  I never  heard anything else by Kenickie so I don't know what</u>
<u n="66" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure I must have</u>
<u n="67" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they sounded</u>
<u n="68" who="S0037">is that ham in is that um pork in the dinner? Bacon?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0115">there's some bacon in there yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh it's nice</u>
<u n="71" who="S0115">well <pause dur="short"/> I hoped so uh <pause dur="short"/> otherwise I've like you know um wasted my time haven't I? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0037">no it's really tasty <pause dur="short"/> it's the right sort of food for today like <trunc>i</trunc> sort of rainy and</u>
<u n="73" who="S0115" trans="overlap">have you given it giving it a good write-up? Oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> I like it</u>
<u n="74" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I am giving it a good write-up <pause dur="short"/> sort of rainy and cold and <pause dur="short"/> like when you've had a long day at work you're just like ahh <pause dur="short"/> it's nice sort of</u>
<u n="75" who="S0115">it reminds me of my old uh shepherd's pies I used to make but</u>
<u n="76" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0115">it's much healthier than them though <pause dur="short"/> cos it doesn't have loads of mince in it</u>
<u n="78" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="79" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="80" who="S0037">mince isn't very good for you but it's quite tasty</u>
<u n="81" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0037">but I'll have to try not to eat too much cos like when we go home at Christmas it's just like mince all the time</u>
<u n="83" who="S0115">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> well um yeah I think uh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did say you know we should um like suggest more or make make more ourselves</u>
<u n="84" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0115">rather than always getting just getting them to cook it</u>
<u n="86" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I suppose it's just because she makes like <pause dur="short"/> like she makes like big batches of things like <pause dur="short"/> like some of the things that she like that</u>
<u n="87" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah but but she said that we should uh we should do that yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I know <pause dur="short"/> I'm just saying like why like mince is <trunc>r</trunc> useful sort of it's easy to cook isn't it like? They're like big bowls of chilli or lasagne or that kinda thing</u>
<u n="89" who="S0115">well it's very rich isn't it?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0037">it is rich</u>
<u n="91" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but um you know that makes it sort of <pause dur="short"/> it's quite cheap as well</u>
<u n="92" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it is <pause dur="short"/> well I had some emails from</u>
<u n="93" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well I'm glad you like it anyway</u>
<u n="94" who="S0037">it's really nice <pause dur="short"/> I had some emails from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> today</u>
<u n="95" who="S0115">oh yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0037">um saying that we should go to <anon type="place"/> like for a reunion cos it's ten years since we left</u>
<u n="97" who="S0115">right</u>
<u n="98" who="S0037">so <pause dur="short"/> I said yes in principle <pause dur="short"/> obviously I need to <trunc>f</trunc> ask you and find out the dates and that</u>
<u n="99" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0037">but <pause dur="short"/> no should be good</u>
<u n="101" who="S0115">and he was saying like oh we should try and get away somewhere as well</u>
<u n="102" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0037">but</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="104" who="S0037">but he copied the email to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't reply <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like <pause dur="short"/> cos d'you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has started his new job?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0115">oh yeah at the bridge place?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0037">yeah and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like ooh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you're very quiet and I was like he's probably run off his feet <vocal desc="laugh"/> making cups of tea and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sent another email that just said and filing and I was like and photocopying so like when Tosh eventually got to his inbox he was like yes I have been busy not like you two just sending one-word emails to each other</u>
<u n="107" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0037">there was like twenty-five emails with just tasks <vocal desc="laugh"/> that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> should've been doing</u>
<u n="109" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0037">like flirting with the old ladies that was like one of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s suggestions</u>
<u n="111" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> what does he actually do?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> you'll have to ask him yourself uh don't really know</u>
<u n="113" who="S0115">Cos I didn't  I didn't  get the <pause dur="short"/> I'm not in on the I'm not in the email so</u>
<u n="114" who="S0037">aw</u>
<u n="115" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="116" who="S0037">um</u>
<u n="117" who="S0115">is this so that like and he's when is his? <trunc>D</trunc> did he say when his party is?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0037"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no mention of it <pause dur="short"/> I asked</u>
<u n="119" who="S0115">so he still hasn't said it yet?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I said how's how's things coming along at chez <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? And he just didn't reply so</u>
<u n="121" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well isn't? He's sort of moving isn't he so?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0037">no but I meant like with his new house</u>
<u n="123" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0037">but he didn't reply</u>
<u n="125" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> right <pause dur="short"/> now he's doing a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> he's uh he's doing a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thing too</u>
<u n="126" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I mean like yeah but <pause dur="short"/> like I I said something else in the email <pause dur="short"/> and at the end I said how's chez <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? and he just he he answered the rest of the email and ignored that bit so</u>
<u n="127" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yes <pause dur="short"/> ignored that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It's all gone wrong <pause dur="short"/> terribly wrong <pause dur="short"/> uh never mind uh</u>
<u n="128" who="S0037">I hope not</u>
<u n="129" who="S0115">uh yeah <anon type="place"/>'s a good place although I feel like it's quite far for a lot of people to travel</u>
<u n="130" who="S0037">I think it's just because</u>
<u n="131" who="S0115">I don't know how many people <trunc>u</trunc> of us are actually there</u>
<u n="132" who="S0037">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> chris was like who we gonna invite? and I was like urr and he was like well we sort of kinda have to invite everyone if it's like the ten year anniversary</u>
<u n="133" who="S0115" trans="overlap">anyway <pause dur="short"/> but I but like almost everybody's far away from there though aren't they?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="135" who="S0115">so it's it has a sort of logistical problem uh I think</u>
<u n="136" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but it's just the sort of fun of going somewhere I think that's part of the thing <pause dur="short"/> cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like oh we'll all go from London together and party train and</u>
<u n="137" who="S0115">I suppose so</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="138" who="S0037">so</u>
<u n="139" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="140" who="S0037">anyway</u>
<u n="141" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll uh <pause dur="short"/> get some more in a minute</u>
<u n="142" who="S0037">hmm?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0115">I'll have some more in a minute um</u>
<u n="144" who="S0037">it was really nice</u>
<u n="145" who="S0115">so I took so it was like uh made by partly by accident cos I made the sort of</u>
<u n="146" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0115">like the main  the main  meat and potato bit and mixed them together and realized it was only half full</u>
<u n="148" who="S0037">fish and potato did you not mean?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0115">meat and uh and fish and potato uh</u>
<u n="150" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0115">mixed them together and realized it only half filled the amount that I wanted</u>
<u n="152" who="S0037">aw</u>
<u n="153" who="S0115">I realized I'd you know not put enough potatoes or whatever</u>
<u n="154" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0115">uh I'd also forgotten the peas <pause dur="short"/> and I'd also forgotten to put the broccoli in but then I thought that'd go separate</u>
<u n="156" who="S0037">on the side yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0115">Cos that's what we normally do for shepherd's pie then <pause dur="short"/> so I then had to do another batch of potatoes and then had to the same again with them and then had to put a load of frozen peas in them and then stick it on and then uh put some cheese on top and then put it in the oven and then</u>
<u n="158" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's alright</u>
<u n="159" who="S0115">so it had uh has a pea layer and like a meat layer</u>
<u n="160" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no it was nice <pause dur="short"/> I like a pea</u>
<u n="161" who="S0115" trans="overlap">pea um leading to the cheesy peas experience at the top</u>
<u n="162" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'm hoping <pause dur="short"/> squeezy cheesy peas <pause dur="short"/> I'm hoping that me um me peas germinate like I look at them every morning before I go work like ahh aww like</u>
<u n="163" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah cos I should get some of those mung beans uh <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>u</trunc> we've got <trunc>u</trunc> any old pretty much any bean can uh sprout I think as long as  as long as  they're intact</u>
<u n="164" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> you'd be surprised</u>
<u n="165" who="S0115">well I I think it's the temperature partly yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0037">I know I wonder if I should bring them in</u>
<u n="167" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um and what I would maybe experiment with is just to get a little uh one of our little bowls and then you know a bit of water</u>
<u n="168" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and see if they <trunc>br</trunc> sprout?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you soak  you soak  them for a while then you empty and leave just a bit of water then you put the cling film on the top and you leave them there in in the warm and</u>
<u n="170" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0115">and once you've sprouted them I guess you're okay to</u>
<u n="172" who="S0037">plunk them in?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0115">you've got the roots and the <trunc>f</trunc> and the leaves coming out so you shouldn't</u>
<u n="174" who="S0037">they were really hardy last year they the peas they were just like I couldn't like they were grew so much</u>
<u n="175" who="S0115">yeah if you gimme gimme a few samples of I might be able to try</u>
<u n="176" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> there's loads <pause dur="short"/> they're in that box</u>
<u n="177" who="S0115">or I could just do <pause dur="short"/> so you can <trunc>s</trunc> maybe stick them in all together and <pause dur="short"/> stick all the seeds in together in a pile <pause dur="short"/> hope they sprout</u>
<u n="178" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no but then I'll not know what they are</u>
<u n="179" who="S0115">well I'll hopefully remember from the <trunc>s</trunc> the colour from the colour of the seed</u>
<u n="180" who="S0037" trans="overlap">some of them are tiny though</u>
<u n="181" who="S0115">alright yeah yeah well we'll we'll do them in do them separately then yeah get lots of like egg cups and like</u>
<u n="182" who="S0037">well they're in the little greenhouse now so hopefully that'll keep them a bit warmer</u>
<u n="183" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I think it's just too cold for <trunc>s</trunc> for sprouting <pause dur="short"/> uh it's it's not been very kind so far uh really the the year hasn't been <pause dur="short"/> yeah but they're inside</u>
<u n="184" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the tomatoes have sprouted though <pause dur="short"/> think I should bring the others in?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0115">the year hasn't been very hot at all <pause dur="short"/> well it depends on are we  are we  <trunc>s</trunc> are we gonna get warm weather again or what?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0037">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> it sort of went nice didn't it and everyone was like I had me flip-flops on and that</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah it was a little bit of <pause dur="short"/> there was a little uh</u>
<u n="188" who="S0037" trans="overlap">was that the summer? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0115">well yeah probably <pause dur="short"/> but there was a little bit of hotness going on</u>
<u n="190" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it was typical though isn't it? Like in the winter everyone's hoping it's gonna snow  hoping it's gonna snow  Then it snows everyone's whinging hoping it's gonna get warmer</u>
<u n="191" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right I don't I didn't want it to snow like uh <pause dur="short"/> not this time</u>
<u n="192" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and it's warm for two weeks everyone's got hoping it's gonna get cooler then it's cool just for the rest of the year</u>
<u n="193" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I didn't want it to snow um <pause dur="short"/> got the gas bill anyway and uh gas</u>
<u n="194" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh did we? How much was it?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0115">uh what I said before um I wasn't that not that pleased with that amount but uh <pause dur="short"/> it's it it was a bit it was for like a <trunc>th</trunc> the whole virtually the whole winter that we were here <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and we did have it cranked up like <pause dur="short"/> it's been really cold</u>
<u n="197" who="S0115">yeah I dunno what the <pause dur="short"/> I think we yeah I think we made some mistakes there with um</u>
<u n="198" who="S0037">but it's still not that bad compared to some people's</u>
<u n="199" who="S0115" trans="overlap">using um where we should've perhaps used the oven instead or if we used uh use it in in different methods</u>
<u n="200" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what how long was that for? I haven't heard this song for ages</u>
<u n="201" who="S0115">we should've perhaps come up with alternative methods to <pause dur="short"/> rather than relying on it cos like just it just was going and it wasn't really doing anything</u>
<u n="202" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> so how long was it for?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0115">three months and a few days so it's <trunc>th</trunc> it's thirty-five pounds a month</u>
<u n="204" who="S0037">that's not too bad though</u>
<u n="205" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but that <pause dur="short"/> we <pause dur="short"/> ideally you'd want a bill for twenty pounds a week but you get uh</u>
<u n="206" who="S0037">yeah but <pause dur="short"/> excuse me</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you get it gets balanced by the fact that the summer months are much less than twenty pounds they should hopefully be ten pounds a month so</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037">it was like <pause dur="short"/> it was last summer like <pause dur="short"/> well I mean even so far we only have it on for hot water now like we don't have any  don't have any</u>
<u n="209" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I mean I deliberately like sort of <pause dur="short"/> I could see it was quite low you know it was eighteen there nineteen there and nineteen here <pause dur="short"/> but I never put it on high and I don't  I don't  intend to either I think I'll I'lll always use alternative means</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037">once you  once you  make the meal</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115" trans="overlap">unless it's ridiculous I'd I'd use alternative means basically</u>
<u n="212" who="S0037">once you make the meal in the evening it's normally</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah cos I don't need the two back rooms you see uh</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115">when I  when I  if I'm sitting here I only use this in the kitchen so if I close that</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115">um things like you know the heat from the shower and stuff <trunc>keep</trunc> that warms the house up quite a lot uh</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's true</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115">they do and the sunlight in the front but not in the back cos there's no sun in the back but sunlight in the front will warm it up</u>
<u n="220" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115">like by a degree usually</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115">um so I yeah I'll just use that rather than <pause dur="short"/> but it was just  it was just  going and going and really wasn't doing anything it was quite annoying</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="225" who="S0115">um and if we'd have cranked it up then it would've cost even more so</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115">um but I think we've left it on maybe a few times that we shouldn't have but we had to</u>
<u n="228" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> I don't think that's too bad considering like</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0037">we were snowed in like d'you not remember and we had to like we had to force the door?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah it was uh that was a that was uh uh <pause dur="short"/> it seems like a long time ago but it <unclear/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it wasn't really <pause dur="short"/> it was this year wasn't it? It was after came back from <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115">uh yeah um <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure exactly when it was but <pause dur="short"/> cos we were worried about getting to uh uh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s wedding that um that it would be snowing wasn't really <pause dur="short"/> did it snow after that or?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah that's right <pause dur="short"/> it did yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it snowed a bit before but then everyone was going oh it's gonna snow muh muh muh like at the start of the year</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037">and her wedding was in the seventh wasn't it of January?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0037">and then <pause dur="short"/> but yeah then it didn't um it snowed after so <pause dur="short"/> have I got one of those teacakes left?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0115">I think we have one each but I'm not sure</u>
<u n="240" who="S0037">whooh <pause dur="short"/> I think so <pause dur="short"/> could go for one of them I think <pause dur="short"/> there was like a jam roly-poly at work today <pause dur="short"/> looked really tasty <pause dur="short"/> I didn't have it though</u>
<u n="241" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is that a Swiss roll?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0037">no like a jam sponge I suppose</u>
<u n="243" who="S0115">is that not what a Swiss roll? Oh just <pause dur="short"/> you mean just like just not rolled? Why's it called roly-poly?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0037">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> maybe it is rolled <pause dur="short"/> it was just looked like jam sponge to me</u>
<u n="245" who="S0115">so it was round <pause dur="short"/> like</u>
<u n="246" who="S0037">it was just like a slice of sponge with jam <pause dur="short"/> maybe on it and through it <pause dur="short"/> maybe the jam was <trunc>u</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> oh I don't know</u>
<u n="247" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Roly-poly</u>
<u n="248" who="S0037" trans="overlap">they always have like hot um</u>
<u n="249" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I guess you get the pole and you roll the pole over it and you know the they join the the rolling pin and then like</u>
<u n="250" who="S0037">oh maybe <pause dur="short"/> I dunno where it comes from <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="251" who="S0115" trans="overlap">guess they get the pole and roll the pole over it and then it gets thin and then you fold it over or something</u>
<u n="252" who="S0037">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> a roly-<trunc>po</trunc> roly-poly is a funny word</u>
<u n="253" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they <trunc>r</trunc> they roll the pastry actually rather than um <pause dur="short"/> rather than that but uh yeah so no I don't know who the biggest band is in the  in the  world uh</u>
<u n="254" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> people often say that when the without measuring uh cos in some country a place like China or</u>
<u n="256" who="S0037" trans="overlap">probably is the Beatles</u>
<u n="257" who="S0115">India or like like China they don't  they don't  really listen to as much rock as as we do in the West do they?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what about Lady Gaga? She's pretty giant</u>
<u n="259" who="S0115">yeah if you're <trunc>tal</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> are you talking in solo artists as well? Uh</u>
<u n="260" who="S0037">oh were we? Sorry <pause dur="short"/> excuse me <pause dur="short"/> are we were we talking rock bands?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0115">well yeah well I said bands so I just meant bands but if you're talking in <trunc>th</trunc> solo artists no I don't that either I don't know the answer to that either um <pause dur="short"/> but hopefully there's um</u>
<u n="262" who="S0037" trans="overlap">she's she's got the most followers on Twitter</u>
<u n="263" who="S0115">who?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0037">lady Gaga</u>
<u n="265" who="S0115">oh yeah well that's not really like <unclear/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I know it's not a measure of everyone in the world <pause dur="short"/> not everyone in the world's on Twitter</u>
<u n="267" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah yeah cos <pause dur="short"/> no they're not are they?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="269" who="S0115">has she? More than</u>
<u n="270" who="S0037">more than anyone yeah</u>
<u n="271" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I dunno who who else would it be you know who <trunc>d</trunc> who do people love I suppose?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0037">dunno</u>
<u n="273" who="S0115">it's like a religious thing isn't it you know like uh</u>
<u n="274" who="S0037">hey that plant's got really big that aloe it's like hanging over the edge of the pot <pause dur="short"/> I can't believe it</u>
<u n="275" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's still I don't  I don't  know if it's any bigger than it was like when it fell over that time <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know if it's any bigger than like</u>
<u n="276" who="S0037">I dunno I think it's looking good</u>
<u n="277" who="S0115">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's it's not bad though</u>
<u n="278" who="S0037">D'you think that tent's gonna be good then?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0115">um the picture looks good I dunno what what are the sizes of it? Supposed to be able to sleep four people?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0037">dunno <pause dur="short"/> shall I have a look? Yeah I got a four  a four  man tent because I thought</u>
<u n="281" who="S0115" trans="overlap">can can you genuinely fit four people in that?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no well that's the thing like <pause dur="short"/> a two man tent fits three and like a four</u>
<u n="283" who="S0115" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0037">sorry <pause dur="short"/> a three man tent fit is good for two and a four man tent's good for three <pause dur="short"/> so I thought me you and plenty of stuff <pause dur="short"/> cos it's a good one</u>
<u n="285" who="S0115" trans="overlap">really? Well why is it called that then?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0037">well it's like how much you could <trunc>a</trunc> how you could actually get in like if you  if you  wanted to like put four people in</u>
<u n="287" who="S0115">yeah alright so it's just  it's just  precisely</u>
<u n="288" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but they'd literally be sleeping like hang on like there like that see? Like four like very affectionate people <pause dur="short"/> who are very well acquainted</u>
<u n="289" who="S0115">well like a family in other words? Yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="290" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no but I think you <trunc>would</trunc> like there wouldn't be much room to like wiggle around <pause dur="short"/> oops</u>
<u n="291" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="292" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> I helpfully left that on the table <pause dur="short"/> so annoying at work</u>
<u n="293" who="S0115">that's it so they all sleep and and their legs are like pointing up to the  to the  front of the tent?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well I think that's probably the most typical</u>
<u n="295" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="296" who="S0037">but it's got two doors <pause dur="short"/> it's got like a front if you pass the little picture <pause dur="short"/> like that front piece like there <pause dur="short"/> that piece there that's a door and also that's a door there</u>
<u n="297" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="298" who="S0037">so</u>
<u n="299" who="S0115">hopefully it's got a good you know ability to to withstand rain then?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah that's the porch bit <pause dur="short"/> that's the porch bit</u>
<u n="301" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's not gonna just totally get soaked</u>
<u n="302" who="S0037">it had good reviews</u>
<u n="303" who="S0115">oh that's good</u>
<u n="304" who="S0037">um it's got a measure here two thousand droplets <pause dur="short"/> I dunno what that means</u>
<u n="305" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0037">um</u>
<u n="307" who="S0115">two thousand droplets</u>
<u n="308" who="S0037">oh it's in <pause dur="short"/> oh here we are here's the English</u>
<u n="309" who="S0115">before it leaks</u>
<u n="310" who="S0037">uh here's the features <pause dur="short"/> um quick pitching <pause dur="short"/> front storage area <pause dur="short"/> porch ground sheet attached to the bedroom <pause dur="short"/> ventilation to reduce condensation <pause dur="short"/> multiple door options <pause dur="short"/> large windows <pause dur="short"/> bright guy lines with glow in the dark runners for increased visibility <pause dur="short"/> there you go</u>
<u n="311" who="S0115">alright</u>
<u n="312" who="S0037">but I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what that <trunc>s</trunc> I know I understand what those symbols mean but I don't know what that one means</u>
<u n="313" who="S0115">uh let me have a look <pause dur="short"/> um you didn't know what the two thousand droplets?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0037">two thousand droplets</u>
<u n="315" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Two thousand candles uh</u>
<u n="316" who="S0037">that's still a good sketch that</u>
<u n="317" who="S0115">it's sort of got <pause dur="short"/> like there's something in the middle which is like <pause dur="short"/> is that? What's that going on in the middle? Is there? Is it just open?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0037" trans="overlap">is that the <trunc>s</trunc> dimensions of the bag?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0115">is it just open?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0037">there?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0115">yeah is it? Is that supposed to</u>
<u n="322" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's the door <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's the door</u>
<u n="323" who="S0115">that's the front door? I see right <pause dur="short"/> so that's normally obviously shut so <pause dur="short"/> no the fly of it though it doesn't seem to have a fly</u>
<u n="324" who="S0037">what d'you mean doesn't have a fly?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0115">everywhere</u>
<u n="326" who="S0037">yeah there's an inside tent and an outside sheet</u>
<u n="327" who="S0115">right is is it all definitely covered by its? I suppose it must be</u>
<u n="328" who="S0037">I think so</u>
<u n="329" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0037">I mean most tents are like that aren't they? Like inside bit outside bit</u>
<u n="331" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0037">see what it's <pause dur="short"/> like the good <trunc>th</trunc> one of the good things I thought was like the instructions are sewn into the bag <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah look contents <pause dur="short"/> carry case inner tent fly sheet guy lines pegs poles <pause dur="short"/> so yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0115">right so we'll have to assemble it then</u>
<u n="334" who="S0037">right now?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0115">well <pause dur="short"/> eventually you know uh</u>
<u n="336" who="S0037">maybe we could assemble it here <pause dur="short"/> d'you think we should? Think it's big enough? What's the?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> we'd need to be <trunc>some</trunc> probably probably in the room through there cos that's</u>
<u n="338" who="S0037">why?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0115">even more space than this</u>
<u n="340" who="S0037">I don't think so I think if we move the sofa and that</u>
<u n="341" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="342" who="S0037">obviously we wouldn't be able to peg it down to the carpet <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> so you think here's better than uh right so if I need to finish what i'm doing um</u>
<u n="344" who="S0037">you what?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0115">I need to finish what I'm doing on the computer so uh <pause dur="short"/> if I can do that then</u>
<u n="346" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0115">hopefully I'll be <pause dur="short"/> hopefully have some time to have some evening afterwards</u>
<u n="348" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and we can put our tent up</u>
<u n="349" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0037">and have like like when you're little and like you make a den? Did you ever do that?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0115">well it's good to have a tent in the house so I think it's good yeah <pause dur="short"/> cool</u>
<u n="352" who="S0037">did you do that? When you were little?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0115">no and I never had a tent and my family never went camping</u>
<u n="354" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no like <pause dur="short"/> no not have a tent</u>
<u n="355" who="S0115" trans="overlap">A den? No I didn't have any brothers and sisters</u>
<u n="356" who="S0037">ah well no but you didn't need to like I used to do it with me nana <pause dur="short"/> like used to put chairs up like get the two living room chairs and put a sheet over them and like</u>
<u n="357" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>u</trunc> maybe once or something but uh no never really had uh playful people who would make dens uh like in my family</u>
<u n="358" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you know like we had one of those um what was it called? Uh a dryer you know those airing rack things? We had one of those that had like three pieces and used to like put that on</u>
<u n="359" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it is good to have your own sort of cave isn't it I think?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0037">well we just used to do it in the summer holidays like it would keep <trunc>ge</trunc> keep us occupied</u>
<u n="361" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no I like that <pause dur="short"/> I would've  I would've  liked to have done it more</u>
<u n="362" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="363" who="S0115">but I never really did it so</u>
<u n="364" who="S0037">and I read it on the news today that um the National Trust have issued this like you know Bucket Lists?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0115">no <pause dur="short"/> book it lists?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0037" trans="overlap">bucket Lists like a hundred things to do before</u>
<u n="367" who="S0115" trans="overlap">book it lists?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0037">bucket buh buhcket?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><trunc>B</trunc> book it bucket lists</u>
<u n="370" who="S0037">aww <pause dur="short"/> Bucket list <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0115">bucket <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>boo</trunc></u>
<u n="372" who="S0037">anyway <pause dur="short"/> they'd be for</u>
<u n="373" who="S0115" trans="overlap">if you would say boookit if you were saying?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0037">I wouldn't say boookit <pause dur="short"/> that means something different</u>
<u n="375" who="S0115">no I mean but you wouldn've said that if it was?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0037">if it was what?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0115">boook <pause dur="short"/> if it was</u>
<u n="378" who="S0037">to book something?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0037">bucket <pause dur="short"/> boooket <pause dur="short"/> I dunno what I would've said</u>
<u n="381" who="S0115">Cos that's ambiguous isn't it cos? you know bucket as in book a ticket versus</u>
<u n="382" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think I would <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think I would probably say boook it but I think I would probably  I think I would probably  correct that <pause dur="short"/> transcriber's gonna have a nightmare with that one <pause dur="short"/> anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/> um</u>
<u n="383" who="S0115">keep it natural? Uh</u>
<u n="384" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> so yeah a Bucket List is like a list of things that um</u>
<u n="385" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0037">you should do before you die like a hundred films you should <trunc>sh</trunc> should see or a <trunc>f</trunc> the top five hundred places you should go <pause dur="short"/> top five hundred? The top fifty places you should go</u>
<u n="387" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="388" who="S0037">you know like a list of things to do before the certain thing happens <pause dur="short"/> ten things to do before you get married</u>
<u n="389" who="S0115">yeah yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> alright I think we need to <trunc>s</trunc> discuss this before cos I remember um accessing the part of my brain where I keep the things to do before you die like uh</u>
<u n="390" who="S0037" trans="overlap">your own list of things <pause dur="short"/> oh right</u>
<u n="391" who="S0115">you know like <trunc>sw</trunc> swimming with dolphins and stuff?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0037">oh yeah yeah we were talking about it before</u>
<u n="393" who="S0115">yeah I was saying like that yeah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0037">anyway <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="395" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I remember that that was that we were walking uh walking home or something um</u>
<u n="396" who="S0037">were we? Ah vague memories cos we're back from the pub?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> no I wouldn't perhaps wouldn't have remembered that but um</u>
<u n="398" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Aay <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> no so it was like um oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> so the National Trust have like made this Bucket List for the like something like <trunc>s</trunc> twenty</u>
<u n="399" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they should change the name of that list <pause dur="short"/> it's really annoying <pause dur="short"/> people would just like half the time discussing like whether they say boooket or bahket or and they wouldn't get round to you know actually booking anything</u>
<u n="400" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oi man <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> it's not about booking it <pause dur="short"/> it's about like a pail you know</u>
<u n="401" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0037">oh god you've misunderstood after all that time <pause dur="short"/> no not not book it</u>
<u n="403" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0037">like bucket like a  like a  bucket of sand</u>
<u n="405" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="406" who="S0037">ah god</u>
<u n="407" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0037">ah <vocal desc="laugh"/> you donkey <pause dur="short"/> so anyway <pause dur="short"/> aw I'm only joking</u>
<u n="409" who="S0115">hey</u>
<u n="410" who="S0037">so they <trunc>h</trunc> made this list of things to do before you're twelve and it's like catch a <trunc>s</trunc> <trunc>g</trunc> make a snail race make a mud pie fly a kite all this sort of thing to try and encourage people to sort of go outside</u>
<u n="411" who="S0115">right</u>
<u n="412" who="S0037">I dunno I can't even remember why I was telling you about that now <pause dur="short"/> the meaning's <vocal desc="laugh"/> got so lost in our confusions</u>
</body>
</text>
