<text id="SP7F">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:27:30</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-07-11</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0439 S0440</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>[unknown]</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Work, family, friends, social. </topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, Inquiring, Complaining, Anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0439">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern - Non-accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0440">
				<exactage>58</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich, Norfolk</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Norfork</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Thrapston (Northants)</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>26</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Examinations Manager in Secondary School</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0440">did you get that thing from did you get any reply form <trunc>e</trunc> from us?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0439">what reply from you?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0440">well I'll sent an email through to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so</u>
<u n="4" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh did you?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0440" trans="overlap">saying are you interested in this?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no I didn't get from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0440" trans="overlap">oh fuck off yeah okay</u>
<u n="8" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah erm but erm yeah so last night <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got herself in this predicament basically she she has like a crush on this guy called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has a girlfriend and it's a long-term girlfriend and they've bought a house together and it's all serious and like I kind of joked with her I was like oh you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> things don't last but erm in this case I'm pretty sure that they're solid <vocal desc="laugh"/> and erm so yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and we when we all went to the <anon type="place"/> last night and saw the fireworks and we went for a walk round cos it had they had like erm a stage and they had a funfair and they had loads of fun like really cool stuff and then we bumped into <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and and like another group of friends?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0440">who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s this guy that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has this crush on</u>
<u n="11" who="S0440" trans="overlap">on yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0439" trans="overlap">with the one with the girlfriend erm and so and I was like er I was talking to them and then I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm gonna go back to erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and people now and she's like oh erm I'll I'll be there in a minute she did not come back in a minute <vocal desc="laugh"/> and she's been like the like kind of the rest of the evening like talking to him and it's kind a part of me just like well <pause dur="short"/> it's fine because she's not actually doing anything bad like she's not trying to like seduce him</u>
<u n="13" who="S0440" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="14" who="S0439" trans="overlap">or anything but then a part of me is also like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what are you doing? you know like he has a girlfriend what's the point?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="16" who="S0439">so <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> she's <pause dur="short"/> got herself in a bad well not a bad situation but just in a <pause dur="short"/> situation</u>
<u n="17" who="S0440">so she didn't come back to you all night?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0439">she did she she came back when we well she came back for a bit</u>
<u n="19" who="S0440"><vocal desc="yawn"/> uhu</u>
<u n="20" who="S0439">and then we went to the <anon type="place"/> and she went to <anon type="place"/> or something like that and then she met us back back in the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0440" trans="overlap">what's <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0439">it's another bar I don't know I I don't know why they went there</u>
<u n="23" who="S0440">who went there? her and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0439">yeah her and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went there and then they came and met us in the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0440">who were you? you and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0439">er no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was on a gay night out</u>
<u n="27" who="S0440">oh</u>
<u n="28" who="S0439">she</u>
<u n="29" who="S0440" trans="overlap">is she gay?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0440">oh</u>
<u n="32" who="S0439">I told you this</u>
<u n="33" who="S0440">oh I didn't know</u>
<u n="34" who="S0439">erm yeah so she has straight nights out and gay nights out <vocal desc="laugh"/> and a hen night on Friday</u>
<u n="35" who="S0440" trans="overlap">oh so who did you who did you</u>
<u n="36" who="S0439">erm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0440" trans="overlap">go with?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0439">I went with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> who else was there? <pause dur="short"/> some other people</u>
<u n="39" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0439">it was good it was fun erm and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> rocked up at about one <pause dur="short"/> so then she was like I I can't do her French accent but she was like I like him so much I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> no he has a girlfriend <pause dur="short"/> but oh well <pause dur="short"/> we erm we went punting last weekend</u>
<u n="41" who="S0440">oh right</u>
<u n="42" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and erm she she erm basically we just go where <trunc>th</trunc> all the fit men are punters <vocal desc="laugh"/> because they obviously like spend all their time in the sun and they like er er you probably do need quite a lot of strength to do</u>
<u n="43" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0439" trans="overlap">punting all day so she was just like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have a look at him and him over there</u>
<u n="45" who="S0440"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0439">and him I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> calm down <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0440"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0439">it was like she was like I wonder how much a tour would be? and I was like I don't know I I think well as you know about maybe twenty twenty-five pounds er an hour to have like a tour?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0440" trans="overlap">it's something like that yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0439">she goes</u>
<u n="51" who="S0440" trans="overlap">it used to it fifteen or fifteen or twenty something like</u>
<u n="52" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I I don't know I've never been on like it's it was</u>
<u n="53" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yes we have we went with erm that</u>
<u n="54" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I didn't go and</u>
<u n="55" who="S0440" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="56" who="S0439" trans="overlap">erm we did we did punting for an hour just as a group and that cost us sixteen pound or something like that so I think with a tour on top it would be a bit more but she was trying to work out whether she whether it was worth investing in a tour just so she could like look at a hot punter all day <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think that's called erm perving <vocal desc="laugh"/> and she was like oh I'm not touching <vocal desc="laugh"/> but <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> she was alright she'll get there <pause dur="short"/> one day</u>
<u n="57" who="S0440">gotta get this air con fixed quickly</u>
<u n="58" who="S0439">yeah it's really hot in here it's really humid today like it's not</u>
<u n="59" who="S0440" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0439" trans="overlap">sunny</u>
<u n="61" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's just humid <pause dur="short"/> whereas <trunc>yes</trunc> it was amazing yesterday it was really nice yesterday the weather <pause dur="short"/> we've been erm <trunc>si</trunc> like at lunchtime there's a big erm cricket pitch outside so we go</u>
<u n="63" who="S0440" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and sit in the sun and sunbathe there that's really cool <pause dur="short"/> I've been trying to get a tan er I'm getting a little bit</u>
<u n="65" who="S0440">yeah you are</u>
<u n="66" who="S0439">it is it is <trunc>slo</trunc> oh</u>
<u n="67" who="S0440">what?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0439">you <pause dur="short"/> wafting around in the middle of the road erm yeah no it's erm I'm getting a little of a tan a little bit of burn but it's not like burn burn it's just a bit rosy</u>
<u n="69" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I've got two bottles of aloe vera at home if you want</u>
<u n="70" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah I probably should</u>
<u n="71" who="S0440" trans="overlap">to take one with you</u>
<u n="72" who="S0439" trans="overlap">actually <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> it's been really good these last few weeks <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0440">I didn't go to Hydro Hiit this Thursday</u>
<u n="74" who="S0439">oh did you not?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0440" trans="overlap">because I was cos I was bottling cherries but</u>
<u n="76" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="77" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I went to Aqua Fit on Monday</u>
<u n="78" who="S0439">I thought you did cos I think I tried to ring you and you weren't in</u>
<u n="79" who="S0440" trans="overlap">well I go to Aqua Fit on Monday and</u>
<u n="80" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0440">and I'm going to Hydro Hiit on Thursday</u>
<u n="82" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="83" who="S0440">yeah I quite like the Hydro Hiit</u>
<u n="84" who="S0439">well I think yeah if you</u>
<u n="85" who="S0440" trans="overlap">what does Hiit stand for?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0439">high <trunc>inte</trunc> er high intensity interval training or high interval <trunc>inten</trunc> no it must be high intensity interval training <pause dur="short"/> it's good apparently it's better for you than like long slogs of cardio</u>
<u n="87" who="S0440">it is it's erm it's he cos he what he does is he does he counts you down on the clock? he'll</u>
<u n="88" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0440" trans="overlap">he'll do two minutes of this and then you'll do two minutes of that then you'll do two minutes of that and then you'll have a minute's rest</u>
<u n="90" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0440" trans="overlap">and then you'll have two minutes of this and two minutes of that and two minutes of that and then a minute's rest</u>
<u n="92" who="S0439">oh okay</u>
<u n="93" who="S0440">and he counts you down on the clock it's quite good you'll have to come one when you come to erm when you come you'll have to come</u>
<u n="94" who="S0439">mum why am I ever gonna go to erm yeah <trunc>c</trunc> erm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0440">on the Thursday night</u>
<u n="96" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah why why am I ever gonna go to Hydro Hiit? I don't need to go to Hydro Hiit</u>
<u n="97" who="S0440">I know you don't need to but it's fun I need a partner</u>
<u n="98" who="S0439">do you?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0439">why don't you get dad to go with you?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0440">oh he won't go</u>
<u n="102" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0440">he's a right bastard</u>
<u n="104" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he won't go with you</u>
<u n="105" who="S0440">no <pause dur="short"/> anything that</u>
<u n="106" who="S0439" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="107" who="S0440">you know anything that I think is good he deliberately says isn't</u>
<u n="108" who="S0439">I know I dunno what's wrong with him this morning he was mega</u>
<u n="109" who="S0440" trans="overlap">oh he's been a</u>
<u n="110" who="S0439" trans="overlap">stressing what the hell</u>
<u n="111" who="S0440" trans="overlap">oh he's</u>
<u n="112" who="S0439" trans="overlap">is wrong with him?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0440">I don't know he's been a right</u>
<u n="114" who="S0439" trans="overlap">he's like he's like I'm not angry it's like well you are dad there's clearly something wrong</u>
<u n="115" who="S0440">yeah he's he's been like that for a while now</u>
<u n="116" who="S0439" trans="overlap">grumpy bastard <pause dur="short"/> yeah and he looked a lot skinnier</u>
<u n="117" who="S0440">he yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I mean I've seen him only a few weeks ago and he seems</u>
<u n="119" who="S0440" trans="overlap">he <trunc>li</trunc> he's getting he yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0439">is he going back to his weird obsessiveness about food again?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0440">no no he's just being stupid with the <unclear>Mac</unclear> cycling he's doing</u>
<u n="122" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="123" who="S0440">he's doing four five hundred miles a week</u>
<u n="124" who="S0439">shit</u>
<u n="125" who="S0440">I know</u>
<u n="126" who="S0439">that's a hell of a lot of cycling</u>
<u n="127" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I know he's doing doing it in hundred mile bursts at the weekend and</u>
<u n="128" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well he's not I thought he's only he's <trunc>ev</trunc> he's never done a hundred miles yet has he?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah he did last weekend he did it during the</u>
<u n="130" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh did he?</u>
<u n="131" who="S0440" trans="overlap">at <anon type="place"/> he goes to the gym twice and yeah he's getting a bit obsessive about the gym again you know</u>
<u n="132" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0440">I don't</u>
<u n="134" who="S0439">well to be fair though for a sixty like for a nearly sixty-year-old it's</u>
<u n="135" who="S0440" trans="overlap">is <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0439" trans="overlap">good that he's still</u>
<u n="137" who="S0440">is that oh yeah I think it is</u>
<u n="138" who="S0439">at least he's still</u>
<u n="139" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0439">you know like</u>
<u n="141" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0439">doing it and keeping fit</u>
<u n="143" who="S0440">I know but there's a limit to getting thin and getting thin isn't there?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0439">yeah yeah he definitely looked a bit skinny</u>
<u n="145" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0439">oh god yesterday we saw this woman and she was er <vocal desc="laugh"/> like we went to <anon type="place"/> and there were tennis courts</u>
<u n="147" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0439">and she was I wouldn't say she was old she just didn't age well if that makes sense</u>
<u n="149" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0439" trans="overlap">like she must have been in maybe her late thirties or early forties</u>
<u n="151" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0439" trans="overlap">but she'd aged badly so she looked quite old and she was wearing this she was quite <trunc>ski</trunc> well she was really skinny she was wearing this little blue tennis skirt but erm she was wearing not very suitable underwear underneath so they <trunc>ke</trunc></u>
<u n="153" who="S0440" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0439" trans="overlap">so the skirt was really short</u>
<u n="155" who="S0440">uhu</u>
<u n="156" who="S0439">and you just saw her bum cheeks hanging out</u>
<u n="157" who="S0440">oh</u>
<u n="158" who="S0439">and like she clearly did not squat or do anything they were like <trunc>rea</trunc> it just looked horrible you know like two saggy weird bum cheeks hanging out and it was just like <pause dur="short"/> woman what are you doing?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0440">you have to squat at Hydro Hiit</u>
<u n="160" who="S0439">do you?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0439">how do you squat in water?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0440">with difficulty</u>
<u n="164" who="S0439">I was gonna say I can imagine <pause dur="short"/> cos yeah it would be weird to squat in <trunc>wa</trunc> I've never tried it <pause dur="short"/> maybe I'll have to give it a go I don't really like swimming very much cos it just</u>
<u n="165" who="S0440" trans="overlap">we don't do any swimming</u>
<u n="166" who="S0439">yeah I know I know I mean I</u>
<u n="167" who="S0440" trans="overlap">there's absolutely no bloody swimming at all</u>
<u n="168" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I just don't like the erm I don't like the chlorine in my hair</u>
<u n="169" who="S0440">well I this is why I use a Philip Kingsley swim cap</u>
<u n="170" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0440">and I don't get any chlorine in there cos it seals it</u>
<u n="172" who="S0439">every time I go in see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's always like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do you erm do you erm go swimming a lot because your hair is really shiny? I'm like and he asks every single time it's like no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I do not go swimming</u>
<u n="173" who="S0440">well I er he said there's a Boots product or a</u>
<u n="174" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0440">or Philip Kingsley I said I use the Philip Kingsley he said it's very expensive though isn't it? and I said yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0439">Philip Kingsley is expensive</u>
<u n="177" who="S0440" trans="overlap">and it's</u>
<u n="178" who="S0439" trans="overlap">in general</u>
<u n="179" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah but he said that the erm Boots one is just as good so I thought well I'll use my Philip Kingsley up and then</u>
<u n="180" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0440" trans="overlap">probably go on to Boots but there's a Boots swimming gym shampoo</u>
<u n="182" who="S0439">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0440" trans="overlap">a body wash</u>
<u n="184" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="185" who="S0440">which I use afterwards as well</u>
<u n="186" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0440" trans="overlap">and that gets rid of all the chlorine off your body as well as your hair</u>
<u n="188" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="189" who="S0440">washes it out neutralises it anyway</u>
<u n="190" who="S0439">yeah that's cool</u>
<u n="191" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0439">I erm we <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yesterday made the worst male comment we we walked past this unisex hairdresser and I was like oh god I never understand unisex hairdressers like it looked like this little barber shop and it said unisex he was like it's like why? would you not go there? I was like no he er women you can't just go to a barber who pretends to be a hairdresser you have to go to a hairdresser if you're a woman <pause dur="short"/> men are just men are always fathomed by the fact that women spend hours in</u>
<u n="193" who="S0440" trans="overlap">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <trunc>uni</trunc> you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s unisex</u>
<u n="194" who="S0439">yeah but he's more of a hairdresser <trunc>tha</trunc></u>
<u n="195" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0439">like he they do men but he's you know he specialises</u>
<u n="197" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0439">in</u>
<u n="199" who="S0440">women</u>
<u n="200" who="S0439">women yeah whereas this one looked like an old man shop or</u>
<u n="201" who="S0440" trans="overlap">well I had well it</u>
<u n="202" who="S0439">it looks a bit bobby mum</u>
<u n="203" who="S0440">yeah it's supposed to be a bobby but it's erm it looks lovely when I get it</u>
<u n="204" who="S0439">oh okay yeah well it's nice</u>
<u n="205" who="S0440">I just didn't want bit thick on top</u>
<u n="206" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0440" trans="overlap">but bobby at the you know cut right short</u>
<u n="208" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I thought you were gonna have it dyed</u>
<u n="209" who="S0440">no he said don't have it dyed I said why not? he says people are paying thousands to have hair your colour at the moment</u>
<u n="210" who="S0439">really? why?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0440">grey is the new in thing</u>
<u n="212" who="S0439">oh god</u>
<u n="213" who="S0440">salt and pepper grey is the new in thing <pause dur="short"/> he said George Clooney has got a lot to answer for</u>
<u n="214" who="S0439">yeah but George Clooney is a silver fox</u>
<u n="215" who="S0440">I know I know I mm I don't know if I'm going the right way now</u>
<u n="216" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I I've got no help I have no idea where we are</u>
<u n="217" who="S0440">oh I'll have to put it in here I'm looking for <anon type="place"/> okay? I don't wanna go <anon type="place"/> I wanna go this</u>
<u n="218" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0440" trans="overlap">this is no this is the way I wanna go that</u>
<u n="220" who="S0439">that made no sense</u>
<u n="221" who="S0440" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0439">okay <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> says you're in trend then</u>
<u n="223" who="S0440">he says yeah he says</u>
<u n="224" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/> to defy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0440">yeah he said to me he says I'm not trying to erm talk you out of it or anything he says but he says at the moment</u>
<u n="226" who="S0439">I've got to go and see him soon</u>
<u n="227" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0439">my hair is a bit shitty at the bottom <pause dur="long"/> what a nice horse <pause dur="short"/> speckly oh no maybe it's just dirty was it speckly or dirty? I couldn't tell</u>
<u n="229" who="S0440">don't know oh <pause dur="short"/> we nearly ended in the oh god two more</u>
<u n="230" who="S0439">more horses this is what happens when you live in the countryside</u>
<u n="231" who="S0440">oh</u>
<u n="232" who="S0439">combine harvester <pause dur="short"/> are they allowed to do that?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0440">they shouldn't do no</u>
<u n="234" who="S0439">doesn't look like they're taking any notice of the fact that there's a car behind you <pause dur="short"/> oh no now they are <pause dur="short"/> oh look what the the horses have like weird things round their ankles like plastic shields <pause dur="short"/> how strange <pause dur="short"/> I wonder what it's to protect</u>
<u n="235" who="S0440">er the fetlocks</u>
<u n="236" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="237" who="S0440">in case they walk across something er bumpy</u>
<u n="238" who="S0439">oh I see yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0440" trans="overlap">that's one of the most erm <pause dur="short"/> er it's what do you call it? parts of a horse very <pause dur="short"/> mm fragile</u>
<u n="240" who="S0439">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> I'll take your word for it <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> oh my god <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0440">oh my god what?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0439"><vocal desc="yawn"/> this week at work has been it's been alright it's been really really hectic and this <trunc>ma</trunc> there's this man at work called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he's a senior project coordinator and he is utter bollocks everybody thinks that everybody knows it but because he's like you know it's like grandad diploma because</u>
<u n="243" who="S0440" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="244" who="S0439" trans="overlap">he's been there for so long</u>
<u n="245" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="246" who="S0439">you can't do anything</u>
<u n="247" who="S0440">uhu</u>
<u n="248" who="S0439" trans="overlap">but he's just crap and he kind of buggered up one of my projects not buggered it like I it's fine but <pause dur="short"/> he just he's he's gone er massively over-budget on it</u>
<u n="249" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0439">he erm <pause dur="short"/> he like the schedule is now is wrong</u>
<u n="251" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="252" who="S0439">and he made a mistake and then I told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> not like in a horrible way she just asked how</u>
<u n="253" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0439" trans="overlap">my week was going and I was like well I had this er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> left my proofs in his inbox for three weeks so we're slightly behind schedule but it's okay we're getting back on track and stuff and she actually had a word with him about it</u>
<u n="255" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="256" who="S0439">and then apparently he told her a different story</u>
<u n="257" who="S0440">oh</u>
<u n="258" who="S0439">and I was like there is no other <trunc>stor</trunc> I'm not entirely sure what other story you're talking about</u>
<u n="259" who="S0440">so she came back to you and said</u>
<u n="260" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no no no</u>
<u n="261" who="S0440" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="262" who="S0439">I er had a chat with her again this week cos I want to take this product to four a a fourth round of proofs</u>
<u n="263" who="S0440">uhu</u>
<u n="264" who="S0439">and it that's not normally necessary but in this case it really is because erm <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="266" who="S0439">have given us loads and loads of changes</u>
<u n="267" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0439">and I want them checked because there was something that I've got massive like well over three hundred changes in this set of proofs and you</u>
<u n="269" who="S0440" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="270" who="S0439" trans="overlap">shouldn't have that many changes</u>
<u n="271" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0439" trans="overlap">in a third set of proofs so</u>
<u n="273" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0439">erm so I had to I had to chat to her anyway and I was just like well we're slightly behind schedule and she goes yeah I spoke to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about that and he came back to me with a different story so I'm just gonna leave it and I was like yeah that's fine don't worry like I'm not I didn't want to get him in trouble or anything <pause dur="short"/> but er</u>
<u n="275" who="S0440" trans="overlap">oh <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0439">are you lost again?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0439">it was the <anon type="place"/> this weekend</u>
<u n="279" who="S0440">yeah I know it always is</u>
<u n="280" who="S0439" trans="overlap">or last weekend did you go?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0440">erm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0439">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh you're lost aren't you? <pause dur="short"/> do you want me to have a look on my phone?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0440">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="284" who="S0439">you alright?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0440">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> we'll have to <pause dur="short"/> just don't press it too hard it's a satnav not a <pause dur="short"/> I dunno can't think of an analogy <pause dur="long"/> calculating your route well we're not very far away at all</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav"/>
<u n="287" who="S0439">you alright? I thought your car had broken again</u>
<u n="288" who="S0440">no you have to</u>
<u n="289" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="290" who="S0440">you can only start it in neutral gear</u>
<u n="291" who="S0439">oh I see that's why but you know that's good because I hate it when you leave my car in <trunc>d</trunc> gear it pisses me right off I'm like mum fuck off <pause dur="short"/> I dunno why you do it <pause dur="short"/> have we erm has anything er have we heard anything from the wicked we <trunc>s</trunc> er wicked witch of the east?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0440">no apart from the fact that when <trunc>sh</trunc> or last week when she was at dad's when I was at dad's he said to me he said do you need a new car? I said er not at the moment he says well if you do don't take any erm credit out borrow off me</u>
<u n="293" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="294" who="S0440" trans="overlap">he said and if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doesn't like it tough <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="295" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0440">thanks dad and then he said erm that he'd er she'd he'd had to call her in the morning cos he wanted <trunc>mo</trunc> some money</u>
<u n="297" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0440">she allows him two hundred pounds spending money a a month</u>
<u n="299" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no you mum this has to be sorted</u>
<u n="300" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I know it must</u>
<u n="301" who="S0439">it's bollocks</u>
<u n="302" who="S0440" trans="overlap">and he said he said I called her up I said er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are coming and I need more he says because when you come he says I I like to have a hundred pounds</u>
<u n="303" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah of course</u>
<u n="304" who="S0440" trans="overlap">in like a</u>
<u n="305" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0440">and I said well you don't need to spend a hundred pounds on us he says well you spend a hundred pounds coming up to see me or</u>
<u n="307" who="S0439">and another horse good god they're all out today aren't they?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0440">yeah so anyway I said</u>
<u n="309" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0440" trans="overlap"><trunc>t</trunc> so cos we took him out for dinner last week and</u>
<u n="311" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0440">I mean the dinner was fifty quid so having spent eighty quid the night before and fifty quid here then he paid for the boat which was eighteen for the three of us</u>
<u n="313" who="S0439">that's not bad</u>
<u n="314" who="S0440">that's not bad it was six it was an hour and a bit on the boat going up and down the river in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0440">learning about <anon type="place"/> and you know and basically it was it it was nice you know it was it was really nice so anyway erm he then came we then came back and he said here's another thirty pounds I said what's that for? and he says oh that's for your petrol</u>
<u n="317" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="318" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I said dad don't be stupid he said no take it he said</u>
<u n="319" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="320" who="S0440" trans="overlap">on principle so I said well I am but I said I'm not taking it every single time I come up and</u>
<u n="321" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="322" who="S0440" trans="overlap">see you</u>
<u n="323" who="S0439" trans="overlap">cos you've been coming up to see him for years why suddenly now</u>
<u n="324" who="S0440" trans="overlap">that's right</u>
<u n="325" who="S0439">is it because <trunc>c</trunc> he thinks like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is</u>
<u n="326" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah I think</u>
<u n="327" who="S0439" trans="overlap">he's trying to make it even or something?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0440">yeah I think I think there's a bit of <unclear/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0439" trans="overlap">did he ever talk to her about the eight grand?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0440">no but that's gonna come up when we erm sort the the</u>
<u n="331" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah you need to sort it you can't</u>
<u n="332" who="S0440" trans="overlap">no that's <trunc>goi</trunc> yeah he's gonna he's gonna see the he's gonna change his will because he wants to leave you lot five thousand pounds each</u>
<u n="333" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah I know you said</u>
<u n="334" who="S0440" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> won't let him because it means there'll be no no money left for her</u>
<u n="335" who="S0439">what? she's such a bitch it's his money <pause dur="short"/> she can't she has no influence over his will</u>
<u n="336" who="S0440">I know she doesn't</u>
<u n="337" who="S0439">if if he wants to write a will where he leaves all his money to charity she can do</u>
<u n="338" who="S0440">she can do nothing about it</u>
<u n="339" who="S0439" trans="overlap">nothing about it anyway so he wants to change it <trunc>th</trunc> there'll be twenty thousand left full stop okay?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0440">erm he wants to change it and my view is what he should change it to is that you know you lot get a minimum of I thought <anon type="place"/> was that way <pause dur="short"/> oh god oh well it's taking me anyway isn't it? so</u>
<u n="342" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0440">yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> you lot get a minimum of <pause dur="short"/> four thousand</u>
<u n="344" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0440" trans="overlap">pounds each and if there's anything left at the end of it yeah whatever but he wants to leave a thousand pound to the witnesses as well</u>
<u n="346" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah of course yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0440" trans="overlap">but there isn't gonna</u>
<u n="348" who="S0439" trans="overlap">he did say that</u>
<u n="349" who="S0440">yeah and he wants to leave a thousand pound to Alzheimer's now that'll take him to his twenty-three grand</u>
<u n="350" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0440">the what what he had left that means there's no money to pay for funerals or whatever <pause dur="short"/> now my view is it doesn't matter whether there's no money to pay for funerals because bollocks me he's</u>
<u n="352" who="S0439">oh <trunc>go</trunc> mum</u>
<u n="353" who="S0440" trans="overlap">oh god he's <trunc>bollo</trunc> you know he's done enough hasn't he? you know that's what I view he's done enough</u>
<u n="354" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0440">erm throughout his life that to pay for a funeral he's only wants he only wants the cheapest coffin</u>
<u n="356" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0440">he's gonna be cremated so he doesn't want an expensive coffin</u>
<u n="358" who="S0439">whack him in a cardboard box</u>
<u n="359" who="S0440">well that's right you know that's the new that's the new thing</u>
<u n="360" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0440">is the cardboard <pause dur="short"/> the cardboard coffin <pause dur="short"/> and my view is that you don't want you know all we want is a car to take him to the funeral we don't need cars for us</u>
<u n="362" who="S0439">no oh god</u>
<u n="363" who="S0440" trans="overlap">you know</u>
<u n="364" who="S0439" trans="overlap">not at all</u>
<u n="365" who="S0440" trans="overlap">that'll do <pause dur="short"/> so my my view is what we should do is just let him do what he wants to but we</u>
<u n="366" who="S0439" trans="overlap">how much does he he has like a hundred thousand</u>
<u n="367" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0439" trans="overlap">at the moment or something?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0440" trans="overlap">but what</u>
<u n="370" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh he's <trunc>g</trunc> yeah he's in the home isn't he?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0440" trans="overlap">he's got that now he's yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0440">so what I my view is is when we come to reading the will I they'll say is there any other any other things left? and I'll say yes there's ten thousand pounds which was paid into <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s account a little while ago which hasn't yet been declared and she'll go what? and I'll say yeah you know the the ISA on the ISA that was paid into your account</u>
<u n="374" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you need proof though you need proof of that</u>
<u n="375" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I've got proof of it</u>
<u n="376" who="S0439">good</u>
<u n="377" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I've got proof of it</u>
<u n="378" who="S0439" trans="overlap">as long as you have</u>
<u n="379" who="S0440" trans="overlap">cos she's got she's got the payment into her account hasn't she?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0439">yeah but er no but as long no but you need that proof cos she can just destroy that</u>
<u n="381" who="S0440"><trunc>sh</trunc>she can't destroy it because it's a bank transaction</u>
<u n="382" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="383" who="S0440">and she can't destroy that bank transaction so</u>
<u n="384" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well as long as you get</u>
<u n="385" who="S0440" trans="overlap">and I will just turn around and say you know</u>
<u n="386" who="S0439" trans="overlap">technically she'd have to prove that you she didn't have it didn't she?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0440">yeah she'd have to prove she didn't have it</u>
<u n="388" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0440">but my view my view is that what she should do is erm I'll just say well I'll take four-and-a-half thousand pounds extra onto the <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="390" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><trunc>s</trunc>so has got</u>
<u n="391" who="S0440">so <unclear>if</unclear> there's no money left what could be</u>
<u n="392" who="S0439" trans="overlap">does grandad not have his bank card then? I thought</u>
<u n="393" who="S0440" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="394" who="S0439">she threw it at him</u>
<u n="395" who="S0440" trans="overlap">she gives now she gives it to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> now she he he she's got it back</u>
<u n="396" who="S0439">how did she get it back?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0440">I don't know but anyway she's got it back and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has it when he <trunc>ge</trunc> when they go on holiday</u>
<u n="398" who="S0439" trans="overlap">this this situation is bollocks it's</u>
<u n="399" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I know it is and I</u>
<u n="400" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's he but he's</u>
<u n="401" who="S0440" trans="overlap">but she brought him up some more money <trunc>ye</trunc> last weekend erm <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="402" who="S0439" trans="overlap">she's such a skank</u>
<u n="403" who="S0440">I</u>
<u n="404" who="S0439">uh</u>
<u n="405" who="S0440">I know she is I I absolutely loathe her I really do</u>
<u n="406" who="S0439" trans="overlap">she's such a <trunc>horr</trunc> it's just about money it's like he's your dad</u>
<u n="407" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0439" trans="overlap">why are you so?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0440">yeah why not?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0439">she treats it she just wants his money and it's so</u>
<u n="411" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="412" who="S0439">sad</u>
<u n="413" who="S0440">I know I know I know</u>
<u n="414" who="S0439" trans="overlap">cos don't get me wrong I do understand that he <trunc>ha</trunc> he can be a grumpy like he can be a grumpy old man sometimes</u>
<u n="415" who="S0440" trans="overlap">he can be a grumpy old fucker but</u>
<u n="416" who="S0439" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="417" who="S0440" trans="overlap">but I mean like last week he was quite happy for me to go</u>
<u n="418" who="S0439">yeah cos</u>
<u n="419" who="S0440" trans="overlap">he didn't want me</u>
<u n="420" who="S0439" trans="overlap">wanted to watch his</u>
<u n="421" who="S0440" trans="overlap">he wanted to watch his tennis</u>
<u n="422" who="S0439" trans="overlap">tennis <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0440">and they actually said to me cor he likes his tennis doesn't he?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0439">he loves his sport in general but then</u>
<u n="425" who="S0440" trans="overlap">and I said yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0439">he's ninety-two years old</u>
<u n="427" who="S0440" trans="overlap">that's right</u>
<u n="428" who="S0439">for Christ's sake</u>
<u n="429" who="S0440">I know I know</u>
<u n="430" who="S0439" trans="overlap">you know like</u>
<u n="431" who="S0440">just leave him you know</u>
<u n="432" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah if he wants to watch his sport let him watch his sport</u>
<u n="433" who="S0440">that's right yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0439">but it just for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to control things the way she does to do that it <trunc>n</trunc> that that shouldn't be it's like but <trunc>s</trunc> at least <unclear>will</unclear> have sorted that with a solicitor so</u>
<u n="435" who="S0440">yeah well unless this is <anon type="place"/> I don't want fucking <anon type="place"/></u>
<event desc="sound of satvav"/>
<u n="436" who="S0440">I don't want <anon type="place"/> I could have come this way before</u>
<u n="437" who="S0439">yeah I'm not entirely sure where we're going</u>
<u n="438" who="S0440">no I'm not either</u>
<u n="439" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I love the way you've actually been driving around for half an hour we actually haven't have not got anywhere <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="440" who="S0440">I know we haven't I know we haven't</u>
<u n="441" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="442" who="S0440">anyway let me turn let me let's get to <anon type="place"/></u>
<event desc="sound of satnav"/>
<u n="443" who="S0439"><anon type="place"/> there we go</u>
<u n="444" who="S0440" trans="overlap">oh <anon type="place"/> yay <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0439">that's just taken us twenty odd minutes to erm get us to here that's that's <trunc>grea</trunc></u>
<u n="446" who="S0440" trans="overlap">anything coming?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0439">no you can go <pause dur="short"/> oh wow look at that</u>
<u n="448" who="S0440">what? that house?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0439" trans="overlap">the window</u>
<u n="450" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0439">that's pretty isn't it?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0440">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's</u>
<u n="453" who="S0439" trans="overlap">there's a lot of houses in <anon type="place"/> that are quite nice they're very big houses aren't they?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0440" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="455" who="S0439">you <trunc>ca</trunc> wow that's a massive house <pause dur="short"/> I wonder how expensive it is it's probably quite expensive</u>
<u n="456" who="S0440" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> is very expensive</u>
<u n="457" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of bump"/>
<u n="459" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0440">what was that? god</u>
<u n="461" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it was a</u>
<u n="462" who="S0440" trans="overlap">a hole</u>
<u n="463" who="S0439">yeah no it was a</u>
<u n="464" who="S0440">drain</u>
<u n="465" who="S0439">drain yeah no offence mum but you're a terrible driver</u>
<u n="466" who="S0440">I'm not a terrible driver <pause dur="short"/> I don't expect a drain to be like that</u>
<u n="467" who="S0439">mm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>wh</trunc> er so we've got the wicked witch of the east how's the wicked witch of the west?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0440">still looking for houses and moaning and groaning that she's gonna lose all her money</u>
<u n="469" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well yeah well <trunc>th</trunc> cos they just well they shouldn't have sold their house to somebody who needs a house in September</u>
<u n="470" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I know I know I'm just <trunc>g</trunc> I I I'm <trunc>gobs</trunc></u>
<u n="471" who="S0439" trans="overlap">they've just shot themselves in the foot haven't they?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I'm completely and utterly gobsmacked I really am</u>
<u n="473" who="S0439">I guess like you said they could rent they could live in nan's house and erm and come and stay with us</u>
<u n="474" who="S0440" trans="overlap">but I don't see why that that is even a <trunc>path</trunc> a a a a that is a valid suggestion and nobody is putting it on the table</u>
<u n="475" who="S0439">well why don't you put it on the table?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I'm going to</u>
<u n="477" who="S0439">cos when's nan's kitchen being done? okay end of August?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0440" trans="overlap">well yeah end of August September but I mean</u>
<u n="479" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0440" trans="overlap">it doesn't matter is it they could be <trunc>y</trunc>you know</u>
<u n="481" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0440" trans="overlap">the kitchen isn't gonna be a problem</u>
<u n="483" who="S0439">yeah if nan comes and lives with you for or lives with yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0440" trans="overlap">which she's gonna live with us when the kitchen's done anyway so</u>
<u n="485" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah she might as well stay for an extra month or so</u>
<u n="486" who="S0440" trans="overlap">she might as well stay there for</u>
<u n="487" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mightn't she?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0440" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="489" who="S0439">but yeah but then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> dad said that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was looking at a house something forty thousand pounds over her budget or something it just</u>
<u n="490" who="S0440" trans="overlap">that's a minimum of forty thousand pounds over her budget</u>
<u n="491" who="S0439" trans="overlap">why would you do that to yourself?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I do not know</u>
<u n="493" who="S0439">why would you</u>
<u n="494" who="S0440" trans="overlap">I</u>
<u n="495" who="S0439" trans="overlap">put yourself in more debt?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0440">I don't know</u>
<u n="497" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that's a massive amount of debt</u>
<u n="498" who="S0440" trans="overlap">but they're saying that they're gonna get erm a er</u>
<u n="499" who="S0439" trans="overlap">an endowment are they?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0440" trans="overlap">an endowment</u>
<u n="501" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0440">but I don't think they know how much they're gonna get on their endowment we were supposed to be getting fifty thousand</u>
<u n="503" who="S0439" trans="overlap">what is an what is an endowment?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0440">well you pay a life insurance for over twenty-five years or whatever and according to how the stock exchange goes you get an endowment at the end of it well we were calculated to get a twenty-six thousand pound endowment at the end of ours we ended up having to pay more towards it cos our endowment never materialised</u>
<u n="505" who="S0439">so how much did you get?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0440">nothing</u>
<u n="507" who="S0439">you got nothing from your endowment?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0440">nothing from our endowment so if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is saying oh we're gonna get a thirty thousand pound endowment next year she needs to work out whether she is gonna get a thirty thousand pound endowment next year</u>
<u n="509" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="510" who="S0440">because if not <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="511" who="S0439">cos like no offence but er how much they they sold theirs for two hundred and sixty thousand?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0439">like I do understand that house house prices are increasing and they are going up to like between three hundred and four hundred thousand pounds but if they can't afford it don't look in that price bracket</u>
<u n="514" who="S0440">they couldn't afford it but they need a mortgage</u>
<u n="515" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="516" who="S0440" trans="overlap">and they don't wanna take out a mortgage but my view is if you don't take</u>
<u n="517" who="S0439" trans="overlap">do they not have a mortage then?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0440">well they</u>
<u n="519" who="S0439" trans="overlap">have they paid off their house?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0440" trans="overlap">their mortgage finishes next year</u>
<u n="521" who="S0439">oh I see okay <pause dur="short"/> so they've only it's only got a pathetic amount left on their mortgage?</u>
<u n="522" who="S0440">yeah they haven't got very much left on their mortgage but the fact is that you know they've just got to be sensible about it and you've got to actually sit there <vocal desc="yawn"/> and work out how much it's gonna cost because yes it will actually eat up all the profit that you've all the money that you've made if you rent it for a thousand pounds a month</u>
<u n="523" who="S0439">yeah of course <pause dur="short"/> they just they've just rushed into it like don't get me wrong I know it's sad that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had cancer but</u>
<u n="524" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0439">she's made this massive decision based on the fact that she wanted something to look forward to</u>
<u n="526" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0439">but now she's become more stressed than</u>
<u n="528" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's worth</u>
<u n="530" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0439">like <pause dur="short"/> it's ridiculous and they wouldn't have to take out a very big mortgage they what a forty if they took out a fifty grand mortgage</u>
<u n="532" who="S0440" trans="overlap">well no they've got whatever mortgage they've got now they'd have to add another what bit onto it</u>
<u n="533" who="S0439">well they can't if they've only got one year left on their mortgage they can't have much to pay off</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav"/>
<u n="534" who="S0440">thank you</u>
<u n="535" who="S0439">yeah they can't have much left to pay off but</u>
<u n="536" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="537" who="S0439">just seems so stupid borrowing forty thousand pounds for now when it's in savings when it's in really good savings</u>
<u n="538" who="S0440">I know</u>
<u n="539" who="S0439">and then they're gonna lose money because they're nan will have to pay a fine to take it out</u>
<u n="540" who="S0440">oh well <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0439">why do we live with why are relatives such like bloody morons?</u>
<event desc="sound of satnav"/>
<u n="542" who="S0440">I know we have</u>
<u n="543" who="S0439">have we?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="545" who="S0439">do you name your satnav?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0440">no</u>
<u n="547" who="S0439">mine's Penny <pause dur="long"/> oh do you know where this place actually is?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0440">yeah</u>
<u n="549" who="S0439">oh okay <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> <pause dur="long"/> I've never been to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh actually I might have driven through but I don't think I've actually ever properly been doesn't look a particularly overly exciting place</u>
<u n="550" who="S0440">it isn't <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="551" who="S0439">looks a bit <trunc>c</trunc>councilly <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> farm awesome <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="552" who="S0440">do you want any strawberries?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0439">er yeah I think I might buy some fruit <pause dur="short"/> I think I might</u>
<u n="554" who="S0440">cool I wanted to bottle some raspberries this afternoon</u>
<u n="555" who="S0439">do you?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0440">mm</u>
<u n="557" who="S0439">so are you gonna go and buy loads?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0440">yep</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
