<text id="SP84">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:49:01</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-26</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0428 S0432 S0485</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Cambridge Law Faculty</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Strangers</relationships>
		<topics>Travelling, archeology, giving lectures, excavating villages, languages, Chinese, history, Arab culture</topics>
		<activity>Alumni Day 2</activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0428">
				<exactage>27</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Aylesbury, Buckinghamshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Eastern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language Research Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified; Italian -- level unspecified; French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0432">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>White British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lincoln</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Midlands/ East Anglia</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Gamlingay, Cambridgeshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Language Research Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified; Chinese -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0485">
				<exactage>71</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Oswestry, Shropshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Kew</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>37 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>University Lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Welsh -- level unspecified; Turkish -- level unspecified; Arabic -- level unspecified; Zulu -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0485">I I well I talk for a living but I when it comes to just talking ad lib it's rather difficult</u>
<u n="2" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0485">I've just been I've just been saying to your colleague erm I've done a a cruise round the Mediterranean about two or three times in a row</u>
<u n="4" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh wow</u>
<u n="5" who="S0485">erm cos I I'm a guest lecturer on the ship</u>
<u n="6" who="S0432">oh wow</u>
<u n="7" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh great what a fantastic job</u>
<u n="8" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0485">yeah well somebody has to do it and it the only problem is the eating and drinking really that's the</u>
<u n="10" who="S0428">is the food very good?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0485">I'm afraid it is yes</u>
<u n="12" who="S0428" trans="overlap">too good <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0485">and so is the so is the wine</u>
<u n="14" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0485">so that</u>
<u n="16" who="S0428">and do you give lectures on archaeology?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0485">yes because we're the the groups are going to see archaeological sites</u>
<u n="18" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0485">er through the Greek Islands and then up the Turkish mainland and er so I talk to them about the sites they're going to see about the background of them and the history and so on before they see them</u>
<u n="20" who="S0432">oh wow</u>
<u n="21" who="S0485">and that way they get to understand the</u>
<u n="22" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0485">er last week I was in  Troyer and er Troy is an archaeologist's site it's not really a visitor site</u>
<u n="24" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0485">er archaeologically everything is there but it's in it's in displayed in such a way unless you understand it first you don't grasp what the site's all about it's got three thousand years just one layer on top of another er and you can't see it but I got everybody to understand what they were about to see</u>
<u n="26" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="27" who="S0485">and I said you go from here to there and there you know get through the site that way round it goes all the way back to the early Bronze Age</u>
<u n="28" who="S0432">wow</u>
<u n="29" who="S0485">well</u>
<u n="30" who="S0428">and what can you see like what what what's visually is there to see there?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0485">it's it's an it the main parts of Troy are a Bronze Age site so it's er from about three thousand two hundred to about twelve hundred BC</u>
<u n="32" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0485">so the earliest is about five thousand years old and these sites in the in the East Mediterranean Middle East all develop in the same way they're er what they call tells or tepes or in in Turkish <foreign lang="ota"/> which is erm a mound which contains many periods</u>
<u n="34" who="S0432">okay</u>
<u n="35" who="S0485">if you imagine you start off in a small village you put stones out as a foundation and you build a house and the house is built of sun-dried mud brick</u>
<u n="36" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="37" who="S0485">so you make a mud brick by the water</u>
<u n="38" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0485">the sun dries it you then take it to to where you're going to build the house and you build several houses and you <trunc>th</trunc> make the roof say with thatch</u>
<u n="40" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0485">at a particular point in time in the middle of the winter you've got a spark hits the thatch the whole thing burns down so you're going build another village so you go back to the water make more bricks take them to the site put the stones out build the bricks put the thatch on top if you do this for several thousand years you actually get layer upon layer</u>
<u n="42" who="S0428">of like mud from different places being taken to another place</u>
<u n="43" who="S0485">yes</u>
<u n="44" who="S0428">if that makes sense that's amazing</u>
<u n="45" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="46" who="S0485">that's and there are thousands and thousands of these sites all all over the East Mediterranean</u>
<u n="47" who="S0428">that's fascinating</u>
<u n="48" who="S0432" trans="overlap">and you can see all the the layers?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0485">well the archaeologically the trick is when you excavate them is to separate those layer out</u>
<u n="50" who="S0432">oh wow</u>
<u n="51" who="S0485">er because you've got to you've got excavate each one separately</u>
<u n="52" who="S0432">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0485">discretely</u>
<u n="54" who="S0428">and do you find things in the layers</u>
<u n="55" who="S0485">yes</u>
<u n="56" who="S0428">of maybe I don't know kind of <trunc>in</trunc> tools or?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0485" trans="overlap">yeah you can well tools you find but particularly in the Bronze Age pottery</u>
<u n="58" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0428">ah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0485">because and pottery changes with every generation I mean you've only got to look at the pottery your grandparents used for example to see it's different to the to the kind of cups you drink with now</u>
<u n="61" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0485">er the the ware itself changes the manufacture changes the shape changes the decoration changes and the use changes</u>
<u n="63" who="S0428">that's incredible</u>
<u n="64" who="S0485">and so we use you can use it as a push pull arrangement when you excavate the site you actually can separate you have to separate out the layers in any given layer you have a time capsule related to that that particular period don't you?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0432">yeah right</u>
<u n="66" who="S0428">so you can tell what when when you get the layers you can tell exactly well not exactly the date but you can date the?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0485">there are some extremely tedious people who spend their whole working life just comparing different</u>
<u n="68" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="69" who="S0428">layers</u>
<u n="70" who="S0485">different styles of pottery from different periods and I know this I know they're tedious cos I was one of them</u>
<u n="71" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0485">erm and you say well this site we can date to that period and has this kind of pottery so if you find this kind of pottery at that site it's going to be about the same period</u>
<u n="73" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0485">do you see?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0485">so it's known as ceramic typology</u>
<u n="78" who="S0428">ceramic typology</u>
<u n="79" who="S0432" trans="overlap">ceramic typology</u>
<u n="80" who="S0485" trans="overlap">it has a fancy name and the what you are trying to achieve to get your ceramic typology is stratigraphic analysis so the analysis of the different strata</u>
<u n="81" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0485">different layers layer upon layer see what I mean?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0428">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0485">so in Troy there are basically nine layers of the site</u>
<u n="85" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0485">from early Bronze Age through to Roman erm but the main</u>
<u n="87" who="S0428" trans="overlap">so what sorry what what years were the the <trunc>bro</trunc>? I'm really bad at</u>
<u n="88" who="S0485">the bronze Bronze Bronze Age is the Neolithic</u>
<u n="89" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0485">which is the new Stone Age is the beginning of agriculture beginning of erm village building city building the whole thing er predates Troy it's it's from about ten thousand years ago to about <trunc>thre</trunc> er five thousand years ago you then start with move into the Bronze Age where bronze replaced stone</u>
<u n="91" who="S0428" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0485">as a but I mean you get all sorts of other changes as well and that lasts for about two thousand years to about twelve hundred BC and then you come into the Iron Age and hopefully by then you've got some kind of writing so you move from prehistory to history</u>
<u n="93" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0485">but before history everything is an archaeological artefact</u>
<u n="95" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0485">of itself you've created that by analysing the site</u>
<u n="97" who="S0428" trans="overlap">wow that's absolutely fascinating</u>
<u n="98" who="S0485">well that's how it's done and it's it's the British that actually invented this system of dissecting these these tells it was er <trunc>Mort</trunc> does does the name Mortimer Wheeler mean anything to you?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0432">no</u>
<u n="100" who="S0485" trans="overlap">oh no he was the first person to popularise archaeology on television</u>
<u n="101" who="S0432">oh oh</u>
<u n="102" who="S0485">steam driven black and white television in those days and er another lady called Kathleen Kenyon who was the daughter of Sir Frederic Kenyon the director of the British Museum and <trunc>Ke</trunc> so it's often known as the Wheeler-Kenyon method of excavating where you have to you cut it if you imagine you've you've had black forest gateau haven't you?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0428" trans="overlap">mm oh okay yes</u>
<u n="104" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="105" who="S0485">and you know it's actually a layer of sponge a layer of cream a layer of cherries a layer of whatever</u>
<u n="106" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="107" who="S0485">you imagine that is what your tell looks like and it can cover <trunc>th</trunc>thirteen hectares say so a big site</u>
<u n="108" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0485">you had to cut into this and determine those different layers</u>
<u n="110" who="S0428">and how thick is a layer I mean?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0485">it varies</u>
<u n="112" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh it varies but</u>
<u n="113" who="S0485">it varies because as you get as the site gets bigger and more important they might even defend it with mud brick walls</u>
<u n="114" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0485">which means you get even greater preservation of the material inside the site er usually on balance you're looking at about erm of let's say one storey buildings about a quarter to a third remains just the bottom</u>
<u n="117" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah yeah oh wow</u>
<u n="118" who="S0428">oh that's a lot I was</u>
<u n="119" who="S0432" trans="overlap">that's more than I was thinking</u>
<u n="120" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I was <trunc>im</trunc> I don't now why I was imagining something</u>
<u n="121" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0485" trans="overlap">and the <trunc>for</trunc> well if you go back into early prehistory</u>
<u n="124" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0485">the Stone Age er the there are sites that I've excavated where they're only a few millimetres thick</u>
<u n="126" who="S0432">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0485">because there there'll be a stopping point for a hunter gatherer group you know for just a few days and then they move on so they</u>
<u n="128" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0485">but if you're dealing with an urban site you know you're dealing with a fairly major occupation and that's how it works that's is known as stratigraphy</u>
<u n="130" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0428">I've never ever heard of heard of it but I mean it makes sense that you would you would do it that way but</u>
<u n="132" who="S0485" trans="overlap">yeah well because but unless you cut it like so the section you cut it in <trunc>u</trunc>usually it's either two three of four metre squares</u>
<u n="133" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0485">and you control the analysis of the different layers by referring to the sections on the all the four sides</u>
<u n="135" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0432">oh okay</u>
<u n="137" who="S0485" trans="overlap">to see exactly where you are because curiously enough all er occupational debris will leave its own fingerprint for some reason or other erm <trunc>e</trunc><trunc>e</trunc><trunc>e</trunc>either through the way it was destroyed er or through any erm alterations being if it was abandoned for a a few decades you'll get mid brick wash over the site and you you the the trick is technically to to define those differences as you excavate so you scrape away at it and you look at the textural differences between one layer and the next</u>
<u n="138" who="S0428">how how did you get into archaeology?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0432" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="140" who="S0485">ah that's a different question</u>
<u n="141" who="S0428">no it's it's fascinating it it's something that I find</u>
<u n="142" who="S0432" trans="overlap"><trunc>wa</trunc> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0428">really interesting but <trunc>n</trunc><trunc>n</trunc> I've never come across</u>
<u n="144" who="S0432">my sister always wanted to do it but she just never did and she still regrets it now she's like I should have gone into it</u>
<u n="145" who="S0485" trans="overlap">well the first the first thing to say and I I you know I I'm pretty long in the tooth now but you don't go into archaeology if you want to make any money</u>
<u n="146" who="S0432">no</u>
<u n="147" who="S0485">because it's it's not really a way of making money it's a way of life</u>
<u n="148" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0485">to me it is anyway</u>
<u n="150" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0485">I am totally and absolutely absorbed by it and have been since I started but I didn't want to do archaeology I didn't didn't think about it I actually wanted to be a geologist</u>
<u n="152" who="S0432">ah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0428" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0485">which is why I got those specimens there which are in themselves totally interesting but in a totally different way</u>
<u n="155" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm oh yeah yeah they're very pretty</u>
<u n="156" who="S0485">right? so er I wanted to be a geologist and that's why I did Middle East ancient Middle Eastern languages</u>
<u n="157" who="S0428" trans="overlap">and where where did you do that? is that?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0432">oh yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0485" trans="overlap">what what?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0428">that makes sense</u>
<u n="161" who="S0485">does that make sense?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0428">was that here or?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0485">no I I er erm er er from <trunc>Lo</trunc>London University of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0428" trans="overlap">wow so which so which <trunc>lan</trunc></u>
<u n="165" who="S0432" trans="overlap">so then you got from the languages to the</u>
<u n="166" who="S0485">oh I mean</u>
<u n="167" who="S0432">geology</u>
<u n="168" who="S0428">we're both language graduates so maybe we'll go in to</u>
<u n="169" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0485">er East Semitic Akkadian which is from Mesopotamia it's the first that's one of the first languages ever written down</u>
<u n="171" who="S0432" trans="overlap">er</u>
<u n="172" who="S0428">oh wow</u>
<u n="173" who="S0485">er five thousand years ago</u>
<u n="174" who="S0428">wow</u>
<u n="175" who="S0485">in cuneiform <pause dur="short"/> er Aramaic Canaanite classical Hebrew classical Arabic</u>
<u n="176" who="S0428">loads of languages</u>
<u n="177" who="S0432" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="178" who="S0485">oh yeah I was that</u>
<u n="179" who="S0432">that's amazing</u>
<u n="180" who="S0485">and I I was the only student in four years</u>
<u n="181" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh how did you chose that course?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0485" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0432">and they still?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0485">well I I didn't really somebody said that's why you should do you should do that so I said oh alright then</u>
<u n="185" who="S0428">okay</u>
<u n="186" who="S0428">give it a go</u>
<u n="187" who="S0485" trans="overlap">but when I when I finished erm I didn't know what to do so I went to the careers advisory service and they said what are you best at? and I said well translating tenth century BC Canaanite inscriptions and they said we don't think there's a lot of call for that at the minute</u>
<u n="188" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0485">and and they were right er and this chap interviewed me and said but but you wanted to be a geologist did you do any field work? and I said I all my teenage life when all my friend were running after girls I was running after rocks</u>
<u n="191" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0485">cos I could understand those better than I could understand</u>
<u n="193" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0428">there you are</u>
<u n="195" who="S0485">so so that's what I did and he said you should combine your field work interest with you ancient languages and become a Middle Eastern archaeologist</u>
<u n="196" who="S0428">there you go</u>
<u n="197" who="S0485">so I said alright then I will</u>
<u n="198" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0485">and he said I know just the place to go and it was the Institute of Archaeology in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0428">wow</u>
<u n="201" who="S0485">er which was then and still is the foremost archaeological research institute in Europe</u>
<u n="202" who="S0428">oh wow</u>
<u n="203" who="S0485">and I was there er man and boy for a good few years erm I finished my doctorate there and then er taught there and so on</u>
<u n="204" who="S0428" trans="overlap">and that's that's lovely that now you're you're able to travel be in those wonderful places use your your skill and use your passion as a way of communicating to everyone who you know</u>
<u n="205" who="S0485" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="206" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0485">well</u>
<u n="208" who="S0428" trans="overlap">what a what an ideal job yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0432" trans="overlap">and still being there in the</u>
<u n="210" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0485">yeah it is I suppose it is you could say that</u>
<u n="212" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0432">so do you do tours of these places of are you just do you just do the lectures?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0485">there we are</u>
<u n="215" who="S0432">do you do you erm lead the tours? or just</u>
<u n="216" who="S0485" trans="overlap">not only I I do lead tours we also organise other tours and er the Temple World actually created see it says</u>
<u n="217" who="S0432">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0485">incorporating IMA travel under IMA Travel we actually set up the alumni programme travel programme for <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0432">oh</u>
<u n="220" who="S0485">in nineteen ninety-two it was actually <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a colleague of mine who did it and I took over from him</u>
<u n="221" who="S0428">so it it are they are they trips for <anon type="place"/> alumni?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0485">they are that's that's all we do <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> alumni</u>
<u n="223" who="S0432">oh <trunc>pu</trunc> just purely the</u>
<u n="224" who="S0485">yeah and some some from the States as well</u>
<u n="225" who="S0432">oh wow</u>
<u n="226" who="S0485">erm we're looking</u>
<u n="227" who="S0432">oh yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0485">yeah we're looking at the possibility of expanding the <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> programme to combine with one or two of the universities in the States like Harvard and unfortunately I have to go out to Greece again next week</u>
<u n="229" who="S0432">oh no</u>
<u n="230" who="S0428">do you want us to go instead?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0485">no</u>
<u n="232" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0432">we can come down</u>
<u n="234" who="S0428" trans="overlap">now we know all about it</u>
<u n="235" who="S0432" trans="overlap">do you need do you need some help? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0485">well I'd love you to but unfortunately they they're expecting me to be there cos I'm going to lecture on yet another ship erm to to show these alumni organisers what it's all about</u>
<u n="237" who="S0432">oh just have to put up with it won't you?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0485" trans="overlap">so that's what I do so what do you do?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0432">oh dear</u>
<u n="240" who="S0428" trans="overlap">well it's not nearly a exciting we work at <anon type="place"/> Press in the language and pedagogy research team and we work on the language side of that so we both we both studied languages as uni erm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0485">what languages did you study?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0428">I did Spanish and Italian</u>
<u n="243" who="S0432">I did Spanish and Chinese</u>
<u n="244" who="S0485">Chinese? yeah that's that's er er and how did you enjoy that?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0432">it was at at first I was questioning why I decided to do it but it was actually really really really interesting really it wasn't as hard as I thought it would be to learn it was yeah I'm glad I did it I'm definitely I'm definitely going to carry on</u>
<u n="246" who="S0485" trans="overlap">well <trunc>i</trunc> yes I mean I I did like every schoolboy did French and so on but the language I think in if I have to think in a foreign language is Turkish</u>
<u n="247" who="S0432">oh</u>
<u n="248" who="S0428">oh really?</u>
<u n="249" who="S0485">yes cos I've spent a lot a lot of time in Turkey</u>
<u n="250" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0428">I was saying my mum grew up in Istanbul earlier</u>
<u n="252" who="S0485">right</u>
<u n="253" who="S0428">yeah its but she doesn't she doesn't speak any Turkish</u>
<u n="254" who="S0432" trans="overlap">does she not no?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0485">it's it's a beautiful language it's it erm well I think it's beautiful it's it's from Mongolia</u>
<u n="256" who="S0428">is it?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0432">oh</u>
<u n="258" who="S0485">it has more akin to Korean than it does to anything in European</u>
<u n="259" who="S0432" trans="overlap">I didn't know that</u>
<u n="260" who="S0428">that's fascinating</u>
<u n="261" who="S0432">I did not know that</u>
<u n="262" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I had</u>
<u n="263" who="S0485">yeah it's an <trunc>agglutinani</trunc>agglutinative language you can stick bits together and make new words and it has suffixes and prefixes and infixes</u>
<u n="264" who="S0432">oh</u>
<u n="265" who="S0485">the negative of a verb is actually an infix in the centre of the verb</u>
<u n="266" who="S0432">wow</u>
<u n="267" who="S0485">so you'd say erm <foreign lang="ota">geliyorum</foreign> I am coming or <foreign lang="ota">gelmiyorum</foreign> I am not coming</u>
<u n="268" who="S0432">oh</u>
<u n="269" who="S0485">so the M in the middle is</u>
<u n="270" who="S0432">so you've got to be really paying attention when you speak</u>
<u n="271" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0485" trans="overlap">yeah you do yes</u>
<u n="273" who="S0428">you can't you can't miss the word there's no not</u>
<u n="274" who="S0485">yeah</u>
<u n="275" who="S0432">wow that's interesting</u>
<u n="276" who="S0428" trans="overlap">so we we we work on on looking at English and how English is changing and kind of taking a descriptive view and that feeding that into the English Language publishing that <anon type="place"/> Press creates and at the moment we're collecting erm the British National Corpus</u>
<u n="277" who="S0485" trans="overlap">yeah right</u>
<u n="278" who="S0428">so twenty years ago they collect I don't know if you did you have you heard of the British National Corpus?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0485">no I'm afraid I haven't</u>
<u n="280" who="S0428">erm so twenty years ago they collected a hundred million words of written and spoken English and I think it was ten million spoken so they recorded conversations like this and they just transcribed them all and it's a freely available source on the internet that you can search and they collected yes erm the written as well and we're basically erm with <anon type="place"/> University updating this resource for the twenty tens</u>
<u n="281" who="S0485">with <anon type="place"/> University?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0428">we do it with <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0432">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0485">how fascinating</u>
<u n="285" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0428">they're kind of world leaders so the <trunc>bran</trunc> it's called corpus linguistics and they're like the they're just brilliant they've got such great resources and people out there it's really good</u>
<u n="287" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0485">why how did they get involved with that?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0428">we're what with <anon type="place"/> or?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0485">yeah no well how did <anon type="place"/> get involved in the first place?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0432">not sure</u>
<u n="292" who="S0428" trans="overlap">it's a it's a branch of linguistics that that kind of since the sixties fifties sixties has been growing and and becoming</u>
<u n="293" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="294" who="S0428">we erm we can show you how it works so it's erm <anon type="place"/> Press have in the corpus that we have we have two billion words that's been collected for about twenty-five years and we also collect learner data</u>
<u n="295" who="S0432">yes</u>
<u n="296" who="S0428">so we can search for example they they get all the exam scripts from <anon type="place"/> University exams from Spain all all round the world and then we can find like the top ten errors for example of Spanish speakers at a particular level er and then we can use this to feed back into the publishing</u>
<u n="297" who="S0485">right</u>
<u n="298" who="S0428">so we work</u>
<u n="299" who="S0432">and we can show them examples erm of how English speakers use the language so we can teach them up-to-date stuff so we won't teach the it's raining cats and dogs for example cos no one says that any more</u>
<u n="300" who="S0485" trans="overlap">do do you no oh they don't?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0432">apparently not <vocal desc="laugh"/> not like we used to</u>
<u n="302" who="S0485">but erm do do you concentrate on pronunciation at all? or is it only on</u>
<u n="303" who="S0428" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0485">individual words?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0432">yeah we just just on words and grammar structures and it's</u>
<u n="306" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0485">because I I er erm I'm currently working on Linear B which is a language was found in Crete but it actually is from it's a middle Bronze Age language from or a Bronze Age language from mainland Greece from the Peloponnese and it's the earliest form of written Indo European er written by the Mycenaean's and unbelievably I was doing this the other day and I found example in this of rhotacisms now you will have come across rhotacism won't you?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0428">rhotacism?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0485">it's the inability of a speaker to distinguish between L and R</u>
<u n="310" who="S0432">oh okay yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh okay just didn't know the word yes</u>
<u n="312" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yep yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0428">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0485">well it's called rhotacism and you actually get this in Linear B</u>
<u n="315" who="S0432">oh</u>
<u n="316" who="S0485">you know four thousand years ago three thousand years ago</u>
<u n="317" who="S0428">wow</u>
<u n="318" who="S0485">isn't that amazing?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0432">yeah that is</u>
<u n="320" who="S0485">where they they actually miswrite or mishear the</u>
<u n="321" who="S0428">the R and the L</u>
<u n="322" who="S0485">the R and the L?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0428">that's fascinating</u>
<u n="325" who="S0432">that is</u>
<u n="326" who="S0485">yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0428">yeah we'd have to</u>
<u n="328" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0485" trans="overlap">no I'm I'm I'm in in I'm really interesting obviously in languages cos that's where I came from</u>
<u n="330" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0485">erm and wherever I've worked I've learnt the language concerned</u>
<u n="332" who="S0432">yeah <trunc>w</trunc> there's someone in our team actually she's erm she does the pedagogy research but her background's in pronunciation</u>
<u n="333" who="S0485">yeah</u>
<u n="334" who="S0432">so it would be it is fascinating to include that but we there are you do have to kind of ignore some bits and just concentrate on others and</u>
<u n="335" who="S0485" trans="overlap">well the other thing on on on the ship that I was teaching on I was talking to the barman he he was from the Philippines and he likes to learn different languages you know wherever he happened to be so I was teaching him about Greek and particularly Turkish so he would get up in the morning and I'd say <foreign lang="ota">gunaydin</foreign> which is good morning er and he he starts in a er now the ship is going to be going to the <anon type="place"/> er erm n the <trunc>spr</trunc> in the spring and it's going round Southern Africa</u>
<u n="336" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0428">oh wow</u>
<u n="338" who="S0485">and I actually worked in Southern Africa for about twenty years so</u>
<u n="339" who="S0432">oh wow</u>
<u n="340" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh wow</u>
<u n="341" who="S0485">so I've been teaching him Zulu cos I learnt Zulu there</u>
<u n="342" who="S0428">how many languages do you speak?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0485">well</u>
<u n="345" who="S0428">you're a polyglot</u>
<u n="346" who="S0485">my <vocal desc="laugh"/> my son says my son actually counted them and he said dad are you aware of the fact you speak fourteen languages</u>
<u n="347" who="S0428">ah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0432">wow</u>
<u n="349" who="S0485">and I said that that that might be the case I said but</u>
<u n="350" who="S0428" trans="overlap">it's like a dream</u>
<u n="351" who="S0485">but my father told me I said I knew a man who could speak fourteen languages and he had nothing useful to say in any of them</u>
<u n="352" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="353" who="S0485">that's that's what I would say</u>
<u n="354" who="S0428">but at least you can talk to a lot more people than we can</u>
<u n="355" who="S0485">yeah we <trunc>Zu</trunc>Zulu is a fascinating language it's the only other language I know the <trunc>la</trunc> the Zulu group is actually Nguni er which has the same phoneme as we have in Welsh which was actually my first language erm which is</u>
<u n="356" who="S0428">oh and what's that thing?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0485">an aspirated L</u>
<u n="358" who="S0428">and how would you <trunc>pro</trunc></u>
<u n="359" who="S0485">as in Llangollen</u>
<u n="360" who="S0432">ah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0428">oh</u>
<u n="362" who="S0485">and Zulu had the same sound</u>
<u n="363" who="S0432">oh</u>
<u n="364" who="S0428">that's incredible</u>
<u n="365" who="S0485">in in <foreign lang="zul"/> for example or <foreign lang="zul"/> it's quite extraordinary and English people cannot hear this sound</u>
<u n="366" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0485">and they pronounce it as a SH so</u>
<u n="368" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah that's yeah that's</u>
<u n="369" who="S0485">so <foreign lang="wel"/> and it's actually <foreign lang="wel"/> but they <trunc>cl</trunc> they don't know how to pronounce it</u>
<u n="370" who="S0432">wow that's</u>
<u n="371" who="S0485">yeah it's interesting</u>
<u n="372" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0485">although a lot of people would tell you that English people are the worst foreign language speakers because they have the lowest numbers of phonemes in their in their er battery of sounds</u>
<u n="374" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0485">they just can't hear them but obviously you prove this to be not the case</u>
<u n="376" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0428">I think it's it's that mixed with a kind of attitude of everyone speaks English so we don't need to learn</u>
<u n="378" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0485">yeah that's the other thing</u>
<u n="380" who="S0428">which obviously I don't agree with but</u>
<u n="381" who="S0485">yeah but you unless you learn the language of people you're with you have no idea how they're thinking</u>
<u n="382" who="S0428">no</u>
<u n="383" who="S0485">you know you presume they're thinking one way but particularly in Africa and I had two or three African languages all cognate but erm <trunc>we</trunc></u>
<u n="384" who="S0428">in was this is in South Africa did you say?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0485">in <trunc>So</trunc> in in Swaziland actually</u>
<u n="386" who="S0428">ah ha</u>
<u n="387" who="S0485">and and South Africa but their their mental construct of of what they see is quite different to a Europeans they actually well they see the same thing but the construct they put on it in their mind is quite different</u>
<u n="388" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0485">and so you think well why aren't you seeing what I'm seeing well they are but they're understanding it differently and that has been a sore point between British colonials and Africans forever</u>
<u n="390" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="391" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="392" who="S0432">we</u>
<u n="393" who="S0485">when I started to learn the their language and see how they saw things I thought oh that's what they that's how they're thinking of it</u>
<u n="394" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0485">that made a tremendous amount more sense</u>
<u n="396" who="S0432">yeah that's what we were talking this the other day weren't we? saying learning a language isn't just learning a language you learn kind of there way of thinking their way and their way of life if you visit the country and</u>
<u n="397" who="S0485" trans="overlap">no it's a no yeah it is it is it is it is it really is</u>
<u n="398" who="S0428" trans="overlap">and the meanings of words</u>
<u n="399" who="S0432">and you see things in a lot of different different ways to what you would if you didn't learn a language</u>
<u n="400" who="S0485">yeah yeah I mean</u>
<u n="401" who="S0432">it is fascinating</u>
<u n="402" who="S0485" trans="overlap">you cannot understand foreign people unless you understand the language</u>
<u n="403" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="404" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0485">you can't sympathise with them at all</u>
<u n="406" who="S0432">yeah I'd love to speak more if I got to learning more</u>
<u n="407" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah me too</u>
<u n="408" who="S0485" trans="overlap">well you and but the Chinese is fascinating but it it's too late <trunc>fo</trunc> now for me to do that but I erm they do say that there is a similarity between Turkish and er you know Chinese certainly Mongolian but I can't I can't sense any any similarity at all when I listen to Chinese people speaking I can't hear anything that I recognise</u>
<u n="409" who="S0432">I would try and help you but I don't know Turkish so</u>
<u n="410" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0485" trans="overlap">no no it it's a <pause dur="short"/> learnt Turkish in a village in southwestern Turkey and it's fairly colourful Turkish erm</u>
<u n="412" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0428">I really like the sound of Turkish</u>
<u n="414" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0485"><vocal desc="cough"/> it is it is it's a it's a super language but when I finally got to Istanbul and started using it there they said you know who is the country hick you know?</u>
<u n="416" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0485">I modified it slightly now but other day I was in a <foreign lang="ota">chai han</foreign> a tea house and ordering tea erm and I wanted it a particular way and this girl came up to me a Turkish girl and said erm which part of Turkey are you from? and I said no I'm not I'm from London and she said what what's it like for a Turk living in London?</u>
<u n="418" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="419" who="S0485">and I said I I'm English</u>
<u n="420" who="S0432">that's got to be compliment</u>
<u n="421" who="S0485" trans="overlap">I'm not Turkish I'm I'm English she couldn't believe it</u>
<u n="422" who="S0432">wow that's really that's amazing</u>
<u n="423" who="S0485">she said but your pronunciation is <trunc>ba</trunc> I said well no it's actually from southwestern Turkey if I'm in that area I would expect somebody to say like not I was actually outside <anon type="place"/> when she said that</u>
<u n="424" who="S0428">wow</u>
<u n="425" who="S0485">yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0432">that's when you've conquered the</u>
<u n="427" who="S0428" trans="overlap">that's yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0485">so but</u>
<u n="429" who="S0428">you mastered it</u>
<u n="430" who="S0485">but just amazing but er</u>
<u n="431" who="S0432">I want to get to that stage in Chinese</u>
<u n="432" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="433" who="S0432">I think they'd be able to tell that I'm not native Chinese</u>
<u n="434" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="435" who="S0485">but you know it it's been one of the great joy I mean do doing the degree was one of the hardest things I've ever done</u>
<u n="436" who="S0428">I can imagine</u>
<u n="437" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0485">classical Arabic was by far the most difficult language particularly Quranic <trunc>ara</trunc>Arabic</u>
<u n="439" who="S0428">how does the script I did erm I did a course in like Arabic erm in Spain actually when I was on studying there</u>
<u n="440" who="S0485">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0428">and how does the script differ has it changed a lot like ancient those ancient scripts to the modern one or?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0485">yeah the <trunc>o</trunc> the it was the Umayyad Caliphate which took Spain erm and and the Omayyad's wrote in what's known as Kufic script</u>
<u n="443" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="444" who="S0485">which is almost individual letters so it's not so cursive</u>
<u n="445" who="S0428">okay yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0485">and it then Latin it became more and more cursive so and then very er colourful colourfully drawn er but the the early forms are a completely different script</u>
<u n="447" who="S0428">and not as joined together that's quite interesting it's so beautiful Arabic</u>
<u n="448" who="S0485" trans="overlap">I yeah I I was I excavated a site in southwestern Turkey a long time ago now yes a long time ago</u>
<u n="449" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0485">and it was a Byzantine church which dated to the sixth century</u>
<u n="451" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="452" who="S0485">and on the floor of the sanctuary there was a Kufic Arabic inscription and and they are this is one of the very few <trunc>in</trunc>inscriptions outside Arabia</u>
<u n="453" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="454" who="S0485">this Umayyad I thought what the hell does this mean? and I just couldn't make it out and I I took an Arabist there with me and he sat and then we slowly slowly worked it out and it it's only a few words but it's the most fascinating thing I think I one of the most fascinating things I ever found the it's actually a piece of Arabic graffiti</u>
<u n="455" who="S0428">ah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0485">and it says <foreign lang="ara">Alaikum rafour Yazid Ibn Sufyan</foreign> that's all it is <foreign lang="ara">Alaikum</foreign> is the erm er er evocative oh god <foreign lang="ara">rafour</foreign> is from the Arabic <foreign lang="ara">rafarat</foreign> to to pardon or forgive pardon Yazid Ibn Sufyan and Yazid Ibn Sufyan we know we know exactly who he is he is the son of Muawiya who was the second caliph of the Umayyad empire and he same around that coast in six seventy-two AD and he must have stopped in the harbour at Knidos where where this was and written his name on the already destroyed Byzantine church</u>
<u n="457" who="S0432">oh</u>
<u n="458" who="S0485">but the more important thing about Yazid is what he did next you would hear about on the news every day of the week every day of the week it was he that er eight years later er when he became caliph himself</u>
<u n="459" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="460" who="S0485">er took an army into Iraq and killed Hussein er the grandson of the prophet</u>
<u n="461" who="S0485">at the battle of Karbala and that caused a great schism between the Shia and the Sunni Muslim</u>
<u n="462" who="S0432" trans="overlap">Sunni</u>
<u n="463" who="S0428">oh</u>
<u n="464" who="S0485">and he is the person held responsible by the Shia for doing that think of that so you hear about what he's done every day of every all the crisis you're getting right now today on today's news between Iran and Saudi Arabia is because Yazid killed Hussein in six hundred and eighty AD</u>
<u n="465" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="466" who="S0432">wow</u>
<u n="467" who="S0485">and there was his name he's written his name on the on the stone and I've I've seen it I've seen his handwriting I mean it's like the thing jumped out of the ground at me</u>
<u n="468" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0432" trans="overlap">his name</u>
<u n="470" who="S0428">it's I mean it's it's fascinating we were at erm a talk in <anon type="place"/> about how erm about erm the representation of Muslim er Muslims in the press and</u>
<u n="471" who="S0485">yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0428">and that was saying you know he I remember him saying oh erm they're you know these Sunnis and these <trunc>shi</trunc> and he was like do you know what that means? do you know do you know what that is do you know what that comes from and we don't know but we read it every day</u>
<u n="473" who="S0485" trans="overlap">well well Shia Shia is Shiat al Ali</u>
<u n="474" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="475" who="S0485">the <trunc>pa</trunc> the party of Ali and the reason why that is the case in six twenty-two you had the first haj when let's let's go back to Mecca you heard about Mecca in the last few days</u>
<u n="476" who="S0428">oh yeah with the</u>
<u n="477" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="478" who="S0485">right Mecca was actually erm a polytheistic shrine</u>
<u n="479" who="S0428">what does that mean?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0485">many gods</u>
<u n="481" who="S0428">ah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0485">there were a thousand gods worshipped at Mecca for hundreds and hundreds of years because it's a water shrine</u>
<u n="483" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="484" who="S0485">there are loads of water shrines you get them all over Britain holy well this that and the other</u>
<u n="485" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0485">they're you know they're they're all</u>
<u n="487" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="488" who="S0485">erm animistic shrines from the past</u>
<u n="489" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0485">and the one in Mecca is important because it's a strong spring in the middle of the desert on the main caravan route from South Arabia to Gaza</u>
<u n="491" who="S0428">okay</u>
<u n="492" who="S0485">so it was a huge er hugely important spring er and the the Kaaba at Mecca you know the one they all parade round this black box</u>
<u n="493" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0485">is actually a Nabataean it's either a temple or a probably a tomb so it goes back into you know years BC</u>
<u n="496" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0485">so it's it's not what Allah put there it's a man-made box if you like</u>
<u n="498" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0485">now erm Muhammad came from a family er from the Quraysh clan who actually administered this this shrine and obviously they were taking taxes from all the caravans going up and down and they had these thousand gods including allat allat is the female of allah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0432">okay</u>
<u n="501" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh wow I did not know know that</u>
<u n="502" who="S0485">yeah so there was a female deity and even allah do you know what it actually means?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0428">the</u>
<u n="504" who="S0485">the lah is what it means</u>
<u n="505" who="S0428">is lah not a letter or?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0485">no al</u>
<u n="507" who="S0428">no</u>
<u n="508" who="S0485">al is the lah is we have no idea what it means</u>
<u n="509" who="S0428">oh</u>
<u n="510" who="S0485">it's the lah so that's where the name comes from now tell Muslim that and you know he might chop your fingers off but that's that's actually where it comes from it's probably some prehistoric deity that was worshiped there along with all these others</u>
<u n="511" who="S0432">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="512" who="S0428">wow</u>
<u n="513" who="S0485">right? now Muhammad said that there can be only one god and that is allah and his his family disowned him and they nearly killed him and he escaped from Mecca to er a town north called Yathrib which is now known as Madinat al-Nabi the city of the prophet and that's the first haj the escape of Muhammad</u>
<u n="514" who="S0428">ah to</u>
<u n="515" who="S0485" trans="overlap">about six twenty-two AD or year zero in the er er Muhammad had a daughter</u>
<u n="516" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="517" who="S0485">called Fatima and she married Ali so Ali was the prophet's son-in-law</u>
<u n="518" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0485">and Fatima and Ali had two sons Hussein and Hassan right? you're talking about seventh century AD things were pretty vicious at the time and everybody disliked everybody else and one by one actually Muhammad died of probably malaria but erm certainly Hassan was first killed Ali was I think he was killed as well and the last member of the prophet's family was Hussein the grandson</u>
<u n="521" who="S0428" trans="overlap">and he</u>
<u n="522" who="S0485">the grandson of the prophet and he was killed in six eighty in Karbala which is why it's you you may of heard of that during the Iraq war it's very very important religious shrine</u>
<u n="523" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="524" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0485">now the Shia absolutely totally blame the Sunni Muslims for for this murder as they still do as though it happened yesterday</u>
<u n="526" who="S0428">that's crazy isn't it?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0432" trans="overlap">it's crazy <unclear/> the impact</u>
<u n="528" who="S0485">and if you go to the Great Mosque in Damascus there's a special shrine on the side of the Great Mosque which is where they say the head of Hussein was taken by Yazid and put in the Great Mosque as a trophy and I've seen people there you know er religious religious tourists from Iran who are Shia Muslims going there and flagellating themselves with chains until the bleed and crying and screaming and you know blaming the Syrians because they're mainly Sunni for this particular disaster as though it happened yesterday or last week</u>
<u n="529" who="S0432">it it the impact it has on their lives is just</u>
<u n="530" who="S0485">yeah it's just</u>
<u n="531" who="S0432">and that long ago</u>
<u n="532" who="S0485">it's it's a schism which is far far worse than anything to do with the er Catholic and Protestant religion and it's much deeper and it's lasted longer and they're not going to solve it</u>
<u n="533" who="S0432">no</u>
<u n="534" who="S0428">but that's almost fascinating in itself that it can last that long and still be that strong</u>
<u n="535" who="S0432" trans="overlap">that yeah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0485">it it's probably more virulent now than it ever has been</u>
<u n="537" who="S0428">yeah but that's fascinating in itself how like yeah <trunc>cul</trunc>culturally how how it's kept up and</u>
<u n="538" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah yeah still central to</u>
<u n="539" who="S0485">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="541" who="S0485">oh it's more than <trunc>ce</trunc> and if it's possibly more than central but it is absolutely totally what they think what they think and the reason why they were going to Syria in the first place by to a Sunni country is because Assad is an Alawite which are more related to the Shia than they are to their own people but if you ask a thorough going Iranian Shia was the Alawites are he'll say oh they're basically pagans you know they they they they don't believe in the same thing but they are taken as Shia er in in in a mainly Sunni area I mean it's these things go back to the to the seventh century</u>
<u n="542" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="543" who="S0485">six hundred and eight</u>
<u n="544" who="S0428">you want to shake them and say <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="545" who="S0485">it was Yazid this lunatic that caused this and there was his name written on this you know carved into the stone with a with a chisel</u>
<u n="546" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0428">that's mental</u>
<u n="548" who="S0485">so when he when he said allah oh god pardon Yazid pardon me he needed it believe me</u>
<u n="549" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="550" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="552" who="S0485">but isn't that fascinating?</u>
<u n="553" who="S0432">that is really fascinating I didn't know any of that</u>
<u n="554" who="S0485">I I like</u>
<u n="555" who="S0428">and did and was it quite a like famous is it did like the the graffiti on the floor had other did other people know it was there or?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0485">no</u>
<u n="557" who="S0428">no you you</u>
<u n="558" who="S0485">we found it</u>
<u n="559" who="S0428">wow</u>
<u n="560" who="S0432">that's amazing</u>
<u n="561" who="S0485">yeah</u>
<u n="562" who="S0428">would would you say that's</u>
<u n="563" who="S0432" trans="overlap">is it still kind of was it preserved?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0485">it's still there it's still there</u>
<u n="565" who="S0432">wow</u>
<u n="566" who="S0428">would you say that was your like greatest or like moment of er</u>
<u n="567" who="S0485">well you might you might think so mightn't you? the great moments of archaeology the great moments in archaeology</u>
<u n="568" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0432">it sounds like erm a TV show</u>
<u n="570" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0485">yeah it is well that's one of them</u>
<u n="572" who="S0432">just one</u>
<u n="573" who="S0485">but it's by no means the most important thing I've ever found er I've just published a book last month about one of the one of the most important things that I was involved I didn't particularly personally find it but I was there when it was discovered and I was the first person to survey it there's a an extremely famous statue produced in Classical world</u>
<u n="574" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="575" who="S0485">er it's called the Aphrodite of Praxiteles Praxiteles was an Athenian sculpture sculptor and the he produced it in his erm studio</u>
<u n="576" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0485">in Athens and the people of Knidos which is here in southwestern Turkey extreme southwestern tip</u>
<u n="578" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="579" who="S0485">er bought this statue and what it is important about it is a a statue of the goddess who is totally undraped it's nude and it was extremely beautiful</u>
<u n="580" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="581" who="S0485">he based it on his mistress who was a woman called Phryne which actually in Greek means the toad</u>
<u n="582" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="583" who="S0432">it's not so nice</u>
<u n="584" who="S0428">very elegant</u>
<u n="585" who="S0485">erm apparently because erm she had rather sallow skin but I think it's the <trunc>o</trunc> the other ladies called her the toad cos she was you know too beautiful</u>
<u n="586" who="S0432" trans="overlap">the lizards</u>
<u n="587" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="588" who="S0485">but it's it's exquisitely beautiful and it became the best known sculpture sculpture in the ancient world for eight hundred years people came from all over the Mediterranean to go and see this sculpture <pause dur="short"/> we don't have the original but we have endless copies of it</u>
<u n="589" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="590" who="S0485">er and have you see ever seen the Venus de Milo?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0432">no I haven't</u>
<u n="593" who="S0485">that's that's one of them that's a a a draped copy</u>
<u n="594" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh oh wow</u>
<u n="595" who="S0485">er and it's that famous and it was a moment in human history at the beginning of the Hellenistic period which is so where civilisation changed so much and it a way this statue represents that change now I excavated at <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> nineteen mm</u>
<u n="596" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="597" who="S0428">I didn't quite catch that</u>
<u n="598" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="599" who="S0485">and erm <pause dur="short"/> people had looked for two or three hundred years for either for the statue or the special temple in which the statue was displayed because Plinia amongst other things was a guy who died in the Vesuvian earthquake of seventy-nine AD he he describes it describes the temple the temple as a very special temple where you could see the goddess from all angles and so on</u>
<u n="600" who="S0428">oh okay</u>
<u n="601" who="S0485">well we didn't find the statue but we did find the temple</u>
<u n="602" who="S0432">oh wow</u>
<u n="603" who="S0428">ah</u>
<u n="604" who="S0485">people had looked for two hundred years for this temple and we found it and I was the first person to survey it so whenever you see a plan of the <anon type="place"/> temple of Aphrodite it's my plan it's</u>
<u n="605" who="S0432" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="606" who="S0428">I'm gonna hang on I'm gonna write that down and I'm gonna look it up can you?</u>
<u n="607" who="S0485">well the <trunc>b</trunc>book is called Looking for Aphrodite</u>
<u n="608" who="S0428">looking can you write it down on here?</u>
<u n="609" who="S0432">with your name <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="610" who="S0428" trans="overlap">thank you I think you just pull but it's really tight</u>
<u n="611" who="S0432">that's amazing and it's yeah and it's just come out?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0485">it came out last month</u>
<u n="613" who="S0432">oh</u>
<u n="614" who="S0428">wow</u>
<u n="615" who="S0485">it's about my experiences</u>
<u n="616" who="S0432">that moment that you found it</u>
<u n="617" who="S0428">that must have just been yeah incredible</u>
<u n="618" who="S0432">yeah wow</u>
<u n="619" who="S0485">but that wasn't the most important thing I've <trunc>fo</trunc> found either</u>
<u n="620" who="S0432">oh really?</u>
<u n="621" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0485">Looking for Aphrodite and it's published by Markosia</u>
<u n="623" who="S0428">oh if it's not <anon type="place"/> Press</u>
<u n="624" who="S0432">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="625" who="S0428">we're joking we're not too biased</u>
<u n="626" who="S0485">Markosia</u>
<u n="627" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="628" who="S0485">that's a new publisher it's digitally published but it's it's you can buy it you can buy it on Amazon</u>
<u n="629" who="S0428">oh</u>
<u n="630" who="S0485">and that's about sorry the site</u>
<u n="631" who="S0432">the enemy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="632" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="633" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0485">a site is called Knidos</u>
<u n="635" who="S0428">Knidos</u>
<u n="636" who="S0485">sometimes wrongly spelt Knedos like that but it's Knidos is the right name</u>
<u n="637" who="S0428">have you seen the erm the <trunc>cla</trunc> the museum in the classics department here? where they have erm plaster casts of all the ancient sculptures</u>
<u n="638" who="S0485">well I'm sure they'll have</u>
<u n="639" who="S0428">that one it's</u>
<u n="640" who="S0485">the toad somewhere</u>
<u n="641" who="S0428">yeah I'll go in and have a look</u>
<u n="642" who="S0485" trans="overlap">cos every every museum I've ever been into</u>
<u n="643" who="S0428">has it</u>
<u n="644" who="S0485">I was in Rhodes museum a couple of weeks ago and there were two toads there you know? I I collect toads you see</u>
<u n="645" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm beautiful toads</u>
<u n="646" who="S0485">yeah</u>
<u n="647" who="S0432">so are you still looking for the the sculpture or?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0485">no</u>
<u n="649" who="S0432">did you look for it and that's</u>
<u n="650" who="S0485">curiously enough</u>
<u n="651" who="S0428">did someone else find it?</u>
<u n="652" who="S0485">no Praxiteles created two statues of Aphrodite</u>
<u n="653" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="654" who="S0485">of his mistress they were identical except for the fact that one was draped and the other one was nude the nude statue became inordinately famous and lasted at Knidos until it was taken to Istanbul erm the end of the fourth century</u>
<u n="655" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="656" who="S0485">er where it was displayed on a palace there and apparently was burnt in a fire in about four hundred and sixty AD so she lasted about eight hundred years but the draped one er was bought by the island of Kos</u>
<u n="657" who="S0428">oh</u>
<u n="658" who="S0485">just across the water from Knidos</u>
<u n="659" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="660" who="S0485">and that apparently disappeared but I think I've found it</u>
<u n="661" who="S0432"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="662" who="S0428"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="663" who="S0485">two weeks ago I think it's in the in the museum in Rhodes and for some reason or other they say it's fourth century BC and it's certainly got the hair and it's got the the the bum is is Greek rather than Roman so it probably is</u>
<u n="664" who="S0428">wow</u>
<u n="665" who="S0485">er er and it's draped</u>
<u n="666" who="S0432">so that's one to investigate</u>
<u n="667" who="S0485">and it's draped and I think it's the <unclear/> Aphrodite</u>
<u n="668" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">was that one stolen from Kos? was stolen from Kos did you say?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0485">yeah</u>
<u n="670" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">probably German tourists they take everything</u>
<u n="671" who="S0485">no no it it wouldn't have been</u>
<u n="672" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="673" who="S0485">I think it's been a long time ago it was stolen but that that's true they do take a lot from that area</u>
<u n="674" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="675" who="S0485">but you know it's it's amazing but that that's not the most important thing I found either</u>
<u n="676" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="677" who="S0485">I I I I I'm not known for any of that in in in academic circles erm I worked on for thirty years on paleo climate the effects of climatic change on human evolution</u>
<u n="678" who="S0428">ah</u>
<u n="679" who="S0485">that's what I'm best known for</u>
<u n="680" who="S0432">ah</u>
<u n="681" who="S0428">you've you've done a bit of everything</u>
<u n="682" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="683" who="S0432">we should get your autograph</u>
<u n="684" who="S0428">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="685" who="S0485">erm yes</u>
<u n="686" who="S0428">and what erm which parts of the world?</u>
<u n="687" who="S0485">er I was in Gaza for about six years because it's an environmentally extremely sensitive area it's also politically sensitive but it was then but then they were</u>
<u n="688" who="S0428">yeah do you think they could be linked? I don't know</u>
<u n="689" who="S0485">no I don't think so</u>
<u n="690" who="S0428">don't think so</u>
<u n="691" who="S0485">and then I worked in Southern Africa for twenty-five years er the the same latitude south</u>
<u n="692" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="693" who="S0485">to find out human evolution took place in the mid latitudes of the earth not in not in Kenya or Northern America it happened somewhere in the middle erm we didn't know enough in those days about what what climate is like through time</u>
<u n="694" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="695" who="S0485">so we've had to invent brand new ways of looking at the evidence for climatic change</u>
<u n="696" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="697" who="S0485">er going back five million years so I had a team of people mainly didn't have anybody from <anon type="place"/> I had people lots of people from Oxford</u>
<u n="698" who="S0428">and is that something could you tell in the mud like how <trunc>th</trunc> you know when you were saying about all those layers of mud</u>
<u n="699" who="S0485">yes in a way</u>
<u n="700" who="S0428">could you tell the weather in the mud or?</u>
<u n="701" who="S0485">you you can yes but it's it's a very different way of approaching it</u>
<u n="702" who="S0432">I'm here</u>
<u n="703" who="S0485">I had with me a really first class paleobotanist er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I worked for well twenty years together and we invented new ways of looking at what climate was like in the past particularly in this part of the world they'd say oh well what what you do you look at pollen</u>
<u n="704" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="705" who="S0485">and pollen survives can survive millions of years</u>
<u n="706" who="S0432">oh</u>
<u n="707" who="S0485">and if you can identify the pollen grain you can identify the species of tree which is grows form</u>
<u n="708" who="S0428">and that's how they do it?</u>
<u n="709" who="S0485">but it's not that clever but we were using er charcoal which is inert</u>
<u n="710" who="S0428">right</u>
<u n="711" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="712" who="S0485">and provided it isn't destroyed it will survive hundreds of thousands of years</u>
<u n="713" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="714" who="S0485">and we were using electron scanning microscopes</u>
<u n="715" who="S0432">wow</u>
<u n="716" who="S0485">to identify we could get down to subspecies level</u>
<u n="717" who="S0432">wow</u>
<u n="718" who="S0485">and find out therefore what the rainfall was like</u>
<u n="719" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="720" who="S0485">what the temperature was like what the assemblage of trees was like and therefore what animals had lived there</u>
<u n="721" who="S0428">that's amazing isn't it?</u>
<u n="722" who="S0432">that is yeah</u>
<u n="723" who="S0485">yeah and</u>
<u n="724" who="S0432">I think we're in the wrong field</u>
<u n="725" who="S0428">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="726" who="S0485">but</u>
<u n="727" who="S0428">maybe we'll skew it like you know we'll go back to work on Monday and we'll say we were doing language research we're now looking at</u>
<u n="728" who="S0432">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="729" who="S0485">well the the other thing they had a a a a one <trunc>pr</trunc> well I had several research projects at <anon type="place"/> in the school of geography one of them was erm what they call <trunc>pa</trunc>particle history where you could look at an individuals an individual sand grain from a deposit and find out exactly what had happened to that sand grain from its inception to its present form whether it had been in water what kind of water whether whether</u>
<u n="730" who="S0428">wow that's crazy</u>
<u n="731" who="S0432">just one tiny</u>
<u n="732" who="S0485">yeah yeah particle history it was it was fascinating</u>
<u n="733" who="S0428">I think we're going to have to stop this research</u>
<u n="734" who="S0432">yeah it's like the</u>
<u n="735" who="S0485">there you go</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
