<text id="SP9Z">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:42:28</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-06-16</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0684 S0685 S0686</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Car journey between Aberystwyth, Wales and Cornwall</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Education, ghosts</topics>
		<activity></activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0684">
				<exactage>58</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Aberystwyth</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Wales</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>39 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Freelance book editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Catonese -- grew up in Malaysia</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0685">
				<exactage>57</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Nantyglo, Monmouthshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Wales</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Welsh</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Aberystwyth</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Wales</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>34 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>wales</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>wales</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>wales</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Professor</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0686">
				<exactage>22</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Aberystwyth</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Wales</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Neutral British</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Aberystwyth/Manchester</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Wales/England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>18 years/ 4 years (as a student)</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="2" who="S0684">from that system where they just didn't get the <unclear/> to comprehensive comprehensive is seen as being more equitable fairer for people from different backgrounds you know that they would have to mix and you wouldn't have you wouldn't determine people's children's erm outcomes you know like careers at the age of eleven on the basis of one test they did</u>
<u n="3" who="S0686">I don't I don't think that's what grammar schools do though</u>
<u n="4" who="S0684">but they do seem to offer a better standard of education</u>
<u n="5" who="S0686">mm</u>
<u n="6" who="S0684">but they were very</u>
<u n="7" who="S0686" trans="overlap">but I don't think the standard of <trunc>e</trunc> of education is unobtainable for comprehensive schools either</u>
<u n="8" who="S0684">no</u>
<u n="9" who="S0686">I think you can probably look at grammar schools and learn from what they are doing right</u>
<u n="10" who="S0684">but you have a much wider range of abilities in</u>
<u n="11" who="S0686">in a comprehensive?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0684">a comprehensive</u>
<u n="13" who="S0686">yeah but mixed sort of mixed-ability classes can hold sort of both the top and the bottom end of the</u>
<u n="14" who="S0684">can you?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0686">of the</u>
<u n="16" who="S0684">did you not did you not find it a problem?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0686">what mixed ability?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0684">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0686">yeah I did yeah I think I think it's for both ends of the classes</u>
<u n="20" who="S0684" trans="overlap">you wish you could have been in a class where everybody wanted to learn</u>
<u n="21" who="S0686">well yeah both that and sort of a class where erm more people were at the same level so I think yeah a lot erm not to be arrogant but you know there was some classes a didn't find challenging erm</u>
<u n="22" who="S0684">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="23" who="S0686">cos of like the level that they were pitched to and I'm sure</u>
<u n="24" who="S0684">because of the mixed ability in the yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0686" trans="overlap">yeah and I'm sure some people in the class equally found that the classes were you know</u>
<u n="26" who="S0684">too difficult yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0686">above <trunc>their</trunc> yeah too difficult and you know they didn't learn learn as they should have from that so erm and then lots of people are very against like streaming classes though erm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0684">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0686">due to ability</u>
<u n="30" who="S0684">because of their ideological principles</u>
<u n="31" who="S0686" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0685">you have streaming in comprehensive schools</u>
<u n="33" who="S0686">you do for certain subjects</u>
<u n="34" who="S0685">mm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0686">but things like so you do for maths erm from the outset and then science and English later but things like history and geography and things like that never stream</u>
<u n="36" who="S0684">I'm all for streaming <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="37" who="S0686">well I think it would help bring out the best in pupils to have stream classes and you know there there was always the opportunity to move between those classes</u>
<u n="38" who="S0684">oh yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0686">on the due to results it's just a traffic light mum</u>
<u n="40" who="S0684">right</u>
<u n="41" who="S0685">but in effect within comprehensive the distinction became between O level and <trunc>GC</trunc> and CSE qualifications</u>
<u n="42" who="S0684">tell me if it starts to move</u>
<u n="43" who="S0686" trans="overlap">what was the CSE?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0685">it was a <trunc>se</trunc> it was a certificate of secondary education which is not as valid as the O level not as difficult to do</u>
<u n="45" who="S0686">oh is that what?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0684">but GSCEs are half way between the two</u>
<u n="47" who="S0686" trans="overlap">the foundation</u>
<u n="48" who="S0685">yeah GCSEs are midway between what the O level and CSE was</u>
<u n="49" who="S0686">but you did fewer O levels didn't you?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0685">you could do couldn't do more than eight</u>
<u n="51" who="S0686">yeah so</u>
<u n="52" who="S0684">really?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0686">most people do at least ten GCSE's now I think</u>
<u n="54" who="S0685" trans="overlap">mm mm but it means you probably do</u>
<u n="55" who="S0684" trans="overlap">how many did you do?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0686">er</u>
<u n="57" who="S0684">fourteen</u>
<u n="58" who="S0686">fourteen yeah</u>
<u n="59" who="S0685">probably never create a threat so they do</u>
<u n="60" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">why did you do fourteen?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0686">why?</u>
<u n="62" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yes</u>
<u n="63" who="S0686">just ended up doing that</u>
<u n="64" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you did twelve though I think</u>
<u n="65" who="S0686">yeah I think they offered I didn't have I did triple science and that was an option</u>
<u n="66" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah it was for me as well</u>
<u n="67" who="S0686">not an option?</u>
<u n="68" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh yeah it was an option</u>
<u n="69" who="S0684" trans="overlap">you did triple science</u>
<u n="70" who="S0686">no I didn't do it as an option</u>
<u n="71" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh right</u>
<u n="72" who="S0686">I just did triple science in the same time everyone else did double science</u>
<u n="73" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh</u>
<u n="74" who="S0686">that's the way that they used to do it and then erm I think I did art outside</u>
<u n="75" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">oh you did extra maths didn't you?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0686" trans="overlap">outside and then I did further maths as well</u>
<u n="77" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah I did art and music outside though</u>
<u n="78" who="S0686">so yeah I think I probably did music as well so</u>
<u n="79" who="S0684">you did do music?</u>
<u n="80" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">outside?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0686">can't remember whether it was inside or outside</u>
<u n="82" who="S0684">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I was discussing why you didn't get an A star why you missed it by one mark <unclear/></u>
<u n="83" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">when did you see him?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0684">when did I see him? a while back</u>
<u n="85" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="86" who="S0684">I went I must have gone to see him about yeah it must have been <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s parent evening or something</u>
<u n="87" who="S0686">well I know why I didn't get an A star</u>
<u n="88" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh that was ages ago</u>
<u n="89" who="S0684">yeah and then he and then he went off he he was trying to look for something in relation to your GCSE</u>
<u n="90" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh right</u>
<u n="91" who="S0684">and he didn't find it but it doesn't matter now you know he's got what he's got</u>
<u n="92" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah it doesn't matter you know if you think</u>
<u n="93" who="S0684">You wish you should have you could have asked for a remark you would have got eleven then</u>
<u n="94" who="UNKMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">no no</u>
<u n="95" who="S0684">one third of a mark</u>
<u n="96" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah but like you know maybe I should have done but it was yeah it's it's by the by now it hasn't changed anything in my life don't think my life is drastically worse because er <vocal desc="laugh"/> because I didn't get that</u>
<u n="97" who="S0684">yes but it would impress people more</u>
<u n="98" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah could I? I don't think it matters really</u>
<u n="99" who="S0685">what is your rules when you hit erm numbers like sixty-nine?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0686">er sixty-eight is the sort of borderline for a erm a viva erm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0685">right</u>
<u n="102" who="S0686">at degree level now</u>
<u n="103" who="S0684">a viva</u>
<u n="104" who="S0686">well yeah see if</u>
<u n="105" who="S0684">to see whether you go into a first?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0686">well yeah they have they take you for an interview <unclear>first</unclear> to see if you get into a first</u>
<u n="107" who="S0684">so you would always have to go for an interview?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0686">erm otherwise they make the decision without you if you can't go to an interview but they tell you I've got the email about it and they said they'd erm just sent to all the students and they said for borderline students they give you a ring on the evening or the afternoon of the twenty-third and you needed to be there on the morning of the twenty-fourth for the interview</u>
<u n="109" who="S0684">what would they interview you about aspects of the modules?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0686">erm yeah general physics questions</u>
<u n="111" who="S0684">so you might get that?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0686">I doubt it but erm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0684">you're nowhere near sixty-eight?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0686">er I think just far enough away to <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0684">what about <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0686">er he might be but I think he's in Glastonbury at the time so he doesn't particularly want</u>
<u n="117" who="S0684"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so when do your results come out?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0686">they give you barely twelve hours to get to Manchester for a</u>
<u n="119" who="S0684">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0686">interview which is pretty outrageous really</u>
<u n="121" who="S0684">if you were at the other end of the country</u>
<u n="122" who="S0686">yeah what if you're coming from Ireland or and international student</u>
<u n="123" who="S0684">you would stick around <unclear/></u>
<u n="124" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">can you not do it on Skype?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0686">no no you have to be there</u>
<u n="126" who="S0684">why why can't they use Skype?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0686">erm because they're neanderthals</u>
<u n="128" who="S0684">ooh</u>
<u n="129" who="S0686">that's on tape well I don't know it's it's just there's no reason for them not to it's erm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0685">not in this day and age it's like a conference call</u>
<u n="131" who="S0684">is he coming up?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0685">no</u>
<u n="133" who="S0686">no there's cones</u>
<u n="134" who="S0684">did did you see in dad's list of <trunc>psy</trunc> presidents of the psychic society?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0684">that one of the early ones was the professor of physics at Manchester</u>
<u n="137" who="S0686">right I don't think that proves anything <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="138" who="S0684">no it doesn't they all they're the sceptics aren't they? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0685">er he wasn't</u>
<u n="140" who="S0684">he wasn't? he was a professor of physics oh boy but it wasn't called Manchester university what was it called then? something college?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0686">er</u>
<u n="142" who="S0684">when was that? mid-nineteenth century? or late nineteenth century?</u>
<u n="143" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">Owen's college?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0684">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0685">yeah most of them were erm there well it was set up to assess the claims of spiritualist mediums ostensibly but it quickly became a kind of science body looking at non-physical erm phenomenon</u>
<u n="147" who="S0684">so he was he believed in them?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0685">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0684">and he tried to find a scientific basis for them?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0686">erm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0684">presumably</u>
<u n="152" who="S0685">I think they were they were developing the notion of a of a kind of para-science which became <trunc>para</trunc> erm parapsychology basically</u>
<u n="153" who="S0686">I don't think we've ever been in as good a position like in modern science and our understanding of the universe to discount sort of apparent paranormal</u>
<u n="154" who="S0684">say the first half of it again I didn't get it</u>
<u n="155" who="S0686">I don't think we've ever been in as good a position as we are now with our understanding of science and the universe to discount the scientific explanations of the paranormal</u>
<u n="156" who="S0685">well it's interesting you would have had an interesting conversation with Bernard Carr who was <trunc>profess</trunc> the was the president when I was a member he was professor of mathematics at King's</u>
<u n="157" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="158" who="S0685">and he felt that science wouldn't be able to explain it because basically there there were in operation non-physical principles <unclear/> to</u>
<u n="159" who="S0686">I think I've come across a couple of mathematicians erm <pause dur="short"/> er Roger Penrose included</u>
<u n="160" who="S0685">mm</u>
<u n="161" who="S0686">erm who's sort of <pause dur="short"/> erm logic and argument in relation to physics is erm sometimes er disputed by physicists themselves I think coming from coming at it from a mathematical perspective and coming at it from sort of a physics perspective you get quite different viewpoints a lot of the time</u>
<u n="162" who="S0685">yeah and Bernard was er he was an astronomer as well</u>
<u n="163" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="164" who="S0685">erm and he was er at the forefront of what one one of these particles that they were trying to trap deep underground</u>
<u n="165" who="S0686">er neutrinos?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0685">neutrinos</u>
<u n="167" who="S0686">as an astronomer?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0685">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="170" who="S0685">erm so he was he did a lot of work on on</u>
<u n="171" who="S0686">what was his name?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0685">Bernard Carr</u>
<u n="173" who="S0686">Bernard Carr right</u>
<u n="174" who="S0684">how do you know him?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0685">well he was president he did a reference for a grant application I did</u>
<u n="176" who="S0684">did you get it?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0685">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0685">no cos he was I was doing the book on erm you know the paranormal book so I he'd invited me to give a talk on it</u>
<u n="180" who="S0684">did he believe in the paranormal?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0685">as a as a phenomenon yeah but in and in you know he was incredulous to believe that every individual case was therefore true</u>
<u n="182" who="S0686">what do you mean he believed in a phenomenon as in there were things that people couldn't explain</u>
<u n="183" who="S0685">yeah</u>
<u n="184" who="S0686">or did he believe that it could be er for example a psychological sort of a case</u>
<u n="185" who="S0685">oh yeah yeah there's a lot of people like that</u>
<u n="186" who="S0686">some people still think that genuinely was there</u>
<u n="187" who="S0685">yeah yeah I do you know Richard Wiseman?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0686">erm yeah the name rings a bell</u>
<u n="189" who="S0685">he is a prominent erm he he's a psychologist psychiatrist</u>
<u n="190" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="191" who="S0685">er and he did a lot of work to debunk erm <trunc>al</trunc> debunk claims through visions</u>
<u n="192" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="193" who="S0685">and spectres and things like that but you know what the society had built up over say a hundred and twenty years or whatever was this corpus of testimonials and experimental things that you know you couldn't just throw away and say that's just all delusionalism</u>
<u n="194" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0685">er so you know the idea of a society was basically to sift and to try and develop a kind of scientific rigour but you know the biggest problem always was the unrepeatability of the phenomenon</u>
<u n="196" who="S0686">I think it's an interesting field to study as in like why why people do this but I think personally if I were if I were in in that field</u>
<u n="197" who="S0684">why people do what? study this or see these things?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0686" trans="overlap">sorry? why why people se these things and experience them</u>
<u n="199" who="S0684">well dad has studied it to an extent</u>
<u n="200" who="S0686">yeah I think it's an interesting field but like personally I'd be probably like coming come at it from the this is false how can I show that this is false you know what other possible explanation could there be?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0684">a lot of people do that dad does it don't you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0685">well I think all I mean it's not just been a ghost story that I've come across that couldn't have been faked but that's the nature of photography you know it's it's not erm as evidential as we assumed it to be</u>
<u n="203" who="S0686">but even if you see things with your own eyes that's not even a that's no proof either is it?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0685">no no it's not no because you can have hallucinations</u>
<u n="205" who="S0686" trans="overlap">the brain stumbles</u>
<u n="206" who="S0684">it maybe true to you yourself personally</u>
<u n="207" who="S0686">I don't well I don't think it can if you're rational I don't think it can be if you've got to know that you can see thing that aren't real for whatever reason</u>
<u n="208" who="S0685" trans="overlap">no the most persuasive erm test I've come across but again I suppose you could say there's always erm room for deceit was erm one of the members of the SPR erm wrote a letter to the society and it was sealed and given to an independent party before he died</u>
<u n="209" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="210" who="S0685">and then when he died he said that he could communicate the contents of that letter in a in a séance which he did</u>
<u n="211" who="S0684"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0685">and they opened the letter and it was there</u>
<u n="213" who="S0686">right well</u>
<u n="214" who="S0685">so you know again you could say well that's a cunning trick</u>
<u n="215" who="S0686">well I can think of numerous ways into which he could do it erm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0684">can I make it? no</u>
<u n="217" who="S0685">no</u>
<u n="218" who="S0686">as to which you know that could have been faked or to me that's not credible proof</u>
<u n="219" who="S0685">no but the question is I mean you know which scientists have to argue is what would constitute credible proof?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0686">erm <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="221" who="S0684">that could have been a big conspiracy could it?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0685">yeah that could be</u>
<u n="223" who="S0686">well in in accordance with sort of scientific principles repeatability experiment and verification</u>
<u n="224" who="S0685">but you can't you know</u>
<u n="225" who="S0686">you can't prove anything but you can repeat it a thousand times and say I've done this a thousand times and it gets the same result a thousand times</u>
<u n="226" who="S0684">but a lot of phenomena don't happen like that</u>
<u n="227" who="S0686">well that <trunc>psy</trunc>psychic or <trunc>psyc</trunc> you know these paranormal phenomena don't but scientific phenomena do</u>
<u n="228" who="S0685">yeah that's what they think that you know the argument was that you couldn't if you applied standard models of of physics or whatever to paranormal it would it would get you nowhere</u>
<u n="229" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0685">so the society basically was trying to come up with erm a parascience I mean that's what you could call it a pseudoscience if you like</u>
<u n="231" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0685">erm in that would would spit the subject of it's enquiry which is in a sense what physics does isn't it? physics grows out of the nature of the object it's scrutinising</u>
<u n="233" who="S0686">yes and no physics I think physics erm tries to find the most the most general case have you ever heard of erm Occam's razor?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0685">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0686">so Occam's razor is sort of taking erm you have two theories erm that produce exactly the same result erm but one of them requires like the <unclear/> of your axiom for the other and it's like is objectively simpler then the simpler one is truer in a sense rem so it's about you know if you can explain it simply erm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0685">mm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0686">or explain it in a really convoluted way why would you explain it in a really convoluted way so to me like having another branch of science that explains this rate of things that <trunc>ex</trunc> existed in our own universe and just come by the general laws at work and pretty much all circumstances so far erm why would he do that so?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0685">mm</u>
<u n="239" who="S0686">I'm not entirely convinced that creating a new branch of science is really the erm the best way to explain it if it is indeed explainable beyond sort of our own what goes on in our minds</u>
<u n="240" who="S0685">mm</u>
<u n="241" who="S0684">how do you explain things like that poltergeist thing we saw the one with the</u>
<u n="242" who="S0685">what the Enfield?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0684">the Enfield yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0685">erm I don't know I mean the the I think it's a mixed bag that one of</u>
<u n="245" who="S0686">how many people actually saw</u>
<u n="246" who="S0685">oh loads</u>
<u n="247" who="S0686">this poltergeist racing across the room</u>
<u n="248" who="S0685">yeah loads</u>
<u n="249" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="250" who="S0685">you know you had er</u>
<u n="251" who="S0686">who were they?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0685">the two main er guys were Maurice Grosse and a guy Lion Treyfeld they're on the</u>
<u n="253" who="S0684"><unclear/> the side again</u>
<u n="254" who="S0685">er Maurice was er an ex RAF pilot</u>
<u n="255" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="256" who="S0685">bit of a Bill basically</u>
<u n="257" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="258" who="S0685">and an engineer and erm</u>
<u n="259" who="S0684">we've lost time with all the delays</u>
<u n="260" who="S0685">oh it's alright it's <unclear/> talking</u>
<u n="261" who="S0684">sorry</u>
<u n="262" who="S0685">er if you'd stop talking we get there quicker</u>
<u n="263" who="S0684">no no it's the delay</u>
<u n="264" who="S0685">erm Guy was erm a Cambridge graduate in History and I knew them because I had breakfast with them</u>
<u n="265" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="266" who="S0685">at the conferences and you know if you had wanted the sort of the two people who were had head screwed on you know? they weren't kind of A one nutters</u>
<u n="267" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0685">and had had a lot of experience of these things erm I mean what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to tell me about you know water would be you know slung at him it was it was quite extraordinary and it <unclear/> boiled egg <vocal desc="laugh"/> but erm when the when they start they were very reluctant to to investigate it because erm the circumstances was it was a council house in Enfield</u>
<u n="269" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0685">and er it was known that the mother was a single mother with about four <trunc>chil</trunc> four young children</u>
<u n="271" who="S0686">yeah okay</u>
<u n="272" who="S0685">one girl was going through puberty that might actually be quite crucial to it erm and some people said oh well what they were trying to do then is to get out of the house so the council would give them a better house</u>
<u n="273" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="274" who="S0685">so they they were sort of suppositions of <trunc>no</trunc> you know a kind of strange motivation</u>
<u n="275" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0685">erm but the SPR were only got involved much later on er</u>
<u n="277" who="S0686">how how how long were these sort of goings on</u>
<u n="278" who="S0685">it was going on for several months</u>
<u n="279" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="280" who="S0685">and it was sort of consistency and</u>
<u n="281" who="S0686">what a third party presumably came into the house</u>
<u n="282" who="S0685">yeah a policeman came in</u>
<u n="283" who="S0686">and what saw?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0685">and yeah and there there were police reports that said you know the policeman and a policewomen so they had corroborated reports erm said a chair physically you know those big arm chairs</u>
<u n="285" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0685">came at them erm and no you know nobody around pushing it just came at them</u>
<u n="287" who="S0686">mm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0685">and erm and another one got hit in the <trunc>he</trunc> er head quite erm hard by a Lego brick</u>
<u n="289" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="290" who="S0685">erm that just sort of appeared and hit him</u>
<u n="291" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0685">and there were things like matchboxes would catch fire in drawers erm there were poolings of water where there shouldn't have been there were lots of these kind of odd phenomenon that was taking place erm the girls er were seen to levitate erm a book in one in their bedroom mysteriously appeared in the bedroom in the house next door</u>
<u n="293" who="S0686">a book?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0685">a book</u>
<u n="295" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="296" who="S0685">erm so that what that was <trunc>ba</trunc> what was technically called a porting where an object would disappear from one realm and appear in another so they brought <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in m</u>
<u n="297" who="S0686"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0685"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came later because he was the more sceptical of both of them but he thought that this was a the kids were actually just playing tricks</u>
<u n="299" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0685">as kids you know do erm but then when they got there erm you know they they had all it was all the kind of hallmarks you know the typical kind of bookcases where you know camera batteries ensemble erm er simply didn't work you know they they all all the power drained out of them even though they had powered them all up before they got there</u>
<u n="301" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0686">er tape recorders would suddenly switch off and not be able to switch back on erm it was just you know if you put in the in his paper on this he had the original tape recorder and the original tape and he played it and within two minutes it <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> so erm anyway it became increasingly centred upon the girl erm who they believed was possessed by a guy called Bill</u>
<u n="303" who="S0686">right what what basis did they have for this?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0685">er because he spoke to her</u>
<u n="305" who="S0686">spoke through her</u>
<u n="306" who="S0685">through her</u>
<u n="307" who="S0686">right okay</u>
<u n="308" who="S0685">erm in a voice that wasn't hers</u>
<u n="309" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="310" who="S0685">and so the explanation for that is that they got eventually <unclear/> and it says well probably what she is using we do actually have two larynxes one which actually doesn't get used</u>
<u n="311" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="312" who="S0685">which erm so which you ventriloquists use so you you don't actually open your mouth but sounds can come out so when she was speaking when Bill was speaking through her she er she had this kind of rough right <trunc>ra</trunc> this kind of east end London accent and he was you know swear like a trooper he was quite a nasty bloke</u>
<u n="313" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="314" who="S0685">and he was basically telling everyone to get out of his house erm and they did find out that there was someone in in the house called Bill</u>
<u n="315" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="316" who="S0685">and er he told them that he <trunc>wo</trunc> he died in a chair and they found out that that was true as well</u>
<u n="317" who="S0684">gosh</u>
<u n="318" who="S0685">erm and you know he said he was he was basically the one who was <trunc>be</trunc>behind it all</u>
<u n="319" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="320" who="S0685">erm but exorcism didn't work in this case and the phenomenon simply died out but it went on for over a year</u>
<u n="321" who="S0686">I do just think there's same you know some things which I can't immediately think of an explanation for especially when you to things like <trunc>a</trunc> large objects that really</u>
<u n="322" who="S0685">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0686">erm you know conceivably someone could throw a Lego brick at someone quite hard and not you know be in the room erm armchairs moving you know for a third party as well you know</u>
<u n="324" who="S0685">yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0686"><unclear/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0685">well they had you know the</u>
<u n="327" who="S0686">professionals who come in come in and be sceptical about</u>
<u n="328" who="S0685">yeah I mean they had to write a police report of what happened basically you know so they they had a a motivation of integrity and I think sometime the girls would play up you know they they they'd kind of do things that worked with the ghost but the girls are actually very scared by this</u>
<u n="329" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0685">erm but it was you now it it's an interesting thing but more interesting I think</u>
<u n="331" who="S0686">but what do you what do you think?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0685">I don't know I mean I I think <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0684">is it?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0686">no you should have gone on the <unclear/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0684">yeah no when when they indicated left I thought they were going to turn left</u>
<u n="336" who="S0686">well they they <unclear/> to turn left</u>
<u n="337" who="S0684">there was as pint there was a lay-by to pull up that was a bit you know I would have gone but because it was turning left I thought you know I won't I won't overtake but I confused the signal</u>
<u n="338" who="S0685">no I don't I don't know what I make of it really erm because the character of Bill I mean this is a thirteen-year-old girl what Bill was saying through her was very adult so either you know there is some kind of very intriguing multiple personality disorder taking place there</u>
<u n="339" who="S0686">which is not beyond the realms of possibility</u>
<u n="340" who="S0685">no it's not</u>
<u n="341" who="S0686">people with Tourette's you know</u>
<u n="342" who="S0685">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0686">erm schizophrenia</u>
<u n="344" who="S0685">yeah erm and there there's a tendency for poltergeist to attract themselves to erm <pause dur="short"/> to young people going through puberty</u>
<u n="345" who="S0686">that's that's odd</u>
<u n="346" who="S0685">well it might be that</u>
<u n="347" who="S0686"><unclear/> correlation</u>
<u n="348" who="S0685">yeah there might be a kind of energy so for example you might say <pause dur="short"/> er it's <unclear/> like what what</u>
<u n="349" who="S0686">what do you mean by this I find sort of quite unscientific</u>
<u n="350" who="S0685">yeah some some people would say we it's actually not a ghost it is actually the girl doing it herself telekinetically that she's actually moving objects around herself via a kind of force</u>
<u n="351" who="S0684" trans="overlap">but that would probably not believe in telekinesis</u>
<u n="352" who="S0686">I I don't er</u>
<u n="353" who="S0684">but could could it be that there is an explanation we what you call a scientific explanation for these things erm that we haven't discovered yet</u>
<u n="354" who="S0686">erm it seem unlikely because you talk about these things which you haven't discovered yet and you may use historical examples like erm you know Einstein didn't you know <unclear/> it's because he and discovered you know someone hadn't discovered something but I think we're at a point now they didn't back then they knew that they didn't know a lot about the universe it builds up <unclear/> like explain sort of <unclear/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0684">yeah no</u>
<u n="356" who="S0686">erm so in terms of</u>
<u n="357" who="S0684"><unclear/></u>
<u n="358" who="S0686">in terms of phenomenon sort of explaining sort of <unclear/> explaining erm electric and magnetic fields I don't see any reason cos that's what you know it takes to be erased you know things like camera batteries to be drained immediately and things like that but it sounds like erm the presence of a large electric <trunc>electr</trunc> electromagnetic area</u>
<u n="359" who="S0684">well it could but I suppose again the problem there is what it it's cause</u>
<u n="360" who="S0686">yeah absolutely I don't I don't know you know that there should be necessarily a particular</u>
<u n="361" who="S0684">are you going out</u>
<u n="362" who="S0684">no <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0685">erm yeah the most intriguing one I've come across is what was callused a soul experiment which was done over three years erm and that was a group of so called mediums who met in school which is a place up in I think it was in London and they actively invited erm scientists</u>
<u n="364" who="S0684">oh close</u>
<u n="365" who="S0685">erm</u>
<u n="366" who="S0686">GPS</u>
<u n="367" who="S0684">psychologists erm conjurers who are always invited with the SPR to come to do séances</u>
<u n="368" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="369" who="S0684">cos scientists were often duped whereas conjurers could see sleight of hand</u>
<u n="370" who="S0686">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0684">erm that was the case do you know William do you know William Cooks?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0686">erm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0684">nineteenth-century scientist who invented the cathode ray tube</u>
<u n="374" who="S0686">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0684">erm he was thoroughly convinced of it and he used to have séances in his house</u>
<u n="376" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="377" who="S0684">erm and there was a manifestation of this young woman erm who was a you know a physical manifestation she could be touched and that happened over three years</u>
<u n="378" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="379" who="S0684">but I mean that's another story that was interesting because he was erm he was one of the most distinguished physicists of his day</u>
<u n="380" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0684">erm and he had anyway had big <unclear/> Faraday</u>
<u n="382" who="S0686"><unclear/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0684">really? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0684">there's a dramatisation of the Enfield haunting on now TV if you want to see it</u>
<u n="386" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="387" who="S0685">yeah we should watch that actually</u>
<u n="388" who="S0684">it's Matthew Macfadyen and Timothy Spall it's very good</u>
<u n="389" who="S0685">Guy didn't like it at all he thought it was far too erm</u>
<u n="390" who="S0686">sensationalist</u>
<u n="391" who="S0684"><unclear/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0685">no he thought it it simply wasn't true to the intensity of what was taking place</u>
<u n="393" who="S0684">what it was less intense?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0685">no it was more intense</u>
<u n="395" who="S0684">ah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0685">than that anyway the Scole experiment was erm it was conducted in the cellar and erm Richard Wiseman who is actually an <trunc>a</trunc> a a a a sceptic</u>
<u n="397" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="398" who="S0685">a very very bright man he was invited to it as well so they got you know all the people who are likely to be able to defame them and see you know the tricks being done and erm the protocols around that were probably the most intense that have ever been established for</u>
<u n="399" who="S0686">when when was this?</u>
<u n="400" who="S0685">nineteen nineties</u>
<u n="401" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="402" who="S0685">and erm they had a whole range of things the they would have a lot of it was done through trances erm in other words people communicated to the other side so called through through a trance but the voices were what were called remote voice manifestations so in other words other rather than coming through the mouth of the medium these voices came from different parts of the room</u>
<u n="403" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="404" who="S0685">erm and so the experiment was to ask for evidence irrefutable evidence and that was what the Scole experiment was designed to do</u>
<u n="405" who="S0686">what what what sort of monitor what did they set up in the room?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0685">erm</u>
<u n="407" who="S0686">heat camera presumably?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0685">there were heat cameras but it had to be done in the dark</u>
<u n="409" who="S0686">why?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0685">erm because those on the other side <unclear/> things particularly where they were transferring in transferring images they wouldn't be able to do it now that's always been the major criticism of the Scole experiment</u>
<u n="411" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0685">that it was done in the dark although you know the the the roots</u>
<u n="413" who="S0686" trans="overlap">it is slightly convenient isn't it?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0685">well it does I mean it that that's the bit that I find although you know Richard Wiseman who is also a conjurer</u>
<u n="415" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="416" who="S0685"><unclear/> he did a thorough examination of the room</u>
<u n="417" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="418" who="S0685">and there were no secret you know there were no kind of projectors or anything left you know in there so that that that was as watertight as you could possibly be</u>
<u n="419" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0685">short of doing it in a <unclear/> or something like that you wouldn't be able to do it erm and he doesn't have an explanation for it I mean he doesn't</u>
<u n="421" who="S0686">well they heard these voices?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0685">they <trunc>hea</trunc> they all</u>
<u n="423" who="S0686">did they see anything?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0685">erm they saw lights</u>
<u n="425" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="426" who="S0685">which were little orbs of light which would erm be hovering in the room and you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> first said oh god you know? that's fibre optics or something you know</u>
<u n="427" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0685">but they weren't because he said you know he could erm speak to a light and say come to my hand and it would and it would rest in his hand it would have no weight</u>
<u n="429" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="430" who="S0685">and then it would pass through his hand and then through the table into the floor and that happened on lots of <trunc>oc</trunc> on lots of occasions</u>
<u n="431" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="432" who="S0685">erm there were objects</u>
<u n="433" who="S0686">but how many times did they did do this?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0685">oh loads over three years</u>
<u n="435" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="436" who="S0685">there were many of these experiments with lots of different people erm</u>
<u n="437" who="S0686">what are they called the Scole experiments?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0685">the Scole experiments?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="440" who="S0685">and then they were asking so these these lights erm you know as I said would would come they would they would be at the bidding of the people who were sitting around it</u>
<u n="441" who="S0686">okay I'm <trunc>o</trunc> I'm still sceptical but erm</u>
<u n="442" who="S0685">well I I wasn't there I mean I mean just think if you were there what would you make of it?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0686" trans="overlap">yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="444" who="S0685">you know</u>
<u n="445" who="S0686">did they have like erm electric and magnetic field detectors?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0685">I don't know what what the paraphernalia was there but</u>
<u n="447" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="448" who="S0685">erm</u>
<u n="449" who="S0686">cos you you'd have thought well I'd have thought I I was setting up that experiment I'd want to know everything about what was going on in that room erm I'd want I'd want a heat map I'd want an electric field map I'd want a magnetic field map erm</u>
<u n="450" who="S0685" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0686">erm I'd want a sound map you know I'd want</u>
<u n="452" who="S0685">yeah they they they had er video cameras going all the time in the dark</u>
<u n="453" who="S0686">what did they pick up?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0685">er lights</u>
<u n="455" who="S0686">they the same lights</u>
<u n="456" who="S0685">not the same lights no shapes geometries</u>
<u n="457" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="458" who="S0685">erm were appearing on them er later on they had er unprocessed film in sealed boxes which had been sealed not by the erm the mediums but by the experiment the people who were observing the experiment</u>
<u n="459" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="460" who="S0685">and when they processed them er they had writing and images on them erm but one of the most remarkable ones was this erm it was dark and then they heard this thump on the table and there was this copy of the Daily Mirror form nineteen forty-one absolutely pristine</u>
<u n="461" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="462" who="S0685">and of course people thought it's just one of those reprints so they actually took it to an analyst and said no this is actually paper that was printed in nineteen forty-one the ink is from nineteen forty-one but there was no yellowing or anything</u>
<u n="463" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="464" who="S0685">I mean I suppose the supposition was that that's a kind of temporal as well as spatial transference</u>
<u n="465" who="S0686">mm okay</u>
<u n="466" who="S0685">and they did was just the sheer weight of evidence that was so compelling to some people I suppose</u>
<u n="467" who="S0684">what do you think?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0685">I don't know</u>
<u n="469" who="S0686">I think I'd want to do a bit more reading into it but</u>
<u n="470" who="S0684">I'm sure there's a lot on the internet</u>
<u n="471" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="472" who="S0685">oh there is and there there was erm the society actually produced it's own erm review of it which is that thick erm <pause dur="short"/> but I I suppose where I parted company which is why I left company with the society was that I felt it would was becoming</u>
<u n="473" who="S0684"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="474" who="S0685"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0684"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0685">it it was enthusiastic about proving things than disproving things</u>
<u n="477" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="478" who="S0685">and I know</u>
<u n="479" who="S0686">yeah it's very dangerous when you have a</u>
<u n="480" who="S0685" trans="overlap">it is and the thing that</u>
<u n="481" who="S0686">agenda</u>
<u n="482" who="S0685">sealed it for me cos I was you know we were talking about phenomenon I said have we ever considered demon possession and they said oh no demons don't exist I thought right I can see where you're coming from that's your presupposition</u>
<u n="483" who="S0684"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="484" who="S0685"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so I thought I don't want any more of this this is just you know this is just going nowhere</u>
<u n="485" who="S0686">well it's it's bad science to cos obviously every <trunc>scien</trunc>scientist comes at it with with a bias or an expectation but you know for you know for the society to have a an agenda is</u>
<u n="486" who="S0685">well I think it was adrift to to erm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="488" who="S0685">one or two individuals I think it's probably quite different now and I and I sort of I had half in mind at one point to get back in contact with them but erm erm I remember when I went up to the erm when I did that London tour in the Serpentine a couple of months ago</u>
<u n="489" who="S0686">okay</u>
<u n="490" who="S0685">we went I went back to the er college of psychic studies which is erm really where a lot of of I mean the college of psychic science studies was the sort of a parallel to the society of psychical research</u>
<u n="491" who="S0686">mm</u>
<u n="492" who="S0685">and you talked you know you you get lots of kind of strange people turning up to these things erm and you know begin to realise that there there there's a strong element of credulity up there and it it you know there are there were some interesting papers on erm psychology you know like the things that you're saying about psychological explanations</u>
<u n="493" who="S0686">well the the human mind it's extraordinarily powerful in how it remembers things</u>
<u n="494" who="S0685">yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0686">as well as what we see and you know erm they've done you know I think it's pretty they've done studies about you know the way that we remember events and that we change what we remember you know even details of a of a car or something because I know that that's particularly erm relevant in erm in court cases</u>
<u n="496" who="S0684">mm</u>
<u n="497" who="S0686">for example where they prove that you know an eyewitness</u>
<u n="498" who="S0684">mm</u>
<u n="499" who="S0686">doesn't always you know even if they're convinced about that what they saw is not always what was there erm</u>
<u n="500" who="S0684">that's that's</u>
<u n="501" who="S0686">the power of suggestion is always very erm</u>
<u n="502" who="S0684">that's remembering I so that's memory but</u>
<u n="503" who="S0686">well memories change even if you think you saw something you know it's the way that you remember it changes</u>
<u n="504" who="S0684">yeah yeah sure but at the time you experience what you think is a paranormal phenomenon you must believe that at the time</u>
<u n="505" who="S0686">yeah sure I I don't I don't doubt that the power of what you believe is</u>
<u n="506" who="S0684" trans="overlap"><trunc>where</trunc> you know what what colour dress somebody was wearing you might not have paid much attention to it because it is a different kind of experience isn't it?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0686">it is but at the same time you know your your brain can trick you into seeing things that aren't there hearing things that aren't there that you know that's well documented in you know especially people who have you you hear voices for examples you know you are actually hearing things that aren't there</u>
<u n="508" who="S0685">but what was interesting with the Scole experiment was that the people they were contacting said they were scientists</u>
<u n="509" who="S0686">right</u>
<u n="510" who="S0685">er that they'd been scientist in the previous life and they were communicating designs erm for something called what was it called? a transdimensional communicator I thought this is Star Trek I mean no scientist would ever call something a transdimensional communicator and if you look at the design basically it's a series of germanium transistors erm</u>
<u n="511" who="S0686">oh right</u>
<u n="512" who="S0685">just a little bit more kind of sophisticated than a <unclear/> you know the sort of thing that Mark Honey would have put put together</u>
<u n="513" who="S0684">well maybe there was some that type of <unclear/> at the time</u>
<u n="514" who="S0685">well maybe yeah but I mean</u>
<u n="515" who="S0686">but you wouldn't have called it that it sounds daft</u>
<u n="516" who="S0684"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="517" who="S0686">that sounds one of the most unconvincing things about the whole</u>
<u n="518" who="S0685">yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0684">but why would they have given it a <trunc>co</trunc> an unconvincing name? if they if they is somebody was pulling</u>
<u n="520" who="S0686" trans="overlap">if someone yeah someone is pulling the wool over someone's eyes you wouldn't it wouldn't have been a scientist and they and they've had called it something <unclear/> sounds likely</u>
<u n="521" who="S0685">well it's something that does appear to have some sort of science kudos about it and and mystique you know mystique is very important in all of this</u>
<u n="522" who="S0684">the children told me that that that that a bit more <unclear/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0686">well exactly and more than a couple of germanium transistors</u>
<u n="524" who="S0684">germanium transistors</u>
<u n="525" who="S0685">well it's a thing that you put in blood clots</u>
<u n="526" who="S0684">not in your garden</u>
<u n="527" who="S0685">no</u>
<u n="528" who="S0686" trans="overlap">it was obviously someone with a very very basic <unclear/></u>
<u n="529" who="S0685" trans="overlap"><unclear/> effects <unclear/> boxes of germanium transistors and they gave off a certain</u>
<u n="530" who="S0684">why is it called germanium?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0686">because it's the main metal there</u>
<u n="532" who="S0685" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> but it it's that makes for a fascinating read</u>
<u n="533" who="S0686">yeah I will I will be reading it for fun I think it's interesting if only to</u>
<u n="534" who="S0685">I mean this society wasn't that uncritical of it you know it it it didn't feel as they felt that the the insistence on darkness was suspicious</u>
<u n="535" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0684">who who carried it out?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0685">erm there were just a husband and wife medium team and they they they <trunc>me</trunc></u>
<u n="538" who="S0684">they did the Scole experiment?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0685">no I mean they had lots of other people er scientists and erm parapsychologist and others who were coming to</u>
<u n="540" who="S0686">to me the most likely explanation that it was a massive hoax very clever but</u>
<u n="541" who="S0685">well if it is erm and I've talked to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> about this he said he couldn't get to the bottom I mean he knew he's a conjurer I mean he you know he'd been he's someone who talks to you know David Copperfield and others you know about how they do their illusions</u>
<u n="542" who="S0686">right well I I I've watched David Copperfield and erm who is the other one? David Blaine and people like that do some of the things that they do and I can't figure out how they do it</u>
<u n="543" who="S0685" trans="overlap">mm mm no I've seen</u>
<u n="544" who="S0686">but I don't think it's anything magical or anything like that</u>
<u n="545" who="S0685">no no no it's not I mean I it's it's it's</u>
<u n="546" who="S0684">they don't claim that</u>
<u n="547" who="S0685">no it's it's very it's very clever I think Youtube videos you can slow em down and you can't tell how they do it</u>
<u n="548" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="549" who="S0685">erm but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was absolutely he said you know he doesn't believe in it but he can't explain it</u>
<u n="550" who="S0686">yeah right I think that's a perfectly valid position er <pause dur="long"/> I do I do believe that there is a side to the explanation <unclear/> out</u>
<u n="551" who="S0685">the odd thing was in the nineteenth century these bands of people who would talk to you form the other side they were all artists now they're all scientists</u>
<u n="552" who="S0686">yeah</u>
<u n="553" who="S0684">that is that is a bit telling</u>
<u n="554" who="S0685">no well it is might be a bit telling but of course in those in the nineteenth century what the artists would do is communicate picture instant pictures <pause dur="long"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
