<text id="SPHU">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:43:00</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-02-24</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>4</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0104 S0167 S0376 S0377</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Work, colleagues, family, daily activities, pets, doctors, parties, friends, neighbours, future plans</topics>
		<activity>Chatting over coffee</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0104">
				<exactage>49</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kemsing, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Kent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Ashford, Kent</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Registered general nurse</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0167">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Ashford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South East/Kent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Romney Marsh, Kent</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Copywriter</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0376">
				<exactage>47</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Farnborough, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South East England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dymchurch</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 yrs 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>care assistant</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0377">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Ashford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dymchurch</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>23 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Carer</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0104">right so that's recording again got a bit muddled up there</u>
<u n="2" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0376">no so I don't see a lot of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> either I only really see her in passing</u>
<u n="4" who="S0104">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0376">erm she's a busy girl isn't she?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0104">I'm I'm I would be surprised if she was organised with things</u>
<u n="7" who="S0377">she must have her she had or having? she must have her interview coming up soon</u>
<u n="8" who="S0104">yeah March some time I can't remember or erm <pause dur="short"/> cos I said to her have a word with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos she's you know but whether she has or not I don't know cos she must see him on Thursday afternoons</u>
<u n="9" who="S0377">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0104">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0376">she jump up here again</u>
<u n="12" who="S0104">yeah she loves you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0376">come here no she's after my jumper</u>
<u n="14" who="S0104">you think she can smell your dogs?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0376">erm no I don't think so cos the dogs don't come on the sofa at my house anymore do they? she might be able to smell the guineas</u>
<u n="16" who="S0104">mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0376">cos I've probably picked a guinea pig up</u>
<u n="18" who="S0104" trans="overlap">mm mm I dunno where <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>'s gone <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0376">probably gone to find a nice pile of towels somewhere</u>
<u n="20" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0104">ah honestly there's a load of towels and tea towels</u>
<u n="22" who="S0377">are you as specific with your towels at home as you are at work?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0376">I bet she is</u>
<u n="24" who="S0104">my towels are you should see the top shelf is all sheets and they're all chucked up higgledy piggledy and the bottom of the the shelf down in the bathroom is towels and they're perfect and ah</u>
<u n="25" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0104">I do have a towel obsession I don't know why</u>
<u n="27" who="S0377"><unclear/> perhaps the <trunc>was</trunc>washing it and <trunc>s</trunc> you must be busy still</u>
<u n="28" who="S0104">I barely did yeah I hardly had any time to do washing yesterday</u>
<u n="29" who="S0377">it's a bit serious when you've not kept up with your washing</u>
<u n="30" who="S0104">we did have it fairly we we did well for them we only had two to put to bed last night and there was some washing but not loads and anyway with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he likes a wash</u>
<u n="31" who="S0376">yeah that's if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> lets him</u>
<u n="32" who="S0377">I know we could tell</u>
<u n="33" who="S0376">she's a bit obsessed with washing</u>
<u n="34" who="S0377">we could tell that they'd had a bit of an obsessive war the other week cos there was washing all over the place and it was all in the wrong place and I was just</u>
<u n="35" who="S0376">oh god</u>
<u n="36" who="S0104"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was talking about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> last night and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said well on Saturday</u>
<u n="37" who="S0376">I think it's my deodorant</u>
<u n="38" who="S0104">on Saturday she just</u>
<u n="39" who="S0376">he's going for my armpit sorry to interrupt but</u>
<u n="40" who="S0104">she's weird with you she's not weird like that with anybody else on Saturday she and she said yes <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you told me all this before</u>
<u n="41" who="S0377"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0104">he went no this Saturday just gone</u>
<u n="43" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0377">I just can't just the two going at the thought of going in after the two of them it's just like oh my god</u>
<u n="45" who="S0104">I thought that once <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> refused to work with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos she was so horrible to him</u>
<u n="46" who="S0377">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0376">why's she putting her nose in my armpit?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0104">mm weird weird cat</u>
<u n="49" who="S0376">must be my deodorant</u>
<u n="50" who="S0104">here she comes she'll have to go in the garden or she might be behind <unclear/> where's she gone? she must have washed her car off she was erm <trunc>spr</trunc> she went I told you didn't I? yesterday morning she was taking me to work</u>
<u n="51" who="S0376">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0104">that big puddle on the front there she had her front wheels in it cos she was turning round she slammed it in to reverse and rammed on the accelerator and it just went and covered the whole car couldn't see out of any of the windows</u>
<u n="53" who="S0376">oh no</u>
<u n="54" who="S0104">it was like we'd been on a rally rally track</u>
<u n="55" who="S0376">oh god</u>
<u n="56" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0376">oh dear</u>
<u n="58" who="S0104">and it was still like it when she picked me up last night</u>
<u n="59" who="S0377">it's alright I'm used to it the whole the whole <unclear/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0104" trans="overlap">well yeah our our drive is <trunc>no</trunc> I know our drive is nothing to yours I wouldn't even try and compete <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0376">you need like a dingy to get to your house at times innit?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0377">it hasn't gone down the last few days actually</u>
<u n="63" who="S0104">what you need is everybody</u>
<u n="64" who="S0376">it's hardcore</u>
<u n="65" who="S0377">hardcore</u>
<u n="66" who="S0104">fill that hole</u>
<u n="67" who="S0377">yeah but you can't fill the hole cos there's a drain it's just going to go down the drain it's not the water's not going to go</u>
<u n="68" who="S0376">there's a big drain in the middle of it?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0377">there's a drain yeah there's two drains either end</u>
<u n="70" who="S0167">hello</u>
<u n="71" who="S0104">hello</u>
<u n="72" who="S0377">hello</u>
<u n="73" who="S0167">hi hello</u>
<u n="74" who="S0377">hello</u>
<u n="75" who="S0167">did you make me one?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0104">no</u>
<u n="77" who="S0167">ah you knew I was home soon</u>
<u n="78" who="S0104">did you erm did you get your ticket?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="80" who="S0104">that's good</u>
<u n="81" who="S0167">it was weird because it said when I was filling in the application form she said oh we don't pay for higher speed I thought oh okay fair enough it just makes it a bit longer</u>
<u n="82" who="S0104">yeah just pay four quid for an upgrade</u>
<u n="83" who="S0167">well I thought oh okay whatever and then erm I went I had to hand in the form and then I had to wait for an hour and <trunc>haf</trunc> no three quarters of a hour downstairs while this other woman like got my warrant ready</u>
<u n="84" who="S0104">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0167">then I had to go to this warrant she wrote in my warrant non high speed erm so I thought ah okay fair enough so I just anyway went to the station to exchange it for a ticket and he just gave me a high speed ticket any route permitted and told me to get on the high speed train</u>
<u n="86" who="S0104">ah he must have liked the look of you</u>
<u n="87" who="S0376">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0167">I don't think he realised I don't think they even think about giving you a high speed tickets now I don't think they even it's the only one that passes there he just typed in probably <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> and that's the first one that came up</u>
<u n="89" who="S0104">yeah well that's good then anyway</u>
<u n="90" who="S0376">that was handy</u>
<u n="91" who="S0167">I didn't just didn't say anything</u>
<u n="92" who="S0104">cos you could have paid a little bit extra I think it's four quid each way for an upgrade</u>
<u n="93" who="S0167">yeah it's four quid but I just thought I'll see what happens I won't make a fuss and I'll see what happens and I thought that might happen so</u>
<u n="94" who="S0104">oh excellent</u>
<u n="95" who="S0167">good</u>
<u n="96" who="S0104">so have you got all your time your times do you have to book seats or anything on the?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0167">no I've just got a standard ticket open return</u>
<u n="98" who="S0104">because if it's one of those one from King's Cross up to the north east you have to book a seat certainly you</u>
<u n="99" who="S0167">well he didn't book me a seat so</u>
<u n="100" who="S0104">oh okay</u>
<u n="101" who="S0167">he said it's an open ticket so yeah that's all</u>
<u n="102" who="S0104">oh that would've been a bummer if you'd had to go to Charing Cross cos</u>
<u n="103" who="S0167">I know I was thinking that and then and then she looked up timetables for me she said oh you get on the eight forty-three and I thought well that's a high speed train but I just thought okay didn't say anything</u>
<u n="104" who="S0104" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0167">erm yeah it just says ten o'clock leave London King's Cross and get on the Aberdeen service to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0104">mm</u>
<u n="107" who="S0167">it just says <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0104">do you know where you're going when you get off?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0167">no it just says get the train to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0104">yeah well</u>
<u n="111" who="S0167">oh <trunc>wa</trunc> yeah when I get off I leave at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0104">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0167">and then I get on erm another one to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0104">yeah but when you get off at <anon type="place"/> do you know have you got a?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0167">oh I have to get a taxi they're putting twenty pounds in my account for a taxi</u>
<u n="116" who="S0104">oh I say</u>
<u n="117" who="S0376" trans="overlap">oh that's nice</u>
<u n="118" who="S0104">I'm gonna go on Jobseekers</u>
<u n="119" who="S0377">well I had one in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0104">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0377">and one here</u>
<u n="122" who="S0376">OL <unclear/> do you think they'd let us have days out?</u>
<u n="123" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0167">well I wish they'd given it to me in cash because erm it's annoying</u>
<u n="125" who="S0104">oh</u>
<u n="126" who="S0167">I have to get the cash out oh yeah here's your money by the way mum</u>
<u n="127" who="S0104">what money?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0167">for your clothes</u>
<u n="129" who="S0104">no you can keep that</u>
<u n="130" who="S0167">oh thanks mum</u>
<u n="131" who="S0104"><unclear/> place to Dobby's you know that</u>
<u n="132" who="S0376">oh yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0377">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0104"><unclear/> keep them got me two pounds forty</u>
<u n="135" who="S0376">we took some up there right and we got about fifteen quid</u>
<u n="136" who="S0104">yeah we got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I got erm twenty quid last time but I've got loads more up there it's just that I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> don't take it all cos that's embarrassing do it in stages</u>
<u n="137" who="S0167" trans="overlap">everyone was everyone was taking loads</u>
<u n="138" who="S0376">I would <trunc>def</trunc></u>
<u n="139" who="S0104">next time</u>
<u n="140" who="S0377" trans="overlap"><unclear>I would take</unclear> the whole lot</u>
<u n="141" who="S0104">we'll take the rest of it</u>
<u n="142" who="S0167">yeah take the rest of it and</u>
<u n="143" who="S0104">all together yeah</u>
<u n="144" who="S0167">and then give the money to me</u>
<u n="145" who="S0104">cos there's still I've still got two or three bags up there haven't I?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0167">yeah there's loads up there</u>
<u n="147" who="S0104">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0167">I don't know if it would be twenty quid's worth though it's only forty P a kilo</u>
<u n="149" who="S0104">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0167">that was like six kilos that bag</u>
<u n="151" who="S0104">well when I went before it was erm fifty P a kilo it's only forty now</u>
<u n="152" who="S0167">but even so you only miss out on</u>
<u n="153" who="S0376">did they check your bags cos they checked some of our stash anything with holes they didn't want</u>
<u n="154" who="S0104">yeah well yeah because I thought they used it as scrap material and it was all going to be cut up so I put any old <trunc>cr</trunc> in</u>
<u n="155" who="S0376">yeah I did yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0167" trans="overlap">no they sell it on I think cos they put a sign there saying the price has gone down cos the second hand clothes market's dropped or something</u>
<u n="157" who="S0104">yeah so they must sell it on</u>
<u n="158" who="S0167">they must sell it</u>
<u n="159" who="S0376" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="160" who="S0104">so they've got to be fit for purpose</u>
<u n="161" who="S0376" trans="overlap">they're picky</u>
<u n="162" who="S0167">still it's better than giving it away bit more</u>
<u n="163" who="S0104">mm</u>
<u n="164" who="S0376">yeah it's nice isn't it?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0167">yeah it's quite popular there were three people waiting when I went</u>
<u n="166" who="S0104">well we ought to sort out all our books and give them to that <anon type="place"/>book shop</u>
<u n="167" who="S0167">well I've just given a load to Save the Children I just had a declutter of my room I don't have any books left</u>
<u n="168" who="S0104">oh I've got loads I've got loads to</u>
<u n="169" who="S0167">yeah <trunc>di</trunc> give the to the bookshop that's a good idea why did you ask today? And they you <unclear/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0104">no I was just talking to this bloke who goes there on a Tuesday and he's a bit he's a bit shy there's there's one bloke one we all started last Tuesday it was all our first day</u>
<u n="171" who="S0167">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0104">well mine was the second day but we and one of them is called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he fancied himself a bit and he's Mr you know chatty chatty chats to everyone</u>
<u n="173" who="S0167">oh no</u>
<u n="174" who="S0104">who's there and then there was another called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0167">not <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0104">who's a bit of a bit of a geek and he's really sweet but very shy and very inward you know and he stands washing up and tries not</u>
<u n="177" who="S0167" trans="overlap">ah a bit of a geek</u>
<u n="178" who="S0104">anyway I was drying up today and he was washing and I was talking to him and I said what do you do?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0167">he probably was thinking of please stop talking to me</u>
<u n="180" who="S0104">I said what do you I felt sorry I feel sorry for him I said what do you? cos he's a bit overshadowed by the <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> bloke as well</u>
<u n="181" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0104">and I said er what do you do for the rest of the week and he said oh I volunteer in the bookshop up the road I thought oh I wanted to say</u>
<u n="183" who="S0167">does he not earn money?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0104">well I don't know</u>
<u n="185" who="S0167">does he just read books or something</u>
<u n="186" who="S0104">I didn't like to delve any further</u>
<u n="187" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0376">probably got a rich mum mum and dad</u>
<u n="189" who="S0104">I'm not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I don't I can't</u>
<u n="190" who="S0167">yeah I wish I could do things like that I can't either</u>
<u n="191" who="S0104">mm so he works at the bookshop all week and that one Tuesday</u>
<u n="192" who="S0167">yeah that's a good idea hadn't thought about the bookshop</u>
<u n="193" who="S0104">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0167">is it have you seen the bookshop? you should you it's really funny it's a really it's a crooked building</u>
<u n="195" who="S0104">I know he said they've only been there a year</u>
<u n="196" who="S0167">it's good it looks good</u>
<u n="197" who="S0104">mm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0376">need another log on the fire <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0104">I think I do have to be careful not to put the moneybox log on spot the moneybox log</u>
<u n="200" who="S0376">what?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0104">I didn't tell you about this?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0377">no</u>
<u n="203" who="S0104">we've got this we've got our holiday fund</u>
<u n="204" who="S0377">oh right</u>
<u n="205" who="S0104"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> bought one those big tins</u>
<u n="206" who="S0377">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0104">that you have to open with a tin opener and every now and again we chuck chuck a note in or whatever and er cos eh cos we're hopeless and saving so but anyway <unclear/> a bit paranoid about thing getting stolen when we get broken in so he's</u>
<u n="208" who="S0376">hid it in a log</u>
<u n="209" who="S0104">let me show you this is what he's <trunc>d</trunc>done to disguise our money box</u>
<u n="210" who="S0376">well just throw it on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0104">he's made it into a log</u>
<u n="212" who="S0376">ah that's really clever</u>
<u n="213" who="S0104">cut the end of the log off and put a magnet on it</u>
<u n="214" who="S0377">that's really clever</u>
<u n="215" who="S0104"><vocal desc="laugh"/> puts it in the log pile</u>
<u n="216" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0376">that's a good idea though isn't it?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0104">well it looks like that but when it's all surrounded by logs you'd never know</u>
<u n="219" who="S0376">yeah no look at that</u>
<u n="220" who="S0104"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it does make me laugh so the rule is with that nothing under a pound denomination goes in there</u>
<u n="221" who="S0376">yeah you just had that you just recorded all that now</u>
<u n="222" who="S0104">oh yeah I just told everybody that we've got a log</u>
<u n="223" who="S0376" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0167">oh no</u>
<u n="226" who="S0104">better delete that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> otherwise you never know</u>
<u n="227" who="S0167">oh no</u>
<u n="228" who="S0104">tried to do it in two sittings <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we had to suspend things</u>
<u n="229" who="S0376">we had to have a break</u>
<u n="230" who="S0104">while we had a break and had a coffee</u>
<u n="231" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0104">we had to suspend recording for a while</u>
<u n="233" who="S0167">that's okay I did erm I did an hour with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> today</u>
<u n="234" who="S0104">oh did you? how is she? why hasn't she been to see me had she while she's been here?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0167">because she's a bitch I don't know we went on a country walk through the footpaths opposite her house and we she had a pair of suede light brown suede shoes and I had these on so it was really inappropriate</u>
<u n="236" who="S0104">oh my god</u>
<u n="237" who="S0167">we've ruined our shoes probably but you know</u>
<u n="238" who="S0104">by the way those towel and tea towels you put here</u>
<u n="239" who="S0167">oh were they not folded correctly?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0104">no they weren't but why I was refolding them</u>
<u n="241" who="S0167">were they not clean?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0104">they were a bit wet</u>
<u n="243" who="S0376">not any more</u>
<u n="244" who="S0104">no</u>
<u n="245" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0376">they were there's one these</u>
<u n="247" who="S0167">oh no</u>
<u n="248" who="S0104">and now the settee I can't get the smell off the settee</u>
<u n="249" who="S0167">ah well I didn't know</u>
<u n="250" who="S0104" trans="overlap">and they've come right through no it wasn't your fault I'm just telling you they're back in the back in the washing machine now</u>
<u n="251" who="S0167">oh what a waste</u>
<u n="252" who="S0104">I suspect my trousers probably now smell of them cos I'm been sitting on this settee I can't get rid of the smell of it</u>
<u n="253" who="S0376">you think you can smell it</u>
<u n="254" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh it will disappear eventually</u>
<u n="255" who="S0104">no I can</u>
<u n="256" who="S0376">I'm pretty sure it's probably not</u>
<u n="257" who="S0104">I can I keep getting wafts of it when I sit down</u>
<u n="258" who="S0167">did you see me mum? as I waved at you today?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0104">yeah yeah didn't you see me wave?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0167">no you didn't look like you recognised me</u>
<u n="261" who="S0104">I didn't until you were just going past just before you tooted I waved</u>
<u n="262" who="S0167">that was good timing wasn't it?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0104">mm it was <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do you listen to all this before you send it?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0167">not every single word I just have to</u>
<u n="265" who="S0376">well thank goodness</u>
<u n="266" who="S0104">oh that's good</u>
<u n="267" who="S0167">oh but like</u>
<u n="268" who="S0376">I forgot myself at one stage</u>
<u n="269" who="S0377" trans="overlap">yeah but it's probably not interesting to anyone else they'll be like oh</u>
<u n="270" who="S0376">we were on about as you get older you get get a bit of you know down here if grey you know I'm not mentioning again cos I</u>
<u n="271" who="S0104">no I'll tell you later</u>
<u n="272" who="S0167">it's alright I I have to have a little listen you know I might catch that little bit</u>
<u n="273" who="S0376" trans="overlap">yeah I'm sure you will</u>
<u n="274" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0376">oh well</u>
<u n="276" who="S0167">we had lunch at the <anon type="place"/> today</u>
<u n="277" who="S0104">oh did you?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0167">just before I left <anon type="place"/> we went for a walk and then walked up to the pub and had a jacket potato</u>
<u n="279" who="S0104">how is she since she came out of hospital?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0167">she seems okay she's doing <unclear/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0104">oh</u>
<u n="282" who="S0167">she's going home tonight</u>
<u n="283" who="S0104">so she's been home for a long weekend and she hasn't been to see me once</u>
<u n="284" who="S0167">you should say something</u>
<u n="285" who="S0104">I will</u>
<u n="286" who="S0376">oh oh my cat wants to come in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="287" who="S0104">he he oh have I locked the cat flap?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0376">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0104">well she's quite clever she actually finds a way of hooking it outwards and climbing through if you leave her long enough</u>
<u n="290" who="S0167">I cleaned I cleaned around the cat bowl today</u>
<u n="291" who="S0104">oh no they're</u>
<u n="292" who="S0167">cos cos you know when they just get it all on the floor and eat it it was all like dried old cat food all round that bowl it was disgusting</u>
<u n="293" who="S0104">yeah no she she eventually she'll she'll learn to hook it outwards and she'll hook it backwards and climb through that way the other two are bit thick they won't do that but I have to lock it when the wind gets up cos it just blows open</u>
<u n="294" who="S0376">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0167">you know what I kept thinking that yesterday that it was open I didn't think to lock it the whole day I was looking at it</u>
<u n="296" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="297" who="S0376">hello</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="298" who="S0104">ah is she cold?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0376">she is a bit she's warming up aren't you mate?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0104">come here she's my baby</u>
<u n="301" who="S0376">can't stay mad at you for long</u>
<u n="302" who="S0104">no I I can't she's my she's my darling</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="303" who="S0376" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="misc"/> come see mummy you</u>
<u n="304" who="S0167"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did you know that apparently <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum got killed two days after we got the kitten?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0104">yeah I knew that</u>
<u n="306" who="S0167">I didn't know that</u>
<u n="307" who="S0104">yeah <pause dur="long"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah cos we used to have little ah she was lovely wasn't she's black fluffy kit cat</u>
<u n="308" who="S0376">ah</u>
<u n="309" who="S0104">and she was beautiful and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm she had her brother from the same litter</u>
<u n="310" who="S0376">mm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0104">and he's ginger and she was black and she was gorgeous and she just disappeared on Boxing Day didn't she? when she was about eighteen months old</u>
<u n="312" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0104">never to be seen again</u>
<u n="314" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0376">yeah I had a cat disappear like that</u>
<u n="316" who="S0377">was she fed somewhere else and <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0104">I don't know no I don't know I think either a fox got her or she was cos next door that was when they used to talk to us they had a black and white fluffy cat</u>
<u n="318" who="S0377">long hair</u>
<u n="319" who="S0104">long haired and this ours was long haired and theirs went missing at about the same time so I wonder if they were</u>
<u n="320" who="S0377">stolen</u>
<u n="321" who="S0104">cat cat nabbed</u>
<u n="322" who="S0376">you know there's a dog there's a van going round stealing people's dogs round in <anon type="place"/> area at the moment</u>
<u n="323" who="S0377">I saw that did you share that on Facebook or something?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0376">I did</u>
<u n="325" who="S0167">yeah I saw that</u>
<u n="326" who="S0376">yeah yeah don't leave your dogs outside shops they're warning people cos they're getting snatched from outside</u>
<u n="327" who="S0104">but what do you do with a long haired cat? cos she wasn't she was only a moggy cat she wasn't anything you know she wasn't Burmese or anything like that so and neither was was theirs but anyway but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got her brother who is a big long haired fluffy ginger and god he's ginormous he's a horrible cat isn't he? he's not like our little <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> was he's erm he's erm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0167">yeah I'm going to go to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and ask her to listen to it</u>
<u n="329" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="330" who="S0104">he's erm you know you're sitting there stroking him like this and then he'll suddenly bite you for no reason</u>
<u n="331" who="S0376">oh really?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0104">yeah he's nasty</u>
<u n="333" who="S0376">he's got a bit of a psycho streak you get some dogs like that though one one dog in a litter</u>
<u n="334" who="S0104">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0376">my my cousin's dog female lab <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s sister is a complete psychopath will bite anyone</u>
<u n="336" who="S0104">really a Labrador?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0376">cos you you look at her funny mate she'll go she's go for you she <unclear/></u>
<u n="338" who="S0104">that's quite unusual with labs isn't it?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0376">yeah oh well <unclear/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0104">well as my friend my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s German Shepherd was like that</u>
<u n="341" who="S0167">mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0104">I was glad when that one snuffed it hello</u>
<u n="343" who="S0376">she's got such a cute little face</u>
<u n="344" who="S0104">I know she's my baby <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has got her sister</u>
<u n="345" who="S0376">not as nice as her</u>
<u n="346" who="S0104">no she's not as beautiful as my little cat</u>
<u n="347" who="S0377"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="348" who="S0104">but she was from a different litter</u>
<u n="349" who="S0376">the other one had a fixation on my armpit that one</u>
<u n="350" who="S0104">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has gone all really weird</u>
<u n="351" who="S0376">and then she started licking my hair</u>
<u n="352" who="S0377">you say it so proudly</u>
<u n="353" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="354" who="S0376">he started pulling my hair didn't he?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0104">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0376">licking it a pulling trying to</u>
<u n="357" who="S0104">she went a bit she goes a bit funny when she's round <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it must be something are you wearing catnip?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0376">that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0104"><unclear/> on the wrong one</u>
<u n="360" who="S0376">I don't know perhaps it was my roll on</u>
<u n="361" who="S0104">could be</u>
<u n="362" who="S0167">I didn't realise today when I was in job centre I forgot to put deodorant on this morning</u>
<u n="363" who="S0104">did you smell?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0167">well it's quite a big jumper so I think it contains the smell but</u>
<u n="365" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0167">I was all sweaty and then I thought oh I forgot to put deodorant on</u>
<u n="367" who="S0376">she was acting really strange first of all it was jumper she liked cos I think she knows it's a cat on it</u>
<u n="368" who="S0104">yeah yeah could be</u>
<u n="369" who="S0376">and then she started trying to get her nose up under here and</u>
<u n="370" who="S0104">it can't be catnip cos the other two aren't interested</u>
<u n="371" who="S0376">no it's probably the deodorant <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0104">ah it's next door</u>
<u n="373" who="S0376">is it?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0167">I thought Easter holidays were over?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0104">they are its ten to five <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="377" who="S0104">quarter to five</u>
<u n="378" who="S0376">god you've got to put prescriptions in</u>
<u n="379" who="S0377">I don't have to put it in today</u>
<u n="380" who="S0376">you don't they have a thing outside where you can just put them in a</u>
<u n="381" who="S0104">you got to put round the chemist or in the <trunc>do</trunc> <trunc>re</trunc> are <unclear/> in the doctors?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0377">no it's not repeat it's just one off dentist script</u>
<u n="383" who="S0104">oh it's a script you've got to take it to chemist?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0104">oh right right</u>
<u n="386" who="S0376">they don't shut till half past weekdays</u>
<u n="387" who="S0167">I don't have to do it today I've had it for about three weeks already so</u>
<u n="388" who="S0376">is it half five on a weekday?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0377">no it's at six it's six o'clock</u>
<u n="390" who="S0376">oh plenty of time then</u>
<u n="391" who="S0377"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0104">no cos at our doctors if you want to put a repeat script in request a repeat script they've just got a little box outside you can put it in there</u>
<u n="393" who="S0377">inside the surgery isn't it?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0376">yeah inside our one</u>
<u n="395" who="S0377">and there's not one round at the doctors</u>
<u n="396" who="S0104">well that's a bit stupid if it's out out out of opening hours isn't it?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0376">yeah no it is bloody doctors useless they are</u>
<u n="398" who="S0104">I think they're in the front garden</u>
<u n="399" who="S0167">there is it that baby's head is freezing</u>
<u n="400" who="S0376">that's really odd it sounds like they're all on helium doesn't it?</u>
<u n="401" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0376">where's it coming from? sounds like</u>
<u n="403" who="S0377">they're in the living room</u>
<u n="404" who="S0104">they're not usually that noisy I can't usually I can hear them upstairs I can hear them when they're upstairs cos the walls are thin but I don't actually hear them downstairs no it'll be that bit</u>
<u n="405" who="S0377">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0104">their house their house only comes to here</u>
<u n="407" who="S0376">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0104">I don't hear them down here usually they must be in the hallway</u>
<u n="409" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0104">their stairs run up there cos they like it when we've got our fire lit cos it it heats their stairwell for nothing they get a nice nice warm walls <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0376">that's probably why they're all sitting on the stairs</u>
<u n="412" who="S0104">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> sitting up against the hall <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh crikey if they can hear if we can hear them that imagine what they must hear from here that night when we were all here having that little party</u>
<u n="413" who="S0167">yeah they probably hear parties mum</u>
<u n="414" who="S0104">oh</u>
<u n="415" who="S0377">oh I think there's they definitely heard that</u>
<u n="416" who="S0376">wasn't that wasn't that supposed to be a games night but it turned out to be a right piss up?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0104" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0377" trans="overlap">it was a games night</u>
<u n="419" who="S0104">and turned into a bit of a bit of a mess</u>
<u n="420" who="S0377" trans="overlap">cos you all cheated</u>
<u n="421" who="S0104">it was a bit messy wasn't it by the end? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> comes out</u>
<u n="422" who="S0377"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> comes out with a toilet flusher in her hand</u>
<u n="423" who="S0104"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came out <unclear/> toilet flush</u>
<u n="424" who="S0377">she was like this trying to <unclear/></u>
<u n="425" who="S0104" trans="overlap">and then and she went upstairs to the upstairs toilet was sick in dad's tool box <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0376">yes I had the pleasure of <trunc>cle</trunc> I had the pleasure of cleaning that</u>
<u n="427" who="S0104">I didn't I didn't cos I was in</u>
<u n="428" who="S0377">you <unclear/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0376">yes</u>
<u n="430" who="S0104">I wasn't in much of a better state I think I was being sick in the bath</u>
<u n="431" who="S0377">you no you'd already been sick</u>
<u n="432" who="S0376">she was paralytic your mother</u>
<u n="433" who="S0167">oh my god</u>
<u n="434" who="S0377">you was drunk before we even turned up</u>
<u n="435" who="S0167" trans="overlap">I'm ashamed</u>
<u n="436" who="S0376">you'd been drinking when we arrived</u>
<u n="437" who="S0104">I'd had a few drinks but then then they started making me drink no you didn't make me I think I</u>
<u n="438" who="S0377">making you drink</u>
<u n="439" who="S0104">no I think I willingly took them that night</u>
<u n="440" who="S0167">what was that?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0104">shots</u>
<u n="442" who="S0377">I don't remember shots that night</u>
<u n="443" who="S0104">and I don't do shots</u>
<u n="444" who="S0377">I remember shots at my house when me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> changing your wine colour</u>
<u n="445" who="S0104">oh that's right yeah see I can't I that's when one I'm alright on wine I get very silly and very</u>
<u n="446" who="S0376">I get drunk very quickly on wine</u>
<u n="447" who="S0104">give me give me spirits and I'm I am hopeless</u>
<u n="448" who="S0376">I'm the other way spirits I can drink you know all night and I'll I'll you know I can pace myself with that wine couple of glasses I'm anybody's terrible</u>
<u n="449" who="S0104">yeah I'm the opposite</u>
<u n="450" who="S0377">I'm okay as long as we never ever do a repeat of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house</u>
<u n="451" who="S0104">oh my god</u>
<u n="452" who="S0376">I wasn't there that night</u>
<u n="453" who="S0104">coming home from there no cos we were doing shots that night</u>
<u n="454" who="S0377" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0104">coming home from there</u>
<u n="456" who="S0377">it weren't just a few shots either it was like you got a number you did a shot</u>
<u n="457" who="S0376">I know oh god</u>
<u n="458" who="S0104">I was being sick out of the car door</u>
<u n="459" who="S0377">I don't remember that</u>
<u n="460" who="S0104"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came and picked me up</u>
<u n="461" who="S0377">I got a lift home with you didn't I?</u>
<u n="462" who="S0104">yes</u>
<u n="463" who="S0377"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was in the car and I remember thinking how is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the car? is she staying at my house? did I ask her? cos I don't remember that bit</u>
<u n="464" who="S0104">oh no maybe it wasn't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s then was it come no it was coming back from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s that's right that night that erm ABBA night she had</u>
<u n="465" who="S0377">oh I wasn't there then</u>
<u n="466" who="S0104">and we were giving <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a lift home of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was he'd picked me up giving <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a lift home we had we had to keep stopping up the avenue for me to open the door and puke out the door <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0167">er</u>
<u n="468" who="S0376">I done it outside my mate's car years ago</u>
<u n="469" who="S0377">hello</u>
<u n="470" who="S0376">she was still driving at the time</u>
<u n="471" who="S0377">was it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sick in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s new car?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0376">the next morning</u>
<u n="473" who="S0377">or out of it</u>
<u n="474" who="S0376">the next morning she'd gone out it'd all dried down the side of her car</u>
<u n="475" who="S0104">oh it's horrible yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was sick in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s car brand new car week old</u>
<u n="476" who="S0376">oh god</u>
<u n="477" who="S0104">puked in it <pause dur="short"/> I think the funniest night was coming back from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s fiftieth and we dropped you off</u>
<u n="478" who="S0377"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0104"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came and picked us up right?</u>
<u n="480" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="481" who="S0104"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came and picked us up</u>
<u n="482" who="S0167"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="483" who="S0104">yeah it was that long ago dad <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and me it was at <anon type="place"/> village hall or something</u>
<u n="484" who="S0377">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0104">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0377">cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> left her shoes behind</u>
<u n="487" who="S0104">that's right yeah and we were dropping <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house which is</u>
<u n="488" who="S0377">it was all <unclear/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0104">the row of houses just before <anon type="place"/> you know</u>
<u n="490" who="S0167">okay</u>
<u n="491" who="S0104">so it was from <anon type="place"/> hall we were just dropping them there and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was quite well I didn't realise <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was as drunk as she was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was absolutely paralytic and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was erm quite drunk</u>
<u n="492" who="S0377">I don't remember being paralytic</u>
<u n="493" who="S0104">you were because I couldn't talk any sense because she gave me a twenty pound note she got out the car and said that's for petrol</u>
<u n="494" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0377">because it was all I had</u>
<u n="496" who="S0104">I said I don't want petrol <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we were driving past anyway and she went no and she absolutely insisted would not have it that she didn't give me this twenty <trunc>poun</trunc></u>
<u n="497" who="S0377">and yet how was I drunk? cos then you gave it to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was clearly drunk</u>
<u n="498" who="S0104">because I didn't realize <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was I knew <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was a bit drunk but I didn't realize she was as drunk so I gave it to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I said give that back to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the morning cos she was staying the night she said okay well she <trunc>we</trunc> didn't give it another thought until some I said to somebody did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> ever get that did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> ever give <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that money back? and they went no I asked you didn't I? did <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> ever <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> ever give you that money back and you said what money?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0377">no</u>
<u n="500" who="S0104">and it turned out the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had woken up the next day gone home said I don't understand this I bought drinks and everything and I've got more money than I had before I went</u>
<u n="501" who="S0377">she was convinced somehow that she'd showed her shoes cos she couldn't find her shoes</u>
<u n="502" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="503" who="S0104">so erm I had to tell her so you owe <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> twenty quid</u>
<u n="504" who="S0376">oh</u>
<u n="505" who="S0377">she was clearly more drunk than I was</u>
<u n="506" who="S0104" trans="overlap">she didn't remember it yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0377">cos I remember giving you the money cos it was all I had</u>
<u n="508" who="S0104">yeah so you would not twenty quid from there to there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0376">I don't know that was a good night was that</u>
<u n="510" who="S0104">it was a good night</u>
<u n="511" who="S0377" trans="overlap">that was a good night</u>
<u n="512" who="S0376">naked waiters</u>
<u n="513" who="S0377">it was the night of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <unclear>party</unclear></u>
<u n="514" who="S0104">I went to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s thingamajig</u>
<u n="515" who="S0376">oh yeah I forgot all about that</u>
<u n="516" who="S0104">that naked waiter was there again only the one</u>
<u n="517" who="S0376">oh god only the one was it the <trunc>nu</trunc> the one that?</u>
<u n="518" who="S0104">no it wasn't we said to him where's your mate? and he said oh you well I did ask him to come and he wouldn't come he said he couldn't</u>
<u n="519" who="S0376">oh</u>
<u n="520" who="S0104">it's wise I think he was a bit scared of you all</u>
<u n="521" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="522" who="S0376">not surprised we kept slapping his bottom</u>
<u n="523" who="S0104">he said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I've still got the scars on mine from you last time <vocal desc="laugh"/> he was quite sweet wasn't he?</u>
<u n="524" who="S0376">was it a good night out there?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0104">well it was sort of just people milling about she she's done it beautifully</u>
<u n="526" who="S0376">has she?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0104">well I should I suspect <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s done it had it done beautifully</u>
<u n="528" who="S0377"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="529" who="S0104">she's got you know everything she's got I was thinking <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants to set up you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="530" who="S0376">mm</u>
<u n="531" who="S0104">is having in the process they've had to put it on hold at the moment cos they've run out of money but out of the process of this thing being built and she wants two cut hair chairs for cutting</u>
<u n="532" who="S0377">yeah</u>
<u n="533" who="S0104">you know she's got the sink and the recliner thing but she wants to just and erm I cos they're about two hundred quid each and they're the ones I'm looking at which are nothing like the ones that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had just two of them sitting there and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'll get you one for Christmas but obviously she hasn't got it yet so it's a sort of IOU Christmas present and she's got the <unclear/> get the other one herself and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has just got everything hasn't she?</u>
<u n="534" who="S0377">yeah</u>
<u n="535" who="S0104">absolutely everything laid out I know</u>
<u n="536" who="S0376">and the other half does</u>
<u n="537" who="S0104">I know tanning booth massage table everything</u>
<u n="538" who="S0167">but at least when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> gets that she'll know she worked hard for that</u>
<u n="539" who="S0376">that's it</u>
<u n="540" who="S0167">she didn't get it given to her</u>
<u n="541" who="S0376">it is</u>
<u n="542" who="S0104">well she'll have one given to her</u>
<u n="543" who="S0377" trans="overlap">it is it is the first thing</u>
<u n="544" who="S0104">for Christmas</u>
<u n="545" who="S0377"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has stuck to in god knows how long though</u>
<u n="546" who="S0104">yeah mm mm</u>
<u n="547" who="S0377">well I I I'm I'm kinda I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s probably said oh well it's a loan but it's the kind of loan that will</u>
<u n="548" who="S0167">never get paid back <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0104">yeah mm mm</u>
<u n="550" who="S0167">the baby is kind of oozing and then the bottom's getting bigger and bigger</u>
<u n="551" who="S0104">oh yeah it's gone a bit lopsided</u>
<u n="552" who="S0167">yeah it's kind of falling out the ear</u>
<u n="553" who="S0104">he's looking a bit eerie</u>
<u n="554" who="S0376">is he coming has he got wax coming out of his ear?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0104">yes</u>
<u n="556" who="S0377">it's earwax</u>
<u n="557" who="S0104">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came with little <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="558" who="S0376">oh</u>
<u n="559" who="S0104">he's he's gorgeous he's such a beautiful baby <pause dur="long"/> what else was I going to say about it? yeah she's got all her shampoos and yeah that's what I was going to say how come <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is doing hair now?</u>
<u n="560" who="S0377">I didn't know she was doing hair</u>
<u n="561" who="S0104">yeah she's got the hair salon and everything</u>
<u n="562" who="S0377">is she doing it or has she got somebody in doing it?</u>
<u n="563" who="S0104">no she's doing it</u>
<u n="564" who="S0377">what like cuts or just?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0104">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="566" who="S0377">really?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0104">I think so cos she cuts <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s hair for her and everything</u>
<u n="568" who="S0376">did she have training then?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0104">well I don't know not as far I mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did two years' training</u>
<u n="570" who="S0377">I don't think I've never mentioned <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in training</u>
<u n="571" who="S0104">she's done a day course I think <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know she's certainly doing hair ups hair up things and all that</u>
<u n="572" who="S0377">yeah</u>
<u n="573" who="S0104">which is a bit of a shame cos she and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had a bit of a</u>
<u n="574" who="S0376">I was going to say weren't they going to sort of like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do hair and?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0104">well it was all very loose yeah but if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got asked to do wedding hair she well she contacted <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and said can she do the makeup? and that would be quite a good thing but obviously <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is doing the hair as well now</u>
<u n="576" who="S0377">I didn't know that</u>
<u n="577" who="S0104">yeah she's got a fully equipped hair salon room and she's got all her own shampoos and things <anon type="place"/>'s shampoos and <anon type="place"/> conditioners and <anon type="place"/> this that and the other</u>
<u n="578" who="S0376">really?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0104">so I don't know how you get around that with erm trade prescriptions and all that business?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0376">yeah</u>
<u n="581" who="S0104">but it is it is lovely I was quite impressed</u>
<u n="582" who="S0377">whenever I see gonna see her I always think ah I really should have plucked my eyebrows before I go and see her cos she looks at them</u>
<u n="583" who="S0104" trans="overlap">oh yes I've made an appointment with her haven't I? next Tuesday</u>
<u n="584" who="S0377">yes</u>
<u n="585" who="S0104">next Tuesday four o'clock</u>
<u n="586" who="S0376" trans="overlap">well you should get her to do them while you're up there</u>
<u n="587" who="S0104">she's doing my eyebrows and eye tinting my eyelashes next Tuesday I've made an appointment</u>
<u n="588" who="S0376">how much is it?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0104">I can't remember she's quite cheap</u>
<u n="590" who="S0377">yeah it's reasonable yeah</u>
<u n="591" who="S0104" trans="overlap">her prices are really reasonable</u>
<u n="592" who="S0376">I reckon we should get spray tans before we go down to Butlins you know</u>
<u n="593" who="S0377">I'd rather not look like a umpa lumpa</u>
<u n="594" who="S0104">yeah no they're a bit I don't like spray tans</u>
<u n="595" who="S0376">well I used to have them done</u>
<u n="596" who="S0104">don't they make you a bit orange?</u>
<u n="597" who="S0376">well it depends what shade you go really doesn't it?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0104">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is going to go to her to have her legs waxed because she's much cheaper than where she usually goes</u>
<u n="599" who="S0167"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="600" who="S0104"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="601" who="S0167">yeah yeah she is</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="602" who="S0104">so have Jobseekers said when you're going to get any money?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0167">well I phoned up yesterday and they said my my application is in the process and they said it would be erm maximum fourth of March cos it can take fourteen working days which is about three weeks</u>
<u n="604" who="S0104">mm</u>
<u n="605" who="S0167">but it could happen before then but fourth of March is the last day</u>
<u n="606" who="S0104">and are they going to give you back pay?</u>
<u n="607" who="S0167">I don't think so well they said everything will be explained on the letter they don't know it's open application</u>
<u n="608" who="S0104">did you apply for it from from when you came back to England?</u>
<u n="609" who="S0167" trans="overlap">they couldn't give me any information <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's when I applied for but I don't know what they'll give me they said you'll just have to wait for the letter to come through see what you've been awarded</u>
<u n="610" who="S0104">oh right mm <pause dur="short"/> be nice if they did that'd be a nice lump sum</u>
<u n="611" who="S0167">mm well I know it I'll I'll be paid from at least the date when I made the claim anyway</u>
<u n="612" who="S0376">yeah</u>
<u n="613" who="S0104">mm</u>
<u n="614" who="S0167">erm but you know I don't know if that'll be hopefully soon</u>
<u n="615" who="S0104"><unclear>ah oh well</unclear> <pause dur="long"/> so is it next week you do <anon type="place"/> or the week after?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0167">week after</u>
<u n="617" who="S0104">oh so it's the end of that week then I was thinking we were going to Butlins next weekend</u>
<u n="618" who="S0167">it's the tenth I start on the tenth</u>
<u n="619" who="S0377" trans="overlap">no it's</u>
<u n="620" who="S0104">no it's the tenth I start on the tenth</u>
<u n="621" who="S0377">we're going to Butlins on the thirteenth don't we?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0104">thirteenth</u>
<u n="623" who="S0377">so it's not</u>
<u n="624" who="S0376">about three weeks innit?</u>
<u n="625" who="S0377">no</u>
<u n="626" who="S0104">no</u>
<u n="627" who="S0377">no cos we'll be on the we'll be on the first of March this weekend won't we?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0376">oh right couple of weeks then</u>
<u n="629" who="S0104">I forget to get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to fill these out</u>
<u n="630" who="S0377">is it the first of March?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="632" who="S0104">these are your consent forms</u>
<u n="633" who="S0376">oh</u>
<u n="634" who="S0104">do you want something to lean on?</u>
<u n="635" who="S0167">the computer is there</u>
<u n="636" who="S0376">no this'll be alright</u>
<u n="637" who="S0104">here you are lean on these one for you</u>
<u n="638" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0104"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that tom tom when we use it</u>
<u n="640" who="S0167">what yeah?</u>
<u n="641" who="S0104">what did we do with the charger? apparently I've sent it back without the charger</u>
<u n="642" who="S0376"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can you grab my handbag that one out there</u>
<u n="643" who="S0104">she can't see can you not see</u>
<u n="644" who="S0377">I forgot my glasses</u>
<u n="645" who="S0376">oh dear</u>
<u n="646" who="S0377">blind as a bat</u>
<u n="647" who="S0167">well wasn't it in the car didn't we use it in the car?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0104">yeah so it must be in the car but I haven't seen it I haven't taken it out the car</u>
<u n="649" who="S0167">I haven't <unclear/></u>
<u n="650" who="S0104">I think I put it back in the box but it must be</u>
<u n="651" who="S0376" trans="overlap">I have a <unclear/></u>
<u n="652" who="S0167">I haven't seen it or noticed it or anything erm</u>
<u n="653" who="S0104">yeah I'll have a look in the car maybe in the boot cos that's where I put it</u>
<u n="654" who="S0376">shedding hair here</u>
<u n="655" who="S0104">you're just a cat magnet <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so what colour is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s orchid?</u>
<u n="656" who="S0376">what's the date today? oh it's er purply pink</u>
<u n="657" who="S0104">twenty-fourth</u>
<u n="658" who="S0376">pinky purply colour</u>
<u n="659" who="S0377">I don't even know I didn't look at the colour</u>
<u n="660" who="S0104">how many times did she mention the fifties deal yesterday?</u>
<u n="661" who="S0377">oh that oh loads oh I lost count I wasn't listening</u>
<u n="662" who="S0104">three times to me</u>
<u n="663" who="S0377">I thought that's what I was going to ask you can you text me this evening and let me know whether tomorrow's her final day or whether Thursday is?</u>
<u n="664" who="S0167">what she's leaving?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0104">no before it's her fiftieth</u>
<u n="666" who="S0377" trans="overlap">it's her birthday</u>
<u n="667" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0104">this is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="669" who="S0377">if you start a new job would you make a point of telling them that it's your fiftieth coming up?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0167">no</u>
<u n="671" who="S0104">everybody every day all the time</u>
<u n="672" who="S0376">do you know what? I can see people better with my glasses on</u>
<u n="673" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="674" who="S0377">that's the general</u>
<u n="675" who="S0104">she suddenly said to me just out the blue yesterday well I'm not doing anything on Friday just going out for a meal</u>
<u n="676" who="S0376">oh</u>
<u n="677" who="S0377">I don't think she's going out with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="678" who="S0104">is she?</u>
<u n="679" who="S0377">I'm not sure cos I overheard them having some sort of conversation I may have got the wrong end of the stick about</u>
<u n="680" who="S0104">see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s quite friendly though I know she's always in the kitchen talking to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but I thought that was more her choice than <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="681" who="S0377" trans="overlap">I'm not sure and then cos she heard I heard her say that and then I heard and then she said to me oh we're just going out for dinner er none of my friends can make it they're all busy or away on holiday and stuff and then she said it's just me and two other people that's all she said well normally you just go it's just me and couple of friends of something you wouldn't go me and two other people bit weird</u>
<u n="682" who="S0104">but she goes on and on about her fiftieth because it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s fiftieth so we did a big collection for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I think she's expecting the same but we have done a collection but it was half hearted and it's not a great deal <pause dur="long"/> yeah no she <trunc>men</trunc> she must have said it to me three or four times yesterday what's happened to the card?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0377">I didn't even know there was one <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> did asked me I said I didn't know</u>
<u n="684" who="S0104">there is a card kicking round</u>
<u n="685" who="S0376">there was one knocking round yeah I haven't <trunc>si</trunc> if if you see it come across it tonight can you sign it for us?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0104">yeah</u>
<u n="687" who="S0377">I may have signed it I may not have there's that many I really don't know</u>
<u n="688" who="S0104">I know cos now there's a collection for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who's eighteen but I don't mind that cos I like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's quite fun he makes me laugh <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what you going to do at the centre? apparently they're only open at the weekends for the next two weeks are you going to take on a weekday or?</u>
<u n="689" who="S0167">well someone said to me on Sunday that they are going to be open for the next few months</u>
<u n="690" who="S0104">oh oh it was only one of the other volunteers said I think they they usually close it in the winter in the summer at weekends</u>
<u n="691" who="S0167">well the man man er who was working with on Sunday said erm oh they've decided to keep it open for the next month or so at least</u>
<u n="692" who="S0104">oh perhaps perhaps she just didn't know about <unclear/> he can come round and say something if he really wants to</u>
<u n="693" who="S0167">like he might</u>
<u n="694" who="S0377">kind of rather he didn't I don't want round here</u>
<u n="695" who="S0376">is he really that bad?</u>
<u n="696" who="S0377">thanks</u>
<u n="697" who="S0104">no he's never come and knocked on the door he's probably cursing and swearing about me at the moment</u>
<u n="698" who="S0167">he's probably going to get a crowbar and smash up the car</u>
<u n="699" who="S0377">oh he can do that I don't mind that</u>
<u n="700" who="S0104">well if he does that I I I well no actually I wouldn't love cos it wouldn't be my car so I suppose it's not my position to love it</u>
<u n="701" who="S0377">it's alright I don't mind</u>
<u n="702" who="S0104">but I'd I'd just get photos I'd just go out there and take lots of photos of him smashing them up</u>
<u n="703" who="S0167">he'd probably smash you up with a crow bar</u>
<u n="704" who="S0104">well then I'd press charges</u>
<u n="705" who="S0167">well then you'd be dead</u>
<u n="706" who="S0104">yeah but there'd be plenty of witnesses to put him away</u>
<u n="707" who="S0167">die a slow and painful death</u>
<u n="708" who="S0104">that would be a death worth that would be worth it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="709" who="S0167">my god <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="710" who="S0104">yeah town what?</u>
<u n="711" who="S0376">this isn't a church town is it? Shall I just put <anon type="place"/> there?</u>
<u n="712" who="S0104">what for your address?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0376">it says where do you currently live? and it says country that's England innit? town? I can put</u>
<u n="714" who="S0104"><anon type="place"/> is a town yeah</u>
<u n="715" who="S0167" trans="overlap">a town really isn't it? yeah</u>
<u n="716" who="S0376">is it? you could blink and miss it</u>
<u n="717" who="S0167">I put <anon type="place"/> as my town</u>
<u n="718" who="S0104">I can't remember what I put</u>
<u n="719" who="S0167">weird baby faces</u>
<u n="720" who="S0104">it's a bit sinister looking isn't it? it's a bit like the Exorcist</u>
<u n="721" who="S0167">haven't seen the Exorcist</u>
<u n="722" who="S0104">I've only seen bits of it captions <pause dur="short"/> when are we doing our Fifty Shades of Grey night then?</u>
<u n="723" who="S0377">we was talking about that earlier wasn't we?</u>
<u n="724" who="S0376">yeah I thought we were going near the end of the month well it is the end of the month</u>
<u n="725" who="S0104">yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0376">well anytime</u>
<u n="727" who="S0104">I I had the twenty-eighth was in my head for some reason</u>
<u n="728" who="S0377">that's this weekend isn't it?</u>
<u n="729" who="S0376">we need to go</u>
<u n="730" who="S0167">I'm going London twenty-eighth</u>
<u n="731" who="S0104">are you? who are you going to see?</u>
<u n="732" who="S0376">oh the guinea pig</u>
<u n="733" who="S0167">we're going to have a picnic in the park save money</u>
<u n="734" who="S0104">what if it's? well you're all poor you're not the only poor one there?</u>
<u n="735" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="736" who="S0104">what if it's raining?</u>
<u n="737" who="S0167">we'll sit under a tree</u>
<u n="738" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="739" who="S0167">we'll probably go to a pub if it's raining</u>
<u n="740" who="S0104">so who are you meeting? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> well she's got a job she can't be that poor</u>
<u n="741" who="S0167"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="742" who="S0104"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can't be that poor cos she's got a full time job</u>
<u n="743" who="S0167">well probably <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> not is not but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is I don't know what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is doing</u>
<u n="744" who="S0104">what does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0167">she's doing a masters at the moment and she's working part time as a waitress and she's doing voluntary work for <foreign lang="fre">Mdecins Sans Frontires</foreign> I don't know if she's got much time to do anything</u>
<u n="746" who="S0104">what's she doing a masters in?</u>
<u n="747" who="S0167">mm human international human thing I don't know some kind of thing she wants to work for an NGO sort of thing some kind of charity based</u>
<u n="748" who="S0104">what's an NGO?</u>
<u n="749" who="S0167">non governmental organisation like <foreign lang="fre">Mdecins Sans Frontires</foreign></u>
<u n="750" who="S0104">oh I see <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="751" who="S0377">here you go</u>
<u n="752" who="S0104">there you go <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="753" who="S0167">thank you very much</u>
<u n="754" who="S0377">that is okay</u>
<u n="755" who="S0104"><unclear/></u>
<u n="756" who="S0167">are you my secretary?</u>
<u n="757" who="S0104">yes</u>
<u n="758" who="S0167">you can get a pay rise if you want get a hundred per cent pay rise</u>
<u n="759" who="S0104">oh great thanks</u>
<u n="760" who="S0167">you can get two pound forty if you want</u>
<u n="761" who="S0104"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="762" who="S0376">what is the date today?</u>
<u n="763" who="S0104">erm twenty-fourth</u>
<u n="764" who="S0377" trans="overlap">twenty-fourth isn't it?</u>
<u n="765" who="S0376">twenty-fourth</u>
<u n="766" who="S0104">twenty-fourth of February god I can't wait till <trunc>feb</trunc> why does January and February just drag and drag and drag?</u>
<u n="767" who="S0376">I don't know</u>
<u n="768" who="S0104">I think it's cos you</u>
<u n="769" who="S0377">cos you don't start doing anything until March cos that's when you actually have some money</u>
<u n="770" who="S0104">yeah no I don't ever have any money <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="771" who="S0377">yeah I don't have money either</u>
<u n="772" who="S0104">money never starts with me</u>
<u n="773" who="S0377">money always just disappears</u>
<u n="774" who="S0104">yeah</u>
<u n="775" who="S0377">I work and work and work and then my money just disappears</u>
<u n="776" who="S0104">you didn't do a very good job this morning on the housekeeping front I have to say</u>
<u n="777" who="S0167">I went out this morning</u>
<u n="778" who="S0104">I got home expecting it to be all nice and spick and span</u>
<u n="779" who="S0167">mum I went out this morning and I cleaned your stupid cat thing stupid cats</u>
<u n="780" who="S0104">they're not my stupid cats one of them's yours</u>
<u n="781" who="S0167">your stupid cat bowl that the cats can't eat <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="782" who="S0377">what are you writing an essay?</u>
<u n="783" who="S0104">yeah why is it taking you so long?</u>
<u n="784" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="785" who="S0104">this is where you've gotta start thinking <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> oh have I done it properly?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0377">yeah I know</u>
<u n="787" who="S0104">that's like you know in exams don't you? when you finish first and you look all around</u>
<u n="788" who="S0377">no I don't do that that clearly doesn't occur to me I just think oh yeah I've done it</u>
<u n="789" who="S0104">and everyone's still writing you're thinking oh ah</u>
<u n="790" who="S0377">probably I've never been first in an exam so it's never occurred to me</u>
<u n="791" who="S0376">I'm going over mine I'm just checking I've done it all</u>
<u n="792" who="S0167">one of my friends finished first</u>
<u n="793" who="S0376">what sort of accent dialect do you think I've got then?</u>
<u n="794" who="S0377">south?</u>
<u n="795" who="S0104">south south east?</u>
<u n="796" who="S0167">southern <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="797" who="S0376">south east London</u>
<u n="798" who="S0104">er</u>
<u n="799" who="S0376">yeah south east</u>
<u n="800" who="S0104">just south east south east England yeah</u>
<u n="801" who="S0167">I think they can probably just work out what accents people have from the recording</u>
<u n="802" who="S0104">yeah</u>
<u n="803" who="S0376">that's it I think oh topic or subject of recording a load of old <unclear>tosh</unclear></u>
<u n="804" who="S0104">yeah</u>
<u n="805" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="806" who="S0104">we'd rather not say</u>
<u n="807" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="808" who="S0104">shall I stop recording now?</u>
<u n="809" who="S0377">yeah oh that's very neat oh does it say your birthday?</u>
<u n="810" who="S0376">hey?</u>
<u n="811" who="S0377">I didn't write my birth date?</u>
<u n="812" who="S0376">does it say birth date?</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
