<text id="SPJR">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:38:59</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-03-09</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0525 S0615</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s home, Lichfield</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Family, work, sign language classes, babies, diet, TV</topics>
		<activity>Mother and daughter chatting over coffee.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, requesting</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0525">
				<exactage>48</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lichfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>26 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation></occupation>
				<socgrade>unknown</socgrade>
				<nssec>unknown</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0615">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Litchfield</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>no</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Sutton Coldfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>11 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Primary School Tearcher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0525">so your dad rang a couple of hours ago <pause dur="short"/> and erm</u>
<u n="2" who="S0615">got there alright then?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0525">yes he texted me last night probably about half eleven to say they were there <pause dur="short"/> but what I didn't realise is they are not actually on the site they are at the docks where the pipes were delivered and they've got to erm sort out six hundred pipes clean them all out and put end caps on them because the customer won't pay</u>
<u n="4" who="S0615" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> how long is that going to take himthen?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0525">well your dad said it's horrendous it's going to take forever he says they haven't got end caps for a start they've been nicked or they've fallen off or they didn't come with them which is a problem that we always used to have erm there's a big box of like rubber end caps but they can't make them fit so your dad had gone out to get more calor gas from a local shop because they are using like a a Canusa type torch to melt down the rubber to try and get it to stick onto the pipe so</u>
<u n="6" who="S0615" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>excellent</unclear></u>
<u n="7" who="S0525">almost like welding it on <trunc>an</trunc> and I don't know <trunc>wha</trunc> he says it's absolutely awful <pause dur="short"/> he said it was quite a nice day up there so I don't think they've had the rain that we had here luckily but he says erm the customer wants to take eight pipes next week he said but er of course we can't <pause dur="short"/> they can't leave the docks until the customer pays the Vat I said well of course they can't and the Vat is two hundred and thirty thousand on that first lot apparently there's six more deliveries coming in next well in ten days' time and they won't be able to shift these so no wonder he's got like a a small posse of people up there on site</u>
<u n="8" who="S0615" trans="overlap">it was lovely up there yesterday <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> so they'll probably never get onto site then in the next couple of days he's just taken them up to do this</u>
<u n="9" who="S0525">well yeah once they do get on to site that's when they need somebody else there to record the delivery notes correctly <pause dur="short"/> I mean we never had to do this before this this is this is just stalling tactics for not paying I can't</u>
<u n="10" who="S0615">oh</u>
<u n="11" who="S0525">you know a pipe is a pipe they've gotta they've gotta flush it through before they use it anyway you have to you know bung water through at high pressure which cleans out all the rubbish tests all the joints I mean that's standard procedure and I am assuming it's a drinking water pipe if it's sewerage well there's even less need to <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I don't know why they are having to do all of this or why <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has agreed to do it all I notice is is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is well out of the way he's he's never up there I suppose he's <trunc>he</trunc> I bet he's washed his hands of it he got the job and he's thinking do whatever</u>
<u n="12" who="S0615" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> what a friend? <pause dur="short"/> manual labour <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0525">well he's probably thinking it is not necessarily not necessary but it is just him and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> these days isn't it so</u>
<u n="14" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0525">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is up there and <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0615">who's that?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0525">he's the guy that used to supply goods to FTD and then has joined us now and he's very much upstairs with the upstairs mentality of the them and us he's in the upstairs team <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> is that cornflakes you are eating?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0615" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> he's joined us <pause dur="short"/> in our team <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0525">oh</u>
<u n="20" who="S0615">lunch <unclear/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0525">oh fair enough <pause dur="short"/> when did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> fall asleep just on the in the car now?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0615">half past two</u>
<u n="23" who="S0525">oh did he oh so he might wake up soon?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0615">mm in the car</u>
<u n="25" who="S0525">it's taken you that long to get here?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0525">roadworks</u>
<u n="28" who="S0615">it was the roadworks</u>
<u n="29" who="S0525">where are they?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0615">erm so if you come from <anon type="place"/> to here you come along the road it's got the Toby Carvery on it</u>
<u n="31" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0615">just before you come to the where it straightens out before you get to <anon type="place"/> just like before it straightens out</u>
<u n="33" who="S0525">near the that</u>
<u n="34" who="S0615">is there a school there?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0525">Balti there's a Balti restaurant you've gone past the the school yeah?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah you've had gone past that</u>
<u n="37" who="S0525">oh right what are they doing? just go roadworks on one side of the road or something?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0615">mm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0525">mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0615">yeah for ages</u>
<u n="41" who="S0525">the roadworks are still in <anon type="place"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was right they are just up by the roundabout</u>
<u n="42" who="S0615">yeah I thought they was still there</u>
<u n="43" who="S0525">mm yeah but they are only erm you know two way now not four way so it doesn't take as long</u>
<u n="44" who="S0615">no</u>
<u n="45" who="S0525">so I was practising my signing the alphabet in under ten seconds last night with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but I'd got I was I thought I was in and <trunc>sh</trunc> my first one was seventeen seconds I got it down to about twelve but it was a bit hit and miss it was quite stressful and anyway we are not going tonight now</u>
<u n="46" who="S0615" trans="overlap">oh gosh <pause dur="short"/> it's only twenty-six letters and it took you seventeen seconds I could do it in twenty I could do <unclear/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0525" trans="overlap"><trunc>a</trunc> you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but said you can't even say it that quick I said don't be so stupid of course you can say the alphabet in less than ten seconds I couldn't <pause dur="short"/> shall I show let's I will show you how quick I am now and you see if you reckon you could do it quicker? okay</u>
<u n="48" who="S0615" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> in <unclear/> seconds <pause dur="short"/> oh shall I time you on it?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0525">well you can sort of in in your head alright</u>
<u n="50" who="S0615">okay</u>
<u n="51" who="S0525">okay so A B C D <pause dur="short"/> e F G <pause dur="short"/> h I J K <pause dur="short"/> l M N <pause dur="short"/> o P Q R S T <pause dur="short"/> u V W X Y Z right do you think you could be much quicker than that? and that was about what fifteen seconds probably</u>
<u n="52" who="S0615" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> no no I don't think I would be <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I didn't count it in my head to be honest</u>
<u n="53" who="S0525">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've kind of got the A B C D E F G <pause dur="short"/> h I J K L M N <pause dur="short"/> o <pause dur="short"/> p Q R S T U V W X Y Z so I've got the first half quicker than the</u>
<u n="54" who="S0615" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="55" who="S0525">I can do that for T</u>
<u n="56" who="S0615">no we are doing that</u>
<u n="57" who="S0525">oh that yeah yeah you are right it should be down there that's erm that's L actually I was doing L</u>
<u n="58" who="S0615">yeah that's what I mean L</u>
<u n="59" who="S0525">yeah no you are right T I get stuck on O P Q R S T U V W X Y Z</u>
<u n="60" who="S0615" trans="overlap">you get stuck on going to <unclear>T</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> you get stuck on to <unclear>T</unclear></u>
<u n="61" who="S0525">do I? O P Q <pause dur="short"/> o P Q R S T <pause dur="short"/> u V W X Y Z oh well anyway I've got another week to practise now <vocal desc="laugh"/> but <trunc>I</trunc>I'm not sure like I say how relevant this is going to be for the exam we've moved on</u>
<u n="62" who="S0615" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I'm sure she thinks you need to know it</u>
<u n="63" who="S0525">mm <trunc>s</trunc>so then</u>
<u n="64" who="S0615">I reckon I could do it in ten ten seconds with practise</u>
<u n="65" who="S0525">oh yeah right oh with practise yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0615">because I I wouldn't be able to do it now in ten seconds would I? I'd need a couple of days</u>
<u n="67" who="S0525" trans="overlap">well <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh alright then okay then you are on</u>
<u n="68" who="S0615">oh I haven't got time to do that have I?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0525">oh I haven't got time now I was accepting the challenge there</u>
<u n="70" who="S0615">no you were right it's</u>
<u n="71" who="S0525">not really <vocal desc="yawn"/> you're right you'd probably win</u>
<u n="72" who="S0615"><unclear/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0525">hey what are you doing?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0615">C</u>
<u n="75" who="S0525">no C just that not that</u>
<u n="76" who="S0615">oh just that</u>
<u n="77" who="S0525">just that</u>
<u n="78" who="S0615">you can't do it like that then?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0525">no no no</u>
<u n="80" who="S0615">are you sure?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0525">yes</u>
<u n="82" who="S0615">that's D</u>
<u n="83" who="S0525">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0615">E F see you need to do it like that D E F</u>
<u n="85" who="S0525">I do D E F got that A B C D E F G H I J K because I and J went together then I J K <pause dur="short"/> l M N you still what?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah because it's still <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="cough"/> <pause dur="short"/> like separating your fingers you know A B C D E F</u>
<u n="87" who="S0525" trans="overlap">A B C <pause dur="short"/> d E F G yeah H I J</u>
<u n="88" who="S0615">I thought you were going D E a minute ago</u>
<u n="89" who="S0525">no but thanks for the tip there in that I've got a split second <pause dur="short"/> c D <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's trickier than you think</u>
<u n="90" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I'd do it <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> where's O? O</u>
<u n="91" who="S0525">yes O is there</u>
<u n="92" who="S0615">why were you doing that for R?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0525">it's that one it's that finger</u>
<u n="94" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0525">because that's what R is</u>
<u n="96" who="S0615">but you were doing that a minute ago</u>
<u n="97" who="S0525">no that's S</u>
<u n="98" who="S0615">yes I know that's S</u>
<u n="99" who="S0525">oh I was there</u>
<u n="100" who="S0615">mm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0525">T</u>
<u n="102" who="S0615">T</u>
<u n="103" who="S0525">U V</u>
<u n="104" who="S0615">oh that's it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0525">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> got it loads got it got it got it</u>
<u n="106" who="S0615"><unclear> can you say it? can do it backwards</unclear></u>
<u n="107" who="S0525"><vocal desc="yawn"/> mm I haven't texted <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to tell her I'm in tonight I don't think she wants tea though so <pause dur="short"/> what have you eaten?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0615" trans="overlap"><unclear> is she at work</unclear>? <pause dur="short"/> is she off work tomorrow?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0525">er yeah Friday she's off she's doing a late tomorrow I'm starving I'm not going to be able to diet I was looking at holidays instead and that cheered me up I don't know who is going to come with me oh maybe a week in <anon type="place"/> again in April</u>
<u n="110" who="S0615" trans="overlap">what kind of holiday? <pause dur="short"/> well what do you want to do? do you want to do that or a cottage or Iceland because you choose one that you want us to come on and we will come on it with you <unclear/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh <trunc>wel</trunc>well Iceland Iceland we're doing later in the year we don't want to go now because we want to see the Northern Lights</u>
<u n="112" who="S0615">yeah late so this year so you are talking about all this year?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0525">oh yeah yeah I'm talking about I'm talking about April I'm talking about I can't wait for the sun</u>
<u n="114" who="S0615">yeah so yeah so let's just in April because you know we've got bags of cash <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's why I'm saying choose one that you want us to come on and we'll come with you</u>
<u n="115" who="S0525">well Iceland</u>
<u n="116" who="S0615">well that's it then we can't possibly afford to do another one</u>
<u n="117" who="S0525" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> right then there we are you're out</u>
<u n="118" who="S0615">I bought a christening outfit</u>
<u n="119" who="S0525">you are out I'll see if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants to go I don't think she will I don't think anybody will</u>
<u n="120" who="S0615">oh no on your own</u>
<u n="121" who="S0525">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0615"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> won't be able to get the time off now</u>
<u n="123" who="S0525">no I know <pause dur="short"/> are you giving that rabbit a name?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0615">it's ratatat</u>
<u n="125" who="S0525">oh <pause dur="short"/> why? you said that was the rat</u>
<u n="126" who="S0615">no I said ratatat is the rabbit in Rhythm Time</u>
<u n="127" who="S0525">oh that what just like that?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0525">oh</u>
<u n="130" who="S0615">but he's got Rhythm Time on his hat so he's about twenty pound more expensive</u>
<u n="131" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh I see <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> what you can buy him?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0525">Rhythm Time is a franchised business isn't it?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0615">yeah <pause dur="short"/> also baby signing is a er <pause dur="short"/> a franchise business</u>
<u n="135" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> is it? <pause dur="short"/> how?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0615">yeah I think I might take him to baby signing</u>
<u n="137" who="S0525">excellent and nanny needs to come as well</u>
<u n="138" who="S0615">well if you just if take them and <pause dur="short"/> kind of submerge them in it</u>
<u n="139" who="S0525">why do you want him to learn that?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0615">well then by the time there's apparently a lady was telling me today that er a woman takes her daughter and she's <pause dur="short"/> she nine ten months? and she can sign food</u>
<u n="141" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0615">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so rather than <pause dur="short"/> obviously she can't talk yet <pause dur="short"/> make noises and stuff but so she's signing milk and <pause dur="short"/> nappy and things like milk</u>
<u n="143" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> really <pause dur="short"/> really</u>
<u n="144" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0525">how clever</u>
<u n="146" who="S0615">mm mm</u>
<u n="147" who="S0525">BSL or Makaton?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0615">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> probably er is is it Makaton? <pause dur="short"/> that's what Mr Tumbles does on the telly</u>
<u n="149" who="S0525">he does Makaton does he?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0615">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="151" who="S0525">I'd like to come if it was BSL where do you where do they do that?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0615" trans="overlap">great <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> where was she saying that they do it? opposite <anon type="place"/> erm train station <pause dur="short"/> er in the church there on the roundabout</u>
<u n="153" who="S0525">oh that church</u>
<u n="154" who="S0615">yes I think they do it in there I don't know how much it is actually maybe I I will have a look now because I would quite like to go to that</u>
<u n="155" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> you'd have to learn it as well otherwise you wouldn't know what he was signing to you</u>
<u n="156" who="S0615">well obviously what I'm going to leave him am I?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/> at four months to pick it up himself</u>
<u n="158" who="S0615">yeah bye <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> I'll come and pick you up in a bit</u>
<u n="159" who="S0525">he doesn't need to sign he just screams</u>
<u n="160" who="S0615">what do you mean just screams? what to tell me what he wants?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> he just cries</u>
<u n="162" who="S0615">yeah but the crying is gonna get less and if he can communicate with me in another way in a few months' time surely that's beneficial to the way <unclear/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0525" trans="overlap">and then and then they're gonna say oh my baby doesn't talk it just signs because he just decided he doesn't need to</u>
<u n="164" who="S0615" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="cough"/> <pause dur="short"/> he's obviously deaf</u>
<u n="165" who="S0525">well no that just they don't need to</u>
<u n="166" who="S0615">of course they need to</u>
<u n="167" who="S0525">no no I'm thinking that will be what somebody will come up with next somebody will say that because because er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s baby well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what's the younger one <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? he was said he was ever so lazy in talking he would get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to say things for him or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would start answering for him <pause dur="short"/> and <trunc>s</trunc>she said he just wouldn't bother and she just didn't know why she said he can but he just doesn't doesn't hardly talk at <vocal desc="laugh"/> so if she says you know do you want a sandwich? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will go yes he does mummy <vocal desc="laugh"/> don't you answer for him and he will go oh</u>
<u n="168" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> baby signing <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> will signing help or hinder my baby's ability to talk?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0525">there you go</u>
<u n="170" who="S0615">you may worry that teaching your baby to sign will slow down his normal speech development in fact research shows the opposite is true signing may actually help your baby to learn to talk adding words to his vocabulary signing is about enhancing not replacing language <pause dur="short"/> signing should be used along with normal speech so your baby can make the link between gesture and words yes so when you are at home you won't <vocal desc="laugh"/> you won't just communicate with your baby <vocal desc="laugh"/> because <vocal desc="laugh"/> without saying anything</u>
<u n="171" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> why? has what? <vocal desc="laugh"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> that's beer anyway</u>
<u n="172" who="S0615">oh if for example he tells you he can hear an aeroplane you can respond you hear an aeroplane yes I can see it look it's over there it's in the <unclear>cloud</unclear> this way you spend more time chatting about what interests your little one which is a great way to help to him learn to talk there we go</u>
<u n="173" who="S0525" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> and is it is it it's just called baby sign it is not called BSL or?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0615">no <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0525">interesting what what day is that on?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0615">more hold your hands open palms facing towards your body with one in front of the other more the hands in front and forwards <unclear/> distance make sure distance oh forward</u>
<u n="177" who="S0525" trans="overlap">what this that <pause dur="short"/> that's more <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0615">hold the hands in front for a short distance</u>
<u n="179" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh what's up? <pause dur="short"/> oh oh no that that <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's more because it's not it's not that one behind</u>
<u n="180" who="S0615">well that's what it says in here</u>
<u n="181" who="S0525">oh right okay</u>
<u n="182" who="S0615">erm put your fingers to your lips food or go move your hand palm up backwards and forwards is that all?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="184" who="S0615">happy draw an exaggerated smile with your mouth with a finger while smiling</u>
<u n="185" who="S0525">oh you see that's happy</u>
<u n="186" who="S0615">mm hot put your hand out and withdraw it quickly where shrug your shoulders with your palms held out where <pause dur="short"/> rabbit winkle wrinkle up your nose or hold up two fingers <pause dur="short"/> past the <unclear>imaginary</unclear> wheel book hold your hands flat with your palms up yes <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0525" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> we learnt those <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0615">code you need to know more about the art of signing sing and sign classes let's see erm <pause dur="long"/> four and five</u>
<u n="189" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> doesn't tell you how much it is</u>
<u n="190" who="S0615">well I'm going to find out though that was just generally erm <pause dur="long"/> generally reading about baby signing <pause dur="short"/> let's see your baby and <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> where have you heard about it?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0615">I talked to some lady who was talking about it today I knew it existed erm it's also like singing and stuff there as well as the.. <pause dur="short"/>where's the <unclear> bloody</unclear> class?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/> first lesson <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0615">by her second birthday she could sign over two hundred words and say over five hundred speaking in three or more word sentences and describing by size and colours</u>
<u n="195" who="S0525">by what? size colour?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0615">I'm excited to say that my youngest <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> made her first sign at milk at twelve weeks having started signing with her at birth this was quickly followed by bath nappy daddy and mummy by four months</u>
<u n="197" who="S0525" trans="overlap">crikey <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="long"/> gosh I wouldn't have thought they'd have erm pick that up first because they don't seem to have the coordination of <trunc>tha</trunc> they just kick their hands and feet I mean even grabbing things is a problem but signing make the sign I would be surprised if that was er I think she's making that up twelve weeks</u>
<u n="198" who="S0615" trans="overlap">mm I know <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> friday <pause dur="short"/> five fifty per family per class <pause dur="long"/> if that's at <anon type="place"/> Methodist Church</u>
<u n="199" who="S0525">mm <pause dur="long"/> well they can phone about it there might be a a waiting list or there might be spaces</u>
<u n="200" who="S0615">yes it's just</u>
<u n="201" who="S0525">can I bring my mother for the family price? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0615">well yes it says per family <pause dur="long"/> mm excellent well we'll er <unclear/> of that special offers free taster session <pause dur="short"/> yes that's relatively okay that Tiny Talk</u>
<u n="203" who="S0525">mm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0615">Tiny Talk is four</u>
<u n="205" who="S0525">I can barely hear you anyway I will need sign classes or you will we will <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0615">why?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0525">because I can't hear</u>
<u n="208" who="S0615">you can't hear</u>
<u n="209" who="S0525">no I can't hear you over there</u>
<u n="210" who="S0615" trans="overlap">definitely <pause dur="short"/> me</u>
<u n="211" who="S0525">yes</u>
<u n="212" who="S0615">why not?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0525">I can't</u>
<u n="214" who="S0615">oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0525">did he have a sleep this morning <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0615"><unclear>page four</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah while we were out in <anon type="place"/> he had a sleep</u>
<u n="217" who="S0525">how long for? <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0615">fourty-five minutes ish</u>
<u n="219" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> just wondering how long he might sleep now?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0615">oh it's got nothing to do with how long he slept for this morning <vocal desc="sigh"/> who knows?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0525">when does he need his next feed? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0615">he had his last one at twelve o'clock didn't he? so</u>
<u n="223" who="S0525">oh when he wakes up now then</u>
<u n="224" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0525">alright then</u>
<u n="226" who="S0615">whenever <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> rubbish wi-fi</u>
<u n="227" who="S0525">yes it is</u>
<u n="228" who="S0615">ah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> I'm going into school tomorrow <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0525">are you? which school?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0615"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0525">why?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0615">just to see everyone</u>
<u n="233" who="S0525">oh do they know?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0615">no</u>
<u n="235" who="S0525">are you taking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0615">well yes that's kind of the point in going let's see what's in the diary for tomorrow it's book week <pause dur="long"/> yeah nothing much much on</u>
<u n="237" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> when do they break up for Easter? I suppose not until the end of the month do they? it will be a late holiday will they be doing Easter activities?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0615">yes they break up <pause dur="short"/> two weeks tomorrow <anon type="place"/> <unclear>flower show</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0525" trans="overlap">the day before Easter</u>
<u n="240" who="S0615">I'm still hooked up to the school diary</u>
<u n="241" who="S0525">oh I see so you know what's going on?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0525">nice</u>
<u n="244" who="S0615">mm <pause dur="short"/> lovely we have got a meeting today <pause dur="short"/> ah oh right</u>
<u n="245" who="S0525">why did your erm Thursday night tutor girl cancel anyway and rearrange for today?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0615">because she thought she had an assembly at mosque tomorrow</u>
<u n="247" who="S0525">but it's today now?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0525">oh so she could have done tomorrow?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0615">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but erm <pause dur="short"/> no I told you what I said to her that <unclear/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0525">oh yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0615">it is not just the case of <vocal desc="sigh"/> yes fine erm I'll drop it and come to you like that because I can't really do that with a little boy</u>
<u n="253" who="S0525">I know she knows you have got to rearrange things it's erm you're not just the beck and call</u>
<u n="254" who="S0615">no</u>
<u n="255" who="S0525">when I saw <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yesterday he said oh I texted <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I said yes I know oh I would like to sort something else out it's just difficult getting over there at the moment but a Saturday would be good he said I need to get this job sorted and out of the way well it's going to take him six months <vocal desc="laugh"/> I wouldn't hold your breath</u>
<u n="256" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="257" who="S0525">but he said it had been good you were better than the other one the other woman is not erm a primary school teacher she's just a someone that's been tutoring for a long time and isn't very up to date on things according to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she is quite old as well</u>
<u n="258" who="S0615">okay uhu</u>
<u n="259" who="S0525">but he he thinks that he said <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s come erm up in her standards up in her levels since Christmas I said well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said to me that she didn't she wouldn't have put her as behind he said I think because we had a word with the school he says and since Christmas he says they have worked hard with her</u>
<u n="260" who="S0615" trans="overlap">well that's good <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> oh that's good</u>
<u n="261" who="S0525">yeah that's what I thought yeah so <pause dur="short"/> I said well you've always said you thought she was a long way behind I said but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't say that to me</u>
<u n="262" who="S0615">no I didn't</u>
<u n="263" who="S0525">you know didn't think that so that's good <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0615">mm</u>
<u n="265" who="S0525">have you got anything cooking for tea tonight?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0615">ah a bit of an issue with that</u>
<u n="267" who="S0525">really <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0615">I forgot to get the salmon out</u>
<u n="269" who="S0525">oh no</u>
<u n="270" who="S0615">so we haven't got anything</u>
<u n="271" who="S0525">nothing tonight then</u>
<u n="272" who="S0615">no we're gonna have to starve</u>
<u n="273" who="S0525">a takeaway</u>
<u n="274" who="S0615">no</u>
<u n="275" who="S0525">diet</u>
<u n="276" who="S0615">well yeah so no takeaway no</u>
<u n="277" who="S0525">no food then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0615">I don't think I should</u>
<u n="279" who="S0525">ah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0615">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0525">what are you doing for a diet? <pause dur="short"/> low fat again?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0615" trans="overlap">not eating <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> I'm not eating</u>
<u n="283" who="S0525">well you have you just come in here and had a bowl of cornflakes</u>
<u n="284" who="S0615">yeah well they are low fat aren't they?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so what are you doing?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0615">well yeah that</u>
<u n="287" who="S0525">okay</u>
<u n="288" who="S0615">I can't do anything else <vocal desc="yawn"/> it's too much hard work to plan stuff</u>
<u n="289" who="S0525">oh eyes are opening no changed his mind</u>
<u n="290" who="S0615" trans="overlap">no no no <pause dur="short"/> sleep little boy sleep</u>
<u n="291" who="S0525">he's going to need a bottle ready</u>
<u n="292" who="S0615">that's okay it's just in there no need to panic</u>
<u n="293" who="S0525" trans="overlap">excellent <pause dur="short"/> I'll have to go and fill the kettle and boil it it's empty at the moment</u>
<u n="294" who="S0615">he won't wake up just yet I don't think <pause dur="short"/> he probably won't no he'll be alright for sleep so I won't leave his pushchair and it's raining out there so</u>
<u n="295" who="S0525" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's been raining all day here</u>
<u n="296" who="S0615">yes it's been raining where we've been all day soaked all the time</u>
<u n="297" who="S0525" trans="overlap">it's horrible <pause dur="short"/> you can't well your dad's comment was at least the weather is nice up there so it must be alright in Glasgow I wonder if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is having a better day she seems to have driven this morning then she told me she was going to get the train she's got her pass now</u>
<u n="298" who="S0615">well it looks like she's driven</u>
<u n="299" who="S0525">yeah she's got a pass now though oh I suppose she might have done yeah <pause dur="short"/> I saw some interesting photos on her bedside table when I was making her bed earlier <vocal desc="laugh"/> she said she <trunc>mis</trunc> well she must have done for er her train pass she was going the other the other day with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> up to the Coop to get them done</u>
<u n="300" who="S0615" trans="overlap">or driven to the station <pause dur="short"/> photos of what? <pause dur="short"/> oh okay <pause dur="short"/> I see</u>
<u n="301" who="S0525">while I was changing her sheets washing her sheets the usual I did say she could strip one of the beds as she was sleeping in the double bed last night I said oh you could just do that in the morning mum yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0615" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> or did she say I'll do it in the morning and then she didn't</u>
<u n="303" who="S0525">no no she didn't she just laughed at me and said oh you'll do it you'll do it</u>
<u n="304" who="S0615">ah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0525">then there was erm oh Britain's Horror Homes we were watching last night and there was this one infested with dust mites and horrible getting bitten and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like er I said well they are everywhere I said everybody has dust mites in the house I said that photo has just been magnified hundreds of times she was oh I don't believe it you know they show the fibres of things as great big so that's well I'm not going to be able to sleep am I? so I said well go strip your bed then I said yeah why am I always washing your sheets? you don't appreciate it and never once strip your bed I said if it was left to you you're probably infested oh how am I going to sleep now? now I know these things exist? she's on about putting a deposit down on this er B and B place as well for Iceland</u>
<u n="306" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> nice <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh <vocal desc="sigh"/> I'm sure she knew that <pause dur="short"/> oh crikey when?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0525">well no I said well we'll have to have a meeting about it then</u>
<u n="308" who="S0615">a meeting how official</u>
<u n="309" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well everybody will have to have their input won't they?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0615">yes</u>
<u n="311" who="S0525">because for a start it will need to be fairly central you don't want to be miles away from like the tour that we wanted to do and I don't know where it is situated so things like that we will need to look at surely</u>
<u n="312" who="S0615" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's rather <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="313" who="S0525">well and it and what the car hire costs would be because erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s trips included that so by the time you've paid <trunc>th</trunc>the airfare and the fees</u>
<u n="314" who="S0615" trans="overlap">it is I know <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah no it's not far off what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> quoted but just it what you know kind of accommodation obviously that you know that might be a better place because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like oh yeah we'll save money because we will like cook in the house and stuff and I'm like well yeah you could do that <vocal desc="sigh"/> it it looks like you are saving money because that's the thing you know probably you know things I'd say well probably not because by the time you've paid for everything extra even when you do everything bit by bit rather than just all in one <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0525" trans="overlap"><trunc>ye</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes and that's right <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's right <pause dur="short"/> well that's why I'm thinking we need to research what it would be to car hire and do the trips because if it's going to come out really expensive then you are better off stopping at at a hotel</u>
<u n="316" who="S0615">but that's like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he said he got the price or?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0525">yeah you see yes that's what I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s price included that's what I'm saying so if we go down the a B and B route then we need to price up try and get an idea of how much the trips would be if we did them ourselves just to sort of see if we are saving money or not because we don't want to end up paying a lot more do we?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="319" who="S0525">and you've probably got bed and breakfast in the hotel so that's your breakfast sorted so that's why I mean we need to have a little meeting and I I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I said well me and your dad are easy on dates I said erm you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> probably can sort of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will be I said it's really going to depend on erm waiting to find out exactly what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is doing and so she's got an actual although do you know it's going to be Monday Tuesday Wednesday?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah definitely <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="321" who="S0525">you do know that?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0525">but anyway I'm sure <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will be able to be flexible with his as well because she's only talking about four days plus a <trunc>we</trunc> you know two days and a weekend or something so they just need to look at different times and see when the cheapest sort of er weekend would be because if we can be flexible we can go obviously not over <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s birthday but we can go any time there's maybe three or four weekends we could choose from</u>
<u n="324" who="S0615">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> any time <pause dur="short"/> yeah see the price</u>
<u n="325" who="S0525">well exactly</u>
<u n="326" who="S0615">what's the price the cheapest?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0525">yeah or even the January</u>
<u n="328" who="S0615">say again</u>
<u n="329" who="S0525">even leave it to January if it is cheaper</u>
<u n="330" who="S0615" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0525">that's where <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have just been and they've put some great pictures up so</u>
<u n="332" who="S0615">yeah <pause dur="short"/> lovely <pause dur="long"/> well we er we'll have our meeting soon</u>
<u n="333" who="S0525">fine you and that stupid rabbit I will have to check with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> what they want to do</u>
<u n="334" who="S0615">yes they will need to be part of the meeting</u>
<u n="335" who="S0525">well they will really <pause dur="short"/> she didn't want <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> included <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> but then she can't leave them behind if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is not driving that was her other condition</u>
<u n="336" who="S0615" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> he needs to hurry up then doesn't he?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0525">well he doesn't turn seventeen for er for a month so <pause dur="long"/> it just depends how quickly he will do it</u>
<u n="338" who="S0615">well you can't really August September October</u>
<u n="339" who="S0525">that's pushing it</u>
<u n="340" who="S0615">you can't really guarantee that he's gonna be done in that three months</u>
<u n="341" who="S0525" trans="overlap">no no <pause dur="short"/> well now you were quick and it took you three months and that was very quick so maybe January would be a better bet or she takes them then if she takes them we are back to half term and we will need to see how much the prices differ</u>
<u n="342" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah no <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's all gone wrong</u>
<u n="343" who="S0525">well there's a lot to think about when you are taking a group isn't it that's the thing</u>
<u n="344" who="S0615">yes definitely</u>
<u n="345" who="S0525">I think four days will be enough anyway for all of us <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0615">yes <unclear/> mm <pause dur="long"/> definitely</u>
<u n="347" who="S0525">how how's his cold doing? is he getting any better? still coughing</u>
<u n="348" who="S0615">he's fine</u>
<u n="349" who="S0525">is he? oh that's good do you think he's too hot under all that blanket or is he alright?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0615"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> it's a fake cough <pause dur="short"/> no he's cracking</u>
<u n="351" who="S0525">a fake cough <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't do a fake cough</u>
<u n="352" who="S0615">he does <pause dur="short"/> for attention</u>
<u n="353" who="S0525"><vocal desc="laugh"/> for attention <pause dur="short"/> is he like his daddy? are you like your daddy <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do you like attention? <pause dur="short"/> typical boy <pause dur="short"/> that's gonna fall</u>
<u n="354" who="S0615" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> no it's not</u>
<u n="355" who="S0525">oh yes it</u>
<u n="356" who="S0615">it's not <pause dur="short"/> miss monkey is going to fall <pause dur="short"/> don't be silly</u>
<u n="357" who="S0525" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it was his blanket I was going to take off him not his monkey <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="358" who="S0615">well I've just felt him and he's okay</u>
<u n="359" who="S0525">okay then <pause dur="short"/> mummy knows best</u>
<u n="360" who="S0615">yeah <pause dur="short"/> too right</u>
<u n="361" who="S0525">fair enough</u>
<u n="362" who="S0615">eh</u>
<u n="363" who="S0525">what's er on your list for tutoring today then? it's the two girls isn't it?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0615">yeah I've got to leave in a minute</u>
<u n="365" who="S0525">what subject?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0615">we are adding and subtracting two digit numbers <pause dur="short"/> using a hundred square</u>
<u n="367" who="S0525">oh <pause dur="short"/> sounds more complicated than it is I'm sure I don't quite know what that means but I bet I could answer the questions</u>
<u n="368" who="S0615" trans="overlap">isn't that exciting? <pause dur="short"/> well a hundred square <pause dur="short"/> yeah all the numbers from one to a hundred in rows of ten</u>
<u n="369" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> in a square <pause dur="short"/> in rows of ten would would work yes</u>
<u n="370" who="S0615">would work as a square so if you've got I don't know sixty-three add twenty-five <pause dur="short"/> you split your twenty-five up you partition it into twenty and five start on sixty-three on the hundred square you add twenty jumping down to where it <unclear/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh I see</u>
<u n="372" who="S0615">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so we're doing that <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0525">yeah why do you learn like that? well I suppose that's how you do it in your head then isn't it?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0525">then you just see you progress from leaving the square behind</u>
<u n="376" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm mm</u>
<u n="377" who="S0525">oh I see it's just</u>
<u n="378" who="S0615">so once they see that sixty-three add twenty is eighty-three and then they can do that quickly in their head</u>
<u n="379" who="S0525" trans="overlap">right I see they just <pause dur="short"/> yeah then it's easy to get to eighty-eight</u>
<u n="380" who="S0615">yeah we are doing <unclear/> that's what children find the most difficult when I asked <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the other day to add what was it? oh yeah one of the girls she had twenty-seven I said oh well add ten on she went twenty-eight twenty-nine thirty thirty-one thirty-two thirty-three thirty-four thirty-five thirty-six thirty-seven yeah so I'm going to ask them first of all they're just <trunc>go</trunc> because they've got their hundred square they've got to fill in the missing gaps as it is <pause dur="short"/> then erm</u>
<u n="381" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh really <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="382" who="S0615">they've got to I'm going to ask them oh what's yeah what's thirty-three add ten and then I'm just going to see straightaway</u>
<u n="383" who="S0525">right <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0615">so we will see <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> how we get on <vocal desc="yawn"/> hopefully</u>
<u n="385" who="S0525">okay <pause dur="short"/> is it <unclear>Little House</unclear> round there?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0615">yeah <unclear>turning</unclear></u>
<u n="387" who="S0525">yeah <unclear>turning</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> and what school are they at?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0615"><anon type="place"/> <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> the kitchen is really small</u>
<u n="389" who="S0525" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> is it? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0615">it's like a lounge and going back into a a dining room probably the ground floor is not much bigger than this lounge <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0525" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh really</u>
<u n="392" who="S0615">because you go in and get straight into the <pause dur="short"/> no no the kitchen goes a bit on because they've got a garage there so you go in and you go into the lounge and then you've got the just the dining table at the back and then you've got the wall wall stairs going up and then you have got the kitchen in there but so the kitchen is just well it's quite it's like a a little box room really you go in and there's a <unclear/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0525" trans="overlap">what and that there's a kitchen <pause dur="short"/> oh right <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> has it got a window?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0615">yeah it's at the back <unclear/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0525">oh it has because that kitchen we looked at in that that house when I was looking at ones for you</u>
<u n="396" who="S0615">which house?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0525">the one you sent me to look at first of all for you and I think you did go and <vocal desc="cough"/> see it</u>
<u n="398" who="S0615">oh yeah that one oh that was horrible wasn't it?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0525">was there was there no window in that kitchen was there? nor was there one at the front and I don't think there was it just it was like a room you went into <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0615">what was behind it then?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0525">I'm just trying to remember I don't think I don't think it had a window in it <pause dur="short"/> that was a really weird layout that was it was like a cupboard off the lounge they had turned into a kitchen</u>
<u n="402" who="S0615" trans="overlap">oh you let it get like that <pause dur="short"/> that was awful <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah well they'd almost like stuck another yeah it was <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0525">there's was waste they had to did they have the the downstairs toilet there in a little hallway?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0615">yeah you went in and it was a little hall and you go to the garage or you had the <unclear/> you went through another door you had a lounge but you had the stairs there but it was like</u>
<u n="405" who="S0525" trans="overlap">that's right <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> it was nice to have that <pause dur="short"/> that's right the stairs yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0615">where would you put your sofa?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0525">that's right</u>
<u n="408" who="S0615">where would you put your TV? because there was no TV point there it was like over there your dining space was quite nice because you had a big the big french doors but yeah then you had the tiny little kitchen</u>
<u n="409" who="S0525" trans="overlap">and your dining table you couldn't could you <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes but if you added erm a table there you are struggling to get sofas and a <pause dur="short"/> well <trunc>it</trunc> it's like yours is now really but probably even smaller than that it was just wasted with that entrance hall</u>
<u n="410" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0525">it was nice to have that and then you felt you were going into something bigger but it was a bit pointless because there was nothing else there then was there?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0615" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> she had already bought that knock that out and then have the erm <pause dur="short"/> maybe if they needed a downstairs toilet have it under the erm stairs or something</u>
<u n="413" who="S0525">mm</u>
<u n="414" who="S0615">and then yeah she would have had a a big lounge dining room at the back and then that kitchen I don't know why why it was so small they could have brought it out to the stairs and had a bigger room which is odd</u>
<u n="415" who="S0525">no yours is better way it's erm proportioned</u>
<u n="416" who="S0615" trans="overlap">we've all <pause dur="short"/> pointing to the garage</u>
<u n="417" who="S0525">mm <pause dur="short"/> and they had three bedrooms upstairs as well didn't they?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0615">yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0525">so you really lost the space because they they were small</u>
<u n="420" who="S0615">yeah they were tiny yeah the bedrooms</u>
<u n="421" who="S0525">mind you that <trunc>you</trunc> your second bedroom is big bigger than you'd normally get in a and probably bigger than you'll get in your next house as a but if you make it into two you really lose the the room don't you?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0615" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I mean you couldn't make ours into two at the moment</u>
<u n="423" who="S0525">no no you are not not that particular one I'm thinking just to use the actual space you've got because our house before in <anon type="place"/> had three bedrooms but you you would have struggled to get a bed in the one are you going to have to go now are you?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0615" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes five minutes to leave</u>
<u n="425" who="S0525">alright then erm</u>
<u n="426" who="S0615">I need to get myself ready</u>
<u n="427" who="S0525">well can you get a bottle and the milk and everything?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0615">yeah because it's all it's all in here</u>
<u n="429" who="S0525">will he need his nappy changing?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0615">he will</u>
<u n="431" who="S0525">before he starts during after?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0615">whenever you want I'll leave it up to you</u>
<u n="433" who="S0525">what's that mark on the floor now?</u>
<u n="434" who="S0615">he hasn't had it <pause dur="short"/> where?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0525">I've just hoovered</u>
<u n="436" who="S0615">a bit of fluff</u>
<u n="437" who="S0525">he hasn't what?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0615">er?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0525">what did you say? he hasn't what?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0615">he hasn't had a nappy change since erm we went out before toy library so about well about one o'clock or something like that so not that long ago</u>
<u n="441" who="S0525" trans="overlap">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> so I'll put a clean one for your feed and then you can poo in it</u>
<u n="442" who="S0615">well it's up to you whatever you feel like I'm late <unclear/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0525" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> have you got your? does he need his cream on?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0615">er?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0525">does he need his cream?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0615">not at the moment he's alright</u>
<u n="447" who="S0525">oh good is he not sore any more?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0615">we haven't we haven't changed his nappy in a while</u>
<u n="449" who="S0525">well no you because you always say <trunc>I</trunc>I'll do it which is fine <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh you are going to wake him up because you're leaving aren't you?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0615" trans="overlap">nanny's missing out <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> well I'm just going to put him on the sofa actually because he's been in that car seat for a while now</u>
<u n="451" who="S0525">alright then I don't like him in the car seat too long with all the regulations <pause dur="long"/> oh here we go <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh bless I can do this <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> I daren't leave him on the sofa now to go in the other room in case I think he's going to er wriggle off it now</u>
<u n="452" who="S0615" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> he's alright if he's asleep because he doesn't</u>
<u n="453" who="S0525">I know yes if he is asleep yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0615">okay right I'm going to go now</u>
<u n="455" who="S0525">well on your way out would you erm put that in the dishwasher fill fill the kettle and boil it so that I can have some warm water ready yeah? alright then <pause dur="short"/> thank you very much</u>
<u n="456" who="S0615" trans="overlap">yeah fine <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> bye now</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
