<text id="SPTQ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:28:38</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-01-18</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0281 S0355</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Restaurant, Brighton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>health, Green Party, jobs, boot sales, relationships.</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about news, personal situation</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0281">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Brighton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>30</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0355">
				<exactage>64</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hove, Sussex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hove, Sussex</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>64 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Business Owner</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>4</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0281">hi <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so <pause dur="short"/> what er kind of day have you had?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0355">I've had a a varied day I have erm <pause dur="short"/> er I was and I've been to the doctor <pause dur="short"/> and erm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0281">what's that about?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0355">that was about my Dupuytren's Contracture</u>
<u n="5" who="S0281">oh sounds nasty</u>
<u n="6" who="S0355">it is it's er</u>
<u n="7" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0355"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's a erm <event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0281">do you take those <event desc="unintelligible"/> for it?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0355">no <pause dur="short"/> no er I wish I could <pause dur="short"/> but it is a erm a I suppose it's a disease but it's a condition where <pause dur="short"/> erm collagen builds up in the hand er and attaches itself to the various erm <pause dur="short"/> er bits on the hand and causes the hand to contract</u>
<u n="11" who="S0281">oh</u>
<u n="12" who="S0355" trans="overlap">the tendons to contract and pull the the hand into a claw</u>
<u n="13" who="S0281">oh so you walk walk around with your hand in a claw mm scaring young ladies?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0355">erm no <pause dur="short"/> not at all</u>
<u n="15" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0355">I wouldn't want to scare young ladies <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no erm so</u>
<u n="17" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well it's funny you should say that cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has got the same thing</u>
<u n="18" who="S0355">oh he has has he?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0355">oh</u>
<u n="21" who="S0281">got the same</u>
<u n="22" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0281">but he's he's not worried about it cos but he he's retired so</u>
<u n="24" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="25" who="S0281">he doesn't have to work so and it doesn't cause him any discomfort</u>
<u n="26" who="S0355">oh right yeah but it does get worse I mean</u>
<u n="27" who="S0281" trans="overlap">does it?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0355" trans="overlap">it's better to get it sorted out before it gets worse</u>
<u n="29" who="S0281">really? I think he</u>
<u n="30" who="S0355" trans="overlap">that's why</u>
<u n="31" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I think he said he already had an operation on the other hand</u>
<u n="32" who="S0355">oh right</u>
<u n="33" who="S0281">and took about five to five to six weeks to recover</u>
<u n="34" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="35" who="S0281" trans="overlap">so it's a</u>
<u n="36" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0281">yeah anyway</u>
<u n="38" who="S0355">oh I wouldn't mind chatting to him about that</u>
<u n="39" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="short"/> okay</u>
<u n="40" who="S0355">just got a text through here one new message <pause dur="short"/> oh right it's er <pause dur="short"/> from my ex girlfriend <pause dur="short"/> well still my girlfriend but we're not er</u>
<u n="41" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0355">we're not er</u>
<u n="43" who="S0281" trans="overlap">a friend who's a girl</u>
<u n="44" who="S0355" trans="overlap">going out</u>
<u n="45" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="46" who="S0355">oh we're friends yeah we're not erm <pause dur="short"/> we're not sleeping together <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm and yeah so the doctor arranged for me to have a an operation or or to rather to see a specialist <pause dur="short"/> erm and she asked me about my diabetes er which I talked about erm she er offered me statins but I said to control my <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> er what is it? my erm cholesterol levels</u>
<u n="47" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0355">but <pause dur="short"/> I said to her look we've left it until my next <pause dur="short"/> sort of large check up in February and I'm going to <pause dur="short"/> go and erm er I'm going to try this diet to get my weight down in the next erm sort of six weeks to get get get er some weight loss going on</u>
<u n="49" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0355">so erm see how it goes then and er yeah that's it erm <pause dur="short"/> and I told her about the pains in my shoulders <vocal desc="laugh"/> er which she didn't offer any input to</u>
<u n="51" who="S0281">what is it? rheumatism?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0355">I don't know I think it could be erm higher <pause dur="short"/> sugar levels attacking the muscles that's what happens in diabetes</u>
<u n="53" who="S0281" trans="overlap">is it?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0281">oh it's er and it's related to the diabetes?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0355">yeah I mean I'm in danger of er terrible things with diabetes if I don't watch it</u>
<u n="57" who="S0281" trans="overlap">really? <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh yeah kidney failure blindness</u>
<u n="59" who="S0281">oh my god</u>
<u n="60" who="S0355" trans="overlap">losing my limbs yeah oh very serious it's a very serious diabetes is a very serious thing <pause dur="short"/> very serious</u>
<u n="61" who="S0281">do you take it seriously? cos you don't seem to <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="62" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well I I keep a check on my figures well I did in her office I checked my figures and it was nine point six after <pause dur="short"/> erm after about an hour and a half after I'd had my breakfast</u>
<u n="63" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0355">which er</u>
<u n="65" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and what should it be?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0355">yeah it wasn't too bad I mean it could could have been a bit better but it wasn't bad <pause dur="short"/> yeah wasn't bad but whereas I should be about when I wake up in the morning about four <trunc>so</trunc>something like that</u>
<u n="67" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0355">I <trunc>sh</trunc> it's probably about seven <pause dur="short"/> so erm <pause dur="short"/> I should er I've got to keep an eye on it but I let I've let it go recently I've let I I've let it go because I haven't erm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0281">well because of Christmas? or</u>
<u n="70" who="S0355">Christmas erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I shall focus on it again</u>
<u n="71" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="72" who="S0355">and er <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'll focus on it again <pause dur="short"/> so I went to the doctor's I left the doctor's and er what did I do then? erm I think I came home and er</u>
<u n="73" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0355">saw you <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I think I had a coffee and a <pause dur="short"/> and a bun <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="76" who="S0355">and er <vocal desc="laugh"/> then erm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0281" trans="overlap">what what about that canvassing? you know you it didn't work out because somebody didn't turn up and you've got to do it tomorrow?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0355">yes I went to canvassing I canvass on behalf of the Green Party and er <pause dur="short"/> I turned up to er canvass on behalf of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's the leader of the Green Party and erm <pause dur="short"/> but er <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I got the time and the place wrong but no-one turned up <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0281" trans="overlap">did he he er give you any explanation?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0355">well I can't I haven't yet contacted the person who er <pause dur="short"/> who erm <pause dur="short"/> who asked me who contacted me in the first place I've just got an email or not an email erm a text through from another councillor to tell me</u>
<u n="81" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0355">erm the telephone number of the person that they believe who co-ordinates <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="83" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0355">campaign so I shall text them to say <pause dur="short"/> is it you I'm supposed to be speaking to? erm and er if so</u>
<u n="85" who="S0281" trans="overlap">why why are they doing why are they doing this so early? cos the election's in May isn't it? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0355">well</u>
<u n="87" who="S0281" trans="overlap">isn't it in May?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0355">probably but I mean why not now? <pause dur="short"/> it's a continuous thing <pause dur="short"/> it starts off if you</u>
<u n="89" who="S0281" trans="overlap">so what</u>
<u n="90" who="S0355" trans="overlap">you had a look</u>
<u n="91" who="S0281" trans="overlap">what's the point of canvassing? you try and basically persuade people to vote for you? I mean is that what you do?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well yes yes it's to</u>
<u n="93" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and you're deciding how you're gonna vote</u>
<u n="94" who="S0355" trans="overlap">er you meet different types of people you meet the person who says I don't wanna know about it <pause dur="short"/> f off and you get really agitated and annoyed <pause dur="short"/> then you meet people who erm go oh yes wonderful I voted I will always vote Green fantastic <pause dur="short"/> then you meet people who er <pause dur="short"/> who ask you loads of questions <pause dur="short"/> they drive you mad <pause dur="short"/> question after question and er you can get trapped by these people erm just talking and talking and talking so I generally</u>
<u n="95" who="S0281">what do you mean trapped?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0355" trans="overlap"><trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="97" who="S0281">you mean just spending too</u>
<u n="98" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well they'll go on and on</u>
<u n="99" who="S0281" trans="overlap">too much time?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0355">they're trying to be clever and prove a point</u>
<u n="101" who="S0281">are they?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0355">and they're probably very very lonely people who who never get people walking up to them and saying hello with a smiling face and saying how are you?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0281"><event desc="unintelligible"/></u>
<u n="104" who="S0355">and <trunc>wh</trunc>what's your opinion? and er you know so they they want a friend and that's nice but if you're going to try and reach a lot of people you can't <pause dur="short"/> like a doctor <pause dur="short"/> you can't devote that much time to to them er but you can er but that's all part of learning how to canvass well I think er knowing how to let them go how to let them go feeling good about themselves erm I normally say well look er er and and I'm <trunc>qui</trunc> er look er you're obviously very interested in this which is fantastic er I would go and look on the website and I will give them the website details and they'll hopefully we we've got another supporter and I say to to <trunc>th</trunc> as well would you be prepared to give an hour of your time a week to something if you care about the planet and the people on it an hour of your time just licking envelopes or or putting out some flyers? er but you know you could do something because you meet people and broaden your horizons learn a bit about ecological er issues peace issues erm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="106" who="S0355">so er yeah there's that type and there's</u>
<u n="107" who="S0281">well <trunc>don</trunc> what's the percentage of people who vote like in the last election?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0355">erm <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't know</u>
<u n="109" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0355">I wouldn't know I think it's in the last general election</u>
<u n="111" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0355">I would think it's pretty small I I would think probably I I don't know I would hazard a guess and say possibly sixty percent possibly I don't know but that's only a guess and that <trunc>cou</trunc> those statistics are easily found out nowadays with computers</u>
<u n="113" who="S0281">mm it would be easy to find out yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0355">yes <pause dur="long"/> what about the background noise of the er where we're recording will that affect the quality of the recording?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0281">well it's not that loud</u>
<u n="116" who="S0355">right okay</u>
<u n="117" who="S0281">mm we've got this little er thing here</u>
<u n="118" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0281">who you can see er <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I I don't think so</u>
<u n="120" who="S0355">okay <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0281">but erm I mean they <pause dur="short"/> be able to hear you see every time the the voice speaks it spikes</u>
<u n="122" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="123" who="S0281">so I don't think so yeah it should be alright</u>
<u n="124" who="S0355">yeah so erm yeah well er I went out canvassing that was er this evening and I met an old girlfriend of mine and erm it was very nice to see her she's a rock climber and runs a women's group for rock climbing women</u>
<u n="125" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0355"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she's won awards for that er through her service to the community and erm er and I was very pleased for her she was very very <pause dur="short"/> proud it was an achievement for her to win that award <pause dur="short"/> er it was not only great for her to win it but it was great of er people in our society to to er help people attain those sort of achievements and feel good about themselves and I and I think that's a wonderful thing erm yeah I think she was the Argus awards she was er <pause dur="short"/> erm nominated for those and er won one of those <pause dur="short"/> so that was good erm</u>
<u n="127" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you haven't said anything about my new glasses</u>
<u n="128" who="S0355">your new glasses let me have a look</u>
<u n="129" who="S0281" trans="overlap">you didn't even notice</u>
<u n="130" who="S0355" trans="overlap">may I I'm sorry I beg your pardon <pause dur="short"/> yes they yeah they suit you</u>
<u n="131" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0355">they look new they look very swish and new</u>
<u n="133" who="S0281">I these are my old frames</u>
<u n="134" who="S0355">yeah really?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0281">yeah I just</u>
<u n="136" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="137" who="S0281" trans="overlap">just put new lenses in</u>
<u n="138" who="S0355">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well they</u>
<u n="139" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well the the guy erm said oh <trunc>sh</trunc> said I I like those I like those frames said er green ones said ah they look black to me</u>
<u n="140" who="S0355">oh</u>
<u n="141" who="S0281">and they look green</u>
<u n="142" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0281">I dunno</u>
<u n="144" who="S0355">are the ears new?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0281">ears?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0355">the ears <pause dur="short"/> your ears they</u>
<u n="147" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0355">they've they're all new</u>
<u n="149" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah I had a <trunc>tra</trunc> I had an ear transplant</u>
<u n="150" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="151" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah well at the same time</u>
<u n="152" who="S0355">still got the er still got the old ears <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0281">ear ear <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="154" who="S0355">I'm stopping smoking that cough is from cough stopping smoking <pause dur="short"/> so that's er something I've been doing stopping smoking and drinking</u>
<u n="155" who="S0281">or not doing</u>
<u n="156" who="S0355" trans="overlap">and drinking mm stopping drinking but</u>
<u n="157" who="S0281">you're in danger of becoming healthy and</u>
<u n="158" who="S0355">well I have been there</u>
<u n="159" who="S0281">if you carry on</u>
<u n="160" who="S0355">I've been there <pause dur="short"/> I have been that man</u>
<u n="161" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and will be again</u>
<u n="162" who="S0355">and shall be again <pause dur="short"/> I shall be again <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh well we enjoyed a very nice meal it was carvery here this evening <pause dur="short"/> at erm <anon type="place"/> in er <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0281">mm yeah and it was amazingly cheap wasn't it?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="165" who="S0281" trans="overlap">have to come here again <pause dur="short"/> pity it's so far away you could</u>
<u n="166" who="S0355">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0281">be a real bonus if you lived close</u>
<u n="168" who="S0355">it would be it would be <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0281">I wonder why they situated it out here outside of <anon type="place"/> rather than inside do you think it's a bit cheaper? for the rents and <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="170" who="S0355" trans="overlap">they looked for a pub that suited the the the concept I think <pause dur="short"/> because the position's good where it is it's got a catchment area <pause dur="short"/> it's er</u>
<u n="171" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well yeah I <trunc>mea</trunc></u>
<u n="172" who="S0355" trans="overlap">near the beach</u>
<u n="173" who="S0281">yeah but</u>
<u n="174" who="S0355"><trunc>i</trunc> it's</u>
<u n="175" who="S0281" trans="overlap">you you've got to you've got to really have a car unless you're really local</u>
<u n="176" who="S0355">well I would imagine there's quite a few locals round here really local <pause dur="short"/> I would have thought erm there's a carvery in the marina</u>
<u n="177" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0355" trans="overlap">and there's a carvery in <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> just</u>
<u n="179" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="180" who="S0355">er up the road here so it's in the middle of two <pause dur="short"/> and then a next carvery from that is at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="182" who="S0355">so they're they're sort of run on the same lines as this <pause dur="long"/> erm yeah so <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0281">I had a bit of a disappointment with that er job interview it was erm <pause dur="short"/> at first I thought it was gonna be okay but then er I got a an email today saying that erm they haven't got as many students coming over as er as they thought so</u>
<u n="184" who="S0355">I'm very sorry to hear that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="short"/> still you never know <pause dur="short"/> something might come of it</u>
<u n="186" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="187" who="S0281">or something else will come up sooner or later</u>
<u n="188" who="S0355">I'm sure <pause dur="short"/> there's a good saying <pause dur="short"/> cream rises</u>
<u n="189" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0355">cream rises er hurrah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0281">yeah but there again so do turds <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0355">well <pause dur="short"/> yeah they do yeah you're right</u>
<u n="193" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> sometimes</u>
<u n="194" who="S0355">and creamy turds</u>
<u n="195" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0355">rise even faster <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="198" who="S0355">yeah I thought we had to keep this recording clean</u>
<u n="199" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0355">no swearing <pause dur="short"/> and rudeness</u>
<u n="201" who="S0281">turd's not a swear word is it?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0355">erm probably not no it's not is it?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0281">it's not the correct word</u>
<u n="204" who="S0355" trans="overlap">like masturbation or vagina it's er</u>
<u n="205" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0355">you <unclear>vagina</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0355">you silly old vagina</u>
<u n="209" who="S0281" trans="overlap">who are <trunc>yo</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> who who are you calling a vagina?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0355">you you vagina</u>
<u n="211" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0355">you you <vocal desc="laugh"/> you sleepy vagina <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0355" trans="overlap">mm so erm <pause dur="short"/> well</u>
<u n="215" who="S0281">what's on the cards for tomorrow?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0355">tomorrow I er would imagine my work associate will be still ill <pause dur="short"/> so I think I will erm I shall er <pause dur="short"/> what shall I do? I don't know I will</u>
<u n="217" who="S0281">do you need do you need him to be there?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0355">not really but if I go and do some work and he's not there then you know I'll feel that I've done more than he has <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0281">well I mean do you can't you since you're you've got a well it seems to me a sort of loose <trunc>wor</trunc> working relationship you can just say</u>
<u n="220" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="221" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well look I'm I'm doing all this work I don't think it's fair that I you you know we split the money fifty fifty can't you say that?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well he he would argue that that erm <pause dur="short"/> it it's it's just better if I don't get into the position of that argument <pause dur="short"/> if I just go yeah I'm not feeling too good either <pause dur="short"/>  it's just simpler to do that because</u>
<u n="223" who="S0281">well can't you talk honestly <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well the truth is I hate work <pause dur="short"/> and er I loathe work by myself anyway</u>
<u n="225" who="S0281">really?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0355">working on my own I find quite lonely sometimes</u>
<u n="227" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0355">unless there is a <pause dur="short"/> a financial erm drive if there's a financial er <trunc>i</trunc>impetus er yeah if there's if I know I can go and oh well actually I am going in to work tomorrow</u>
<u n="229" who="S0281">is that a woman who's?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0355" trans="overlap">a customer an old customer of mine phoned me up and asked me if I could do a small job for her which I can and I can <event desc="unintelligible"/> for that it won't be much</u>
<u n="231" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0355">be a <unclear>retainer</unclear> or something for that is a <event desc="unintelligible"/> so then</u>
<u n="233" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and then</u>
<u n="234" who="S0355" trans="overlap">that'll be nice</u>
<u n="235" who="S0281" trans="overlap">you can do the work afterwards</u>
<u n="236" who="S0355">I might do</u>
<u n="237" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0355">I might do but I've got to go and buy some materials</u>
<u n="239" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0355">which I'm not too sure about doing</u>
<u n="241" who="S0281">you've still got those bits and pieces those er that you've been buying lately to get to sell and resell haven't you?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0355"><pause dur="short"/> I have I have but er it's where do I?<pause dur="short"/> erm yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0281">well where do you sell them?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0355">where do I sell them exactly?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0281">oh I <trunc>thou</trunc> oh I thought you had people in mind when you buy them where you could</u>
<u n="246" who="S0355">well I do I do I do but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> one of the people who buys er bits and bobs off me she has as she's redecorating her shop and she said she's not buying anymore stock until she has redecorated</u>
<u n="247" who="S0281">yeah well that's <unclear>nice</unclear></u>
<u n="248" who="S0355">so it's fair enough erm</u>
<u n="249" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0355">she's got to clear all the stuff out of the shop that she's got in there to redecorate <pause dur="short"/> and it would be nice for her to set everything out erm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="252" who="S0355">with erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0281">have you ever thought about getting a shop and buying and selling stuff?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well I have but the it's er <pause dur="short"/> it's a big commitment <pause dur="short"/> erm you've got to sit unless you've got a shop in a very busy place where you've got lots of people coming in and out and <pause dur="short"/> and like a gift shop something like that on <anon type="place"/> seafront selling objet d'art would be good down there you know <pause dur="short"/> but it's er <pause dur="long"/> places <pause dur="short"/> in a seaside town that you're aiming for <pause dur="short"/> for turnover from the general public IE holiday makers <pause dur="short"/> really depends on the weather and some years you can actually <trunc>s</trunc> take virtually nothing the whole year because er the weather's so appalling certainly if it's in a place where the <pause dur="short"/> that only really caters for the <pause dur="short"/> sun seekers or tourists it's erm sometimes in the winter it can be completely dead</u>
<u n="255" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="256" who="S0355">so it's quite difficult looking for a market if you deal in <pause dur="short"/> really really <pause dur="short"/> upmarket pieces you've got to get get you've got to find the the market and and erm and and go for market <pause dur="short"/> I mean if you have really top dollar stuff in a shop erm you can't put any rubbish in there you can't put anything for a fiver in there people <pause dur="short"/> people you lose credibility it's all got to be magnificent quality</u>
<u n="257" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0355">erm <pause dur="short"/> er er</u>
<u n="259" who="S0281" trans="overlap">you you were saying you were saying earlier that like erm</u>
<u n="260" who="S0355">or all a fiver</u>
<u n="261" who="S0281" trans="overlap">you you er <pause dur="short"/> you you hate work or hate working <pause dur="short"/> well <trunc>wh</trunc>what?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I'm <trunc>tir</trunc> I don't hate it I'm tired of it I've worked very hard all my life since I was fifteen and er grafted a lot and I'm get getting old I'm sixty <pause dur="short"/> four this year sixty-four this year <pause dur="short"/> and I'm getting aches and pains and I I I've had my family I've had my life I've had my child I've I've had it all and now it's my time before I die it's my time <pause dur="short"/> it's time for me to give myself those little things like a an afternoon <vocal desc="laugh"/> in the country walking a dog I'd like a dog I can't have one cos I work</u>
<u n="263" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="264" who="S0355">erm be lovely to have a dog</u>
<u n="265" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="266" who="S0355">be nice to have the time to give a girlfriend during the day you know it's and <trunc>li</trunc> well be with them now and again during the day rather than just at weekends <pause dur="short"/> so maybe you know <pause dur="short"/> maybe things'll go right</u>
<u n="267" who="S0281">so you're equating having a dog with a girlfriend? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0355">well</u>
<u n="269" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0355">I think they look er I I I missed that I'm sorry <pause dur="short"/> I wear hearing aids</u>
<u n="271" who="S0281"><trunc>ha</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0355">yes that's true that was a little wind up what was your what was your <trunc>jocul</trunc> jocular remark Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0281">no just about <pause dur="short"/> maybe any <trunc>similarit</trunc></u>
<u n="274" who="S0355" trans="overlap">dogs and women</u>
<u n="275" who="S0281"><pause dur="short"/> any similarities between dogs and women you know</u>
<u n="276" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well I'd like er <pause dur="short"/> I'd like er er a a woman like er <pause dur="short"/> like one of those er</u>
<u n="277" who="S0281">a Spaniel?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0355">no I'd like</u>
<u n="279" who="S0281">a Doberman? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0355">I'd quite like a <pause dur="short"/> I'd quite like a</u>
<u n="281" who="S0281" trans="overlap">a Pekingese?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0355">no I'd quite like erm <pause dur="short"/> I'd quite like er <pause dur="short"/> er oh what are they called? Labradors they're nice</u>
<u n="283" who="S0281">oh they're lovely</u>
<u n="284" who="S0355">Labradors or er or</u>
<u n="285" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well er you remember I had one didn't remember Honey?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0355">I did yes yes</u>
<u n="287" who="S0281">she's</u>
<u n="288" who="S0355" trans="overlap">she was golden</u>
<u n="289" who="S0281" trans="overlap">she was lovely</u>
<u n="290" who="S0355" trans="overlap">she was golden she was a Golden Retriever wasn't she?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0281">er no a Labrador</u>
<u n="292" who="S0355">oh was she? she was gold though</u>
<u n="293" who="S0281">mm Golden Labrador</u>
<u n="294" who="S0355">oh right Golden Labrador <pause dur="short"/> so erm</u>
<u n="295" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah it broke my heart when er</u>
<u n="296" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh dear</u>
<u n="297" who="S0281" trans="overlap">she died er I had to bury her</u>
<u n="298" who="S0355">oh I'm so sorry</u>
<u n="299" who="S0281">in the garden</u>
<u n="300" who="S0355">I'm sorry about that</u>
<u n="301" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="long"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> same with the cat remember we took them both to France and</u>
<u n="302" who="S0355">oh you took Honey to France the dog to France then?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah the two yeah the</u>
<u n="304" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0281">said the other night you know</u>
<u n="306" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0281" trans="overlap">the well when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came round she said when when we went to France <pause dur="short"/> we had the bed in the back</u>
<u n="308" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="309" who="S0281">and <pause dur="short"/> er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> er and Honey and Becky the cat</u>
<u n="310" who="S0355"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh yes yes oh</u>
<u n="311" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0355">ah <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the parrot?</u>
<u n="313" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the boy</u>
<u n="314" who="S0355">oh the boy <trunc>y</trunc>yes that's <trunc>righ</trunc></u>
<u n="315" who="S0281">mind you</u>
<u n="316" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0281" trans="overlap">he he does talk a lot</u>
<u n="318" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0281">got verbal diarrhoea</u>
<u n="320" who="S0355">lays the occasional egg</u>
<u n="321" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0281">are you thinking of having a a dessert then?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0355">not really</u>
<u n="325" who="S0281">no</u>
<u n="326" who="S0355">I'm a diabetic <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0355">West Country chocolate fudge cake served hot or cold with fluffy cream and Belgian chocolate sauce oh god</u>
<u n="329" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm yummy</u>
<u n="330" who="S0355">no I don't want it <pause dur="short"/> I've got strength and resilience I'm going for the ice cream instead</u>
<u n="331" who="S0281"><vocal desc="cough"/> no</u>
<u n="332" who="S0355">oh you look you can get bottomless ice cream here <pause dur="short"/> help yourself</u>
<u n="333" who="S0281" trans="overlap">what the hell's that?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0355" trans="overlap">to all the soft Cornish style ice cream and sauces <pause dur="short"/> one ninety-nine</u>
<u n="335" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0355">shall we share one?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="338" who="S0355">it says we can't share it on the menu</u>
<u n="339" who="S0281">really?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0355">well I could get one and you could <pause dur="short"/> and then you could have some</u>
<u n="341" who="S0281">okay <pause dur="short"/> do you <pause dur="short"/> do you want to do it now?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0355">maybe <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> waving the are we still recording here?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="344" who="S0355">oh we've done twenty-five minutes <pause dur="short"/> oh wow there you go so to give these lovely Cambridge <pause dur="short"/> spies er erm people a <pause dur="short"/> a erm a conversation</u>
<u n="345" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0355">they'll be yawning about what people do won't they?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="348" who="S0355">although I suppose what they do isn't much difference <pause dur="short"/> is it?</u>
<u n="349" who="S0281">I I dunno I dunno really how how these conversations are gonna be used got no idea</u>
<u n="350" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well you know I mean if they're going with Cambridge it's very doubtful they'd come to a place like er</u>
<u n="351" who="S0281">why not?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0355">the <anon type="place"/> carvery well because er they I think they'd consider it beneath them</u>
<u n="353" who="S0281">well it's not actually <trunc>Ca</trunc>Cambridge University it's Cambridge University Press</u>
<u n="354" who="S0355">oh right well I still well they're probably reasonably well paid though aren't they?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0281">well I should imagine so</u>
<u n="356" who="S0355">I mean they wouldn't come to place where you get a a roast meal and <trunc>s</trunc> erm <pause dur="short"/> for four pound thirty-six and</u>
<u n="357" who="S0281">why not?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0355">well I think it's the type of people they'd be sitting amongst</u>
<u n="359" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0355">I mean they really don't you think so?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0281">no</u>
<u n="362" who="S0355">no <pause dur="long"/> so you don't think they're elitist?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0281">I should think they're</u>
<u n="364" who="S0355" trans="overlap">or snobs?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0281">they're <pause dur="short"/> normal people as er as anybody who can be called normal is normal</u>
<u n="366" who="S0355">right <pause dur="short"/> there you go then <pause dur="short"/> there you go</u>
<u n="367" who="S0281">I mean people could call us normal but there again how wrong would they be? <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0355">well they're</u>
<u n="369" who="S0281" trans="overlap">how wrong could I could they be?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I mean the most interesting fact is that I think about these interviews that get recorded and sent to to these people at Cambridge Press is that people really don't tell them what they're thinking <pause dur="short"/> I mean people all play the game don't they?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0281">well it's not really it's <trunc>i</trunc> you've got it in your head it's like an interview <pause dur="short"/> you know I'm not interviewing you</u>
<u n="372" who="S0355">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="373" who="S0281">that's right <pause dur="long"/> so do do you want erm erm stop this and er?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0355">I'm easy yeah we'll get some ice cream yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can</u>
<u n="375" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I'll go and get some ice cream</u>
<u n="376" who="S0355">yeah okay</u>
<u n="377" who="S0281" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> right okey dokey</u>
<u n="378" who="S0355">okay</u>
<u n="379" who="S0281">oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
