<text id="SPVY">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:48:43</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-13</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0024 S0144</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>The countryside, Norfolk</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Comedy, superstition, policemen, publicity, university, holidays</topics>
		<activity>Couple go for a walk in the countryside.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T03</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0024">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Dereham, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>28</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0144">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Norwich, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0144">right <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> okay so what was that thing you saw?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0024">oh well I don't usually watch that BBC programme but</u>
<u n="3" who="S0144" trans="overlap">what programme?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0024">um <pause dur="short"/> morning Breakfast thing <pause dur="short"/> breakfast <pause dur="short"/> bBC Breakfast</u>
<u n="5" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but sometimes it has some nice stories but they do sell <pause dur="short"/> they sell everything <pause dur="short"/> and you know any visitors they have <pause dur="short"/> it's just like a chat show really <pause dur="short"/> and then they add news in every so often</u>
<u n="7" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="8" who="S0024">so</u>
<u n="9" who="S0144">well they give people the chance to sell their products</u>
<u n="10" who="S0024">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0144" trans="overlap">but in a conversational way kind of way so it gets round the er advertising law</u>
<u n="12" who="S0024">which is what all chat shows do but they do it in kind of a newsy kind of way</u>
<u n="13" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah but</u>
<u n="14" who="S0024">Cos they slip in the news</u>
<u n="15" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0024">at the</u>
<u n="17" who="S0144">there's a word for it isn't there <pause dur="short"/> I've forgotten what it's called</u>
<u n="18" who="S0024">I don't know</u>
<u n="19" who="S0144">anyway <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0024">but um yeah this um this guy with cerebral palsy was on there <pause dur="short"/> he's up in Newcastle <pause dur="short"/> I don't know <pause dur="short"/> no no <pause dur="short"/> I don't know he's up north somewhere and er yeah he's he's a comedian and he he um he can't speak <pause dur="short"/> I've forgotten what he calls himself <pause dur="short"/> he's he calls himself I lost my voice or something like that <pause dur="short"/> he's got a tee-shirt</u>
<u n="21" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0024">and bless him <pause dur="short"/> he he's written all of his jokes out on the computer one finger at a time <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Written it all of his jokes out <pause dur="short"/> and then he um brings the um the computer has this synthesised speaker <pause dur="short"/> and it's quite good actually cos it's much it's improved on how they used to do it <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="23" who="S0144">so it doesn't sound like Stephen Hawkin</u>
<u n="24" who="S0024"><trunc>N</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> no <pause dur="short"/> it's it sounds like a posh <anon type="place"/> RP Britain <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0144">oh okay</u>
<u n="26" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and it he said he doesn't really like the voice but</u>
<u n="27" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="28" who="S0024">the poshness makes it a bit funnier</u>
<u n="29" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0024">his whole thing <pause dur="short"/> but he stands at the in front of the crowd</u>
<u n="31" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0024">and he um he he presses his jokes to and it reads off the jokes and he kind of does a few actions to go with it <pause dur="short"/> a few expressions <pause dur="short"/> um and it looked really funny <pause dur="short"/> he like takes the piss out of himself quite a lot</u>
<u n="33" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0024">and about and so he does a lot of jokes <pause dur="short"/> well I don't know how many jokes they were just the ones I saw <pause dur="short"/> there's jokes about some disabilities and stuff like that <pause dur="short"/> and they were quite funny</u>
<u n="35" who="S0144">ha</u>
<u n="36" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> really good <pause dur="short"/> and now he's doing um he's become so successful that he's doing a tour of Britain</u>
<u n="37" who="S0144">oh okay</u>
<u n="38" who="S0024">yeah I think it's really nice <pause dur="short"/> like and there was like there was a packed out comedy club to see him <pause dur="short"/> and they said he was the best <pause dur="short"/> that was well they interviewed a few people afterwards and they said he was the best one for that night and stuff</u>
<u n="39" who="S0144">oh right</u>
<u n="40" who="S0024">and</u>
<u n="41" who="S0144">what his material was good? Or it was like a gimmick?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah I think so <pause dur="short"/> no his material was good <pause dur="short"/> his material was good</u>
<u n="43" who="S0144">oh that's good</u>
<u n="44" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and he said that was his dream to become a stand-up comedian but then he lost his voice</u>
<u n="45" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0024">so Ah I think it's really sweet that</u>
<u n="47" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0024">yeah somebody can achieve something like that <pause dur="short"/> become a stand-up comedian and they can't  and they can't  talk</u>
<u n="49" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ha ha</u>
<u n="50" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0144">it's pretty impressive really isn't it</u>
<u n="52" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0144">I remember there was a study done on er accents and humour</u>
<u n="54" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0144">I think they found like the South-East like RP accent was the least funniest <pause dur="short"/> cos they did a study where that they had the same joke</u>
<u n="56" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="57" who="S0144">and they told the same joke in like different accents</u>
<u n="58" who="S0024">oh I didn't know that</u>
<u n="59" who="S0144">to like a group of people</u>
<u n="60" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0144">I think it was the Brummie accent that came out top</u>
<u n="62" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0144">and then</u>
<u n="64" who="S0024">well the Northern Northern accents</u>
<u n="65" who="S0144">yeah Jordie accent</u>
<u n="66" who="S0024">or Irish</u>
<u n="67" who="S0144">or Liverpudlian</u>
<u n="68" who="S0024">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> any of the fast accents I think <pause dur="short"/> the fast ones so</u>
<u n="69" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos I think like our accent I think it's associated with I dunno business or</u>
<u n="70" who="S0024">yeah well with him cos it's in a cos you don't expect him to have that kind of voice so it kind of works</u>
<u n="71" who="S0144">oh <pause dur="short"/> there's the private jet again</u>
<u n="72" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0024">oh he must go past the same time every day</u>
<u n="74" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="76" who="S0024">that's a good experiment actually</u>
<u n="77" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah cos I I hate my accent</u>
<u n="78" who="S0024">joke <unclear/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0144">I hate it <pause dur="short"/> I wish I had a regional accent <pause dur="short"/> it's so much more interesting <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0024">but we've kind of developed our accents</u>
<event desc="sound of peacock"/>
<u n="81" who="S0024">oh <pause dur="short"/> hello? What's that? Peacock</u>
<u n="82" who="S0144" trans="overlap">that's a peacock <pause dur="short"/> ha <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know they made that noise <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0024">well you don't see many peacocks do you</u>
<u n="84" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> it sounded like a comic kind of ah ha</u>
<u n="85" who="S0024">look there it is look</u>
<u n="86" who="S0144">is that the female?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0024">they've got a nice little little</u>
<u n="88" who="S0144">yeah it's nice isn't it</u>
<u n="89" who="S0024">thing there <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0144">ha</u>
<u n="91" who="S0024">yeah that's a good experiment <pause dur="short"/> I like that</u>
<u n="92" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0024">if I could remember jokes I'd be able to tell you one of his jokes by I er</u>
<u n="94" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0024">ah <pause dur="short"/> why am I so rubbish at remembering jokes? I can't even remember one</u>
<u n="96" who="S0144">no I'm the same</u>
<u n="97" who="S0024">one out of the whole lot</u>
<u n="98" who="S0144">nope <pause dur="short"/> no I looked at</u>
<u n="99" who="S0024">I can't believe you didn't see him on the TV today</u>
<u n="100" who="S0144">well I didn't get up till about well half nine <pause dur="short"/> I never watch those morning breakfast things</u>
<u n="101" who="S0024">oh mum cooked some good food today <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0024">I was stuffed <pause dur="short"/> I couldn't even eat tea <pause dur="short"/> cos er cos she gave us those cream tea scones at like <trunc>t</trunc> what was it ten o'clock in the morning?</u>
<u n="104" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0024">like ha oh</u>
<u n="106" who="S0144">they were good they were</u>
<u n="107" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0144">I don't know what happened to the crumpets though</u>
<u n="109" who="S0024">oh <pause dur="short"/> well that's the first time she's tried to make crumpets</u>
<u n="110" who="S0144">they were too thick weren't they <pause dur="short"/> they didn't <pause dur="short"/> they were too yeasty</u>
<u n="111" who="S0024">well I I don't think she cooked them for long enough or she cooked them too high temperature or something like that <pause dur="short"/> she fried them</u>
<u n="112" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0024">I think she should have grilled them <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know anyway</u>
<u n="114" who="S0144">she fried them?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0024">yeah well it gave I don't know it gave her a choice of what to do</u>
<u n="116" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0024">I I I um I know nothing about making crumpets so <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0144">no I'd never thought about making crumpets <pause dur="short"/> I thought they just came out of a pack</u>
<u n="119" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0024">they're they look really hard don't they?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0024">well they they obviously are cos mum usually gets most of her cooking right</u>
<u n="123" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0024">but first try for everything</u>
<u n="125" who="S0144">ha</u>
<u n="126" who="S0024">but now that they've failed I don't think she's gonna want to cook any more</u>
<u n="127" who="S0144">ha</u>
<u n="128" who="S0024">she's the crumble expert instead</u>
<u n="129" who="S0144">ha</u>
<u n="130" who="S0024">ah <pause dur="short"/> yum rhubarb</u>
<u n="131" who="S0144">yeah did you know it's Friday the thirteenth today?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0024">yeah I know cos it no cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said oh I've got my operation Friday the thirteenth</u>
<u n="133" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0024">she was really worried cos she's really superstitious</u>
<u n="135" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I was trying to find out the origins today <pause dur="short"/> and it's one of those things</u>
<u n="136" who="S0024" trans="overlap">of Friday the thirteenth? Thirteenth?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's one of those things that no one knows <pause dur="short"/> ha and there's about a thousand different ideas <pause dur="short"/> but most of them the one's I was reading they were all like Christian</u>
<u n="138" who="S0024">um</u>
<u n="139" who="S0144">like there was one like saying Jesus was crucified on the</u>
<event desc="sound of car"/>
<u n="140" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="141" who="S0144">Jesus was crucified on the Friday the thirteenth</u>
<u n="142" who="S0024">really?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0144">I don't know how they would know that <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And er another one said the the last supper because there was thirteen at the dinner table</u>
<u n="144" who="S0024">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0144">you know it all sounds like a load of bollocks to me <pause dur="short"/> what were the other things?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0024">um what did I think? I though it was something to do with the witches witch craze</u>
<u n="147" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="148" who="S0024">something to do with the witches</u>
<u n="149" who="S0144">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> it could be anything couldn't it</u>
<u n="150" who="S0024">no I have read stories about it but I can't remember them</u>
<u n="151" who="S0144">yeah exactly but it each story is different isn't it</u>
<u n="152" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="153" who="S0144">so <pause dur="short"/> I dunno</u>
<u n="154" who="S0024">I was just thinking about <trunc>Tu</trunc> the Tunisians are really funny with er ha with er before before revolution number number eight was their favourite <pause dur="short"/> er is it number eight? No not number eight <pause dur="short"/> number seven <pause dur="short"/> seven <pause dur="short"/> seventh of November <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="155" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0024">number seven was their favourite favourite number in the world <pause dur="short"/> seven is my lucky number <pause dur="short"/> seven seven seven <pause dur="short"/> and then after the revolution you put number seven on the board and they all go ah oh no</u>
<u n="157" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0144">yeah it's number sixteen now</u>
<u n="159" who="S0024">I used to always tell that <pause dur="short"/> did you used to tell that joke? Cos I used to have seven people in my family on the board <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And then you'd go what do you think number seven is <pause dur="short"/> what's the question?</u>
<u n="160" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0024">and they'd go ah I don't know</u>
<u n="162" who="S0144">no I <trunc>alw</trunc></u>
<u n="163" who="S0024">er it might be my lucky number <pause dur="short"/> and they'd all go oh no teacher no</u>
<u n="164" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0144">no I always used to er when I was doing that TV news project I made <pause dur="short"/> I asked them to like just think about the news channels they watch on TV</u>
<u n="166" who="S0024">oh yeah and they had Seven News channel</u>
<u n="167" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0024">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0144">and I I kept like the government channel like on the flip</u>
<u n="170" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0144">like on purpose cos every time I put it up er they just listening to the gasps in the class go oh teacher no</u>
<u n="172" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0144">ah it's funny <pause dur="short"/> er what else did I see on the news? I saw <pause dur="short"/> did you see the policeman in Hanoi?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="175" who="S0144">it looked like the road between Hanoi and Hai Phong <pause dur="short"/> and it was er one of those buses that hurtles along there at about a hundred miles an hour</u>
<u n="176" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0144">ha <pause dur="short"/> and this bus was getting a ticket by er like a traffic warden <pause dur="short"/> and the bus driver got pissed off and just decided to drive off</u>
<u n="178" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0144">and the ticket inspector jumped on the front of the bus like so his like feet were on the bumpers</u>
<u n="180" who="S0024">oh no</u>
<u n="181" who="S0144">and the driver didn't stop</u>
<u n="182" who="S0024">oh no</u>
<u n="183" who="S0144">and he went hurtling down the highway for like thirty minutes</u>
<u n="184" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0144">with this  with this  traffic warden just stuck on the front of it</u>
<u n="186" who="S0024">ah</u>
<u n="187" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="188" who="S0144">before he stopped and got chased by all the the locals <pause dur="short"/> the driver got chased by all the locals <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0024">oh God <pause dur="short"/> but like it just in Vietnam it doesn't surprise me</u>
<u n="190" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0024">oh God <pause dur="short"/> how crazy they are</u>
<u n="192" who="S0144">yeah they're funny</u>
<u n="193" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0024">do you think afterwards they were oh actually well done it was quite funny when we reflect upon it</u>
<u n="195" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="196" who="S0024">like they used to with their <trunc>prac</trunc> with their scams</u>
<u n="197" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0024">patting each other on the back <pause dur="short"/> oh you scammed me out of loads of money</u>
<u n="199" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0024">but that was a really good scam <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="201" who="S0144">yeah but it what surprised me the most <pause dur="short"/> well it didn't surprise me but the way the people chased the driver</u>
<u n="202" who="S0024">ah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0144">like they <trunc>take</trunc> took sides with the police</u>
<u n="204" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0144">like automatically</u>
<u n="206" who="S0024">well they would do because they have to</u>
<u n="207" who="S0144">yeah because they show</u>
<u n="208" who="S0024">they have to</u>
<u n="209" who="S0144">they have to show have to demonstrate it that they're on the police's side</u>
<u n="210" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0144">even though they're not deep down</u>
<u n="212" who="S0024">oh but yeah but they wouldn't want somebody on the back front of a bus</u>
<u n="213" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0024">that's just too dangerous</u>
<u n="215" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's true <vocal desc="laugh"/> Er</u>
<u n="216" who="S0024">that's yeah that's</u>
<u n="217" who="S0144">what else did I see?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0024">oh I missed that one</u>
<u n="219" who="S0144">there was a er a woman in Bolton who er who got dumped over Facebook by her boyfriend</u>
<u n="220" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0144">and so she ah she drove her car into the bowling alley that he worked in</u>
<u n="222" who="S0024">into the bowling alley?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0024">like through the wall?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0144">yeah and they <trunc>sh</trunc> they showed it on the CCTV from inside the bowling alley</u>
<u n="226" who="S0024">oh no</u>
<u n="227" who="S0144">and she went flying like literally</u>
<u n="228" who="S0024">idiot</u>
<u n="229" who="S0144">like really fast straight through the front door and smashed it all up</u>
<u n="230" who="S0024">idiot <pause dur="short"/> she could have killed loads of people</u>
<u n="231" who="S0144">into the the kiosk bit where they give out the shoes and stuff</u>
<u n="232" who="S0024">ha</u>
<u n="233" who="S0144">she could have done yeah <pause dur="short"/> she could have easily and I think she got away <pause dur="short"/> she didn't even go to jail</u>
<u n="234" who="S0024">what?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think she just had to pay a fine but</u>
<u n="236" who="S0024">that's oh God some people</u>
<u n="237" who="S0144">psychopath</u>
<u n="238" who="S0024">mind you the Vietnamese driver is just as bad</u>
<u n="239" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0024">but some people they're just crazy</u>
<u n="241" who="S0144">ah yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0024"><unclear/> lose their mind</u>
<u n="243" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it's weird isn't it when you get so upset by something that you don't</u>
<u n="244" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0144">I dunno</u>
<u n="246" who="S0024">you don't think of any consequences</u>
<u n="247" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="248" who="S0024">and just like</u>
<u n="249" who="S0144">you just completely lose it don't you</u>
<u n="250" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0144">I don't think I've ever got to that kind of mentality</u>
<u n="252" who="S0024">no <pause dur="short"/> I don't think we're like that</u>
<u n="253" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0024">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> we can get angry</u>
<u n="255" who="S0144">I think everyone can get er angry <pause dur="short"/> it depends what happens doesn't it</u>
<u n="256" who="S0024">I think I've only been really angry like fuming bright red steam out the ears about three times in my life I think</u>
<u n="257" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0024">I can't even remember the situations <pause dur="short"/> I remember one of them was because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wouldn't clean the house</u>
<u n="259" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0024">yeah and I had a fight with him <pause dur="short"/> but <trunc>Ke</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It seems so petty doesn't it <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="261" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="262" who="S0024">the build up but there was</u>
<u n="263" who="S0144">it is the build up yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0024">like obviously like it builds builds builds builds builds</u>
<u n="265" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0024">things get said <pause dur="short"/> and then suddenly you can explode</u>
<u n="267" who="S0144">you just erupt</u>
<u n="268" who="S0024">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0144">huh</u>
<u n="270" who="S0024">but it seems so petty but it's just something that tips you over the edge innit</u>
<u n="271" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0024">but yeah I don't think it's happened to me much <pause dur="short"/> that's good though it hasn't</u>
<u n="273" who="S0144">ha</u>
<u n="274" who="S0024">oh when I used to drive in the city</u>
<u n="275" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0024">ooh oh</u>
<u n="277" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> there was another story er in Belgium <pause dur="short"/> er do you know the TV channel TNT?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> or I've heard of it <pause dur="short"/> is it? Oh I don't know whether it's news</u>
<u n="279" who="S0144">it's one of those channels you never watch</u>
<u n="280" who="S0024">or what is it?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0144">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I never watch it <pause dur="short"/> I know it's there though</u>
<u n="282" who="S0024">I think it's news</u>
<u n="283" who="S0144">but they're promoting it in this village in Belgium <pause dur="short"/> and they had they just had this big button in the middle of the town square saying press this to see drama <pause dur="short"/> ha <pause dur="short"/> so someone obviously walked past and stopped and and pressed it <pause dur="short"/> and as soon as they pressed it this ambulance just appeared out of nowhere</u>
<u n="284" who="S0024">what?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and er and these guys were carrying this patient into the ambulance and dropped the the bed so the patient fell on the floor</u>
<u n="286" who="S0024">oh one of those</u>
<u n="287" who="S0144">and put it back on the the thing put it in the ambulance <pause dur="short"/> drove off but then the the patient flew out of the back of the ambulance</u>
<u n="288" who="S0024">oh ah ah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0144">and then these two cars came round and it was these guys all dressed in black and they er started having a shoot off with the police</u>
<u n="290" who="S0024">what?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0024">like with a real gun?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0144">well not real guns but it looked real</u>
<u n="294" who="S0024">God</u>
<u n="295" who="S0144">and then they had like fake injuries as well and fake blood and stuff <pause dur="short"/> and so it was like some dead people lying about</u>
<u n="296" who="S0024">huh</u>
<u n="297" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And then <pause dur="short"/> what else was there? And then they all drove off and then oh there were meanwhile there was a big punch up going on about the ambulance people <pause dur="short"/> started having like a big fist fight <pause dur="short"/> and then</u>
<u n="298" who="S0024">oh my God</u>
<u n="299" who="S0144">after the police had disappeared this American football team ran out of nowhere <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And then this woman drove past riding a bike in just er like her underwear <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And then this big sign came down the side of the building like advertising TNT <pause dur="short"/> it was quite clever</u>
<u n="300" who="S0024">yeah but ah er <pause dur="short"/> are you sure that was real? That's not just a whole advert</u>
<u n="301" who="S0144">no no I saw it</u>
<u n="302" who="S0024">the whole advert that is the film</u>
<u n="303" who="S0144">no it's in the kind of same style as the er that mobile phone that <pause dur="short"/> what was it?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0024">yeah but the whole thing was an advert? Or that actually happened to somebody stood there and pressed a button and it happened to him really?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0144">no someone <pause dur="short"/> yeah the person that pressed the button was real</u>
<u n="306" who="S0024" trans="overlap">he wasn't an actor?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="308" who="S0024">really? Oh God I'd freak</u>
<u n="309" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0024">oh that would freak me out so much</u>
<u n="311" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0024">but it's not he cos he pressed the button so he he might register this is all happening because of this</u>
<u n="313" who="S0144">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0024">but everybody else who's around there just shopping they wouldn't have a clue what it was about</u>
<u n="315" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> I quite like promotions like that though <pause dur="short"/> they're good</u>
<u n="316" who="S0024">yeah but I <trunc>d</trunc> ah ooh</u>
<u n="317" who="S0144">ha <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0024">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> that would flip you out so much <pause dur="short"/> you wouldn't know what to do with yourself</u>
<u n="319" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0024">yeah pretty clever</u>
<u n="322" who="S0144">and another story I saw about university <pause dur="short"/> er I think it was one of the ones in London <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember which one <pause dur="short"/> but they're gonna ban alcohol in certain parts of the university cos they've got quite a big Muslim um population in in the university</u>
<u n="323" who="S0024">where? Where?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0144">I dunno it's one of the ones in London <pause dur="short"/> um cos a lot of the students have said it's evil and immoral having all this alcohol around <pause dur="short"/> so they're gonna ban it</u>
<u n="325" who="S0024">right</u>
<u n="326" who="S0144">in certain parts</u>
<u n="327" who="S0024">right <pause dur="short"/> well surely they only sell them in the bars</u>
<u n="328" who="S0144">well</u>
<u n="329" who="S0024">you don't have to go in the bar <pause dur="short"/> there's <trunc>caf</trunc> coffee shops too surely</u>
<u n="330" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0024">they wouldn't sell beer in the coffee shop would they?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0144">I dunno</u>
<u n="333" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="334" who="S0144">I dunno it's one of those</u>
<u n="335" who="S0024">I don't know about that <pause dur="short"/> that's I mean I do  I do  disagree with students going mental <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Beering it up and going crazy</u>
<u n="336" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="337" who="S0024">like over the top crazy <pause dur="short"/> not just having beers <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0144">I suppose it's okay if there isn't an area like a social area you can go where they don't serve alcohol</u>
<u n="339" who="S0024">yeah that's all they need</u>
<u n="340" who="S0144">then that's fair enough <pause dur="short"/> but I mean</u>
<u n="341" who="S0024">well yeah they just need a coffee shop that doesn't sell it so</u>
<u n="342" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> otherwise though you're in danger of just angering people <pause dur="short"/> like even more you know</u>
<u n="343" who="S0024">but well maybe maybe that was maybe the universities are going over the top <pause dur="short"/> are they selling it everywhere?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0144">I don't know</u>
<u n="345" who="S0024">are they selling it in like vending machines <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0144">no you can't do that here</u>
<u n="347" who="S0024">I've seen it in a hotel <pause dur="short"/> in a hotel there was a vending machine</u>
<u n="348" who="S0144">that wasn't in England</u>
<u n="349" who="S0024">oh <unclear/> Oh <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> actually do you know where that was?</u>
<u n="350" who="S0144">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> they do it in lots of countries</u>
<u n="351" who="S0024">that was that no it wasn't <unclear/> in Egypt was it <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="352" who="S0144">I think Korea that had</u>
<u n="353" who="S0024">no somewhere recently</u>
<u n="354" who="S0144">I remember they <pause dur="short"/> do you remember that hotel that had a load of dildos in the vending machine? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0024">yeah that was Korea <pause dur="short"/> a love motel</u>
<u n="356" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0144">ah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0024">ha <pause dur="short"/> oh cultures are funny <pause dur="short"/> but er you don't wanna lose your <trunc>f</trunc> the British culture of drinking</u>
<u n="359" who="S0144">well no that's it</u>
<u n="360" who="S0024">even though it is  it is  in a bad state at the moment</u>
<u n="361" who="S0144" trans="overlap">I know <pause dur="short"/> yeah I know</u>
<u n="362" who="S0024">it er it that something needs to be done <pause dur="short"/> but they've already put the price up on alcohol</u>
<u n="363" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0024">like <trunc>sh</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> it's not fair</u>
<u n="365" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and have you noticed how those boxes of beer have got a lot smaller as well</u>
<u n="366" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0144">ah they're gonna end up having those really tiny cans the size of Red Bull</u>
<u n="368" who="S0024">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0144">selling beer like that <pause dur="short"/> like they do in Asia</u>
<u n="370" who="S0024">well no <pause dur="short"/> well they have big bottles too</u>
<u n="371" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well parts of Asia <pause dur="short"/> well Korea then and Japan</u>
<u n="372" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="373" who="S0144">hmm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0024">yeah it is difficult that one</u>
<u n="375" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="376" who="S0024">you don't wanna lose the culture but you've gotta do something about it <pause dur="short"/> but to do it just for the sake of doing it because er oh there must be coffee shops that other people can go to</u>
<u n="377" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0024">if they don't wanna be surrounded by it <pause dur="short"/> there must be</u>
<u n="379" who="S0144">well it's just university in England you associate the the Student's Union</u>
<u n="380" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah ha</u>
<u n="381" who="S0144">with getting drunk really</u>
<u n="382" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0144">Don't you</u>
<u n="384" who="S0024">yeah when mum was at uni  when mum was at uni  you see cos when she was at uni she used to get everything for free yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0024">she got her  she got her  sheets washed for free</u>
<u n="387" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0024">she got like they got their dinners for free <pause dur="short"/> everything they got for free</u>
<u n="389" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0024">it was crazy <pause dur="short"/> but anyway she used to work in the student bar <pause dur="short"/> voluntary <pause dur="short"/> but you got all of your drinks <pause dur="short"/> you could drink in there for free <pause dur="short"/> but people didn't abuse it <pause dur="short"/> you know like if you like now they pay people to go and work in there <pause dur="short"/> but you wouldn't get your drinks free</u>
<u n="391" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0024">but they used to do it used to volunteer in there to get your drinks free <pause dur="short"/> but then I guess you just got loads of people guzzling it</u>
<u n="393" who="S0144">hmm mm</u>
<u n="394" who="S0024">and drinking over their wage <vocal desc="laugh"/> I dunno</u>
<u n="395" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="396" who="S0024">over what a wage would be</u>
<u n="397" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="398" who="S0024">I dunno</u>
<u n="399" who="S0144">hmm</u>
<u n="400" who="S0024">shame it's not like the old days though like when they were all at uni <pause dur="short"/> I remember when they took us to Plymouth <pause dur="short"/> mum dropped me off at Plymouth <pause dur="short"/> she was going you don't need sheets</u>
<u n="401" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0024">they'll give you some sheets <pause dur="short"/> I was going no I really need some sheets <pause dur="short"/> I've gotta take <pause dur="short"/> look you've got lots in the cupboard <pause dur="short"/> I wanna <trunc>ta</trunc> I need to take some with me <pause dur="short"/> she was going they'll give them to you for free <pause dur="short"/> I was going it's not like the old days</u>
<u n="403" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0024">I wish it was <pause dur="short"/> she was going don't worry you'll get all these lovely meals</u>
<u n="405" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0024">I didn't get one single meal <pause dur="short"/> and halls were more expensive than living in a house</u>
<u n="407" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0024">and so <pause dur="short"/> and that just phew that was unbelievable to them</u>
<u n="409" who="S0144" trans="overlap">it's disgusting isn't it</u>
<u n="410" who="S0024">they were like how can that possibly be that <pause dur="short"/> they didn't <pause dur="short"/> it took ages for me to explain</u>
<u n="411" who="S0144" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Didn't they believe you?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0024">no not really because they'd never experienced that kind of thing before <pause dur="short"/> they were like well that's what halls are for <pause dur="short"/> they're for people getting integrated into the university for cheap rent</u>
<u n="413" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well you get a tiny box room <pause dur="short"/> don't you</u>
<u n="414" who="S0024">but it's not cheap rent at all is it</u>
<u n="415" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="416" who="S0024">you pay actually I mean it's a ridiculous amount</u>
<u n="417" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="418" who="S0024">if you pay for those tiny little rooms</u>
<u n="419" who="S0144">the way they re-marketed it was er oh it's the best way to meet people in your first year</u>
<u n="420" who="S0024">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> and lots of people do still go down that root because they want to meet a group of people</u>
<u n="421" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0024">and then they go off to live with their</u>
<u n="423" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0024">group of people later</u>
<u n="425" who="S0144">yeah well I moved in with people doing their masters <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0024">oh yeah that was</u>
<u n="427" who="S0144">it was pretty awful</u>
<u n="428" who="S0024">that wasn't good for you was it</u>
<u n="429" who="S0144">so I had to join a couple of clubs to meet people</u>
<u n="430" who="S0024">oh that's good</u>
<u n="431" who="S0144">but it wasn't easy</u>
<u n="432" who="S0024">it made you</u>
<u n="433" who="S0144" trans="overlap">that's how I met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0144">so I guess</u>
<u n="436" who="S0024">well that that made you get out and about</u>
<u n="437" who="S0144">yeah but you know</u>
<u n="438" who="S0024">but yeah it's not</u>
<u n="439" who="S0144">I didn't have anyone to go to er didn't have anyone to go to the night clubs with</u>
<u n="440" who="S0024" trans="overlap">the bar with cos <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="441" who="S0144">do you know what I mean it was  it was  difficult</u>
<u n="442" who="S0024" trans="overlap">shall we go down that way?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0144">okay <pause dur="short"/> so it wasn't till my second year really that I</u>
<u n="444" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="445" who="S0144">started making friends</u>
<u n="446" who="S0024">then you lived with me</u>
<u n="447" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="448" who="S0024">and we lived with twelve blokes and me</u>
<u n="449" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0024">that was a bit I was a bit gutted at the time <pause dur="short"/> not cos I'd moved in cos everybody was lovely</u>
<u n="451" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="452" who="S0024">but I I just had didn't have any female bonds</u>
<u n="453" who="S0144">mm <pause dur="short"/> well when you moved in there was still some rooms empty wasn't there</u>
<u n="454" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> when I moved in there was only four guys there</u>
<u n="455" who="S0144">Cos I remember trying to sell it to you <pause dur="short"/> oh don't worry we'll get some girls in</u>
<u n="456" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0024">oh yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="459" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="460" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0024">but I enjoyed it <pause dur="short"/> I I did quite enjoy living with loads of blokes actually</u>
<u n="462" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="463" who="S0024">I mean when the girls moved in the next year I didn't really get on with any of them anyway</u>
<u n="464" who="S0144">no <pause dur="short"/> it was bitchy wasn't it <pause dur="short"/> they were quite girly girls weren't they</u>
<u n="465" who="S0024">er Lou wasn't a girly girl</u>
<u n="466" who="S0144">yeah I suppose yeah <pause dur="short"/> ooh</u>
<u n="467" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I do <pause dur="short"/> I don't know cos most people go though all those stages of life don't they where they</u>
<u n="468" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0024">I don't know live with a couple of good girl friends or <pause dur="short"/> I never even went on holiday with a group of good girlfriends <pause dur="short"/> I mean I've got some good girlfriends but</u>
<u n="470" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="471" who="S0024">I never</u>
<u n="472" who="S0144">yeah you didn't miss much <pause dur="short"/> I went on a couple of lad's holidays <pause dur="short"/> they were the worst holidays I've ever been on</u>
<u n="473" who="S0024">ah I bet you didn't think that at the time</u>
<u n="474" who="S0144">well I just got drunk <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> It was rubbish</u>
<u n="475" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0144">and tried to pull <pause dur="short"/> and failed</u>
<u n="477" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0024">ah <pause dur="short"/> maybe that's where it went wrong <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="480" who="S0024">everybody puts erm too much pressure on themselves <pause dur="short"/> don't they? When they go on holidays like that</u>
<u n="481" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah it was the time when you know it was really popular <pause dur="short"/> you know it was late nineties <pause dur="short"/> you know Ibiza was</u>
<u n="482" who="S0024">where did you go again? Ibiza?</u>
<u n="483" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="484" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="485" who="S0144">I went to Tenerife and</u>
<u n="486" who="S0024">mm that's right</u>
<u n="487" who="S0144">Benidorm</u>
<u n="488" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="489" who="S0144">and it was the time when all those shows were on TV about the club reps and everything <pause dur="short"/> and everyone was shagging each other and I remember at the time I thought eh this is gonna be brilliant</u>
<u n="490" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0144">it just wasn't like that <pause dur="short"/> it was just people getting too drunk vomiting everywhere and getting into fights</u>
<u n="492" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0024">and with holidays like that you've just got you've got to drag yourself out in the daytime to sit on the beach haven't you</u>
<u n="494" who="S0144" trans="overlap">and then feeling sick the next day <pause dur="short"/> it's like great <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0024">Cos otherwise you just  you just  flake out and just</u>
<u n="496" who="S0144">yeah but when you're not drinking enough water and</u>
<u n="497" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="498" who="S0144">it's too hot</u>
<u n="499" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="500" who="S0144">you know I didn't see any culture or speak to anyone local</u>
<u n="501" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="502" who="S0144">and see anything <pause dur="short"/> apart from a few bars</u>
<u n="503" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0144">full of dick heads <pause dur="short"/> so you didn't miss anything by I mean not doing that</u>
<u n="505" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="506" who="S0144">apart from maybe catching Chlamydia or something</u>
<u n="507" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> yeah I suppose <pause dur="short"/> yeah well I'd like  I'd like  to plan a erm cos you said you always wanna go skiing and cos I've said for years that I wouldn't wanna go skiing</u>
<u n="509" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well I dunno really <pause dur="short"/> there's things I'd rather do <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<event desc="sound of car"/>
<u n="510" who="S0144">where are these cars coming from?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0024">but it does make a erm I think it would make a er a nice group holiday if you got  if you got  the right kind of people all together</u>
<u n="512" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0024">in like a little cabin and</u>
<u n="514" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="515" who="S0024">or one of those cottage holidays we always talked about doing when we lived down in Plymouth</u>
<u n="516" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0024">remember we said oh yeah let's get everybody together and go and stay in a cottage all together like a group of friends</u>
<u n="518" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that would be good</u>
<u n="519" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0144">or like a walking holiday</u>
<u n="521" who="S0024">yeah a walking holiday</u>
<u n="522" who="S0144">well like</u>
<u n="523" who="S0024">well we've done walking holidays</u>
<u n="524" who="S0144" trans="overlap">we've sort of done that <pause dur="short"/> they're brilliant</u>
<u n="525" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0144">they are good</u>
<u n="527" who="S0024">apart from cos it was oh I mean oh that was so beautiful <pause dur="short"/> but we were well we did get knackered and <trunc>free</trunc> cos it was so cold</u>
<u n="528" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="529" who="S0024">and er you know we all had to have a nap in the afternoon <pause dur="short"/> it was crazy <pause dur="short"/> and then cos we were</u>
<u n="530" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well we had to go to bed at about six o'clock as well <pause dur="short"/> remember all huddled round in the dark</u>
<u n="531" who="S0024" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> huddled around yeah</u>
<u n="532" who="S0144">with a candle</u>
<u n="533" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="534" who="S0144">with nothing to eat apart from maybe a pot of noodles</u>
<u n="535" who="S0024">oh and they sold those weird fried</u>
<u n="536" who="S0144">fried Mars bars?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0024">Mars bars <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0144">did they?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0024">yeah but erm</u>
<u n="540" who="S0144">where?</u>
<u n="541" who="S0024">we and we said when we get to the top we're gonna try one of those <pause dur="short"/> and and</u>
<u n="542" who="S0144">I don't know</u>
<u n="543" who="S0024">we did and it was disgusting</u>
<u n="544" who="S0144">yeah it was disgusting yeah <pause dur="short"/> ha</u>
<u n="545" who="S0024">and they get more expensive the closer you get to the top anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="546" who="S0144">yeah well I'd like to do</u>
<u n="547" who="S0024">yeah more expensive and worse quality</u>
<u n="548" who="S0144">yeah I like holidays with a challenge in them <pause dur="short"/> where you've got like a a goal to get to</u>
<u n="549" who="S0024" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="550" who="S0144">and you get there and you you go yay I did it</u>
<u n="551" who="S0024">yeah not just sitting on the beach</u>
<u n="552" who="S0144">no it's</u>
<u n="553" who="S0024">but snorkelling or</u>
<u n="554" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0024">or walking hiking</u>
<u n="556" who="S0144">I hate sitting on the beach</u>
<u n="557" who="S0024">oh I I like erm</u>
<u n="558" who="S0144">it's so boring</u>
<u n="559" who="S0024">I like a couple of hours on the beach reading my book and</u>
<u n="560" who="S0144" trans="overlap">A couple of hours maybe yeah and then that's enough for me</u>
<u n="561" who="S0024">swimming <pause dur="short"/> as long as the  as long as the  seas nice enough to swim in</u>
<u n="562" who="S0144">as long as there's something to do yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0024">and it's warm enough <pause dur="short"/> we've had some good</u>
<u n="564" who="S0144">I'd much rather sit by a lake than</u>
<u n="565" who="S0024">we had some good times on a beach though</u>
<u n="566" who="S0144">well if there's snorkelling then yeah definitely</u>
<u n="567" who="S0024">well we're gonna go and live next to a beach again</u>
<u n="568" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean</u>
<u n="569" who="S0024">we keep going and living next to beaches</u>
<u n="570" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0024">you've gotta ask yourself why</u>
<u n="573" who="S0144">well</u>
<u n="574" who="S0024">why do we keep ending up in port towns? Harbours?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ha</u>
<u n="576" who="S0024">near harbours</u>
<u n="577" who="S0144">ha</u>
<u n="578" who="S0024">funny innit?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I saw about a guy who</u>
<u n="580" who="S0024">I do prefer to be by the sea</u>
<u n="581" who="S0144">there was a guy dressed up as a storm trouper</u>
<u n="582" who="S0024">what?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0144">who walked across Australia <pause dur="short"/> I think he's just finished <pause dur="short"/> it's like five thousand miles</u>
<u n="584" who="S0024">really?</u>
<u n="585" who="S0144">and <trunc>s</trunc> he had to pull a little cart with all of his stuff in it and his tent and all his belongings and stuff</u>
<u n="586" who="S0024">why didn't he put it on his back?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0144">well I it was too heavy I guess</u>
<u n="588" who="S0024">he walked across Australia?</u>
<u n="589" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0024">whoa</u>
<u n="591" who="S0144">yeah it took him I don't know it took him about eight months I think</u>
<u n="592" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0144">it said he was walking for about ten hours a day</u>
<u n="594" who="S0024">go on then <pause dur="short"/> what would you do?</u>
<u n="595" who="S0144">no I'd love to do something like that</u>
<u n="596" who="S0024">A really big challenge</u>
<u n="597" who="S0144">but I can't really do it now <pause dur="short"/> I wish I'd done it when I was a bit younger</u>
<u n="598" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah when you</u>
<u n="599" who="S0144">Cos you haven't got the time</u>
<u n="600" who="S0024">when your knees don't go and your</u>
<u n="601" who="S0144">yeah and my ligaments are fucked</u>
<u n="602" who="S0024">hips pop out <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="603" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="604" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="605" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="606" who="S0024">oh dear</u>
<u n="607" who="S0144">but I'd yeah something like that I'd love to do</u>
<u n="608" who="S0024">maybe we could be those</u>
<u n="609" who="S0144">yep</u>
<u n="610" who="S0024">like really bulchy not bulchy no like really strong granny and granddad you know going we're gonna go on a trek</u>
<u n="611" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="612" who="S0024">and walk across all the way around England <pause dur="short"/> bye</u>
<u n="613" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="614" who="S0024">and just <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> do you think we would? It depends if my hips and my knees last</u>
<u n="615" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="616" who="S0024">and if your foot lasts <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="617" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="618" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="619" who="S0144">well it's got better again now <pause dur="short"/> these walks are helping me out a little bit</u>
<u n="620" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0144">yeah well like we were saying yesterday I'd like to do the coast to coast</u>
<u n="622" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="623" who="S0144">I'd like to do Ben Nevis <pause dur="short"/> snowdon <pause dur="short"/> and Scafell Pike or whatever it's called <pause dur="long"/> I'd like to know how many miles I've walked in my life <pause dur="short"/> I can't even</u>
<u n="624" who="S0024">I was gonna buy you one of those um wrist counters for your birthday last year and I couldn't find one <pause dur="short"/> I went driving up and down in a taxi</u>
<u n="625" who="S0144">A wrist counter?</u>
<u n="626" who="S0024">to all the sports shops</u>
<u n="627" who="S0144">did you?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="629" who="S0144">ah <pause dur="short"/> ha ha</u>
<u n="630" who="S0024">and then you didn't get much for your birthday in the end did you</u>
<u n="631" who="S0144">mm mm</u>
<u n="632" who="S0024">Cos I  cos I  couldn't find what I wanted and then I ran out of time</u>
<u n="633" who="S0144">mm <pause dur="short"/> that's what happened with you as well</u>
<u n="634" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="635" who="S0144">mhm</u>
<u n="636" who="S0024">well I suppose if you don't get what you want then what's the point of getting what you don't want</u>
<u n="637" who="S0144">well exactly I don't really want anything anyway</u>
<u n="638" who="S0024">ah <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure you do <pause dur="short"/> you could do with a new computer <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> You could do with a new</u>
<u n="639" who="S0144">it still works</u>
<u n="640" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it er in the heat we need  we need  to buy another fan</u>
<u n="641" who="S0144">yeah that is a problem</u>
<u n="642" who="S0024">where did we buy that last fan from? That was from a shop or that actually that should be alright <pause dur="short"/> we should be able to get one</u>
<u n="643" who="S0144">that was just <pause dur="short"/> yeah you can like USB fans</u>
<u n="644" who="S0024">do you want one of those wrist counters one day?</u>
<u n="645" who="S0144">what is it?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0024">it just it it it clocks how many paces you take <pause dur="short"/> or how many miles you've done or or something like that <pause dur="short"/> so you go for a jog</u>
<u n="647" who="S0144" trans="overlap">er <pause dur="short"/> I don't know actually</u>
<u n="648" who="S0024">and and and you can time it</u>
<u n="649" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="650" who="S0024">so you go for a jog and like er cos what I thought when we used to go for that little jog around the park and we never could agree on how far it was</u>
<u n="651" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="652" who="S0024">then <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I thought you could like see how fast you do it</u>
<u n="653" who="S0144" trans="overlap">doesn't it depend though</u>
<u n="654" who="S0024">and yeah</u>
<u n="655" who="S0144">does it it what it counts the <trunc>mo</trunc> the motion of your arm?</u>
<u n="656" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no it counts</u>
<u n="657" who="S0144">is that what it does?</u>
<u n="658" who="S0024" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="659" who="S0144">Cos surely that depends on how big you are</u>
<u n="660" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="661" who="S0144">how big your stride is</u>
<u n="662" who="S0024">I don't know how it works <pause dur="short"/> it somehow clocks how many miles you've done</u>
<u n="663" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="664" who="S0024">maybe you tie it round your ankle <pause dur="short"/> maybe that would be better</u>
<u n="665" who="S0144">it's like a pedometer kind of thing?</u>
<u n="666" who="S0024">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's it <pause dur="short"/> is that what?</u>
<u n="667" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="668" who="S0024">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I just saw it</u>
<u n="669" who="S0144">no I don't know if I would want one of them anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0024">well I think they're good</u>
<u n="671" who="S0144">so <pause dur="short"/> oh well oh I like the GPS things they've got now</u>
<u n="672" who="S0024">what? Can you tie that to your wrist? GPS watch or something?</u>
<u n="673" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no they <trunc>look</trunc> just a little GPS thing</u>
<u n="674" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="675" who="S0144">and it's got a map on it <pause dur="short"/> like the Ordnance Survey maps</u>
<u n="676" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="677" who="S0144">it's got them all programmed in</u>
<u n="678" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="679" who="S0144">they come to a scale of like one to fifty but you can then buy better ones like one to twenty-five which I think is the proper like Ordnance Survey thing</u>
<u n="680" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="681" who="S0144">you know where you can see the footpaths and everything <pause dur="short"/> and you can just walk like that <pause dur="short"/> and then it it can you know it <trunc>cal</trunc> calculates your your journey and you can store where you've walked and everything</u>
<u n="682" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah I think wait a few years</u>
<u n="683" who="S0144">oh yeah there's still lots of problems with it</u>
<u n="684" who="S0024">because they can't even make those things to go in the car right</u>
<u n="685" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="686" who="S0024">yet</u>
<u n="687" who="S0144">and also it does kind of take away from the romance of it as well</u>
<u n="688" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="689" who="S0144">just like walking off into the countryside</u>
<u n="690" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I used to love having like you used to have your map in your plastic bag didn't we</u>
<u n="691" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="692" who="S0024">and then you get it out</u>
<u n="693" who="S0144">that's what I mean</u>
<u n="694" who="S0024">and you have a little argument about where you are and</u>
<u n="695" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0024">and which direction you're gonna go</u>
<u n="697" who="S0144">it's all part of it isn't it</u>
<u n="698" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> if you do if you</u>
<u n="699" who="S0144">not having a little a bit of plastic that's</u>
<u n="700" who="S0024">if you haven't got that kind of orientation thing</u>
<u n="701" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="702" who="S0024">like all you have to do is walk <pause dur="short"/> it's too easy</u>
<u n="703" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> plus you can still get stuffed <pause dur="short"/> I mean if you run out of battery</u>
<u n="704" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="705" who="S0144">in the middle of somewhere</u>
<u n="706" who="S0024" trans="overlap"><unclear/> Yeah</u>
<u n="707" who="S0144">or the satellite goes down <pause dur="short"/> you're stuffed aren't you?</u>
<u n="708" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="709" who="S0144">so you've still gotta have the map anyway</u>
<u n="710" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> I like maps and trying to work out where you are</u>
<u n="711" who="S0144">yeah I love maps</u>
<u n="712" who="S0024">but one thing is we usually get somewhere and we say we look at the maps and go well we need one of those <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit expensive</u>
<u n="713" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we'll we'll wait till we see a cheaper one</u>
<u n="714" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And then we get to the next shop <pause dur="short"/> we we really need on of those cos otherwise we're gonna get really lost again <pause dur="short"/> nah it's a bit expensive</u>
<u n="715" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="716" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And then we never end up buying one <pause dur="short"/> I mean they but</u>
<u n="717" who="S0144">and then we get really lost</u>
<u n="718" who="S0024">but they're they're expensive cos they took such a they took a long time to make those maps surely</u>
<u n="719" who="S0144">yeah but once they're made that's it <pause dur="short"/> I don't know how they do make them</u>
<u n="720" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah but</u>
<u n="721" who="S0144">it's quite clever isn't it really</u>
<u n="722" who="S0024">very clever very <pause dur="short"/> like how do they measure all the <pause dur="short"/> I mean now they've got</u>
<u n="723" who="S0144" trans="overlap">all the contours and everything</u>
<u n="724" who="S0024">yeah but now they've got like the the stuff from the satellites they can</u>
<u n="725" who="S0144">yeah but you can't</u>
<u n="726" who="S0024">they can judge them</u>
<u n="727" who="S0144">you can't gage the er the height though can you?</u>
<u n="728" who="S0024">er</u>
<u n="729" who="S0144">on a satellite image</u>
<u n="730" who="S0024">I suppose somebody has to walk it or drive it and</u>
<u n="731" who="S0144">I don't know how they would do it</u>
<u n="732" who="S0024">and measure it and <pause dur="short"/> and then they get those</u>
<u n="733" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="734" who="S0024">well yeah cos you get those things that you set at sea level don't you</u>
<u n="735" who="S0144">yeah an altimeter</u>
<u n="736" who="S0024">and then somehow <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've lost all my language today</u>
<u n="737" who="S0144">yeah well that's another good thing about those GPS things <pause dur="short"/> it tells you your altitude</u>
<u n="738" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="739" who="S0144">which is good if you're climbing a mountain or something</u>
<u n="740" who="S0024">yeah it's good if you know you</u>
<u n="741" who="S0144">you have to go back down a hundred metres or</u>
<u n="742" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="743" who="S0144">before you go to sleep</u>
<u n="744" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="745" who="S0144">that's good</u>
<u n="746" who="S0024">or you're like those crazy blokes who those big rugby blokes that <vocal desc="laugh"/> in that highest village place in in India</u>
<u n="747" who="S0144">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Ah</u>
<u n="748" who="S0024">what was that place called?</u>
<u n="749" who="S0144">I dunno</u>
<u n="750" who="S0024">those big rugby blokes <pause dur="short"/> rar <pause dur="short"/> what eh? We're alright <pause dur="short"/> we were at three three thousand five hundred?</u>
<u n="751" who="S0144">no it was about four thousand</u>
<u n="752" who="S0024">was it four? I don't know <pause dur="short"/> well it was at the threshold wasn't it</u>
<u n="753" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="754" who="S0024">of of you</u>
<u n="755" who="S0144">I think the threshold's about two and a half thousand I think</u>
<u n="756" who="S0024">oh is it?</u>
<u n="757" who="S0144">that's when you can start feeling altitude sickness</u>
<u n="758" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but it was the highest <pause dur="short"/> was it the highest village in the world?</u>
<u n="759" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="760" who="S0024">not any more</u>
<u n="761" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="762" who="S0024">with electricity?</u>
<u n="763" who="S0144">no it wasn't that one <pause dur="short"/> it was</u>
<u n="764" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="765" who="S0144">another one</u>
<u n="766" who="S0024">oh and they went oh we're alright <pause dur="short"/> we're gonna go out walking for the day <pause dur="short"/> and they ran <pause dur="short"/> we saw them didn't we <pause dur="short"/> they went running up and down up and down up and down round and round</u>
<u n="767" who="S0144">idiots</u>
<u n="768" who="S0024">running up and down the hills having the time of their lives <pause dur="short"/> they were like little goats</u>
<u n="769" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="770" who="S0024">or big big baulky goats cos they had all those muscles didn't they</u>
<u n="771" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="772" who="S0024">and then they <trunc>n</trunc> God I thought they were gonna die</u>
<u n="773" who="S0144">like yeah</u>
<u n="774" who="S0024">I was really worried</u>
<u n="775" who="S0144">they did look fucked</u>
<u n="776" who="S0024">one of them couldn't breath at all</u>
<u n="777" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="778" who="S0024">he was going ah huh ah huh</u>
<u n="779" who="S0144">they were idiots</u>
<u n="780" who="S0024">I know</u>
<u n="781" who="S0144">well they were <trunc>ty</trunc> typical British like ah</u>
<u n="782" who="S0024" trans="overlap">they they went home as well <pause dur="short"/> they had to go home</u>
<u n="783" who="S0144">oh yeah</u>
<u n="784" who="S0024">they were going to do the same route as us and go all the way round and they had to go home</u>
<u n="785" who="S0144" trans="overlap">no they just fucked themselves up <pause dur="short"/> just trying to out-man each other</u>
<u n="786" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="787" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="788" who="S0144">er</u>
<u n="789" who="S0024">hmm</u>
<u n="790" who="S0144">right so tomorrow because this bloody game isn't on BBC or ITV</u>
<u n="791" who="S0024">ah</u>
<u n="792" who="S0144">erm shall I phone the pub in Barnham Broom?</u>
<u n="793" who="S0024" trans="overlap">I think phone <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="794" who="S0144">and see if they've got ESPN or</u>
<u n="795" who="S0024">I think it'd be better for us to walk to Barnham Broom and watch it rather than</u>
<u n="796" who="S0144">but er</u>
<u n="797" who="S0024">I dunno rather than</u>
<u n="798" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well I'll have to phone them up but from what I remember of that pub they've only got like a TV in one of those mounted brackets in the top corner of the room</u>
<u n="799" who="S0024">no no they had a big screen <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure</u>
<u n="800" who="S0144">I don't think so</u>
<u n="801" who="S0024">well phone them up <pause dur="short"/> and say have you got a big screen <pause dur="short"/> are you <trunc>watch</trunc> playing the game?</u>
<u n="802" who="S0144">do you know what I mean? I don't wanna go there if people are having their their Sunday lunches</u>
<u n="803" who="S0024">it's Saturday</u>
<u n="804" who="S0144">oh okay <pause dur="short"/> oh that's a point <pause dur="short"/> I have visions of me you know a big family having their dinner and me come on <pause dur="short"/> oh come on ref you fucking <trunc>cu</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="805" who="S0024" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but it's it's not really the right atmosphere to watch some football though I don't think</u>
<u n="806" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="807" who="S0024">but I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it might be <pause dur="short"/> it might be better</u>
<u n="808" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well that's why I was thinking maybe Dereham's better</u>
<u n="809" who="S0024">er</u>
<u n="810" who="S0144">it might have more of a sporty kind of bar with a big screen TV</u>
<u n="811" who="S0024">you've gotta get there</u>
<u n="812" who="S0144" trans="overlap">although Dereham's not really like that either is it</u>
<u n="813" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="814" who="S0144">yeah it'll take an hour to get there</u>
<u n="815" who="S0024" trans="overlap">you're best off going into the city but</u>
<u n="816" who="S0144">then we'll have to <pause dur="short"/> it'll cost us around twenty quid on the bus <pause dur="short"/> it does seem a bit pointless <pause dur="short"/> I'll phone the bar er the <anon type="place"/> huh <anon type="place"/> one when we get back</u>
<u n="817" who="S0024">yeah if not phone  if not phone  phone the social club and say</u>
<u n="818" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="819" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they've they have always been quite nice to us there and they and the people in there would be there to watch the football</u>
<u n="820" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but we are we we're not members <pause dur="short"/> and they're a bit funny</u>
<u n="821" who="S0024">yeah but they have always been fairly nice to us <unclear/></u>
<u n="822" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah they have done yeah but I feel guilty <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="823" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="824" who="S0144">and I wanna watch the game in relative comfort</u>
<u n="825" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="826" who="S0144">not</u>
<u n="827" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="828" who="S0144">looking over my shoulder <pause dur="short"/> feeling guilty cos we haven't paid</u>
<u n="829" who="S0024">but it was friendlier than the other pub when I know we haven't been in there for a year but like when when we were sitting there</u>
<u n="830" who="S0144">what other pub?</u>
<u n="831" who="S0024">everybody would say hello as they walked in <pause dur="short"/> oh hello <pause dur="short"/> like cos they wanted to know what who you were or something they were like very inquisitive of who you are</u>
<u n="832" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="833" who="S0024">so they were quite friendly</u>
<u n="834" who="S0144">yeah they were yeah</u>
<u n="835" who="S0024">like they would walk in and go hello <pause dur="short"/> and they all said goodnight to us when we left</u>
<u n="836" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="837" who="S0024">goodnight</u>
<u n="838" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="839" who="S0024">and even though we kept ourselves to ourselves for most of the night <pause dur="short"/> but in the pub they are they're a bit</u>
<u n="840" who="S0144">yeah a bit local</u>
<u n="841" who="S0024">alright? Do you wanna <trunc>si</trunc> do you wanna sit by the  by the  fire in which they mean sit by the window</u>
<u n="842" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="843" who="S0024">so it looks like there's people in here <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="844" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="845" who="S0144">ha <pause dur="short"/> what so we can keep an eye on you</u>
<u n="846" who="S0024" trans="overlap">sit sot there cos like we're on the main road</u>
<u n="847" who="S0144"><unclear/> Yeah</u>
<u n="848" who="S0024">when people look in it'll look busy</u>
<u n="849" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Ah <pause dur="short"/> beautiful colours isn't it</u>
<u n="850" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <unclear/> Lovely</u>
<u n="851" who="S0144">it's a nice time to go for a walk actually</u>
<u n="852" who="S0024">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="853" who="S0144">okay what's that pub called? <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="854" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="855" who="S0144">right <pause dur="short"/> have you got a yellow pages? That'll be on the internet won't it</u>
<u n="856" who="S0024" trans="overlap">no we burn it</u>
<u n="857" who="S0144">oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="858" who="S0024">we don't use it</u>
<u n="859" who="S0144">well it does burn well</u>
<u n="860" who="S0024">look on the internet <pause dur="short"/> it's like the best fire starter</u>
<u n="861" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="862" who="S0024">that comes free to your door <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="863" who="S0144">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I thought the bible was quite good</u>
<u n="864" who="S0024">that doesn't come free to your door any more</u>
<u n="865" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="866" who="S0024">it's er <pause dur="short"/> they used to be free didn't they</u>
<u n="867" who="S0144">wow look at those colours</u>
<u n="868" who="S0024">mm</u>
<u n="869" who="S0144">it's like a painting</u>
<u n="870" who="S0024">ha</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="871" who="S0144">just huh</u>
<u n="872" who="S0024">so I've gotta phone <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because</u>
<u n="873" who="S0144">what is she coming tomorrow?</u>
<u n="874" who="S0024">you want to go <pause dur="short"/> but she wants to pop over in the morning</u>
<u n="875" who="S0144">right well I think kick off</u>
<u n="876" who="S0024">Cos she said Ray's gonna finish work in the afternoon so she wants to pop over and see us in the morning <pause dur="short"/> or see me in the morning</u>
<u n="877" who="S0144">right</u>
<u n="878" who="S0024">but if we need to get somewhere by twelve o'clock</u>
<u n="879" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="880" who="S0024">we need to have a plan of action to say right we've gotta be at so and so at twelve o'clock</u>
<u n="881" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="882" who="S0024">so come round really early or something</u>
<u n="883" who="S0144">well she's gonna have to come round about ten o'clock then</u>
<u n="884" who="S0024">yeah I know</u>
<u n="885" who="S0144">Cos it takes an hour to walk to the pub</u>
<u n="886" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="887" who="S0144">ha <pause dur="short"/> well it takes it took us forty forty minutes was it? Forty-five?</u>
<u n="888" who="S0024" trans="overlap">ah but she's got one  she's got one  seat in her car so you could walk to the pub and I'll meet you down there</u>
<u n="889" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="890" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> She can drive me</u>
<u n="891" who="S0144">I'll sit on the bonnet <pause dur="short"/> and I'll hold on like a a Vietnamese traffic warden</u>
<u n="892" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="893" who="S0144">ha</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="894" who="S0144">er so what is it Friday?</u>
<u n="895" who="S0024">mm mm</u>
<u n="896" who="S0144">er so what shall we do tonight then? So I might do another hour of work because I can't see me doing any tomorrow</u>
<u n="897" who="S0024">mm <pause dur="short"/> well we played a big game yesterday so I think I might I dunno try and get something else done <pause dur="short"/> I might just try and do something</u>
<u n="898" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="899" who="S0024">but I don't want to be lazy tonight</u>
<u n="900" who="S0144">well is there anything on telly worth watching then tonight?</u>
<u n="901" who="S0024">no I don't think so <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I only watch The Apprentice <pause dur="short"/> it's like oh Tuesday night <pause dur="short"/> right I'm watching</u>
<u n="902" who="S0144">it's Wednesday</u>
<u n="903" who="S0024">oh Wednesday night I'm watching television at half past nine</u>
<u n="904" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's the only thing I've been watching</u>
<u n="905" who="S0024">ah but</u>
<u n="906" who="S0144">I didn't even watch it this week though so</u>
<u n="907" who="S0024">mum and I are watching that thing um ah I've forgotten what it's called <pause dur="short"/> we've been watching a series <pause dur="short"/> but we haven't watched it in a while but we've been recording them</u>
<u n="908" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="909" who="S0024">so we've got those to have a look at <pause dur="short"/> but we missed one and I was hoping they might repeat it</u>
<u n="910" who="S0144" trans="overlap">what is it? Yeah</u>
<u n="911" who="S0024">er <pause dur="short"/> it's about erm this <trunc>th</trunc> they there's all these house mates in the fifties <pause dur="short"/> they've got some cool outfits</u>
<u n="912" who="S0144">ha</u>
<u n="913" who="S0024">I want the whole wardrobe of that that thing <pause dur="short"/> and er and um this guy kind of does some weird I don't really know what's happened yet some social experiment or something <pause dur="short"/> and he gets all these different kinds of people who study different things who are from different places and gets them all to come and live with him <pause dur="short"/> and it's something to do with all the flat mates <pause dur="short"/> but it keeps flicking back to the scene <pause dur="short"/> he's died now like ages in the future they're all  they're all  like sixty-five years old something like that</u>
<u n="914" who="S0144">yeah?</u>
<u n="915" who="S0024">and um he <trunc>le</trunc> he's left his house to all of the flatmates they had when he was twenty</u>
<u n="916" who="S0144">right</u>
<u n="917" who="S0024">well they must have been younger than that <pause dur="short"/> they were all at university <pause dur="short"/> eighteen or nineteen twenty something like that <pause dur="short"/> and he's left them all of his house so they've all kind of they're all kind of getting back together</u>
<u n="918" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0024">to clean out the house and sort it out <pause dur="short"/> and they haven't seen each other for all that time</u>
<u n="920" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="921" who="S0024">so I the whole story is you know work out what why they were all living together in the first place <pause dur="short"/> you know what this whole experiment thing was <pause dur="short"/> cos he interviewed <trunc>s</trunc> all these people to come and live with him at the time <pause dur="short"/> and he had affairs with quite er two of them so far <pause dur="short"/> it's probably gonna be all of them by the end of it</u>
<u n="922" who="S0144">what it's him and a house of girls</u>
<u n="923" who="S0024">no no there's only three girls <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="924" who="S0144">I was gonna say it sounds a bit like a porno to me</u>
<u n="925" who="S0024"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm but erm er what was I going to say? I dunno it's about their lives back then and then it's kind of intermingling with their lives now <pause dur="short"/> it's good <pause dur="short"/> I like it</u>
<u n="926" who="S0144">right <pause dur="short"/> so is it? What's it gonna be some kind of sinister thing or spooky or what? Or just drama?</u>
<u n="927" who="S0024" trans="overlap">er <pause dur="short"/> it's just a drama but I think it's gonna turn out that them all getting together was really important for some reason <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="928" who="S0144">what for some spiritual reason?</u>
<u n="929" who="S0024">no</u>
<u n="930" who="S0144">like they didn't</u>
<u n="931" who="S0024">experimental reason</u>
<u n="932" who="S0144">right</u>
<u n="933" who="S0024">I don't know</u>
<u n="934" who="S0144">what like a Lost?</u>
<u n="935" who="S0024">er</u>
<u n="936" who="S0144">A kind of thing that doesn't make sense and drags on <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="937" who="S0024">well I've only watched two of them so far</u>
<u n="938" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="939" who="S0024">so I'll let you know if it drags on</u>
<u n="940" who="S0144">ha</u>
<u n="941" who="S0024">but we've missed number three and we haven't got it recorded</u>
<u n="942" who="S0144">oh right</u>
<u n="943" who="S0024">so we don't know whether to skip it and just catch up</u>
<u n="944" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well if your dad didn't have a limit on his downloads you could watch it on</u>
<u n="945" who="S0024">I know</u>
<u n="946" who="S0144">thingy</u>
<u n="947" who="S0024">oh God <vocal desc="laugh"/> We've gotta upgrade him</u>
<u n="948" who="S0144">I know</u>
<u n="949" who="S0024">God</u>
<u n="950" who="S0144">we're twenty gigabytes over <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="951" who="S0024">it's you watching all those You Tube videos</u>
<u n="952" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="953" who="S0024">it is</u>
<u n="954" who="S0144">I only watched a couple <pause dur="short"/> it was downloading our work</u>
<u n="955" who="S0024">football</u>
<u n="956" who="S0144">oh and that <pause dur="short"/> let's not talk about that though</u>
<u n="957" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="958" who="S0024">oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="959" who="S0144">ah</u>
<u n="960" who="S0024">oh I can't believe it cos twenty-five pounds over</u>
<u n="961" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="962" who="S0024">this time <pause dur="short"/> we're gonna have to pay that</u>
<u n="963" who="S0144">no it's fifteen pounds over</u>
<u n="964" who="S0024">oh is it?</u>
<u n="965" who="S0144">Cos you're allowed ten gigabytes then he has to pay five pounds per five gigabytes or something</u>
<u n="966" who="S0024">pound a gigabyte then</u>
<u n="967" who="S0144">pound a gigabyte yeah <pause dur="short"/> so fifteen quid</u>
<u n="968" who="S0024">oh</u>
<u n="969" who="S0144">which you know</u>
<u n="970" who="S0024">well you know thing is that package was suitable for them when they were</u>
<u n="971" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="972" who="S0024">on their own</u>
<u n="973" who="S0144">yeah cos they</u>
<u n="974" who="S0024">but cos we're staying</u>
<u n="975" who="S0144">yeah but it's annoying cos like I</u>
<u n="976" who="S0024" trans="overlap">but the thing is if they upgrade it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then we go away and then</u>
<u n="977" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well can't they just go back again?</u>
<u n="978" who="S0024">oh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> you know what those hotlines are like <pause dur="short"/> you'd be on the telephone paying ten pounds anyway just to try and downgrade it <pause dur="short"/> and then they'll</u>
<u n="979" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="980" who="S0024">argue their case <pause dur="short"/> no you don't want to do that <pause dur="short"/> let me put you through to somebody with a special deal <pause dur="short"/> la le la le la</u>
<u n="981" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="982" who="S0024">ah look at that purple pink</u>
<u n="983" who="S0144">yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> huh <pause dur="short"/> oh I've gotta make my movie <pause dur="short"/> I forgot</u>
<u n="984" who="S0024">yeah you've still got to think of what your item is</u>
<u n="985" who="S0144">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="986" who="S0024">I love your idea</u>
<u n="987" who="S0144">you think it's a good idea?</u>
<u n="988" who="S0024">I love it yeah I love it</u>
<u n="989" who="S0144">I don't know how to film it</u>
<u n="990" who="S0024">but</u>
<u n="991" who="S0144">what time of day <pause dur="short"/> cos I need to make scenes that are gonna when he keeps finding the object I need to then cut to a day time scene to break up the to then have a following like night afterwards so <pause dur="short"/> so there needs to be some scenes in the garden but the whole like</u>
<u n="992" who="S0024" trans="overlap">scenes in the garden? But the whole thing is about a television isn't it?</u>
<u n="993" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well exactly</u>
<u n="994" who="S0024">so</u>
<u n="995" who="S0144">or <pause dur="short"/> but I need to signify like different days</u>
<u n="996" who="S0024">yeah</u>
<u n="997" who="S0144">I need to make that clear <pause dur="short"/> ah so maybe just a quick shot <pause dur="short"/> I only wanna make it like five minutes long</u>
<u n="998" who="S0024">yeah but five minutes it's longer than you think to make five minutes of tape</u>
<u n="999" who="S0144">yeah I know yeah</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0024" trans="overlap">if you're having short short scenes</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0024">I don't know</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0144">right <pause dur="short"/> turn this off</u>
</body>
</text>
