<text id="SPXW">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:55:00</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-29</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0261 S0262</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>House-sitting in Australia</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Innovations in education, strategic directions for publishing companies and telecommunication companies i.e. mobile phone suppliers and service suppliers, ICT, business strategies, project management, </topics>
		<activity>A couple talking about educational innovations and developments in telecommunications then that leads onto setting up an idea for a business.  </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, announcing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0261">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British/New Zealand</nat>
				<birthplace>Wellington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>New Zealand</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/NZ</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Kiwi English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>non_uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>non_uk</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>non_uk</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>non_uk</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Entrepreneur</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0262">
				<exactage>41</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dorchester</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South of England</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified; German -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0261">okay this is part two of our discussion this is more about education et cetera and strategic erm direction with that okay fire away</u>
<u n="2" who="S0262">erm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0261">so we were talking about erm the context of of trying to find a strategic direction where innovators are heading and seeing if you can erm er focus your your joining up in that context so the example was in places like Vietnam that erm outfits like the British Council are connecting up with tech erm outfits like Nokia erm to er collaborate on trying to get erm English learning materials out in in a digital publishing arena</u>
<u n="4" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0261">through tech companies erm as opposed to outfits like Pearson er or or other digital publishing houses</u>
<u n="6" who="S0262">yeah and er you know really that that's</u>
<u n="7" who="S0261">so who's actually running the the the publishing side of it? are they saying the techs the tech companies are? or are they saying that that's a mechanism for them to self-publish through a tech er erm output?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0262">they I think I think you know if you start with the core business of what a publishing company does it's always got to get its content out there it's got to be able to sell it and so British Council erm are in a good position because they publish content they are in a good position and they're massive enough to partner up with Nokia and get people into <trunc>Ch</trunc>China and Vietnam who will work away with the tech people and work a way of making a mobile learning experience as seamless and as as fun and and as brilliant as possible erm so that's where the real tech stuff will come through is making sure that on a Nokia you've got a <trunc>pru</trunc> <trunc>fan</trunc>fantastic learning experience a mobile Nokia</u>
<u n="9" who="S0261">yeah so the context is trying to erm include mobile devices erm as platforms for spreading the message e-learning et cetera erm and er er supplying people with products to the tools that they're going to use to be able to get exposure to er whatever they're trying to learn and the better their tick product erm the er the potentially the larger the market you can access</u>
<u n="10" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay this is it so this is another one successfully implemented in ten countries in three continents the Bridge IT project is now being piloted in Vietnam by the British Council in partnership with Nokia and the Pearson foundation initially twenty primary teachers from ten poorly resourced budget schools <unclear/> in Ho Chi Minh city Bridge IT uses smart phones and networks to deliver materials and professional development to educators <pause dur="short"/> erm around the world in order to develop teaching capacity enable learners to access digital learning materials through mobile technology with the focus purely on English for this pilot project selected British Council learning resources including videos and songs stories grammar activities from the Learnenglish Kids website have been uploaded to a cloud server the teachers using their Nokia education delivery software already installed in Nokia smartphones can download the teaching resources to smartphones using the 3G network they then connect them to the TVs or data projectors and display the materials as teaching aids okay do you want me to continue?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0261">yeah yeah yeah I'm <trunc>l</trunc>I'm listening <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0262">okay <pause dur="short"/> with the power of mobile technology students can now explore state-of-the-art educational programmes regardless of their school's location internet access or academic resource budget <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> head of primary education at the Ho Chi Minh city department of education said at the launch this project promises to bring an effective tool to help schools in poorer areas where they can implement the digital English teaching method more effectively with the help of technology to <unclear>digitise lessons</unclear> I believe this will bring benefits to those pupils instead of covering subjects such as maths and science as in the Philippines and other countries the Vietnam pilot project will focus only on teaching English in primary schools this approach fits in to Vietnam's ministry of education and training plan to implement ICT and digital learning resources as part of the English twenty twenty strategy so you've got a few years there then to upgrade the teaching and learning of English across primary and secondary levels furthermore since two thousand the ministry has been placing ICT on reform agenda as both an object of education and an innovating teaching methodology an important pedagogical tool from two thousand two thousand and seven Vietnam moved up fifteen places in a worldwide list of ICT development putting it among the top ten developing countries however research has shown that while many schools and teachers have access to ICT for administration purposes and some for making lesson materials very few use it as a tool for creative learning in the classroom the pilot project was launched on the twenty-fifth of January in Ho Chi Minh city as one of the participating schools followed by a two-day workshop <unclear>money</unclear> for all the participating teachers the workshop <trunc>t</trunc> aimed to equip them with the skills needed to use smartphones to access quality teaching and learning materials provided by the British Council and mapped to Vietnam's national curriculum through the <unclear>NED platform</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> director of the British Council Vietnam <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said we're delighted to partner with Nokia and Pearson foundation in this meaningful project <unclear>the</unclear></u>
<u n="13" who="S0261">Pearson</u>
<u n="14" who="S0262">who?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0261">Pearson</u>
<u n="16" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="18" who="S0262">foundation</u>
<u n="19" who="S0261"><unclear>right</unclear></u>
<u n="20" who="S0262">that's different though from Pearson publishing</u>
<u n="21" who="S0261">oh is it?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0261">different place?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0262">er <unclear/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0261" trans="overlap">same company different</u>
<u n="26" who="S0262">philanthropic <trunc>philan</trunc></u>
<u n="27" who="S0261">philanthropic?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0261"><unclear>right</unclear> okay</u>
<u n="30" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but we can check that out <unclear/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="32" who="S0262">the British Council Vietnam can contribute a vast experience in teacher training to this project in the past ten years the British Council Vietnam has trained nearly eight thousand English teachers face-to-face and over two hundred and fifteen thousand teachers indirectly furthermore taking advantage of the Nokia education delivery platform the world-renowned learning English and teaching English resources of the British Council will have a huge potential to be shared among hundreds of thousands of Vietnamese children living in remote and disadvantaged areas across Vietnam the success of the pilot which ends next May so it's May two thousand and fourteen will be measured by the enthusiasm and commitment of the twenty selected English teachers well crikey that's not very much er of the twenty selected English teachers in using the Nokia smartphones</u>
<u n="33" who="S0261" trans="overlap">did you say May twenty-fourteen?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="36" who="S0262">erm and the <unclear>NED</unclear> as well as the British Council learning resources there will be mid-course and final evaluations through observations feedback questionnaires attitudinal <unclear/> surveys er I haven't heard of one of those and focus group discussions</u>
<u n="37" who="S0261">mm <pause dur="short"/> okay so that's an example of something that is going on and then er</u>
<u n="38" who="S0262">and then there's another one about China which is doing exactly the same <unclear>thing</unclear></u>
<u n="39" who="S0261">right right okay so <trunc>w</trunc>what we want to try and nail that's an example</u>
<u n="40" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0261">what we now want to look at is within Southeast Asia what kind of countries are likely to take on this type of programme? or are heading in a more <trunc>cr</trunc> progressive <trunc>p</trunc> direction</u>
<u n="42" who="S0262">yeah you <trunc>nee</trunc></u>
<u n="43" who="S0261">that that that that are growing into that</u>
<u n="44" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0261">they're not already through it</u>
<u n="46" who="S0262">well no one's gonna have been through <unclear>erm any of this</unclear></u>
<u n="47" who="S0261">no cos it's a new thing</u>
<u n="48" who="S0262">er er potentially South Korea maybe Japan anyone who's got already very well-established erm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0261">ICT</u>
<u n="50" who="S0262">er <trunc>y</trunc>yeah</u>
<u n="51" who="S0261">and and policy and networks and</u>
<u n="52" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0261">and <trunc>g</trunc> and money et cetera</u>
<u n="54" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah yeah but these are <trunc>s</trunc> top ten developing countries</u>
<u n="55" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah so they're <trunc>f</trunc> relative they're relatively wealthy</u>
<u n="56" who="S0262">so if we just know what the top ten developing countries are</u>
<u n="57" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0262">we can focus on those to start with and I'd suggest that South Korea and Japan isn't a developing country</u>
<u n="59" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="60" who="S0262">but if we're interested in looking at the top ten developing countries then we can figure out where others might be heading</u>
<u n="61" who="S0261"><unclear>yeah</unclear> and this is referencing Southeast Asia is it?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0262">yes</u>
<u n="63" who="S0261">it's in context of Southeast Asia?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0262">yeah it's in the supplement for Southeast Asia or <trunc>w</trunc> Asia Pacific</u>
<u n="65" who="S0261" trans="overlap">Asia Pacific</u>
<u n="66" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0261"><trunc>o</trunc>okay erm <pause dur="short"/> okay erm alright so if <vocal desc="misc"/> so if we know that list can we find that list? now?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0262">do you can I just tell you how it works? how the British Council have partnered up with Nokia?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0261">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0262">tell you how the technology works?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="73" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0262">so erm the er the British Council and Nokia have been collaborating since two thousand and nine to deliver learning materials through Nokia <trunc>non</trunc>non-smartphone headsets the materials consist of text-based and GPRS-based English learning content created by ELT professionals from the British Council available at various different levels it also includes culture and history and is designed to teach English sentences test vocabulary and punctuation users access materials by either subscribing to a text message service or browsing online through Nokia phones materials are delivered <trunc>th</trunc>through Nokia Life an application pre-installed on Nokia mid and low-end mobile devices and offer personalised information for daily living learning sharing to millions in developing markets primarily to those who never use a PC that's interesting</u>
<u n="75" who="S0261">yeah so what they're saying is <trunc>k</trunc>is keep it simple yeah? so they've done it on a text-based delivery that's cheap doesn't cost a lot of money</u>
<u n="76" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0261">they're saying that's subscription-based so <trunc>m</trunc> either you're paying a certain amount per month to have access to it or maybe on a daily rate or whatever it is erm through a pay-as-you-go service or you look at it via the internet which is on a data-related service</u>
<u n="78" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0261">so if you've got enough money to pay for the data you would access it through there</u>
<u n="80" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0261">but presumably the text message delivery system is the cheapest possible way to get the message out there</u>
<u n="82" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0261">erm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="85" who="S0261">who knows? there might be other ways to deliver it that are that er that that's that that's that's the starter and also they're saying pre-smartphones</u>
<u n="86" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="87" who="S0261">so they're they're devices that can be provided at a very low cost as well</u>
<u n="88" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0261">which are probably more likely secondhand or or er er I don't know</u>
<u n="90" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0261">how many will still be manufactured but</u>
<u n="92" who="S0262">well with three hundred million English learners in China five hundred and sixty-four million internet users and over one point one billion mobile phone subscribers in China</u>
<u n="93" who="S0261" trans="overlap">they're probably still</u>
<u n="94" who="S0262">you could go on forever</u>
<u n="95" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah er</u>
<u n="96" who="S0262">with er old crap phones</u>
<u n="97" who="S0261">yes yes that's right</u>
<u n="98" who="S0262">erm according to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> the British Council's head of English learner product development in China</u>
<u n="99" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><unclear>well</unclear> you've got different the point is you've got different levels</u>
<u n="100" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0261">so you can you can they're all different markets</u>
<u n="102" who="S0262">it's it's <trunc>w</trunc>what we call differentiation of <unclear>the</unclear> market</u>
<u n="103" who="S0261">yeah mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0262">erm and the content reflects the diversity and diverse needs of English learners in China <unclear/> what you said when people started to realise the necessity of learning English in the early nineteen nineties in China er eighties sorry the aim for the mast <trunc>v</trunc> the vast majority was the chance to study abroad nowadays learners include elementary students big business teachers and retirees and both that's another one retirees we haven't heard that one before and both rural and <trunc>ur</trunc> er urban residents yeah this needs <trunc>r</trunc> their needs range wildly from education to career development and to social requirements and in order to help them learn</u>
<u n="105" who="S0261"><unclear>what are the</unclear></u>
<u n="106" who="S0262">we at the British Council of high quality English learning materials through an increasing number of <unclear>chanuals</unclear> channels called including including Nokia Life</u>
<u n="107" who="S0261">what were their needs again?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0262">so erm elementary students</u>
<u n="109" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="110" who="S0262">teachers <pause dur="short"/> new one was retirees</u>
<u n="111" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="112" who="S0262">and now we're looking specifically at erm what they call rural and urban residents</u>
<u n="113" who="S0261">okay so so there's there's a mix of the market and <unclear>the</unclear> mix of different types of the population et cetera</u>
<u n="114" who="S0262">so if you wanted to focus on a niche market start with</u>
<u n="115" who="S0261">you could pick one of them</u>
<u n="116" who="S0262">and the British Council are not gonna be doing all of these brilliantly</u>
<u n="117" who="S0261">no</u>
<u n="118" who="S0262">it's far too fucking</u>
<u n="119" who="S0261">no</u>
<u n="120" who="S0262">big a market and there'll be other people trying to</u>
<u n="121" who="S0261">be in on it</u>
<u n="122" who="S0262">cram in</u>
<u n="123" who="S0261">as well</u>
<u n="124" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0261">yeah cos if we're somebody's doing it somebody else is doing it also in a different way</u>
<u n="126" who="S0262">but they've got to run a business a big business so they've got to show profit</u>
<u n="127" who="S0261">yes that's right</u>
<u n="128" who="S0262">whereas if you're coming in</u>
<u n="129" who="S0261">er er on</u>
<u n="130" who="S0262">on a niche <unclear>share</unclear></u>
<u n="131" who="S0261">er on a smaller</u>
<u n="132" who="S0262">you <trunc>c</trunc>you can run a business</u>
<u n="133" who="S0261">level</u>
<u n="134" who="S0262">but you don't have to show as much profit you don't have to be running it at you know</u>
<u n="135" who="S0261">well you don't have to be running if for shareholders</u>
<u n="136" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="137" who="S0261">you don't have to be running it to deliver erm month er quarterly reports</u>
<u n="138" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so you don't have to stay in the big you don't go in the mainstream sections where they have to be they'll go in mainstream like for example mainstream is erm in China elementary students the reason why they're focusing on elementary students is because</u>
<u n="139" who="S0261" trans="overlap">before we go on with that</u>
<u n="140" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0261">can I just finish off the needs that</u>
<u n="142" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay yeah that's the end of it</u>
<u n="143" who="S0261">erm but you did say that their needs were something specific</u>
<u n="144" who="S0262">oh sorry so yeah their needs range wildly from education to career development so that's not just about erm teaching <trunc>Engli</trunc> er teaching Chinese teachers how to teach English it's actually about saying</u>
<u n="145" who="S0261" trans="overlap">business career development</u>
<u n="146" who="S0262">if you learn English if you learn English where in the world can you go with it?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0262">what can you do with English once you've got it?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0261">that's right</u>
<u n="150" who="S0262">that's career development</u>
<u n="151" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="152" who="S0262">okay?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0262">and then erm and how do you keep your English going as you're as you're progressing through your career</u>
<u n="155" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="156" who="S0262">that's a very big part and then <trunc>s</trunc> to social requirements so potentially more foreigners living in China they're not really speaking Chinese yet because it's taking them too long so there's more <trunc>infl</trunc> there's more impact or need for this for</u>
<u n="157" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm well there's a <trunc>b</trunc>there's a business niche in knowing English and dealing with the people who are moving in</u>
<u n="158" who="S0262" trans="overlap">it's a <trunc>s</trunc><trunc>s</trunc>a social <trunc>socia</trunc>social requirement can be work</u>
<u n="159" who="S0261">that's right</u>
<u n="160" who="S0262">it can be outside of work</u>
<u n="161" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="162" who="S0262">yeah? so it's it's another way of looking at don't need to <trunc>l</trunc> necessarily look at the work way of doing things</u>
<u n="163" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="164" who="S0262">it's all those other well like the Chinese housewives who sit around speaking to erm native English speakers</u>
<u n="165" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="166" who="S0262">because they all live in Shanghai and Beijing</u>
<u n="167" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0262">Guangzhou blah blah blah yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah so the <trunc>n</trunc>the need is I er I want to learn this so I can become a certain part of society</u>
<u n="170" who="S0262">yeah <unclear>but I can</unclear></u>
<u n="171" who="S0261">or you can look at it in a private context</u>
<u n="172" who="S0262"><unclear>I</unclear></u>
<u n="173" who="S0261">of I want to travel somewhere so I want to learn it</u>
<u n="174" who="S0262">absolutely</u>
<u n="175" who="S0261">it could be on a vocational level</u>
<u n="176" who="S0262">tourist level</u>
<u n="177" who="S0261">it could be like the community's class level</u>
<u n="178" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0261"><unclear/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0262">that would be rural and urban you know that sort of er well rural how the fuck do you teach some rural people English?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0261">er well you</u>
<u n="182" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><trunc>w</trunc>what's the point?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0261">er as a community group</u>
<u n="184" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0261">you know you're er somebody comes in and once a month er everybody go everybody goes to the</u>
<u n="186" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well you're raising their aspirations yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0261">the village hall and listens to what's <trunc>d</trunc>what's done</u>
<u n="188" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0261">and they collaboratively learn</u>
<u n="190" who="S0262">and it's raising aspirations cos rural you'll never be on the same aspirational level as an urban dweller</u>
<u n="191" who="S0261" trans="overlap">that that's that's right yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0262">so it's good for the Chinese to get their rural people thinking a bit more you know higher level</u>
<u n="193" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0262">erm and so the next bit is erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a vice president for Nokia in China says the wide range of content means that we can also graduate service according to what consumers want so the scalability is massive that's what he's saying <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>r</trunc> the wide range of content meaning there are so many different people out there who want different types of content that they can scale it up at any level</u>
<u n="195" who="S0261">er yes so you can you can identify paths which er running er er with stronger thread for a particular period of time</u>
<u n="196" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0261">cos there'll be trends</u>
<u n="198" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0261">and erm you can say well we want to be on that pathway for this time and move to a different pathway as and when say the growth in it starts or something like that</u>
<u n="200" who="S0262">and the generations are getting older so you'll you will watch a little elementary kiddie that's what I was about to explain to you that if you teach elementary in two thousand and fourteen their appetite for this kind of content will grow with them as they progress through their</u>
<u n="201" who="S0261" trans="overlap">throughout their lives</u>
<u n="202" who="S0262">language development so by the <trunc>le</trunc> age of eleven it's quite possible that they will become fluent in English and they've never even left China</u>
<u n="203" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0262">and there's some people believe that because of this type of er learning activity and access to resources you could actually you really could be fluent like almost native English speaker</u>
<u n="205" who="S0261">yes okay</u>
<u n="206" who="S0262">cos you start so young when their brains are so</u>
<u n="207" who="S0261">developing</u>
<u n="208" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0261">yeah er of course erm so <pause dur="short"/> right so er similarly the the identification is is that there's a there's a massive stream er a massive stream of opportunity <trunc>reg</trunc>regarding all of that</u>
<u n="210" who="S0262">so it's not quite the end yet so it goes for both partners the initiative provides so this is the win win provides an invaluable opportunity to reach a vast underserved market Nokia Life is available on simple phones used by rural and migrant workers meaning the content is probably the first contact that those people have actually had with a mobile English learning product and anything from the British Council so it's the first time that they'll ever see something like this which I can totally imagine to be true</u>
<u n="211" who="S0261">what was it called again? Nokia</u>
<u n="212" who="S0262">Nokia Life</u>
<u n="213" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="214" who="S0262">says <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> director of the British Council China she adds that many of these users will become city residents with the same aspirations and the same need to use English and that with rapid social change in China new media is the only way to get the message out there</u>
<u n="215" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="216" who="S0262">so it's what we said</u>
<u n="217" who="S0261">it's it's spreading it's spreading the word to a large audience <unclear>really</unclear> in a in a very <trunc>sp</trunc>specific and easy way</u>
<u n="218" who="S0262">and it's it's it's it's keeping them plugged in because language doesn't</u>
<u n="219" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="220" who="S0262">it's not something you can consume overnight you can't just go and buy a bag</u>
<u n="221" who="S0261" trans="overlap">no you need to need to be ongoing</u>
<u n="222" who="S0262">you you yeah that's what what's brilliant about language and makes so much money well English particularly is because you you you've gotta <trunc>p</trunc> you've gotta keep at it to get any good at it</u>
<u n="223" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0262">so that's why there is always gonna be scalability using the English language as a product</u>
<u n="225" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="226" who="S0262">well maybe not scalability but <unclear>longetivity</unclear></u>
<u n="227" who="S0261">yeah <trunc>long</trunc>longevity</u>
<u n="228" who="S0262">longevity</u>
<u n="229" who="S0261">erm <pause dur="short"/> right erm so does that kind of get us to a point?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0262">I think so</u>
<u n="231" who="S0261">yeah?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0262">for mobile technology</u>
<u n="233" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="234" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="235" who="S0261">okay so <trunc>i</trunc>in that context if you were considering <trunc>h</trunc>how one let's say there's product X and product X needs to be delivered then the from our point of view the things that one needs to have access or or to or no are the the technological delivery of such stuff</u>
<u n="236" who="S0262">yeah get your hands on everything that you can find that they're talking about so you'd go through you'd go and you know you'd you'd go and find someone in Vietnam and go can I have a look at your phone? and can I have a look at how it works? and can you show me how it works? and can you? and you'd actually see it up close and <trunc>f</trunc> and personal</u>
<u n="237" who="S0261">so one could suggest that an action is to actually erm contact erm locals using the service <pause dur="short"/> so you you look at it on different levels to see how it's delivered how people use it what it's delivered on any potential er elements where it's at different levels so that could be on different devices</u>
<u n="238" who="S0262">and the <unclear>fact of the</unclear> thing is is that you you gotta understand the structure of the British Council and how it operates because the British Council need content providers they can either choose to have erm you know managers who er assess the quality of content but who knows? they might be outsourcing the content to</u>
<u n="239" who="S0261">a large provider <pause dur="short"/> pearson</u>
<u n="240" who="S0262" trans="overlap">they might be finding someone who just fucking writes lesson plans and fucking comes up with new ideas for English every single fucking day erm so whether we could provide content to someone like the British Council or whether they're actually a closed a closed off</u>
<u n="241" who="S0261">closed shop</u>
<u n="242" who="S0262">content creator themselves but the suggestion is is that you know okay well done British Council who are in Vietnam who are in China but you're not gonna be the only people there</u>
<u n="243" who="S0261">no</u>
<u n="244" who="S0262">and I think you can bet that there'll be pretty other substantial companies doing similar things but perhaps with different mobile erm <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0261">companies</u>
<u n="246" who="S0262">companies</u>
<u n="247" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="248" who="S0262">yep</u>
<u n="249" who="S0261">erm so</u>
<u n="250" who="S0262">and you gotta think about Nokia because if Nokia isn't actually doing all that well in the global market</u>
<u n="251" who="S0261">yeah but they're trying to change that</u>
<u n="252" who="S0262">well <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="253" who="S0261">they're back into the smartphone market</u>
<u n="254" who="S0262">well er but clearly they're</u>
<u n="255" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="256" who="S0262"><trunc>f</trunc>funny they're going around this bit too they're on the the lower scale as well</u>
<u n="257" who="S0261">er when what do you mean sorry?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0262">well smartphone means you know you gotta have a certain income to be able to find a <trunc>s</trunc> to <trunc>f</trunc> to <trunc>b</trunc> to <trunc>f</trunc> to buy a smartphone</u>
<u n="259" who="S0261">yeah so maybe they're just keeping their niche is at a different level</u>
<u n="260" who="S0262">but China <trunc>d</trunc> you <trunc>c</trunc> you know not everyone can afford a smartphone</u>
<u n="261" who="S0261">that's right so they're they're</u>
<u n="262" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so why are they?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0261">carrying on making</u>
<u n="264" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0261">the lower level phone so everybody else has technologically moved on and Nokia's going well there's still a market to supply all this stuff so we still manufacture that stuff for people</u>
<u n="266" who="S0262">right so they've differentiated</u>
<u n="267" who="S0261" trans="overlap">at at a lower price</u>
<u n="268" who="S0262">again in the market</u>
<u n="269" who="S0261" trans="overlap">to <unclear>fringe</unclear> the market yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0262">yeah?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0262">so you know what what we'd all think is being western we'd go it's all about three G four G</u>
<u n="273" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0262">it's all about the next one the next one the next one</u>
<u n="275" who="S0261" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="276" who="S0262">what we forget is probably all of these other countries in the developing world are still using <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0261" trans="overlap">still operating yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0262">stuff we had <trunc>w</trunc> about five eight nine ten years ago</u>
<u n="279" who="S0261" trans="overlap">at a yeah er yes of course of course</u>
<u n="280" who="S0262">but it's still gonna be useful <trunc>f</trunc> to them the technology the mobile technology with the right way of getting it on the phone already <trunc>pre</trunc> what's the word? installed like that's what Nokia Life is it's already installed with English content on it jeez that's <trunc>fuc</trunc> that's clever cos you're already getting an appetite going for it</u>
<u n="281" who="S0261">yes that's right I mean erm that's no different than a lot of other delivery systems to do with different products which are inherently it's like Windows Windows is a part of a of the majority of a certain type of PC right?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0262">let's just talk about</u>
<u n="283" who="S0261">yeah?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0262">phone mobile phones yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0261" trans="overlap">but that's er it's an example of</u>
<u n="286" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><trunc>y</trunc>yeah yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0261">of built-in delivery system</u>
<u n="288" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0261">yeah? so</u>
<u n="290" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><unclear>but no</unclear> but that's slightly different because I think what I'm saying is and you're gonna get to the tech bit in a minute but what I'm saying is is that there's content someone's written it and then someone has decided how that content fits into the tool and then how that tool sits inside the mobile phone technology</u>
<u n="291" who="S0261">so you can say that there are different levels of contents that are delivered to different devices same message but presented in different ways because you've got basic middle top-end delivered to one G three G four G right? so</u>
<u n="292" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0261">you've actually got several different versions of of the content that is delivered at the same time to different customers</u>
<u n="294" who="S0262">and now you've tripled or <trunc>f</trunc> quadrupled <unclear>or <trunc>w</trunc></unclear> your market</u>
<u n="295" who="S0261" trans="overlap">your output yeah and your market yeah yeah so it's stacked</u>
<u n="296" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0261">it's lots lots of layers to it</u>
<u n="298" who="S0262">content and you've <trunc>t</trunc> hit already four of five different types of generation of mobile phone</u>
<u n="299" who="S0261">mm yes so</u>
<u n="300" who="S0262">so who's who's doing that technology?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah but can before we yes</u>
<u n="302" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0261">before we move on I just wanna capture capture er what I was trying to say</u>
<u n="304" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0261">erm and <unclear><trunc>n</trunc>now I've</unclear> forgotten it so erm</u>
<u n="306" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0261">that er that annoys me erm but we're saying that there are different levels let's just summarise this there are different levels of content <pause dur="short"/> delivered to different technological devices <pause dur="short"/> now erm <pause dur="short"/> different technological tech devices erm so what I was <trunc>g</trunc> otherwise gonna try and get in there was British Council they er have all of these different levels different people provide the content</u>
<u n="308" who="S0262">er we don't know that</u>
<u n="309" who="S0261">we don't know that erm <vocal desc="misc"/> so <pause dur="short"/> from our point of view that's what I wanted to make a point about the British Council have gone onto these different countries and they've created a strategic connection that's very high it's not something that we have the the ability to do</u>
<u n="310" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="311" who="S0261">so we we we are pitching to be in a different level where you're actually working with these outfits or for these outfits or the connection to those outfits as a pathway to deliver your product</u>
<u n="312" who="S0262">I think</u>
<u n="313" who="S0261">because you don't wanna go in at the top level because you might find that difficult</u>
<u n="314" who="S0262" trans="overlap">I think if you could provide content if you even if you could provide content you'd get screwed by the British Council erm cos they'd copyright it and everything and it wouldn't be yours er I I I actually just don't think they would go there I'm I could be wrong but I think you'd get <trunc>sc</trunc> shafted by <unclear/> <trunc>str</trunc>straight off</u>
<u n="315" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah well they basically say that we hire you as a consultant and therefore everything we have is our copyright</u>
<u n="316" who="S0262">right what I think you do is you go you you interrogate that market and find out what the actual product looks like and you find all the different types of users and then you think about a service that you add value to the way that they're using the technology so your services <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's got nothing to do with the British Council you're saying to the British Council thank you for doing the legwork and providing us with all this stuff but now seriously we've gotta show these people how to maximise how to use it because when they're walking round on their mobile phone it's not obvious to them what they're meant to be doing how are they meant to practice pronunciation for example? how are they meant to get the <trunc>com</trunc> you know all these kinds of questions is where you erm go to erm some other people and you go ah now what are we doing here? are we suggesting that actually we're using mobile technology as a way to mainstream <trunc>s</trunc> erm people into language classes? cos that's actually the traditional way of learning a language or is it that we're actually saying to them you can have a blended experience? you can come sometimes to some of our services but you also can knock around just with your phone and and see how far you go</u>
<u n="317" who="S0261">right okay so I mean the the <trunc>th</trunc>that leads onto er another question which is people were delivered this service but but how is it reinforced? what</u>
<u n="318" who="S0262">how do you learn?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0261">how do you learn it?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0262">how do you learn to use the mobile</u>
<u n="321" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="322" who="S0262">to get the language experience? cos that to me is not obvious</u>
<u n="323" who="S0261">no no but <trunc>l</trunc> er let's put that aside let's er they have to learn the how to use the mobile to have access to the service</u>
<u n="324" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0261">right? so erm <trunc>w</trunc>we're not in a <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="326" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but can you ask that put that question down? cos that's important</u>
<u n="327" who="S0261">right so say that again</u>
<u n="328" who="S0262" trans="overlap">how do you use the technology the mobile phone technology</u>
<u n="329" who="S0261">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0262">to learn the language? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0261">yes and that's the bigger picture of erm seeing how the service works and erm er picking out some of those points about how does somebody get from basic to some kind of competent level through this through this process?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0261">over what period of time?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0261">because there are good examples online of people who are trying to train people to learn language in three months</u>
<u n="336" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="337" who="S0261">right? so speed is of the essence</u>
<u n="338" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="339" who="S0261">so if you can provide somebody a good service on the back of you know you can learn off looking at how westerners are doing it for themselves</u>
<u n="340" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="341" who="S0261">between themselves</u>
<u n="342" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="343" who="S0261">so is that a model that you can then approach to a a foreigner who is trying to learn the language as a basic</u>
<u n="344" who="S0262">mm mm</u>
<u n="345" who="S0261">yeah? because the presumably if you can take <trunc>tha</trunc> those cores you can say <unclear>the supplier</unclear> it doesn't matter who it is what level what language we've got this core mechanism which is if you do this you er there must be reinforcement now er I imagine a lot of this is done through visual media high-end delivery through video et cetera</u>
<u n="346" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0261">which won't exist on a cheap <trunc>advi</trunc></u>
<u n="348" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0261">er device but it will exist on the new technologies with the right ICT et cetera four G whatever</u>
<u n="350" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="351" who="S0261">so there could well be er developing countries which are looking to implement that erm as as as a start because instead of investing in infrastructure which is crap stuff that goes under the ground they've jumped that technological gap and they're putting in cell phone <unclear>towers</unclear> straight up</u>
<u n="352" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="353" who="S0261">so their investment goes up like that</u>
<u n="354" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0261">straight away the quality of their investment is huge because they haven't had to spend all this money in the past</u>
<u n="356" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="357" who="S0261">they don't have to keep an old system going</u>
<u n="358" who="S0262" trans="overlap">mm I mean it's in a way it's</u>
<u n="359" who="S0261"><unclear>you know</unclear>? so they can actually jump the jump the gap a lot better</u>
<u n="360" who="S0262" trans="overlap">this is what <trunc>s</trunc> Australia should be doing forget the fucking broadband network</u>
<u n="361" who="S0261">yeah I know</u>
<u n="362" who="S0262">just fucking go mobile technology</u>
<u n="363" who="S0261">yes yeah but erm er well and and I think some people would argue well it's a dead investment erm but</u>
<u n="364" who="S0262" trans="overlap">which one?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0261">the the broadband thing but but</u>
<u n="366" who="S0262">yeah well every Australian you talked to rolled their eyes about it</u>
<u n="367" who="S0261">mm erm er mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know enough about the the future of where it's going but I er I it it is something that is expandable if you have the right core of of wires in the ground you can expand it to in some kind of element of of degree</u>
<u n="368" who="S0262">so what does mobile technology use? satellite?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0261">yeah they use a satellite so it's different and the capacity of it is a bit different too because satellites can only be a certain size in the sky can't do everything and that you know what happens when you get too many people all in one place the network gets overloaded so that's when you go to the wire because it's hardwired that's why it works better because because of a variety of reasons but so they're complementary in a way yeah?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0262">well write that down because then if they're in a complementary relationship a value-added service could be a complementary service to one or to the other</u>
<u n="371" who="S0261">er a value-added service of delivery?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0262" trans="overlap">so if you were <trunc>c</trunc>if you were complementing yeah if you've got two complementary er technologies one is the mobile and the one is the <trunc>n</trunc> er network or whatever</u>
<u n="373" who="S0261"><unclear/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0262">broadband whatever their country has if you are trying to complement that you can <trunc>compl</trunc>complement by adding value so if somebody's struggling with how to use their mobile you could complement that by putting up a website on the internet which tells you how to use the mobile</u>
<u n="375" who="S0261">well well part part of the message is normally nowadays when you deliver content you deliver it in a variety of mechanisms and and formats you know so</u>
<u n="376" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but that's in the western world</u>
<u n="377" who="S0261">mm yeah but what you're saying is is the same thing</u>
<u n="378" who="S0262">I am thinking the I am thinking developing countries</u>
<u n="379" who="S0261">yes we should note that</u>
<u n="380" who="S0262">yeah this is er I'm not thinking at all about you know where we're at I'm thinking</u>
<u n="381" who="S0261" trans="overlap">erm delivery of but there <trunc>i</trunc>there is a point which is delivery of content in developing countries erm because as as as an output as a business output right? you can actually feed a new chain which is you deliver <trunc>someth</trunc> you you create it all at the same time as if you're in a western block you only deliver part of that because the technology is of of a certain level when the technology er</u>
<u n="382" who="S0262">catches up</u>
<u n="383" who="S0261"><unclear>builds</unclear> you can actually go through another cycle</u>
<u n="384" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0261">of reintroducing it and resubmitting it</u>
<u n="386" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0261">for the new market</u>
<u n="388" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="389" who="S0261">the new technological market but you've already done all that work in the in the background which predominantly is just the output through what <trunc>s</trunc>something that you've gotta do at the time</u>
<u n="390" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="391" who="S0261">yeah? erm or that you could choose <trunc>y</trunc>you're just doing it at a certain level you output that and you go back and recreate something using the same content visually described</u>
<u n="392" who="S0262">yeah alright yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0261" trans="overlap">you know what I mean</u>
<u n="394" who="S0262">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0261">then there's the opportunity to go round the round the washing machine again if that's the case</u>
<u n="396" who="S0262" trans="overlap">what? so there's so there's a sustainability factor? that's what you're saying?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0261">for the product</u>
<u n="398" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0261">yeah <trunc>tha</trunc>that can survive</u>
<u n="400" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well you should write that down sustainability</u>
<u n="401" who="S0261">erm <trunc>f</trunc> <trunc>tha</trunc>that has er a an additional longevity er <trunc>long</trunc>longer life through that mechanism mm</u>
<u n="402" who="S0262">yeah it's what you call product life cycle</u>
<u n="403" who="S0261">yes erm <pause dur="short"/> but we're kind of talking about a lot of detail here er I mean I'm</u>
<u n="404" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah I'm trying to look at the bigger picture stuff yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah I I think we should kind of step back and and look at some of the bigger picture and part of</u>
<u n="406" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well some of the things you need to research you need to research you need to research that relationship between Nokia and British Council erm so you could look at Nokia and I could look at British Council erm and then you then you need to find out on both sides who is Nokia's competitors in the same countries that we're talking about let's <unclear/> just choose Vietnam and China</u>
<u n="407" who="S0261">before we before we go there er</u>
<u n="408" who="S0262">I'm just telling you how you find out more information</u>
<u n="409" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah <trunc>tha</trunc>that's that's</u>
<u n="410" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but why would you stop me from that? cos what I'm telling you is really good</u>
<u n="411" who="S0261">no carry on sorry</u>
<u n="412" who="S0262">it's just that it's not the same way you approach things</u>
<u n="413" who="S0261"><trunc>n</trunc> <trunc>n</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc><trunc>s</trunc>sorry er <trunc>j</trunc>just carry on</u>
<u n="414" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0261">yeah carry on</u>
<u n="416" who="S0262">this is the way my business brain works it's that's how I've been trained to think of markets</u>
<u n="417" who="S0261" trans="overlap">that's fine that's fine you don't need to I'm just I've stopped right so carry on</u>
<u n="418" who="S0262" trans="overlap">okay so you'd <trunc>fi</trunc>you'd find out who Nokia's erm you'd find out if there was another type of partnership like Nokia and British Council so you'd find out and then you would just do erm as much sort of SWOT analysis on both of those erm and then you would look for erm you would look at the ways that big companies can't always provide everything to everyone brilliantly that's the question I always say to myself is there's only so much they can do they can't do it all and they can't do it all at a personal level that some people would pay money for <pause dur="short"/> and I'm particularly thinking about these er the richer ones in these countries who can afford to pay for a little bit of value-added service <pause dur="short"/> using the cheap cheap stuff though</u>
<u n="419" who="S0261">so what you're saying is is if you were gonna tap the markets you would try and tap the market of those who are willing to pay for a product?</u>
<u n="420" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="421" who="S0261">and of course then you're <trunc>p</trunc></u>
<u n="422" who="S0262" trans="overlap">or service</u>
<u n="423" who="S0261">or service and therefore you're pitching erm er er more of er a higher quality higher price which obviously delivers more profit rather than I mean you can look at it on two ways you can say we're delivering this product at this level but we have a charity arm which is delivering this at that level which gives you the benefit of</u>
<u n="424" who="S0262">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0261">you're you're not just pandering to the wealthy you're providing something also but it's a similar business stream</u>
<u n="426" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="427" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="428" who="S0262">you you normally make a splash if you go in with the community value to start with and you work away at it and then you start building relationships with the wealthier ones</u>
<u n="429" who="S0261">er yeah but er I'm just making that connection that you know</u>
<u n="430" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well write that down as well because you you might start from the wealthy way I would suggest that you get a name for yourself quickly if you go on the community level into a developing country</u>
<u n="431" who="S0261"><unclear>well <trunc>y</trunc> er then</unclear></u>
<u n="432" who="S0262">cos you make those contacts at the government level <pause dur="short"/> once you go in on a community charity what's it called thing? non-profit organisation then er you start making you know <pause dur="short"/> nGO type relationship type people who are then also very well connected cos they've been in the country forever and then you get to meet the wealthy people <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0261">right erm okay that that sounds that sounds cool so er erm that's got you to that point</u>
<u n="434" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="435" who="S0261">so if we move on from there erm if we now step back</u>
<u n="436" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="437" who="S0261">and we look at the bigger picture</u>
<u n="438" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="439" who="S0261">and we say erm what is it that we could put together that fits something like that?</u>
<u n="440" who="S0262">okay but always remember</u>
<u n="441" who="S0261" trans="overlap">without the detail</u>
<u n="442" who="S0262">we're in no we're in research mode</u>
<u n="443" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="444" who="S0262">so we've got to think of big picture research you've got to cos we're not we're not at the stage yet to offer anything we haven't got anything to offer <unclear/></u>
<u n="445" who="S0261">no my my okay I'll put my my question differently which is erm is it likely that we would fit into a market like this?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0262"><trunc>y</trunc> er well this is what you have to explore</u>
<u n="447" who="S0261">right so all of that's <trunc>unknow</trunc> er really where I'm coming from is is is it erm going to provide us value to research this straight up?</u>
<u n="448" who="S0262">well what you would do to justify your further research and development is you would actually do erm er a you would do a erm</u>
<u n="449" who="S0261">a SWOT analysis</u>
<u n="450" who="S0262">no you would just basically list financial state er <trunc>st</trunc> financial data so you'd go how much is the world market? erm</u>
<u n="451" who="S0261"><unclear/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0262">how much is the you know? how much is? so you'd find out how big your market is and</u>
<u n="453" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="454" who="S0262">how much money is being churned around inside that industry</u>
<u n="455" who="S0261" trans="overlap">and whether it's growth</u>
<u n="456" who="S0262">and I think <vocal desc="laugh"/> you would then</u>
<u n="457" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0262">split it up into segments and go</u>
<u n="459" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="460" who="S0262">if we looked at this one how much money could we make?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="462" who="S0262">because it's already making so much money</u>
<u n="463" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><unclear/> that that that's fine</u>
<u n="464" who="S0262">yeah that's how you'd do it</u>
<u n="465" who="S0261" trans="overlap">yeah and right erm <pause dur="short"/> okay so <trunc>w</trunc>well that is that is potentially something that we would have to do along the way as well</u>
<u n="466" who="S0262">well I'd suggest that I mean I know quite a lot about the market because obviously I've worked in it but if you wanted some erm sort of reassurance that I mean I say the market the industry the the global industry and even developing country industry er would be worth your while to explore erm research and development then you just need to put down billions of dollars and then you'd be looking at it and going <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>you know</unclear> billions of dollar means that somebody's paying for this <unclear>it means</unclear> there's profit that's being made</u>
<u n="467" who="S0261">and where's the money come from?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0262">and who's making money? and how are they making it?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0261">mm mm erm <pause dur="short"/> okay well maybe er what I'm trying to get er a a a context of is that stuff sounds cool what things can <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do while he's away to feed into this kind of thing?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0262">well I would say for your own information you need to know how big the markets are <unclear>and</unclear> how big the industries are you need to get the financial information so that when you go when you go you're going in with right I know how much this this industry is worth <unclear>yeah</unclear> I know the worth of the industry</u>
<u n="471" who="S0261">it's just that very high level information</u>
<u n="472" who="S0262">but it's <trunc>c</trunc> it's macro</u>
<u n="473" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="474" who="S0262">you've got the macro and then when you go in micro you understand the context of the macro you can always place it when you're talking to people within a macro context erm and then you know er when you're on the ground you're doing the micro work erm and then you piece the macro and the micro together and you really then understand the industry</u>
<u n="475" who="S0261">erm <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="long"/> for er you you've kind of erm tacked onto this quite quite erm is this just because it's something that's popped up that's er that's caught your eye? or?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well you can see it's an exercise in your analytical thinking of how you would approach any industry if you're interested in it</u>
<u n="477" who="S0261" trans="overlap">that that that that's right but my <trunc>qu</trunc></u>
<u n="478" who="S0262">so</u>
<u n="479" who="S0261">my question is is that you've picked up on a particular thing out of out of a gazette that that demonstrates something</u>
<u n="480" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well only cos you asked me before you went to the shop can you talk <trunc>l</trunc>let's talk about education</u>
<u n="481" who="S0261">yes and</u>
<u n="482" who="S0262">if you'd asked me to talk about something else I would've done the same thing</u>
<u n="483" who="S0261">mm er <trunc>y</trunc> er which is valuable so erm how does that help us also understand <trunc>w</trunc> so out of that exercise we would understand how it's being done in other countries if it is as well?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0262">well I think you're learning how to break down break down an industry break down into a market apply some kind of analytical thinking in terms of like you know <trunc>h</trunc>how do I research where the opportunities might be? and then once I've got a sniff or a whiff of something how do I go to that local environment that country or that particular city or wherever and find these people and find out whether my hunch is right or not? my hypothesis is actually correct or not</u>
<u n="485" who="S0261" trans="overlap">okay so my I'm still wanna get to the point of do you see value in researching this particular point?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0262">well I'm at the same point as you how can I answer that question unless I've done the actual homework?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0261">are there other different points that are worthwhile considering?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0262">what points?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0261">er I dunno er er erm what I'm interested in is trying to establish a thread of something that that both of us see <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="490" who="S0262" trans="overlap">why don't you just get off your chest what you're trying to say cos you're asking me questions when I think you've already got some of your <trunc>v</trunc> own points of view</u>
<u n="491" who="S0261">no no I don't I don't know erm my point of view is that</u>
<u n="492" who="S0262" trans="overlap">well in order to answer that kind of question you'd already had to start thinking about <trunc>some</trunc> ask that question to me you must be thinking something else</u>
<u n="493" who="S0261">no no no I'm not thinking of anybody <trunc>e</trunc> <trunc>a</trunc>anything else I'm certainly thinking that there's a thread here is there another thread that actually you see value or you have awareness of that is worthwhile researching that you would rather research in context of looking to build some kind of business stream?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0262">so you're asking me is there another area other than English language another English you know is there another industry?</u>
<u n="495" who="S0261">or education related you know</u>
<u n="496" who="S0262">no look I'm in the business of education if anybody asks me to do anything I would never go outside of the the the the the business of education I think what you're asking me is is that are you just looking at the English language education? or are you interested in other aspects of education?</u>
<u n="497" who="S0261">yes exactly</u>
<u n="498" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0261">in context of business if we what we talked about was if if we try and kind of er have a vision of what we we might maybe do we don't know yeah? but erm that's what I'm trying to get some tangibility about you know?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah erm no not no I I'm not business wise no I can't I can't see anything right now that I think is erm er er a viable way of making some money</u>
<u n="501" who="S0261">a er er a right goer</u>
<u n="502" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0261">okay so if er if we if we simply looked at it in context of what we might like to do together</u>
<u n="504" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0261">and we don't know whether there's money in it or not but er <unclear>using</unclear> imagination</u>
<u n="506" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0261">in in relation to the skills that we've got</u>
<u n="508" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0261">yeah? so you've got the business and the education side of things and I've got a tech side and a project management side</u>
<u n="510" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="511" who="S0261">erm and we both have an interest in working together in in that kind of area</u>
<u n="512" who="S0262">and and we don't wanna be a middle man</u>
<u n="513" who="S0261">no</u>
<u n="514" who="S0262">we're not gonna go to British Council and go we'll fucking work really hard for you and you'll take all the fucking credit</u>
<u n="515" who="S0261"><trunc>a</trunc><trunc>a</trunc>absolutely so we wanna</u>
<u n="516" who="S0262" trans="overlap"><unclear>you know</unclear> we we are our own outfit</u>
<u n="517" who="S0261"><trunc>y</trunc>yes</u>
<u n="518" who="S0262">but we've figured out exactly why we're our own outfit and how we remain our own outfit yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0261" trans="overlap">er and and and we want to have our strength</u>
<u n="520" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0261">on the background of the product and services that we're going to provide</u>
<u n="522" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0261">we don't want to be effectively working for somebody else</u>
<u n="524" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="525" who="S0261"><unclear>you know</unclear></u>
<u n="526" who="S0262">no</u>
<u n="527" who="S0261">cos that's what we're trying to get away from</u>
<u n="528" who="S0262"><vocal desc="yawn"/> yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0261">yeah so even as a as a as an <trunc>e</trunc>an expert a consultant in something we we don't want to unless there's wads of cash in it and it's</u>
<u n="530" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0261">the the market you but you can't do that from the start anyway you need to be</u>
<u n="532" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah it's it's you er yeah</u>
<u n="533" who="S0261">you need to've started something</u>
<u n="534" who="S0262">it's easier to just take it like erm you know you take your vegetables to the marketplace and you sell them on that day</u>
<u n="535" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="536" who="S0262">if you start on that concept</u>
<u n="537" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="538" who="S0262">you find your consumer</u>
<u n="539" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="540" who="S0262"><trunc>y</trunc> they pay you ten quid for something</u>
<u n="541" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="542" who="S0262">you get money through the door</u>
<u n="543" who="S0261">absolutely</u>
<u n="544" who="S0262">and you know you don't have to worry about big company clients</u>
<u n="545" who="S0261">no</u>
<u n="546" who="S0262">and all that fucking shit</u>
<u n="547" who="S0261" trans="overlap">none of none of that stuff</u>
<u n="548" who="S0262">you just phone the consumers</u>
<u n="549" who="S0261" trans="overlap">no bureaucracy</u>
<u n="550" who="S0262">and you sell them something</u>
<u n="551" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="552" who="S0262">you get money through the door and then once you really understand what their needset are</u>
<u n="553" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="554" who="S0262">you can perhaps work your way through into other areas</u>
<u n="555" who="S0261" trans="overlap">er er er er yes that's right</u>
<u n="556" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that's what I would do</u>
<u n="557" who="S0261">and and part of it is is ensuring that you've got a a stable cash flow on the background of an a simple product to start with</u>
<u n="558" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah but the credentials I have for the English language area</u>
<u n="559" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0262">is enough even if I wanted to rub shoulders with the British Council people erm you know</u>
<u n="561" who="S0261">to to roll on in</u>
<u n="562" who="S0262">I can chat away to them and find out information</u>
<u n="563" who="S0261">yes okay so there is</u>
<u n="564" who="S0262" trans="overlap">if they you know had had a few drinks on board and were talking about what they were doing</u>
<u n="565" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="566" who="S0262">erm or you know it it was sort of like erm just sort of rubbing shoulders in the right Ho Chi Minh city</u>
<u n="567" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="568" who="S0262">just an expat thing</u>
<u n="569" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="570" who="S0262"><unclear>and</unclear> British Council and some other people turning up</u>
<u n="571" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="572" who="S0262">and I would go chat chat chat chat chat and you'd go chat chat chat chat chat</u>
<u n="573" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="574" who="S0262">and I'd be chatty teacher person you'd be chatty sort of whatever tech kind of project manager person</u>
<u n="575" who="S0261" trans="overlap">tech guy yeah but I'm interested in delivering services through tech to people</u>
<u n="576" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0261">so that's the other arm of it mm</u>
<u n="578" who="S0262">well and actually I think if you always say you're a project manager</u>
<u n="579" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="580" who="S0262">it always makes sense</u>
<u n="581" who="S0261">yes of course</u>
<u n="582" who="S0262">cos you just say I manage projects</u>
<u n="583" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="584" who="S0262">and if they think oh fuck I've got this project that needs managing</u>
<u n="585" who="S0261">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="586" who="S0262"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what sort of thing can you do? <unclear>will you come and be project manager</unclear>?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0261">right</u>
<u n="588" who="S0262">I've got Prince whatever</u>
<u n="589" who="S0261">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="590" who="S0262"><unclear>that's it</unclear></u>
<u n="591" who="S0261">yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0262">credibility is already straight away there</u>
<u n="593" who="S0261">yeah of course</u>
<u n="594" who="S0262">you don't need to <trunc>c</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> tell em anything else</u>
<u n="595" who="S0261">no</u>
<u n="596" who="S0262">don't even <trunc>t</trunc>tell em you're an engineer</u>
<u n="597" who="S0261">absolutely</u>
<u n="598" who="S0262">not interested</u>
<u n="599" who="S0261">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="600" who="S0262">just wanna know you know have you got those skills to transfer into any project?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0261">yes absolutely of course</u>
<u n="602" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="603" who="S0261">so erm</u>
<u n="604" who="S0262">so you're not a technical person you're you're a manager of technical people</u>
<u n="605" who="S0261">yes that's right</u>
<u n="606" who="S0262">and if we had a company you would be managing those technical people</u>
<u n="607" who="S0261" trans="overlap"><trunc>tha</trunc>that's a very good point</u>
<u n="608" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="609" who="S0261">that's a very good point that you make erm <pause dur="long"/> so if we carry on with what skills we've got and er <trunc>w</trunc> and we talk about what uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was talking about</u>
<u n="610" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I've just sorry sorry</u>
<u n="611" who="S0261"><unclear/></u>
<u n="612" who="S0262">I've just thought about this <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc> the the way you and I would manage projects would be so entirely different</u>
<u n="613" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="614" who="S0262">so that is er that is in terms of <trunc>s</trunc> er uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> there would be a massive problem there okay? cos er I it makes complete sense that you're the project manager but remember I've also had <trunc>mana</trunc> project manager experience through filmmaking et cetera et cetera</u>
<u n="615" who="S0261" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="616" who="S0262">so</u>
<u n="617" who="S0261">yeah but that's about sharing the knowledge and trying to find a common path together</u>
<u n="618" who="S0262">it <trunc>c</trunc></u>
<u n="619" who="S0261">that that that does say well <trunc>y</trunc> when you're dealing with this type of project this is how it's delivered and as a project manager I learn er elements of how that project is put together so the the the core system of managing a project is is the same then you get people who specialise in certain types of projects which carry information that you don't understand or have awareness of to start with</u>
<u n="620" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="621" who="S0261"><unclear>you know</unclear>?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0262">if you wanted to <trunc>buil</trunc> <trunc>b</trunc> er build an oil rig</u>
<u n="623" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="624" who="S0262">build an oil rig</u>
<u n="625" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="626" who="S0262">who's at the top of the chain? apart from the CEO who makes er you know whatever the company I'm not <trunc>sa</trunc> I'm I'm saying people on the oil rig or around the sea where they're trying to actually fucking get this thing in the ground who's there?</u>
<u n="627" who="S0261">well you'd er <trunc>ha</trunc> you'd er you</u>
<u n="628" who="S0262">who's there? who's the top top <trunc>ho</trunc>honcho?</u>
<u n="629" who="S0261">you well you would er have a very large engineering company</u>
<u n="630" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="631" who="S0261">who who's probably a consultant that has been hired by the company BP whoever</u>
<u n="632" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0261">to build such a thing like er <unclear>the case and the mixing</unclear> was Halliburton <unclear>you know</unclear>?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0261">erm er and er you're talking about massive contracts so the people at the top would be the CEO of the consultant company the CEO of the the er oil company if that's what you mean</u>
<u n="636" who="S0262"><unclear/> one down from that</u>
<u n="637" who="S0261" trans="overlap">in terms of the operation on the ground</u>
<u n="638" who="S0262">yeah the operations managers</u>
<u n="639" who="S0261">you you you would have erm you would have a strategic board which would run the project specific for the</u>
<u n="640" who="S0262" trans="overlap">can you write can you can you make a diagram of this?</u>
<u n="641" who="S0261">right okay so right up the top you would have the project board yeah? and that project board would be made up of representatives from erm er various companies companies and the client yeah? so that could be the er you could have a delivery through a variety of</u>
<u n="642" who="S0262" trans="overlap">just keep <trunc>dr</trunc>drawing and I'll go to the toilet</u>
<u n="643" who="S0261">yeah okay</u>
<u n="644" who="S0262">and then you can explain it to me when you get back</u>
<u n="645" who="S0261">yeah okay</u>
<u n="646" who="S0262"><unclear/></u>
<u n="647" who="S0261">that sounds cool I'll just pause this for a moment</u>
<event desc="recording skips"/>
<u n="648" who="S0262">where you were wanting to be when you left your engineering career cos you've always wanted to be a project manager and you were a project manager as well in some jobs so that's interesting isn't it? but what would <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> say er the what would <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> say about that?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0261">well you see I don't think that what we see here is relevant to to our situation</u>
<u n="650" who="S0262">okay so how no not not our now let's start talking about you</u>
<u n="651" who="S0261">yes okay me</u>
<u n="652" who="S0262">right so what so what are you doing now?</u>
<u n="653" who="S0261">okay so erm so in what's in my head</u>
<u n="654" who="S0262">mm</u>
<u n="655" who="S0261">the way er if we consider that we've got time here yeah? and <pause dur="short"/> that what we wanna try and do is over that time try and connect a few dots together so if we consider what we were talking about the other day it was the idea that you and I work together on some collaborative stream to be able to work together in business to be er you know to to deliver whatever products <trunc>w</trunc>whatever value to whoever yeah? so if we say that on this timeline that is over here where we connect yeah? so this is the period leading up to that where this is this is full time yeah? and so to start with where we're at over here is me in this one and you in that one right? and we have got to both come together and converge at this point over time so here at the moment you're at <anon type="place"/> and then we might consider that over time you're at <anon type="place"/> plus we'll call it B for business yeah?</u>
<u n="656" who="S0262">or E for more education <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="657" who="S0261">plus E</u>
<u n="658" who="S0262"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="659" who="S0261"><unclear>you know</unclear>? B plus E yeah?</u>
<u n="660" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="661" who="S0261">well you're at the moment you're <anon type="place"/> plus E</u>
<u n="662" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="663" who="S0261">yeah? okay? so you're er you're doing both of those</u>
<u n="664" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but I'm also plus B too cos we're already starting about er talking about business</u>
<u n="665" who="S0261">er <trunc>y</trunc> mm mm <trunc>y</trunc>yeah that's but just hear me out <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="666" who="S0262">okay</u>
<u n="667" who="S0261">you know? so where I'm at at the moment is that I'm actually in a subset of of this B</u>
<u n="668" who="S0262">right</u>
<u n="669" who="S0261">so what I'm looking at trying to do if I call that D B yeah? alright? what I'm trying to do is that that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s business at the moment which we want to try and align in such a way that we get the most out of this that feeds into that into the business</u>
<u n="670" who="S0262">that means we need to know what B is</u>
<u n="671" who="S0261">there is part of that</u>
<u n="672" who="S0262">yeah</u>
<u n="673" who="S0261">but if from my point of view if I can step back and go ethereally there are certain things that we wanna operate and know how to operate here that I can be learning now that that that already feeds into that straight up so part of that is the business operation side of things</u>
<u n="674" who="S0262">jeez that's reverse engineering <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="675" who="S0261">well I'm in advance of it</u>
<u n="676" who="S0262" trans="overlap">not not <unclear>other <trunc>peo</trunc> they're not you're</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="677" who="S0261">I'm in advance of it I need to operate a business now</u>
<u n="678" who="S0262">yeah I know but not many business people go about trying to approach building a business with with <unclear>our er</unclear> sort of retrospective way of looking at it</u>
<u n="679" who="S0261">well I'm not retrospectively looking at it I'm here now leading up to it</u>
<u n="680" who="S0262" trans="overlap">yeah but you've <trunc>p</trunc>you've picked a point in the future</u>
<u n="681" who="S0261">I'm in advance I'm in advance</u>
<u n="682" who="S0262">no er no <unclear/></u>
<u n="683" who="S0261">I'm I'm leading up to it</u>
<u n="684" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no okay alright</u>
<u n="685" who="S0261">I I'm already if we've got that I'm already in B here this just happens to be my B not our B</u>
<u n="686" who="S0262">we're here now yeah?</u>
<u n="687" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="688" who="S0262">this is the future</u>
<u n="689" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="690" who="S0262">yeah? this is the future's future</u>
<u n="691" who="S0261">yes</u>
<u n="692" who="S0262">okay and that's like B D B yeah?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0261">mm</u>
<u n="694" who="S0262">so in order to see the future's future you'd need to know what the future is and then from the future you'd need to know where you're at now</u>
<u n="695" who="S0261">yes that's right so I know where I'm at now</u>
<u n="696" who="S0262" trans="overlap">but we haven't got a crystal ball though</u>
<u n="697" who="S0261"><trunc>n</trunc>no no no <vocal desc="laugh"/> you I understand what you're saying but I'm trying to take it <pause dur="short"/> we don't know what that is right? that's</u>
<u n="698" who="S0262" trans="overlap">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> so how can you decide what to do now to feed into that if we don't know what that is?</u>
<u n="699" who="S0261">no no no <unclear/> but er think</u>
<u n="700" who="S0262" trans="overlap">that's what you said</u>
<u n="701" who="S0261">right okay so if we think about the things that we want how we want to deliver this stuff it's in a digital format it's online all of those kind of things that's what I'm saying that there's</u>
<u n="702" who="S0262" trans="overlap">oh but is it? we haven't done our research yet we don't even know what B is we're just talking about ideas at the moment they're not even concrete</u>
<u n="703" who="S0261">er that that's right but <trunc>i</trunc>if we put two and two together what we <trunc>kno</trunc></u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
