<text id="SPXX">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:38</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A pub, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>The North East, work, fashion, bands</topics>
		<activity>ANON and ANON talking in the pub</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0115">so you said you and that guy anyway?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0037">na <pause dur="short"/> so I was at the bar <pause dur="short"/> I was at the bar and there was women who were like quite merry um <pause dur="short"/> one of them was like they were like I dunno like tickling each other or were doing something weird <pause dur="short"/> and one of them like sort of bashed into us</u>
<u n="3" who="S0115">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0037">and she went oh <trunc>s</trunc> sorry sorry and I went oh don't worry about it it's fine <pause dur="short"/> and she went ee are you from Newcastle? And I thought oh here we go and I said ah Sunderland and she was like ee I'm from Boldon and I was like ah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that's that's half and half though isn't it?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0037" trans="overlap">can you believe <trunc>i</trunc> yeah I know and she was like  she was like  ee how you doing? and her friends were like thing is though you've just like put that on <pause dur="short"/> they were like you don't talk like that Mary or whatever <pause dur="short"/> and she was like shut your mouth you <pause dur="short"/> like she'd gone like she'd gone totally into like Sunderland mode like Northeast mode and she was like ee how you doin pet? as if we like lifelong friends <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like yeah yeah fine</u>
<u n="7" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="8" who="S0037">and she was like ee good on you for keeping your accent <pause dur="short"/> I've lost mine a bit <pause dur="short"/> and I was like have you? Cos you actually sound like your accent's stronger than mine <pause dur="short"/> and her friends were like she doesn't talk like that  she doesn't talk like that  she's just putting it on</u>
<u n="9" who="S0115">where <trunc>w</trunc> well where was she was from then?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0037">from Boldon</u>
<u n="11" who="S0115">no no no I mean like what's she doing here?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0037">and then she said ee what what you doing here then? Like like she I could tell I I'd listened to her a little bit before like her speech totally changed like before she knew I was from there</u>
<u n="13" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0037">she was like oh sorry sorry I bumped into you there and then I was like ah don't worry about it <pause dur="short"/> and she's like ee hello <pause dur="short"/> um and then she said um she was from Boldon and then she said what brings you down here? And I said ah I work down here <pause dur="short"/> and then she said something like it's not the same is it? and I said ah it's no it's a lot more expensive and I said Ah <pause dur="short"/> three pound odd that was and it's one pound eighty at home it's horrible isn't it? And she said and anyway we were just chatting and her friends were like all of her friends were just like taking the piss out of her <vocal desc="laugh"/> like oh are you <anon type="place"/> now are you? Are you Mary <vocal desc="laugh"/> like she'd obviously</u>
<u n="15" who="S0115">well so <trunc>w</trunc> where um what was she doing here then?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0037">her husband lived here or something aye she moved down here ten years ago or twenty years ago</u>
<u n="17" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="18" who="S0037">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> she's got her birthday party group over there she's like <pause dur="short"/> her eyes were all pointing in different directions and that</u>
<u n="19" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0037">her friends were just <trunc>lit</trunc> like absolutely like taking the Mickey out of her</u>
<u n="21" who="S0115">well</u>
<u n="22" who="S0037">and she's like tara pet and I was like yeah I wouldn't even say that but bye <vocal desc="laugh"/> Then I said to the barman he was like does that happen very often? And I said d'you know what like whenever I meet someone from the Northeast it's like we're like blood brothers instantly <pause dur="short"/> I said people always say  people always say  when they hear it ah <trunc>y</trunc> I'm from are you from <anon type="place"/> are you from the Northeast Newcastle? And if you are and they are that's it <pause dur="short"/> they're like besties</u>
<u n="23" who="S0115">well <pause dur="short"/> actually we we we met some in uh Eccleshall</u>
<u n="24" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and I said</u>
<u n="25" who="S0115">uh more than uh more than once in fact twice uh we met um</u>
<u n="26" who="S0037">ah they get all over man</u>
<u n="27" who="S0115">we met sort of like the pub was owned by some some</u>
<u n="28" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well in here <pause dur="short"/> d'you remember when we were in here and there was that party on? They were from <anon type="place"/> definitely or or somewhere near</u>
<u n="29" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh oh round the back <pause dur="short"/> uh it feels like a different place when uh when you're out the back</u>
<u n="30" who="S0037" trans="overlap">outside yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0115">I wonder what it's like now <pause dur="short"/> if you look</u>
<u n="32" who="S0037">uh the lights are on <pause dur="short"/> it's twinkly isn't it?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0115">it must be really really good out there like</u>
<u n="34" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's probably cold <pause dur="short"/> it's probably cold though</u>
<u n="35" who="S0115" trans="overlap">kind of feel like I'd like to go there but</u>
<u n="36" who="S0037">unless they've got them like burners on</u>
<u n="37" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0037">um but uh</u>
<u n="39" who="S0115">stocks are up</u>
<u n="40" who="S0037">ay?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0115">market</u>
<u n="42" who="S0037">oh that's good</u>
<u n="43" who="S0115">uh everything's up</u>
<u n="44" who="S0037">oh my god so so you know at work you know <trunc>m</trunc> when I went to Brno</u>
<u n="45" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0037">so you know I have to fill in expenses?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0037">so I pay for things on me work Barclaycard and then I have to <pause dur="short"/> so you have like oh it says oh <pause dur="short"/> me Barclaycard statement like any bank statement it says on this day you paid this person this amount <pause dur="short"/> so it's like ah your train fare this amount <pause dur="short"/> ah you bought a sandwich at the train station this amount <pause dur="short"/> ah you went to Tescos this amount like all your things are there so you have to account for all of those <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="49" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0037">but when I went to Brno like um <pause dur="short"/> it's like you buy you know like tram tickets?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="52" who="S0037">and um they're just pennies aren't they like just <pause dur="short"/> you know like odd coppers and um <pause dur="short"/> so obviously you can't be like paying with your Barclaycard <pause dur="short"/> you can't be like oh seven pence here's my Barclaycard like</u>
<u n="53" who="S0115">uh I don't know <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean you could try that</u>
<u n="54" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but you there's just <pause dur="short"/> well you know what it's like like in Paris or in in like in Lodz or in like um Berlin <pause dur="short"/> can't like exactly buy or in fact here on the bus <pause dur="short"/> you couldn't get on the bus and just like whack out your Barclaycard <pause dur="short"/> if you got the Number A from there you couldn't like crack the Barclaycard out like</u>
<u n="55" who="S0115">ah not but um is that the thing like <trunc>i</trunc> we <trunc>ta</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> we were telling about Japan you know the thing I was telling you about Japan that you could if you could do a whole journey across Japan like just with a like a an electronic type thing?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0115" trans="overlap">ah swiping thing yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> well they're bringing that in here aren't they? That's the  that's the  Barclaycard advert where he's down like a water chute in New York?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0037">anyway so what happened was so I paid for things out of my own cash <pause dur="short"/> cos I had some of my own money <pause dur="short"/> um and that was in Czech Crowns so I paid for stuff like just like <trunc>li</trunc> small things like tram tickets and like really like little like bits of change things <pause dur="short"/> but then um I was like oh I should claim those back really I mean it's not very much but like they add up you know like to a couple of pound or about ten quid or something <pause dur="short"/> and I wasn't really that bothered but I thought no no no it's <pause dur="short"/> I was there on a work trip I should  I should  claim them</u>
<u n="59" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0037">what you have to do is you have to um account for the days that you were there <pause dur="short"/> then you have to go on Financial Times Dot-com <pause dur="short"/> you have to put in those dates <pause dur="short"/> you have to find the average currency conversion rate over those dates <pause dur="short"/> you have to find out how much you paid in total so like mine was like like ten Crowns or something</u>
<u n="61" who="S0115" trans="overlap">should've should uh put it into an Excel spreadsheet</u>
<u n="62" who="S0037">yeah but it changes <pause dur="short"/> that's the point like you've gotta it'll it'll never be the same <pause dur="short"/> you've gotta then print off the thing from the Financial Times <pause dur="short"/> circle the calculation that you've used i <pause dur="short"/>e <pause dur="short"/> one pound equals</u>
<u n="63" who="S0115" trans="overlap">maybe there's  maybe there's  an app for that</u>
<u n="64" who="S0037">oh god it was so long-winded like</u>
<u n="65" who="S0115">well how many days were you there all then?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0037">well just a few days <pause dur="short"/> so it wasn't</u>
<u n="67" who="S0115">so you only had like well like five four or five um</u>
<u n="68" who="S0037">it was just a like a few days</u>
<u n="69" who="S0115"><trunc>Individ</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> but you had to find it so so then d'you store that in in in FT is it easy to uh to go back?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0037">well you go to Europe and then like um the good thing about Europe is so you put the days in and it shows you like the main graph it's like the Euro against what <trunc>u</trunc> you know the Pound or whatever</u>
<u n="71" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the Czech Koruna</u>
<u n="72" who="S0037">but then underneath they have all of the like <pause dur="short"/> cos you select like your main currency so you select Pound <pause dur="short"/> then underneath they have all of the currencies of Europe which in fact aren't very many obviously cos like the Euro</u>
<u n="73" who="S0115">no it's you know there's a few</u>
<u n="74" who="S0037">there's the Swiss Franc <pause dur="short"/> there's the Czech Koruna <pause dur="short"/> there's um <pause dur="short"/> I think Croatia has a different one</u>
<u n="75" who="S0115">oh yeah I'm sure that all of those uh all uh all the Yugoslavian ones</u>
<u n="76" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no not all of them like <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>esto</trunc></u>
<u n="77" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah no no Yugoslavia's not part of the Eurozone</u>
<u n="78" who="S0037">Estonia has a different one <pause dur="short"/> so there's like a few</u>
<u n="79" who="S0115">yeah Yugoslavia's got the Kroni or whatever uh</u>
<u n="80" who="S0037">kroni?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0115">kroni <trunc>i</trunc></u>
<u n="82" who="S0037">so all of those are listed so then you have to like find them all and <pause dur="short"/> then you have to do all the stupid calculations like it's such a long-winded process I thought God <pause dur="short"/> for ten quid <pause dur="short"/> but I don't know <pause dur="short"/> I suppose it's worth doing</u>
<u n="83" who="S0115">well um</u>
<u n="84" who="S0037">no but ten quid's ten quid isn't it?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0115">yeah it's a good story the on the one <trunc>bu</trunc> one it's uh you know round Easter it's always good to have uh an uh miracle at Easter</u>
<u n="86" who="S0037">well I don't know if it is a miracle lots of people have problems and recover like</u>
<u n="87" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but if it happens at Easter then it's uh more miraculous</u>
<u n="88" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well like our plant I mean that's that's more</u>
<u n="89" who="S0115">yeah oh you mean Jesus?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0037">Jesus the aloe plant</u>
<u n="91" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="92" who="S0037">yeah I mean</u>
<u n="93" who="S0115">yeah well</u>
<u n="94" who="S0037">I suppose Easter's just for me I I being not very religious I just see it as a time for like having a few days off work it's gonna be so nice next week</u>
<u n="95" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="96" who="S0037">next week I only have to work for four days that's gonna be so good</u>
<u n="97" who="S0115">oh yeah nice to get a that that that extra weekend</u>
<u n="98" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I've had such a long stretch like I've had <pause dur="short"/> okay I went to Brno but that was work really it wasn't like loads of like holiday and relaxation</u>
<u n="99" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0037">I haven't had any time off since Lucy's wedding and at the start of January so be so nice to have that <pause dur="short"/> well I didn't wanna use my holiday unnecessarily</u>
<u n="101" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0037">so <pause dur="short"/> I haven't had any time off until <trunc>n</trunc> until then so it's gonna be really nice</u>
<u n="103" who="S0115">yeah yeah um</u>
<u n="104" who="S0037">looking forward to it</u>
<u n="105" who="S0115" trans="overlap">sure it would uh Easter um</u>
<u n="106" who="S0037">we'll have an eggy time</u>
<u n="107" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>We</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> is it the next one then?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0037">next weekend yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0115">mm like uh</u>
<u n="110" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so I'm off Friday and on Monday as well so that's nice</u>
<u n="111" who="S0115">yeah yeah uh that'll be hopefully be able to do something nice</u>
<u n="112" who="S0037">yeah well I've bought a nice bit of uh gammon joint of</u>
<u n="113" who="S0115">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0037">gammon ham actually you know ham</u>
<u n="115" who="S0115">get a barbecue take it down the  take it down the  park</u>
<u n="116" who="S0037">put it on the barbecue? A <trunc>j</trunc> massive joint?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh like <trunc>tan</trunc> like a oven <pause dur="short"/> you you'd have to sort of</u>
<u n="118" who="S0037" trans="overlap">build a tandoor in the uh on Jesus Green?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0115" trans="overlap">build an an oven <pause dur="short"/> like a <pause dur="short"/> yeah you'd basically get a fire started uh</u>
<u n="120" who="S0037">yeah?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0115">start up a bonfire</u>
<u n="122" who="S0037">right</u>
<u n="123" who="S0115">uh put the put it in the middle of the bonfire</u>
<u n="124" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah I think there might be some rules about that</u>
<u n="125" who="S0115">yeah <trunc>y</trunc> you've got them them them granite you know stone things?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0037">oh that's right yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0115">you you start a bonfire on top of one of them</u>
<u n="128" who="S0037">put your like a</u>
<u n="129" who="S0115">put your your your hock inside it</u>
<u n="130" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><trunc>Ha</trunc> ham hock yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0115">uh and then you know in in a like a cover of some kind <pause dur="short"/> You know like a foil</u>
<u n="132" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0115">put it in there</u>
<u n="134" who="S0037">some interesting ideas</u>
<u n="135" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and uh it'll it'll have a really smoky flavour</u>
<u n="136" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <trunc>a</trunc> so yeah <pause dur="short"/> and</u>
<u n="138" who="S0037">or</u>
<u n="139" who="S0115">but yeah we could also you know um</u>
<u n="140" who="S0037">could just slow cook it and it'll be</u>
<u n="141" who="S0115" trans="overlap">go on a  go on a  somewhere you know like</u>
<u n="142" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="144" who="S0037">not sure where</u>
<u n="145" who="S0115">and and we're supposed to get a tent what we could do is get a tent and then uh</u>
<u n="146" who="S0037">temporary tent?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and set set it up like next to  next to  the ham hock like in the park</u>
<u n="148" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Okay <pause dur="short"/> plan's coming together</u>
<u n="149" who="S0115">you know if you've got a tent that's good <pause dur="short"/> but if you've got a tent and ham then that's even better</u>
<u n="150" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah we should do that I looked at so many <pause dur="short"/> I looked at so many different ones like we really should decide on one</u>
<u n="151" who="S0115"><trunc>I</trunc> what?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0037">we really should decide <pause dur="short"/> we really should decide on one like I looked at so many tents <pause dur="short"/> it's one of those things like like me dad when me dad when me dad was looking for a <trunc>s</trunc> me dad was looking for a new phone <pause dur="short"/> what are they doing?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0115">um drugs</u>
<u n="154" who="S0037">drunk?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0115">uh they're just hanging out <pause dur="short"/> just uh <trunc>s</trunc> playing around</u>
<u n="156" who="S0037">ah it's annoying isn't it?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0115">some wrestling</u>
<u n="158" who="S0037">it's not what you want</u>
<u n="159" who="S0115">uh blokey stuff</u>
<u n="160" who="S0037">I hate blokey stuff</u>
<u n="161" who="S0115">sorry what were you saying?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0037">really gets on my nerves</u>
<u n="163" who="S0115">what? Blokes</u>
<u n="164" who="S0037">blokes yeah <pause dur="short"/> like this sort of bloke <pause dur="short"/> has he got a Burberry hat on</u>
<u n="165" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh they'll they'll they'll have they'll die out eventually yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0037">has he got a Burberry cap on?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0115">no it's it's just  it's just  green</u>
<u n="168" who="S0037">I hate caps</u>
<u n="169" who="S0115">you mean baseball caps?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0115">not not like flat ones? D'you like flat caps?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0037">I like a flat cap on a on an old gent <pause dur="short"/> not not yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0115" trans="overlap">unless it's  unless it's  a Burberry flat cap <pause dur="short"/> do they have Burberry flat caps?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0037">ah he's pretending to do something very rude to that man over there <pause dur="short"/> it's not necessary</u>
<u n="175" who="S0115">he's just in a happy mood uh</u>
<u n="176" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="177" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="178" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he's come into like the pub with all of his tools on his tool belt as if that's some like masculinity display</u>
<u n="179" who="S0115">either that or uh like a porn film</u>
<u n="180" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0115">whoa he's just <trunc>cu</trunc></u>
<u n="182" who="S0037">you've obviously I wouldn't know so</u>
<u n="183" who="S0115">yeah well no but no uh uh</u>
<u n="184" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> A stereotype</u>
<u n="185" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the cable you know just come to fix the cable</u>
<u n="186" who="S0037">ah it's bad <pause dur="short"/> no what I was saying about me dad is like the problem with like trying to choose anything like me dad was looking for a phone you know like a like I suppose like a smartphone or something</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115">is that that's the first line? I'm looking for phone</u>
<u n="188" who="S0037">no that's not the first line</u>
<u n="189" who="S0115">no phones in here just just me the shower</u>
<u n="190" who="S0037">alright this is taking an unusual turn</u>
<u n="191" who="S0115">sorry about that</u>
<u n="192" who="S0037">um but he spent so long looking that and his research was so extensive that actually by the time he'd got anywhere new things are on the market you know? His research was so he took so long comparing all of the various possibilities that actually it was like one of those never-ending cycles like</u>
<u n="193" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0037">if you compared everything in that much detail like you would never get to the end cos there would always be something new</u>
<u n="195" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="196" who="S0037">in the end he did he he did buy one yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but he did  he did  get one in the end didn't he?</u>
<u n="198" who="S0037">but I don't think he was very happy with it <pause dur="short"/> and I think he'd got something that was more like businessy <pause dur="short"/> I think he was persuaded by things like battery life like old man old folk considerations <pause dur="short"/> he was horrified when I told him that I I charge my smartphone like every day or something <pause dur="short"/> horrified</u>
<u n="199" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh was that one of his that was one of his factors?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but like that's the stupid thing though he's an  he's an  electrician <pause dur="short"/> he knows  he knows  the power you know he knows the wattage of a phone he knows the price per watt kilowatt hour even <pause dur="short"/> he knows <pause dur="short"/> he could easily work out how much it would cost to charge a phone for thirty minutes every day <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure it's not very much <pause dur="short"/> I'm positive</u>
<u n="201" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> the problem like</u>
<u n="202" who="S0037">just like</u>
<u n="203" who="S0115">I think I mean I <trunc>do</trunc> I don't think it's that bad to to to charge yours every day because um because well</u>
<u n="204" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like you don't charge it for like ten hours do you?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0115" trans="overlap">just sort of like because you have to charge yourself once a day <pause dur="short"/> you can simply charge it when you're charging yourself</u>
<u n="206" who="S0037">you do have to charge yourself</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115">yeah so when you go to bed <pause dur="short"/> I mean simply plug it in um</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0115">and um leave it on overnight <pause dur="short"/> and so that's not a problem that uh <pause dur="short"/> I mean obviously it would be better if it  if it  lasted for <trunc>t</trunc> two or three days but but I would it it</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well that's one thing actually the Blackberry that I took to Brno it did last a really long time</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah the <pause dur="short"/> I mean the problem is that is you don't wanna have to use your thumbs all the time do you?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0037">no I don't like the</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115">that that thing on the smartphone's really good you know the the Swype thing which is uh</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037" trans="overlap">swype <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115">really it allows you to to use a very little amount of energy for uh to to get through</u>
<u n="216" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's a good invention</u>
<u n="217" who="S0115">so I think it would allow like potentially really fast typing uh that's what I was saying before</u>
<u n="218" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think there's loads of stuff I don't even know like <pause dur="short"/> You know there's like a little tutorial when you first use it? And um there's loads of stuff that I don't even</u>
<u n="219" who="S0115">well some of the things that are a bit annoying is is like apostrophes and stuff like if you're saying it's a good day today or something</u>
<u n="220" who="S0037">I think it does that though and and I think it does  it does  learn like it does um</u>
<u n="221" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah well it certainly learns vocabulary yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0037">Cos like some of the stupid things that I say like owt and nowt and like how man and like little <trunc>s</trunc> like you know it does learn them</u>
<u n="223" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="224" who="S0037">yeah it does do it's <pause dur="short"/> look</u>
<u n="225" who="S0115">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> I I um <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think it's it it like you could type almost as fast as uh as you know as uh as a manual typer</u>
<u n="226" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I sometimes get paranoid like in the office because like I'm quite a heavy typer like <pause dur="short"/> I'm quite a loud sort of typer</u>
<u n="227" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0037">and sometimes if I've like got an email in me mind that I want to send <pause dur="short"/> like I don't really I don't need to look at the keys I've done that much typing <pause dur="short"/> me thesis and everything <pause dur="short"/> and um I feel like sometimes I'm just like going <event desc="sound of keyboard typing"/> shh like <pause dur="short"/> cos I bash the keyboard so hard</u>
<u n="229" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0037">I'm sure it can't be very good</u>
<u n="231" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0037">I should get a better technique</u>
<u n="233" who="S0115">well I guess you've learned that technique you know somehow so</u>
<u n="234" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but I feel like our office is so quiet sometimes I feel like I'm being really loud like <event desc="sound of keyboard typing"/> like on the keyboard</u>
<u n="235" who="S0115">but I know that the way you type like you you don't put your fingers in the right  in the right  place so uh</u>
<u n="236" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but I think it's one of those things that once you've learned  once you've learned  it like</u>
<u n="237" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah well it that's what I was saying before but</u>
<u n="238" who="S0037" trans="overlap">actually I it's because I've got like um</u>
<u n="239" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="240" who="S0037">I type with actually with more of one hand than the other <pause dur="short"/> I'll type more like that d'you know what I mean like? My left hand does like a <trunc>s</trunc> some small ones but my right hand is more rangy <pause dur="short"/> and I think that's because</u>
<u n="241" who="S0115">yeah I actually have I do too much with my left hand and</u>
<u n="242" who="S0037">so you do a lot of like control and stuff like?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0115" trans="overlap">control in with the left</u>
<u n="244" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0115">whereas I should share uh share the control like</u>
<u n="246" who="S0037">well I didn't even know for ages that there was like even like control and shift on the other side like I didn't even</u>
<u n="247" who="S0115">sorry?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0037">I didn't even know for a very long</u>
<u n="249" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you didn't know where well I didn't even know there was a control on the  on the  right side so</u>
<u n="250" who="S0037">ah well</u>
<u n="251" who="S0115">I only <trunc>u</trunc> use the left one</u>
<u n="252" who="S0037">well that's what I'm saying <pause dur="short"/> I know that one I don't know that I didn't know there was one there</u>
<u n="253" who="S0115">no no I thought you  I thought you  used uh oh right</u>
<u n="254" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="255" who="S0115">when I do shift I always use the right one I think like</u>
<u n="256" who="S0037">do you?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0115">often always use that</u>
<u n="258" who="S0037">oh I don't</u>
<u n="259" who="S0115">whereas when I use control I always use the left</u>
<u n="260" who="S0037">I try and use more keyboard strokes like there's some I really like some of the alt ones I really remember <pause dur="short"/> like ones that I use a lot like in certain bookmarks and creating you know like when you're hyperlinking another document like <pause dur="short"/> alt I I K and alt I I I</u>
<u n="261" who="S0115">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0037">they're like create create bookmark and insert bookmark</u>
<u n="263" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh those are really useful yeah <pause dur="short"/> well I think you know <trunc>wi</trunc> with um uh IT you know there there's so many useful things you could do with uh with macros to to automate</u>
<u n="264" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="265" who="S0115">uh but but like it's not <trunc>someth</trunc> I think I need to know a lot more macros</u>
<u n="266" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0115">but uh you know to do a lot more stuff but I mean I recently worked out how to do like to do a macro that went through like a a whole folder of files um in you know through Word <pause dur="short"/> I I could do that with with Python</u>
<u n="268" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you did what?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0115">could do that with Python before <pause dur="short"/> like if you wanna find and replace in documents uh</u>
<u n="270" who="S0037">oh in a folder? That's useful</u>
<u n="271" who="S0115">I mean I could do them with Python but uh I didn't know how to do it in in Visual uh in Visual Basic in Word but but you can do loads of uh like if you're using um Word or Excel or Access you can do loads of like um</u>
<u n="272" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0115">uh useful macros in uh Visual Basic <pause dur="short"/> which um <pause dur="short"/> just like if you've got annoying task generally speaking there should be a way to to make that task less annoying</u>
<u n="274" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well that's what I <pause dur="short"/> I was saying that at work like I think like if there's something you think that you wanna do there's definitely definitely an easier way than doing it manually like</u>
<u n="275" who="S0115">yeah I mean I think there's always an easier way to be honest like and until unless you're at the very vanguard of technology</u>
<u n="276" who="S0037" trans="overlap">always</u>
<u n="277" who="S0115">like um</u>
<u n="278" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0115">like like you know like</u>
<u n="280" who="S0037">like I <trunc>wa</trunc> like I was saying before you're you're never gonna be the first person who's thought ah I wish it would do X like it's very very rarely</u>
<u n="281" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well unlikely there's there's some some things you might</u>
<u n="282" who="S0037">no but <pause dur="short"/> very rarely isn't it?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0115">it it you may there may not be a free uh available one or whatever</u>
<u n="284" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0115">but uh no I mean uh <pause dur="short"/> but yeah say I mean even for for for transcription I mean if I was to train um uh you know something to recognize my voice like you know you could speak into that like uh obviously</u>
<u n="286" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> would you like some of this?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0115">uh yeah <pause dur="short"/> um but yeah I think there's there is always a way to be uh more efficient about things and and there's not always time but uh</u>
<u n="288" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah his perfume was so strong <pause dur="short"/> did you get that?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0115">no not not</u>
<u n="290" who="S0037">ah really strong <pause dur="short"/> really puts me off you know Sorry sorry <pause dur="short"/> I do like a bit of uh aftershave or perfume and that but when it's like  when it's like  you can like taste it <pause dur="short"/> I feel that's a bit much</u>
<u n="291" who="S0115">what?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0037">when you can like taste someone's perfume after they've left</u>
<u n="293" who="S0115">ah right no I didn't get that but uh</u>
<u n="294" who="S0037">did you not?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0115">yeah in well in your mouth's pretty bad isn't it?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0037">you're like</u>
<u n="297" who="S0115">it it just feels weird doesn't it?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0037">sorry I didn't mean to cut you off</u>
<u n="299" who="S0115">that was  that was  doing his uh</u>
<u n="300" who="S0037">oh his cat</u>
<u n="301" who="S0115">Cos he's he's just won <trunc>y</trunc> he's just won the by-election so they just showed some clips you know some of the bad stuff like</u>
<u n="302" who="S0037">yeah yeah yeah he's cat thing</u>
<u n="303" who="S0115">the cat thing and uh uh Saddam Husain thing and um</u>
<u n="304" who="S0037">ah that was pretty bad</u>
<u n="305" who="S0115">I think well <pause dur="short"/> like <trunc>Ame</trunc> America used to be a ally of Saddam so that's</u>
<u n="306" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="307" who="S0115">that's I guess he <pause dur="short"/> people were siding with him I suppose against uh against Iran or against uh uh Soviet Union um and uh at one time <pause dur="short"/> but uh <pause dur="short"/> the cat thing I guess is difficult to</u>
<u n="308" who="S0037">oh he's awful</u>
<u n="309" who="S0115">explain like</u>
<u n="310" who="S0037">oh he's horrible</u>
<u n="311" who="S0115">why what made him do that but uh that was his own choice so</u>
<u n="312" who="S0037">ah it's so cringey it's so hard to watch <pause dur="short"/> You know people talk about like Borat and like all those ones but that's awful to watch</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="313" who="S0115">Cos he he chose to go on um um to go on Big Brother</u>
<u n="314" who="S0037" trans="overlap">big Brother <pause dur="short"/> and why would you even do that like it's desperation it you ask me</u>
<u n="315" who="S0115">but he  but he  chose to <pause dur="short"/> no it's that he he he thought he could do any like you know he <trunc>th</trunc> thought he could  he could  do anything anyone said and like somehow come across well yeah out of it but um</u>
<u n="316" who="S0037" trans="overlap">come across well <pause dur="short"/> ah it's bad it's really bad</u>
<u n="317" who="S0115">yeah it's pretty pretty silly isn't it? Like but his performance against the uh against that tribunal though or whatever it was was was really great</u>
<u n="318" who="S0037">oh in America</u>
<u n="319" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0037">congress</u>
<u n="321" who="S0115">that was really good I liked that <pause dur="short"/> a good performance that was</u>
<u n="322" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that was quite funny <pause dur="short"/> yeah um <pause dur="short"/> yeah so when I was in here sorry <pause dur="short"/> when I was in here on Wednesday like all that bit through there was like there was a band on <pause dur="short"/> and we were sat like in the little corner like round there</u>
<u n="323" who="S0115">yeah so like where where where was the band then?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0037">just through there see where that birthday party is?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> there's <trunc>tho</trunc> those those um Geordies</u>
<u n="326" who="S0037" trans="overlap">there <pause dur="short"/> they cleared a space <pause dur="short"/> just one Geordie <pause dur="short"/> one <trunc>i</trunc> like pseudo-Geordie I'll call her</u>
<u n="327" who="S0115">the place is much busier on a Friday than a Saturday isn't it?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0037">actually it was  it was  quite busy on Wednesday you know like <pause dur="short"/> by the time I was leaving at like half nine-ish ten-ish or whenever it was I had to like push through people to get past</u>
<u n="329" who="S0115">oh really?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0037">maybe people come down for the band you know like</u>
<u n="331" who="S0115">oh yeah yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="332" who="S0115">yeah I mean there's a</u>
<u n="333" who="S0037" trans="overlap">everyone likes a bit live music don't they?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0115">yeah I haven't seen a live band for a long time I don't think</u>
<u n="335" who="S0037">well these ones were alright like they started like the first half <pause dur="short"/> so they must've started about nine-ish half eight-ish nine-ish <pause dur="short"/> and the first half was like just like generic blues blues rock sort of <pause dur="short"/> some stuff that I recognized some stuff I didn't like not really um anything groundbreaking or annoying actually it was kind of more like <pause dur="short"/> like um a lot of sort of um what's it called? Dire Straits-y sort of like <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> You know that kind of  that kind of  stuff <pause dur="short"/> like um</u>
<u n="336" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah <pause dur="short"/> did uh is that was Thin Lizzy there?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0037">yeah that was Thin Lizzy but</u>
<u n="338" who="S0115">whiskey In The Jar</u>
<u n="339" who="S0037">that was but You know what I mean that like <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> like that sort of</u>
<u n="340" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><unclear/> What was that <unclear/> um?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0037">that's Dire Straits isn't it? Sultans Of Swing</u>
<u n="342" who="S0115">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah I know that one</u>
<u n="343" who="S0037">so it was more that sort of which is very listen-to-able</u>
<u n="344" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0037">um</u>
<u n="346" who="S0115"><trunc>S</trunc> yeah sort of um</u>
<u n="347" who="S0037">not my choice but harmless background-y fine <pause dur="short"/> knit knit-to-able anyway <pause dur="short"/> you know for the knitting <pause dur="short"/> and then anway</u>
<u n="348" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well yeah yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0037">and then it got a bit weird like then it was like <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> crazy horses like</u>
<u n="350" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0037">so that was like a bit out of place <pause dur="short"/> and then it started to be like <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/> I got soul but I'm not a soldier <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="352" who="S0115">right <pause dur="short"/> so they were mainly um</u>
<u n="353" who="S0037">it got progressively weirder</u>
<u n="354" who="S0115">then rocking actually yeah that type</u>
<u n="355" who="S0037">yeah but it started off being like quite nice and then ended up being a bit like aw and like you know that song that was on the Keane song that was on before Eveyone's Changing <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="356" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like oh Keane yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0037">and like uh Coldplay and all that kinda like floppy sort of</u>
<u n="358" who="S0115" trans="overlap">some floppy stuff</u>
<u n="359" who="S0037">really not my sort of thing that sort of rock rock in the very very very loosest sense of the word</u>
<u n="360" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="361" who="S0037">rock with a very very much a lower case R like</u>
<u n="362" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well like</u>
<u n="363" who="S0037">you know What I mean that sort of like?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0115">yeah no no I <trunc>don</trunc> I haven't seen uh <pause dur="short"/> I didn't think that they had the like the um cover bands</u>
<u n="365" who="S0037">sorry?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0115">I didn't realize they had cover bands in this pub so</u>
<u n="367" who="S0037" trans="overlap">uh every Wednesday apparently <pause dur="short"/> I was talking to the barmaid</u>
<u n="368" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I mean I knew they had them in the Portland over there but uh I didn't know about um</u>
<u n="369" who="S0037">quite a different calibre of band I feel</u>
<u n="370" who="S0115">yeah they were always sort of loud metal bands and more sort of rock um</u>
<u n="371" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't think you would get like a covers a cheesy Keane covers band in here uh <trunc>i</trunc> sorry in the Portland</u>
<u n="372" who="S0115">no I guess not <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="373" who="S0037">it would be like The Virgin Mary's like Suspenders or something in there like some stupid like <vocal desc="laugh"/> Pseudo Death</u>
<u n="374" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0037">industrial</u>
<u n="376" who="S0115">like <trunc>w</trunc> one one of the names was uh Bleeding From Within</u>
<u n="377" who="S0037" trans="overlap">bleeding From Within yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's better than my one</u>
<u n="378" who="S0115">well what was it? Suspenders and what?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0037">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I was making stuff up <pause dur="short"/> I I'm</u>
<u n="380" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but there's a pub just down there <pause dur="short"/> there there's a lot of pubs in this  in this  little area but uh that one just down there it's just always it's ridiculous ridiculously quiet</u>
<u n="381" who="S0037">you know but the</u>
<u n="382" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's like there's like a fish tank which is strange cos not pubs don't normally have fish tanks in them</u>
<u n="383" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like <pause dur="short"/> no I've got nothing against a pub with a fish tank though <pause dur="short"/> but do you not wonder if it's the times that we've been in like?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you go in there right and it's like <trunc>y</trunc> you can hear the fish you know</u>
<u n="385" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like we've never been in <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> I know I've been there but what I'm saying is like we've never been in on a Friday</u>
<u n="386" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the fish are bored <pause dur="short"/> they're trying to get out</u>
<u n="387" who="S0037">we've never been on a Friday night though it might be like jumping that might be the place to be</u>
<u n="388" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh I dunno <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="389" who="S0037">no but we've only in <pause dur="short"/> we went in once when we wandered in <pause dur="short"/> we went in once with your parents like <pause dur="short"/> on like a Sunday afternoon I mean</u>
<u n="390" who="S0115" trans="overlap">get ones with <pause dur="short"/> no no I went in before uh it was kinda like being in a waiting room of like like a restaurant except like that actually that was the main bit and like the restaurant was just like the restaurant of a waiting room or something</u>
<u n="391" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it is bad like sometimes you know if you go in a pub and then like there's only one other person there and they're just listening to you and you're a bit like you can't say what you wanna say it's <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's not nice <pause dur="short"/> but maybe we just haven't given it a <trunc>g</trunc> a chance maybe we should go like and see what the crack is and</u>
<u n="392" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah well we can go along there right now and I I think the crack will be like pretty much the same as as what the crack normally is but still</u>
<u n="393" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't mean now <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> yeah maybe</u>
<u n="394" who="S0115">yeah we can see so</u>
<u n="395" who="S0037">so do you think we should go next door now or d'you think we should go like or stay here or?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="397" who="S0037">it's always kinda cold next door which sort of gets on my nerves</u>
<u n="398" who="S0115" trans="overlap">what time is it uh I've it's twenty-three eighteen <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> yeah we could go there and</u>
<u n="399" who="S0037">it's always a bit <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="400" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they they close at the same time don't they cos they're obliged to</u>
<u n="401" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's always a bit  it's always a bit  cold though that's one thing like</u>
<u n="402" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0037">yeah it is cheaper but it is <pause dur="short"/> they don't have music on and it's it's a bit like</u>
<u n="404" who="S0115">not much atmosphere</u>
<u n="405" who="S0037">not much atmosphere</u>
<u n="406" who="S0115">yeah cos you know it's like Wetherspoons um based on George Orwell's idea of what a good pub would be</u>
<u n="407" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="408" who="S0115">and he didn't like music in pubs which I don't really agree with that so like</u>
<u n="409" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I think it's good to have something background-y <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if I want like</u>
<u n="410" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like but but but like <pause dur="short"/> all Wetherspoons well apart from the Lloyds bars Wetherspoons Wetherspoons have no music in them <pause dur="short"/> bit of uh</u>
<u n="411" who="S0037">God</u>
<u n="412" who="S0115">entertainment uh</u>
<u n="413" who="S0037">so annoying</u>
<u n="414" who="S0115">so yeah is it uh is it the barman no it's someone  no it's someone</u>
<u n="415" who="S0037">yeah it's like some lads pulling hilarious lads' pranks</u>
<u n="416" who="S0115">I was uh cos I think they know the barman I think something like that</u>
<u n="417" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="418" who="S0115">anyway um <pause dur="short"/> yeah so uh <pause dur="short"/> pubs should have music that has  that has  <trunc>m</trunc> final uh <pause dur="short"/> but Wetherspoons don't apart from those bars that is my final thing that I would say</u>
</body>
</text>
