<text id="SPZA">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:18:40</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-28</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0509 S0510</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON &amp; ANON's home, Hastings</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Books, Flowers, Cooking, Utensils, Taking Blood, Dissection, College</topics>
		<activity>Mother and Daughter chatting and cooking</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0509">
				<exactage>16</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hastings</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hastings</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0510">
				<exactage>47</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hastings</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Receptionist</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0509">yeah I think Neil Gaiman is really great cos he was the <unclear/> one you you know the one?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0510">erm Neil Gaiman what? didn't he do some Doctor Who stuff as well yeah?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0509" trans="overlap">he did he did do Doctor Who</u>
<u n="4" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="5" who="S0509" trans="overlap">erm but he's just a really cool person and I tell you about this charity bundle of books that he was doing he did that</u>
<u n="6" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh oh tell me about that again <unclear/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0509" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="8" who="S0510">was that to raise money or something?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0509">yeah it was to raise money was it was it was written for two <unclear/> one was like a it was literary literacy <trunc>cha</trunc> charities that he was doing it for</u>
<u n="10" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah right</u>
<u n="11" who="S0509">but erm he sold like all these rare books of his erm or e e e-versions of these rare books of his</u>
<u n="12" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="13" who="S0509">and <trunc>the</trunc> they were yeah and he raised loads of money which was nice</u>
<u n="14" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="15" who="S0509" trans="overlap">but he's kind of one of a group of authors who do a lot of charity stuff <trunc>the</trunc> the Waterstones are now doing a thing for the Syrian refugees where a load of authors like Neil Gaiman</u>
<u n="16" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0509">are donating a bunch of their books for free and when you buy them all the money goes to erm Syria Syrian refugees</u>
<u n="18" who="S0510">oh fantastic</u>
<u n="19" who="S0509" trans="overlap">which is cool</u>
<u n="20" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0509">so he's doing that as well so is Patrick Ness who you know the book that I was reading before?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0509">I finished it now I don't know if I told you</u>
<u n="24" who="S0510">oh no you didn't</u>
<u n="25" who="S0509">but yeah that that's all that's all finished it was really good</u>
<u n="26" who="S0510">was it?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0509">he is an amazing writer</u>
<u n="28" who="S0510" trans="overlap">is that part? is it part of the trilogy though that you read?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0509">no it's not it's his new one</u>
<u n="30" who="S0510">right okay</u>
<u n="31" who="S0509">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0510">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sorry to interrupt you there</u>
<u n="33" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0510">look at that</u>
<u n="35" who="S0509">oh my gosh</u>
<u n="36" who="S0510">stupendous</u>
<u n="37" who="S0509" trans="overlap">they look lovely</u>
<u n="38" who="S0510">gorgeous</u>
<u n="39" who="S0509">yeah they do ah <unclear/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0510" trans="overlap">I love the smell of lilies yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0509">oh and they go with that <unclear>bath</unclear> really well like the same colour</u>
<u n="42" who="S0510">they do they do do you know what? when I bought them</u>
<u n="43" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="44" who="S0510">they were supposed to only have one day in you know? in so were sort of sell by the twenty-fourth or something</u>
<u n="45" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0510">but they're not like all open</u>
<u n="47" who="S0509" trans="overlap">and they're not</u>
<u n="48" who="S0510">no and they're still to open up properly</u>
<u n="49" who="S0509">oh yeah so you bought these last week didn't you?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0510">like last week last Wednesday and they were due to sort of</u>
<u n="51" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh my gosh</u>
<u n="52" who="S0510">expire on the Thursday in terms of sell-by</u>
<u n="53" who="S0509">they're doing amazingly then</u>
<u n="54" who="S0510">but yeah there's only one that's actually <trunc>o</trunc> started opening well one that's opened</u>
<u n="55" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0510">and there's a couple that have started opening actually but</u>
<u n="57" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="58" who="S0510">they've still got quite a lot of life to go</u>
<u n="59" who="S0509">yeah well that's good cos they'll probably just get dried out in my room and just turn into fossilised flowers <unclear/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you'll have dry flowers by the end of it yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I will indeed</u>
<u n="62" who="S0510">but less <unclear/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0509" trans="overlap">but yeah I've finished my amazing Patrick Ness book</u>
<u n="64" who="S0510">yeah so what's so amazing about Patrick Ness then?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0509">he just he writes I don't know he writes really beautifully it's just it and it's <trunc>li</trunc> yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0510" trans="overlap">is he always of a particular style? or does he mix it up</u>
<u n="67" who="S0509" trans="overlap">no he seems to change style like between his books</u>
<u n="68" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="69" who="S0509">like his last one was really sort of quite complexly written</u>
<u n="70" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0509">and then this one's sort of written it's written from the point of view of this guy and it's really sort of erm colloquial</u>
<u n="72" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="73" who="S0509">not like you know? the apostrophes replacing letters in every other sentence but just like slang and that in it</u>
<u n="74" who="S0510">okay</u>
<u n="75" who="S0509">and it just reads like someone's talking to you</u>
<u n="76" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="77" who="S0509">but erm at the beginning of each chapter it's got an excerpt from what the indie kids are doing in their town did I tell you about this?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0510">no</u>
<u n="79" who="S0509">and the indie kids erm well they're the group who always have the massive adventure in the town and you know? ten years ago it was the zombie ghost and then five years before that vampires blew up the school</u>
<u n="80" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh right</u>
<u n="81" who="S0509">and it's always the er the indie kids the people with names like Satchel and Dylan and Finn</u>
<u n="82" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0509">who these adventures always happen to</u>
<u n="84" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="85" who="S0509">erm and the time of the indie kids has come again and the immortals are attacking</u>
<u n="86" who="S0510" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="87" who="S0509">and at the beginning of each chapter it has a little kind of paragraph of what's happening with the indie kids</u>
<u n="88" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0509">while that chapter's taking place</u>
<u n="90" who="S0510">ah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0509">and then it goes into the rest of them cos it's the rest of us just live here</u>
<u n="92" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0509" trans="overlap">so it's like you know? the indie kids do all this but the rest of us just live here</u>
<u n="94" who="S0510" trans="overlap">live here right</u>
<u n="95" who="S0509">and we're just normal people who want to graduate high school or whatever</u>
<u n="96" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0509">and erm and then occasionally  the world of the indie kids and the characters of the novel will cross over like at one point they run over a deer with glowing eyes and then the deer comes back to life it's really weird</u>
<u n="98" who="S0510">oh</u>
<u n="99" who="S0509" trans="overlap">and then yeah and then one of the friends in this group I mean they're supposed to be the rest of us</u>
<u n="100" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0509">but one of them is erm a quarter god of cats he he's the <trunc>god</trunc> he's the grandson of the god of cats</u>
<u n="102" who="S0510">meow</u>
<u n="103" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0509">so at one point one of the indie kids things was that the gods came down you know? and eh</u>
<u n="106" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="107" who="S0509">that so one of them <trunc>co</trunc> has all this healing power and like at one one bit where they interact with the indie kids he heals this guy and it's really it's really cleverly done</u>
<u n="108" who="S0510">if you put certain herbs under his nose does he go a bit wild?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0509">no but like cats flock to him</u>
<u n="110" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0509">and I would have thought gather round him it's quite funny</u>
<u n="112" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0509">like the mountain lion comes down and just sort of cuddles up to him</u>
<u n="114" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0509">it's quite funny but erm yeah they've all got like their all these kids have got got like their own problems like one of them's got OCD and that</u>
<u n="116" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="117" who="S0509">and it's all then the main character has the OCD and it's really interesting and kind of mm oh gosh and then like at the end the <vocal desc="laugh"/> the guy who's quarter god is like the gods have been trying to get me to take over from my mum for years and become a full time god and I've been saying no but I said that I will if I can heal well cos normally he can just heal cats but he can do a little bit of healing on humans</u>
<u n="118" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="119" who="S0509">erm he he said he would if he could heal his friend who has the OCD cos obviously the OCD is like in the mind so it's like</u>
<u n="120" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0509">a different thing and so he's now bound to this contract with them his friend is like I don't I don't want you to cos I want to see if I can overcome it myself which is really cool</u>
<u n="122" who="S0510" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0509">it's a really nice ending</u>
<u n="124" who="S0510">just stop that <unclear>healing</unclear> malarkey</u>
<u n="125" who="S0509">but erm there was all of the drama going on between them all cos yeah it was great though</u>
<u n="126" who="S0510"><unclear/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0509" trans="overlap">and like one of the characters in it who's like this sort of the new boy who's rolled into town you think that it's the prince of the immortals like the way it's written it's set up so that he could be the prince of the immortals but then</u>
<u n="128" who="S0510" trans="overlap">right yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0509">it and then you get to a few chapters before the end and it's written in a way that's like oh he isn't then?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0510">oh right</u>
<u n="131" who="S0509" trans="overlap">but like you've been tricking me all along because really they are all normal and that's what you're trying to say</u>
<u n="132" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="133" who="S0509">that's quite very good</u>
<u n="134" who="S0510">ah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0510">so what's the moral of the story <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? is that it? like don't be fooled by <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0509" trans="overlap">you've been tricking me all along no it's like friendship</u>
<u n="138" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="139" who="S0509">they're a really cool group of friends</u>
<u n="140" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="141" who="S0509">yeah they're really yeah it's cool</u>
<u n="142" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> ah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0509">and yeah friendship and trust your friends</u>
<u n="144" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0510">we like that kind of thing yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah but the other one that I love of his was more than this which is just like sends you into the onto the floor in like spasms of literary pleasure</u>
<u n="148" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0509"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0510">was this? was this the complicated one? or was it?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0509">yeah it was more <trunc>sophis</trunc> sophisticated language would have been the word</u>
<u n="152" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0509">erm yeah but that's cos he always twists a bit of fantasy into it</u>
<u n="154" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="155" who="S0509">like his his trilogy that he did was like full on fantasy then more than this was like futuristic kind of fantasy</u>
<u n="156" who="S0510">okay</u>
<u n="157" who="S0509">and then this is just like normal world but there's all this stuff with the indie kids going on</u>
<u n="158" who="S0510">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah so it's eh it's very good</u>
<u n="160" who="S0510">so ah he's on your must read list then now?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah yes</u>
<u n="162" who="S0510">I've got actually another Patrick erm that I really</u>
<u n="163" who="S0509" trans="overlap">Patrick Gale?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0510">yeah Patrick Gale</u>
<u n="165" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0510">and it's funny cos what you were saying about you know? erm er the books with the indie kids</u>
<u n="167" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0510">about how at the beginning it gave you this little description of what was happening with the indie kids</u>
<u n="169" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0510">but then it went into what was happening with the rest of the world sort of thing</u>
<u n="171" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0510">erm and Patrick Gale this particular book that he did called <unclear/> on an exhibition</u>
<u n="173" who="S0509">I remember that one</u>
<u n="174" who="S0510">aw such a good book that was the first one of his that I read actually and the main character the essential character was this sort of <trunc>Corni</trunc> well American woman living in Cornwall but she came to the UK sort of as a student erm</u>
<u n="175" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0510">I think she moved to London first and then ended up in Cornwall met met this amazing guy who took her on with child</u>
<u n="177" who="S0509" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="178" who="S0510">and all the rest of it</u>
<u n="179" who="S0509">oh</u>
<u n="180" who="S0510">and erm she was like this really typical sort of artist <trunc>art</trunc> artist who has crazy moments</u>
<u n="181" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="182" who="S0510">and you know? shuts herself away for weeks on end and all the rest of it but at the beginning of every chapter he would focus on one of her paintings so the opening sort of <unclear/> if you like</u>
<u n="183" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="184" who="S0510">was just a description of this incredible painting that she had drawn or painted</u>
<u n="185" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="186" who="S0510">erm and then in some way it links into the overall story it wouldn't necessarily</u>
<u n="187" who="S0509" trans="overlap">mm hm</u>
<u n="188" who="S0510">always link into what was happening in that chapter it might have been that particular painting she painted in a period of her her life where it had <trunc>par</trunc> particular significance because she met somebody and you know? there was some theme in there to do with it but you know? it was just an interesting kind of concept if you like for a a book a</u>
<u n="189" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="190" who="S0510">just a thread through</u>
<u n="191" who="S0509">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0510" trans="overlap">particularly as it was about her her amazing creativity</u>
<u n="193" who="S0509">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="194" who="S0510" trans="overlap">and her in her life and you know? how how that changed over the course of her life I mean in the end she was sort of well she always was she a sort of manic depressive really</u>
<u n="195" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0510">erm and the depressive side of her character got the better of her in the end</u>
<u n="197" who="S0509">right oh dear</u>
<u n="198" who="S0510" trans="overlap">and the final chapter was this started off with a description of a painting that she'd left to her children</u>
<u n="199" who="S0509">right</u>
<u n="200" who="S0510">which was I won't go into it any more but you know? it was very poignant and very significant to the overall sort of</u>
<u n="201" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah the overall story</u>
<u n="202" who="S0510">I can tell that you are multitasking <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0510">you are only half connected what have you got on the go now?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0509" trans="overlap">no I am you've been talking you've been talking about your book and how great it was</u>
<u n="206" who="S0510" trans="overlap">have I been rabbiting? okay</u>
<u n="207" who="S0509">and that that the paintings</u>
<u n="208" who="S0510">are you? good to know you're paying attention</u>
<u n="209" who="S0509">I am I can multitask you see</u>
<u n="210" who="S0510" trans="overlap">you always are <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0509">but erm I'm slicing apples for the crumble now I'm just going to guess the amount</u>
<u n="212" who="S0510">yeah cos they said eight granny Smiths on the erm the pie but but the the remainder are they the remainder?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah no it's there's more apples but this is the remainder of the stuff I've already peeled so I might get you on peeling duty in a minute cos I'm going to need more that this probably</u>
<u n="214" who="S0510" trans="overlap">are you? I can see there's still quite a lot of peel on those apples darling</u>
<u n="215" who="S0509" trans="overlap">no there's not there's a little bit so I'm going to cut them off I have been cutting them off okay</u>
<u n="216" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay</u>
<u n="217" who="S0509">it's okay don't worry</u>
<u n="218" who="S0510">okay</u>
<u n="219" who="S0509">you see?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0510">careful of that finger</u>
<u n="221" who="S0509">yeah see that other bit that I cut off? <unclear/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I do indeed yeah you're going to get quite a collection there <pause dur="short"/> eh?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0509">alright just cos I can't peel</u>
<u n="224" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0509">ah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well you know? if that's all you've got to worry about in the world you're you're a very lucky girl</u>
<u n="227" who="S0509" trans="overlap">like I was saying earlier should've done catering shouldn't I?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0509">then I'd be fine</u>
<u n="230" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> it's all about the tools as well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know? if we had a really good peeler</u>
<u n="231" who="S0509" trans="overlap">really good peeler</u>
<u n="232" who="S0510"><unclear>it'd be</unclear> happy days</u>
<u n="233" who="S0509" trans="overlap">cos we've got a proper tin opener now you had no idea how happy I was</u>
<u n="234" who="S0510" trans="overlap">I like that that is amazing isn't it?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0509">I was like oh my god it's a tin opener and not a piece of rust</u>
<u n="236" who="S0510" trans="overlap">you can actually use it <vocal desc="laugh"/> piece of rust</u>
<u n="237" who="S0509">that's what the other one was</u>
<u n="238" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> no</u>
<u n="239" who="S0509">it was though it was a piece of rust</u>
<u n="240" who="S0510" trans="overlap">ah no it was those cheap pound tin openers that that you get for camping trips and things</u>
<u n="241" who="S0509" trans="overlap">you can't see this is what I've learned</u>
<u n="242" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0509">for when I move away from home</u>
<u n="244" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0509">ah I will be investing in the best</u>
<u n="246" who="S0510">yes</u>
<u n="247" who="S0509">tin opener available</u>
<u n="248" who="S0510">yes</u>
<u n="249" who="S0509">I am not gonna put up with <unclear>a</unclear> substandard tin opener</u>
<u n="250" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's a false economy it really is</u>
<u n="251" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0510">no I</u>
<u n="253" who="S0509">I'm not entirely sure what that means but yes</u>
<u n="254" who="S0510">well you know? <trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> it's to economise in such a fashion is sort of not false but you know? there's no point in you doing it because it doesn't help you actually end up spending more or having more you know? trouble</u>
<u n="255" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh yeah that makes sense okay</u>
<u n="256" who="S0510">because you know? they run out a lot quicker</u>
<u n="257" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0510">or you know? they just are not up to the job yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0509">they never work in the first place</u>
<u n="262" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah quite but we you know? we've soldiered on with our our pound tin openers for a long time</u>
<u n="263" who="S0509">we have <unclear/> how much did that tin opener cost?</u>
<u n="264" who="S0510">oh well let's just say it was an Aldi special I was drawn to the baskets in the midea middle of the Aldi aisle</u>
<u n="265" who="S0509">was it still a pound?</u>
<u n="266" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0510">no it wasn't a little bit more I think it was about three pound but you know? ah in any other supermarket or your choice you probably would've paid double that but</u>
<u n="268" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0510">it was on an Aldi special basket</u>
<u n="270" who="S0509" trans="overlap">weird Aldi specials</u>
<u n="271" who="S0510">you know? discounts</u>
<u n="272" who="S0509" trans="overlap">we're living the high life</u>
<u n="273" who="S0510">but it is like you say</u>
<u n="274" who="S0509" trans="overlap">sorry</u>
<u n="275" who="S0510">it's a proper tin opener</u>
<u n="276" who="S0509">yeah it works</u>
<u n="277" who="S0510">you don't need to have extra muscles in your wrist to kind of get it go the other way round</u>
<u n="278" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I know I just couldn't do it I I was never sure how to put it on because neither way seemed to work</u>
<u n="279" who="S0510" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0509">and I was just like does the wheely bit go on? does the little blunt bit go on?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/> the little blunt bit yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah erm did you get the <trunc>ble</trunc> not the blender the whisky thing from Tesco's?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh my goodness oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I completely forgot about that</u>
<u n="284" who="S0509">well you're going to have to get it at some point but okay</u>
<u n="285" who="S0510">hopefully it'll still be there if I go tomorrow</u>
<u n="286" who="S0509">oh surely you'll be fine</u>
<u n="287" who="S0510" trans="overlap">I'll go I'll go in after work tomorrow tomorrow</u>
<u n="288" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0510">erm yeah I'm kind of cos I had the doctors this morning and I parked up outside Iceland and <unclear/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0509" trans="overlap">did they take blood from you?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0510">they took lots of blood darling</u>
<u n="292" who="S0509">ah you okay?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0510" trans="overlap">many vials yes oh yeah apparently you know I was quite a cool customer today she was saying you know I was about the eighth person she'd seen that morning</u>
<u n="294" who="S0509" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="295" who="S0510">and it was only nine fifteen</u>
<u n="296" who="S0509">oh my god</u>
<u n="297" who="S0510">erm and you know?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh <unclear/> for that</u>
<u n="299" who="S0510">she said you know? she never knows what kind of day it's going to be erm</u>
<u n="300" who="S0509"><unclear/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0510">yeah apparently fainters all sorts of fainters</u>
<u n="302" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh my gosh</u>
<u n="303" who="S0510">erm you know? where she literally as she's taking the blood at the same time she's taking the blood she's seen the blood colour drain from their faces</u>
<u n="304" who="S0509" trans="overlap">oh my gosh</u>
<u n="305" who="S0510">and then they're like oh I'm a little faint and they have to get up onto the couch and I said well they're definitely not the kind of people to give blood then are they? and she said no no definitely not</u>
<u n="306" who="S0509">did I erm tell you about you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> from drama? from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0510" trans="overlap">er okay yeah</u>
<u n="308" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/> erm did I tell you about him fainting?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0510">no</u>
<u n="310" who="S0509">he erm in science when they were doing dissection he fainted twice</u>
<u n="311" who="S0510">ah bless him</u>
<u n="312" who="S0509">I know</u>
<u n="313" who="S0510">can't blame him really it can get pretty gruesome</u>
<u n="314" who="S0509">it was like when we did it in class cos we had to do the heart and stuff</u>
<u n="315" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0509">I had to stick my fingers through the passages of a pig's heart</u>
<u n="317" who="S0510">oh thanks for that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I really appreciate that</u>
<u n="318" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> least I didn't tell you was eating your dinner</u>
<u n="319" who="S0510">oh that's good</u>
<u n="320" who="S0509" trans="overlap">so erm yeah no it's not fun</u>
<u n="321" who="S0510">no</u>
<u n="322" who="S0509">but like even watching them do the dissection like in our class <unclear/> people were like oh I'm out of here</u>
<u n="323" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0509">no thanks</u>
<u n="325" who="S0510">yeah I seem to remember that when I was at school</u>
<u n="326" who="S0509">and there was no point well I guess there was cos some people learn practically but</u>
<u n="327" who="S0510">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0509">but like it wasn't like how do you dissect a heart? on the exam but then I guess they have to teach you cos you probably do have to do that at like A level or uni or whatever</u>
<u n="329" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm but they could at least wait till then if you're really interested in the subjects and you really want to put yourself through that</u>
<u n="330" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah apparently biology is really hard at A level</u>
<u n="331" who="S0510">is it?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="333" who="S0510">mm never did it at A level no I wouldn't have fancied doing it at A level it wasn't really</u>
<u n="334" who="S0509">no</u>
<u n="335" who="S0510">of interest</u>
<u n="336" who="S0509">it didn't float your boat</u>
<u n="337" who="S0510">no indeedy</u>
<u n="338" who="S0509"><vocal desc="sigh"/> oh I've got my <unclear/> my first <unclear/> mentoring tomorrow</u>
<u n="339" who="S0510">ah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0509" trans="overlap"><unclear/> with the new mentor</u>
<u n="341" who="S0510">hurrah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0510">that'll be interesting</u>
<u n="344" who="S0509">it will indeed</u>
<u n="345" who="S0510">how long do they put aside for that? an hour is it?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0509">yeah I think so I presume so</u>
<u n="347" who="S0510" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="348" who="S0509">I've got it wait when have I got it? I've got it after the double psychology cos I have a massive like three hour gap so I have it then</u>
<u n="349" who="S0510">ah that's a good time to do it then</u>
<u n="350" who="S0509">yeah I wish they'd moved my study period to then could you imagine how great that would have been cos I was going to stay in there anyway <unclear/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah what? they'd moved it to Friday instead? what? after your last lesson?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0510">ah that's a shame</u>
<u n="354" who="S0509" trans="overlap">but I still get out I still get out at like one o'clock so I still have the afternoon</u>
<u n="355" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0509">but <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0510">is there any way of bartering with that?</u>
<u n="358" who="S0509">I don't know I feel a bit cheeky cos I've already</u>
<u n="359" who="S0510">well if you don't ask you don't you know?</u>
<u n="360" who="S0509" trans="overlap">I but I've already had it moved from the Monday because that was cos I you know? I'm auditioning for that play</u>
<u n="361" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah but then that's to do with curricular stuff so you know?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0509" trans="overlap">yeah if I don't if I don't get into that then I could be like I could just be like I think we should get it moved back to the Monday now</u>
<u n="363" who="S0510" trans="overlap">back yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0509">since I only really wanted it moved because of that</u>
<u n="365" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0509">please let me</u>
<u n="367" who="S0510"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="368" who="S0509">don't think they will they want us to do another drama trip but it's only to the college so it's like four quid but</u>
<u n="369" who="S0510">oh okay</u>
<u n="370" who="S0509">still I was like</u>
<u n="371" who="S0510"><unclear/> aren't they?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0509">I know there's like three of them</u>
<u n="373" who="S0510">but that's fantastic</u>
<u n="374" who="S0509">I know it's nicer actually going to see theatre</u>
<u n="375" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0509">but like you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="378" who="S0509">she she can't really afford it and she applied for the bursary and she didn't get it</u>
<u n="379" who="S0510">oh really?</u>
<u n="380" who="S0509" trans="overlap">so she's like she's not going to be very happy cos she's going to be I can't pay for it</u>
<u n="381" who="S0510" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="382" who="S0509">ah so</u>
<u n="383" who="S0510">so we we don't know whether our bursary are</u>
<u n="384" who="S0509">don't know</u>
<u n="385" who="S0510">no</u>
<u n="386" who="S0509">we'll see I've got the documents to give you back</u>
<u n="387" who="S0510">oh yeah lovely</u>
<u n="388" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0510">ah that's a shame for her so is she not going to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0509">no she she has to it's compulsory</u>
<u n="391" who="S0510">oh right right</u>
<u n="392" who="S0509" trans="overlap">so they've managed to afford it but they can't it's not really</u>
<u n="393" who="S0510" trans="overlap">yeah can't mm mm</u>
<u n="394" who="S0509">and cos she's travelling from is it from <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/>? she was going to <anon type="place"/> college</u>
<u n="395" who="S0510">right</u>
<u n="396" who="S0509">but I think she lives in <anon type="place"/> now she's going back to her college instead</u>
<u n="397" who="S0510">aw that's better for her kind of</u>
<u n="398" who="S0509">yeah she just</u>
<u n="399" who="S0510">travel and moneywise</u>
<u n="400" who="S0509">yeah you know? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you might not know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> from my er stage school drama?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0510">I don't know her no unless she was in the erm ah the psychologists erm psychotherapists one</u>
<u n="402" who="S0509" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="403" who="S0510">no?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0509">no but I erm I've told you about her before she's like my main friend there</u>
<u n="405" who="S0510">aha</u>
<u n="406" who="S0509">and erm she er she was I think she did a year at <anon type="place"/> studio school but she's come back to retake her AS levels at <anon type="place"/> now</u>
<u n="407" who="S0510">really?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0509">yeah so there's loads of people who are retaking ASs</u>
<u n="409" who="S0510">mm</u>
<u n="410" who="S0509"><trunc>co</trunc> some come from other colleges some <unclear/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0510" trans="overlap">interesting yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0509">yeah it is interesting</u>
<u n="413" who="S0510">interesting they're all coming to <anon type="place"/> that will <trunc>sa</trunc> that will say a lot for <anon type="place"/> really</u>
<u n="414" who="S0509" trans="overlap">that's good</u>
<u n="415" who="S0510">yeah</u>
<u n="416" who="S0509">yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0510">that is good</u>
<u n="418" who="S0509">mm</u>
<u n="419" who="S0510">I'm just going to quickly nip up</u>
<u n="420" who="S0509">okay <unclear/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0510" trans="overlap">be back in a mo</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
