<text id="SPZR">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:13:47</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-04-25</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0390 S0391 S0392</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Home maintenance, recent events, businesses, music, food and drink, parking, technology, food and drink</topics>
		<activity>Grandmother's visit</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, anecdote telling, making arrangements, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0390">
				<exactage>76</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kendal</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>British</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Near Thirsk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>12 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0391">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Darlington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>British</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>County Durham</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Near Thirsk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>15 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0392">
				<exactage>15</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Newcastle-upon-time</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern/Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Near Thirsk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>15 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Full-time education</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0392">so did you get your plumbing sorted then?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0390">I got it sorted I sorted it myself <pause dur="short"/> thank you</u>
<u n="3" who="S0392">what was it that was wrong with it?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0390">well</u>
<u n="5" who="S0392" trans="overlap">exactly?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0390">there's erm a bend and there's two big <trunc>scre</trunc> big sort of er washers attached no not washers screw things and I just tightened them up and it hasn't leaked for three days</u>
<u n="7" who="S0392">was it in the kitchen or the bathroom or?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0390">kitchen it was a cupboard where I keep all my stuff</u>
<u n="9" who="S0392">and it had all leaked all over <unclear/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0390" trans="overlap">and it had all leaked so I've scrubbed that out</u>
<u n="11" who="S0392">ah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0390">I got all the stuff out and it is all over the kitchen</u>
<u n="13" who="S0392">and your telephone is back up and running?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0390">oh yes don't don't say telephone don't say British Telecom just don't</u>
<u n="15" who="S0392"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0390">because I'm going to have a fit if you do</u>
<u n="17" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0392">it was dreadful awful <pause dur="short"/> two weeks could you believe it?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0392">really?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0390">two weeks without it</u>
<u n="21" who="S0392">did your mobile work okay?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0390">huh I made four calls on an 0 eight hundred number</u>
<u n="23" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0390">to British Telecom but it's charged that was seventeen pounds</u>
<u n="25" who="S0392">really?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0390">so I am in a bit of a <pause dur="short"/> not a bad temper exactly because I've come down a bit</u>
<u n="27" who="S0392">you should be able to get that refunded</u>
<u n="28" who="S0390">I don't know I'm gonna to <trunc>st</trunc> I'm going to try</u>
<u n="29" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="30" who="S0390">I'm drafting a letter of complaint</u>
<u n="31" who="S0392">is there any more news on the petrol station compensation form?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0390">well they say that it there was nothing wrong with the pump</u>
<u n="33" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0390">but I don't know whether I believe them because I've got my petrol there for years and years</u>
<u n="35" who="S0392">and it's always gone right</u>
<u n="36" who="S0390">it has always been right</u>
<u n="37" who="S0392">so are you going to follow it up with something then or?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0390">I think so I am thinking about it probably but I am gonna be <pause dur="short"/> follow up British Telecom most decidedly</u>
<u n="39" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0390">mm</u>
<u n="41" who="S0392">they they are just called BT now I think because a lot of companies are doing that they are getting rid of they are just making it into the initials</u>
<u n="42" who="S0390" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="43" who="S0392">do you know what I mean? so like do you remember what used to be Scottish and Southern Energy is now SSE</u>
<u n="44" who="S0390">yes</u>
<u n="45" who="S0392">and it doesn't stand for anything BP is now BP officially it doesn't stand for anything they are registered as BP</u>
<u n="46" who="S0390">what's BP?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0392">well it was British Petroleum</u>
<u n="48" who="S0390">yes it was</u>
<u n="49" who="S0392">and they are registered as BT now so that's that's</u>
<u n="50" who="S0390">oh right okay I believe you maybe thousands wouldn't</u>
<u n="51" who="S0392">no it is true</u>
<u n="52" who="S0390">no I believe you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that's only a erm a phrase</u>
<u n="53" who="S0392">a saying yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0390">I believe you and have you practised for tomorrow?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0392">tomorrow it is not tomorrow I'm worried about so much in fact I'm not worried about anything because tomorrow I am just playing the second violin part so there shouldn't be any worries about that and then in all the <trunc>other</trunc></u>
<u n="56" who="S0390">I thought you were playing on your own tomorrow?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0392">no there's erm <pause dur="long"/> there's just the two of us play second violin that's alright and then on the days after that it is just me by myself so it doesn't matter because if I go wrong at all then there's nobody sat next to me who is getting it right who I've who is going to put me off and anyway for these theatre things you just sort of adapt the music</u>
<u n="58" who="S0390" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="59" who="S0392">you don't play exactly you can make bits hard bits easier this one is really</u>
<u n="60" who="S0390" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="61" who="S0392">simple so I won't need to make any of it easier</u>
<u n="62" who="S0390">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0392">in fact I might even want to make some of it more advanced</u>
<u n="64" who="S0390">this is Tuesday?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0392">this is the well all week yeah we have</u>
<u n="66" who="S0390">oh sorry when your grandma and I are going</u>
<u n="67" who="S0391">can I just see what drink <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants? would you like a cold white or a room temperature red? or not quite cold rose?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0390">what's already opened?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0391">oh it doesn't matter because</u>
<u n="70" who="S0390">yes it does you tell me</u>
<u n="71" who="S0391">because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at the weekend we will drink two bottles of wine</u>
<u n="72" who="S0390">well I would like a red then please</u>
<u n="73" who="S0391">lovely</u>
<u n="74" who="S0392">anyway yeah as I said Sunday is one practice Monday is a dress rehearsal and that's all the practice we get we don't get a practice at any other time at all</u>
<u n="75" who="S0390">I think that's amazing</u>
<u n="76" who="S0392">mm</u>
<u n="77" who="S0390">I do really</u>
<u n="78" who="S0392">well that's how it works in proper theatres they give you the music and then they expect you to go home and everyone practise</u>
<u n="79" who="S0390">right okay but now let's get back to Saturday</u>
<u n="80" who="S0392">yes</u>
<u n="81" who="S0390">where are you playing first? school or</u>
<u n="82" who="S0392">the school event they've put us right on at the start</u>
<u n="83" who="S0390" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="84" who="S0392">so that's start about seven say it takes us ten minutes to do that</u>
<u n="85" who="S0390">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0392">then I should <vocal desc="laugh"/> realistically I should be across at the <anon type="place"/> Singers I'm not even needed over at the other church until about quarter past half past eight but I should I might even be there before the thingy started</u>
<u n="87" who="S0390">well they don't start until half seven</u>
<u n="88" who="S0392">exactly so I might even be there for that</u>
<u n="89" who="S0390">you might even be there for that</u>
<u n="90" who="S0392">I only realised the other day</u>
<u n="91" who="S0390" trans="overlap">thank you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0392">I only realised the other day that erm I only realised the other day that I might even be there before anybody else gets there so</u>
<u n="93" who="S0390">oh I don't think you will</u>
<u n="94" who="S0392">no I know I don't mean anybody else obviously I was just</u>
<u n="95" who="S0390">now listen I'm parking I will be there very early so I can get a place to park</u>
<u n="96" who="S0392">yeah but most of the audience won't be turning up to about twenty past ten past</u>
<u n="97" who="S0390">well I know your grandma is going to be there at ten past</u>
<u n="98" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0390">and I will probably be there at seven o'clock</u>
<u n="100" who="S0390">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0391">did you examine the parking set up?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0390">oh yes you were <trunc>rig</trunc> actually <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you and I were talking at odds look that square</u>
<u n="103" who="S0391">mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0390">you're coming over the bridge</u>
<u n="105" who="S0391">uhu</u>
<u n="106" who="S0390">and you come round</u>
<u n="107" who="S0391">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0390">and there's a a road there and a road there</u>
<u n="109" who="S0391">yeah one into the houses you mean?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0390">that that doesn't go anywhere there isn't you can't I thought</u>
<u n="111" who="S0391" trans="overlap">no but you can park in there can't you?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0390">well you could if you wanted</u>
<u n="113" who="S0391">did you examine behind the pub or the church?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0390">I examined behind the church</u>
<u n="115" who="S0391">right</u>
<u n="116" who="S0390">and there are four car park</u>
<u n="117" who="S0391" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="118" who="S0390">car parking places</u>
<u n="119" who="S0391">are you going to get one of those?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0390">well I hope but if I don't I'm seeing your mum's not you know she is coming with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0391">yes</u>
<u n="122" who="S0390">what I am going to do is I go back into <anon type="place"/> and I will park at the nearest car park and maybe if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s there at night he will walk me down to the car</u>
<u n="123" who="S0391" trans="overlap">oh that will be fine</u>
<u n="124" who="S0390">that will be okay</u>
<u n="125" who="S0391">yeah that will be alright</u>
<u n="126" who="S0390">that's what I am planning anyway</u>
<u n="127" who="S0391">right right</u>
<u n="128" who="S0392">talking about those er initials you know a</u>
<u n="129" who="S0390">yes</u>
<u n="130" who="S0392">a minute ago I was saying</u>
<u n="131" who="S0390">yes</u>
<u n="132" who="S0392">well there's other things sometimes they initialise it and then they change what it stands for so if you think of a DVD</u>
<u n="133" who="S0390">yes</u>
<u n="134" who="S0392">originally it was a digital video disk but now</u>
<u n="135" who="S0390">hang on a <unclear/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0392">a digital video disk</u>
<u n="137" who="S0390">digital video disk yes</u>
<u n="138" who="S0392">that got shortened to DVD and now people say it is digital versatile disk <pause dur="long"/> so</u>
<u n="139" who="S0390">well there are different <trunc>one</trunc> now can you explain in words that I can understand</u>
<u n="140" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="141" who="S0390">about because my new thing you know er recorder</u>
<u n="142" who="S0392">yes</u>
<u n="143" who="S0390">now whatever do you call it that thing there?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0392">a DVD player</u>
<u n="145" who="S0390">a DVD player and recorder</u>
<u n="146" who="S0392">yes</u>
<u n="147" who="S0390">it says it is blue ray what does blue ray mean?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0392" trans="overlap">are you using it with a high definition television?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0390">well it is just a new television no it is not a new television it is an old television</u>
<u n="150" who="S0392">is it HD?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0390" trans="overlap">no it is not high no it is not HD</u>
<u n="152" who="S0392">well blue ray well there's no point in buying a blue ray to go with that then because blue ray is a really expensive add ons but it what it means it is like a DVD that's really high quality it has got high definition</u>
<u n="153" who="S0390">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0392">so it is like a a modern TV would high definition and this is if you want that bit more</u>
<u n="155" who="S0390" trans="overlap">I've just bought it</u>
<u n="156" who="S0392">quality</u>
<u n="157" who="S0390">have I bought the wrong one?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0392">well what you can do is wire up that one with your erm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0390">with my new one?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0392">with your new television screen</u>
<u n="161" who="S0390">that's now how I don't think that's high definition either</u>
<u n="162" who="S0392">it will be if it is new most of them these days are high <trunc>def</trunc> and erm that would mean but then blue ray the actual disks cost a bit more money as well whereas I think I don't think you can tell the difference really between blue ray and HD</u>
<u n="163" who="S0390">you can or you can't?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0392">I don't think you can you might be able to if you are really discerning</u>
<u n="165" who="S0390">now I've got DVD RAM and they won't play on the blue ray</u>
<u n="166" who="S0392">no DVD RAM is erm <pause dur="short"/> they're</u>
<u n="167" who="S0390" trans="overlap">if they put it</u>
<u n="168" who="S0392">I think they are maybe for storing data is it the ones that?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0390" trans="overlap">no I can store a program I can <trunc>sti</trunc> and play it on the other DVD recorder but the blue ray won't play it</u>
<u n="170" who="S0392">no because blue ray is only for blue ray disks which are recorded in high definition and they sort of come in a smaller packet you can see they've got a bit of blue at the top and it's a bit <trunc>smal</trunc> it is more like a square</u>
<u n="171" who="S0390">well actually any of the <trunc>pre</trunc> any of the ones I've recorded won't play on the erm blue ray but all the</u>
<u n="172" who="S0392" trans="overlap">but although the reason for that</u>
<u n="173" who="S0390">disks I've got</u>
<u n="174" who="S0392">maybe because there's two types of DVD there's DVD dash RW and DVD plus RW</u>
<u n="175" who="S0390">right okay</u>
<u n="176" who="S0392">some DVDs the dash RW they are a bit cheaper they are the same quality and they are older but they only play in some machines DVD plus RW</u>
<u n="177" who="S0390" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="178" who="S0392">they're a little a little more expensive and they only play in certain types of machines some play but I think that one there plays both of them but you will get some machines that will only play dash and some that erm play plus as well usually they play dash but some of them can't play plus</u>
<u n="179" who="S0390">right</u>
<u n="180" who="S0392">it is very rare you get one that can't play plus I mean sorry that can only play plus that's that's pretty rare</u>
<u n="181" who="S0390" trans="overlap">right okay</u>
<u n="182" who="S0392">so maybe these DVD disks you have got are plus only</u>
<u n="183" who="S0390">its its erm its a double recorder I can record onto the hard disk which I am finding is very good</u>
<u n="184" who="S0392">so that's like a built in storage inside it</u>
<u n="185" who="S0390" trans="overlap">yes it is</u>
<u n="186" who="S0392">that you record into yes</u>
<u n="187" who="S0390">and you can't record onto a DVD</u>
<u n="188" who="S0392">no</u>
<u n="189" who="S0390">any disk but you can play a disk</u>
<u n="190" who="S0392">yes but you might not be able to play the DVD plus which is <pause dur="short"/> this only applies to ones you make yourself on a computer or a recorder the ones you buy in a shop are usually playable on all machines</u>
<u n="191" who="S0390">that's exactly it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0390">exactly thank you</u>
<u n="194" who="S0392">that's a pleasure</u>
<u n="195" who="S0390">now then you know my other question?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0392">which one is this?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0390">when I send an email</u>
<u n="198" who="S0392">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0390">every time it's er</u>
<u n="200" who="S0392">I tell you what what we will do I stand above you while you are doing it and watch</u>
<u n="201" who="S0390">you will and do that?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0392">yeah or I can control your computer from here if you want I can set up and do remote access <unclear/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0390">no no no</u>
<u n="204" who="S0392">no</u>
<u n="205" who="S0390">I don't go for</u>
<u n="206" who="S0392" trans="overlap">I will come and stand over your shoulder</u>
<u n="207" who="S0390">no that's right I mean I just <vocal desc="cough"/> I just switch it off</u>
<u n="208" who="S0392">what happens?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0390">no I don't switch it off I go to the little bit and we will sort it</u>
<u n="210" who="S0392">what exactly happens?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0390">well it's okay</u>
<u n="212" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="213" who="S0390">but every time it goes dark on the screen and then I get a little message in a box that says waiting for programs to close so I leave</u>
<u n="214" who="S0392">actually that's because it doesn't like you to shut your computer down if there is something still running and if it terminates</u>
<u n="215" who="S0390" trans="overlap">well how do I know what's running?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0392">well if it terminates a program half way through it running you might lose some saved data so it waits for it to close down properly it is doing it for your favour really</u>
<u n="217" who="S0390">I don't mind that that's <trunc>some</trunc> but then I go back to my <pause dur="short"/> you know I will go back tomorrow I will switch on the email</u>
<u n="218" who="S0392">yes</u>
<u n="219" who="S0390">and it will say you did not close the the program down</u>
<u n="220" who="S0392">oh in that case always go to home page never press restore last session because if you press restore last session</u>
<u n="221" who="S0390" trans="overlap">I don't know about restore last session</u>
<u n="222" who="S0392">you should never press that because that is always a sort of fixed</u>
<u n="223" who="S0390">I don't do that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I just go straight onto the email and then little message will come up this program did not close down properly erm so and so do you wish to do <trunc>suc</trunc> do you wish</u>
<u n="224" who="S0392">yeah the options are do you want to restore your last session? in other words go to the place where it was when you switched it off the last time</u>
<u n="225" who="S0390">no it is asking me will I accept this? click here if you will accept this email</u>
<u n="226" who="S0392">is this email or internet? because</u>
<u n="227" who="S0390">it is email I am talking about the letters I know I am ignorant on these things</u>
<u n="228" who="S0392">no no it is just that I've I've had people in the past they are they are saying email email and what they mean is internet access</u>
<u n="229" who="S0390">no this is email I mean</u>
<u n="230" who="S0392" trans="overlap">but this is definitely email yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0390">with the BT phone being off</u>
<u n="232" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="233" who="S0390">it told me that it might I might have to re something reset the hub</u>
<u n="234" who="S0392">oh reset the hub</u>
<u n="235" who="S0390">do you know how to do that?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0392">through experience here I've managed to become quite proficient with these hubs</u>
<u n="237" who="S0390">I think it might be</u>
<u n="238" who="S0392" trans="overlap">I can do anything with a hub nowadays after all the problem with</u>
<u n="239" who="S0390" trans="overlap">oh well that's good but I don't think erm yesterday I went onto I did some emails and I did some erm I went onto the internet to get the tablet</u>
<u n="240" who="S0392">yes</u>
<u n="241" who="S0390">well I haven't got it properly because I oh and I will tell you something else you can do</u>
<u n="242" who="S0392">yes</u>
<u n="243" who="S0390">I haven't I got no form to register for the doctors and I haven't done it yet so you can come up and</u>
<u n="244" who="S0392">the tablet is a magazine isn't it you are not buying dodgy tablets off ebay or anything?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0390"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0392">because now you are talking about the doctors</u>
<u n="247" who="S0390">sorry</u>
<u n="248" who="S0392">that got me worried</u>
<u n="249" who="S0390">sorry sorry yeah it was the tablet I wanted your dad's article</u>
<u n="250" who="S0392" trans="overlap">I see yeah yeah</u>
<u n="251" who="S0392">on the Green Party and that so</u>
<u n="252" who="S0392">well that's on the blog so you don't need to</u>
<u n="253" who="S0390" trans="overlap">I got the blog</u>
<u n="254" who="S0392">log into that</u>
<u n="255" who="S0390">it was on a tablet blog</u>
<u n="256" who="S0392">yeah you don't need to log in for that bit</u>
<u n="257" who="S0390" trans="overlap">yeah but I do because there are erm <pause dur="short"/> things that that I read and maybe</u>
<u n="258" who="S0392" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0390">haven't saved</u>
<u n="260" who="S0392">I see yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0390">and I would like to save</u>
<u n="262" who="S0392">okay yeah and you want to register for the doctors I think I need to do that because I've tried to do it but they were having a scheduled maintenance when I wanted to do it</u>
<u n="263" who="S0390" trans="overlap">well I haven't done it properly</u>
<u n="264" who="S0392">and I've not got round to it since</u>
<u n="265" who="S0390">I couldn't <trunc>acc</trunc> <trunc>acc</trunc></u>
<u n="266" who="S0392">neither have I</u>
<u n="267" who="S0390">to be honest I haven't tried</u>
<u n="268" who="S0392">oh right</u>
<u n="269" who="S0390">so that won't that's funny me talking about the tablet</u>
<u n="270" who="S0392">and then</u>
<u n="271" who="S0390">and then immediately talking</u>
<u n="272" who="S0392">it got me worried</u>
<u n="273" who="S0390">no I am not buying listen I won't even take an Aspro or a <trunc>para</trunc> paracetamol if I don't have to</u>
<u n="274" who="S0392">yes</u>
<u n="275" who="S0390">so there's no way I am going to buy dodgy tablets on the internet</u>
<u n="276" who="S0392" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> I'm a bit like that</u>
<u n="277" who="S0390">but I am still thinking I had better get a phone and don't ask me</u>
<u n="278" who="S0392" trans="overlap">have you been using a mobile?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0390">pardon</u>
<u n="280" who="S0392">a mobile</u>
<u n="281" who="S0390">yes you know smart one of these that you can do this with and stroke it down</u>
<u n="282" who="S0392">stroke it down</u>
<u n="283" who="S0390">I mean that's what you do but erm BT eventually two days before you know I waited for what twelve days and then they put a divert on so that my <pause dur="short"/> what is it? oh the calls coming through to my BT number came through to my mobile</u>
<u n="284" who="S0392">hey that's handy isn't it?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0390">oh they've taken it off now but it was</u>
<u n="286" who="S0392">oh</u>
<u n="287" who="S0390">hey that was handy because I had it</u>
<u n="288" who="S0392">I think that</u>
<u n="289" who="S0390">now you are talking double talk now what's what's mobile in German?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0392">handy</u>
<u n="291" who="S0390">handy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0392">ah yeah that's good</u>
<u n="293" who="S0390"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0392">now what they do now is er BT do a thing called BT monophone it is like a package you can buy in and I think I didn't really understand it</u>
<u n="295" who="S0390" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0392">but I think that involves diverting calls from</u>
<u n="297" who="S0391">okay <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="298" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0391">okay folks</u>
<u n="300" who="S0392">anyway we had better go through</u>
<u n="301" who="S0390">we better go and have our</u>
<u n="302" who="S0392">so that was an interesting discussion</u>
<u n="303" who="S0390">have some sustenance</u>
<u n="304" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="305" who="S0390">and then we can say other things</u>
<u n="306" who="S0392">yeah</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
