<text id="SQ2C">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:33:04</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-01-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Science, cosmology, geek fashion, bling, food</topics>
		<activity>Talking while cooking dinner – science, cosmology, geek fashion, bling, talking about the meal.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0115">special spot</u>
<u n="2" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0115">it it gets sort of jammed in place and rides alongside it a bit like it's <unclear/> using using</u>
<u n="4" who="S0037">yeah it was really weird like I'd never seen anything</u>
<u n="5" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I remember like like <trunc>Jup</trunc> like Jupiter's Trojans live like they move at sixty degree angles in and out <pause dur="short"/> you get trapped between the um the pull of the Sun and the pull of Jupiter</u>
<u n="6" who="S0037">oh that's weird</u>
<u n="7" who="S0115">so the Trojan so the being shared by the two pulls I mean they get pulled into the same orbit</u>
<u n="8" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0115">um but they don't actually orbit Jupiter they just <trunc>h</trunc> they just stay in the same place</u>
<u n="10" who="S0037">it's so weird like <trunc>wha</trunc> I wonder what possessed them to do that like with uh an atom</u>
<u n="11" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> so it's the theory of uh uh it's it's <trunc>Ber</trunc>  it's <trunc>Ber</trunc>  uh Boer's original theory was that? That electrons orbit the atom like planets?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0037">so were they trying to do it so that they could like um prove his Einstein's laws on worked on really small scale? Is that the point?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0115">no it's nothing to do with Einstein it's uh <pause dur="short"/> it's to prove that Boer's  that Boer's  laws might be correct and it has apparently applications in uh like new types of <trunc>com</trunc> quantum computers and um</u>
<u n="14" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0115">uh some kind of <trunc>m</trunc> lasers I think</u>
<u n="16" who="S0037">in lasers?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like some kind of high speed lasers or something but</u>
<u n="18" who="S0037">I didn't read the whole article I just sort of skimmed it</u>
<u n="19" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they they don't they get the they get they jammed it in place though using like <trunc>s</trunc> it's supercooled or something <pause dur="short"/> it's not</u>
<u n="20" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah I <trunc>rem</trunc></u>
<u n="21" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they had to  they had to  fix <pause dur="short"/> it wouldn't have worked under conditions <unclear/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think they do some of that in Lancaster some of that supercooling stuff</u>
<u n="23" who="S0115">yeah well they then they blast it with like pulses and stuff and uh</u>
<u n="24" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0115">they had to <trunc>blab</trunc> to force the electron pieces to go in place <pause dur="short"/> but it you there's other articles related that explains that type that special type of atom <pause dur="short"/> the Rydberg atom or whatever it is <pause dur="short"/> other articles explaining that uh what it is um <pause dur="short"/> you you can see a diagram of the uh</u>
<u n="26" who="S0037">not enough water</u>
<u n="27" who="S0115">you can see a diagram of the uh um <trunc>l</trunc> electron clouds going round it</u>
<u n="28" who="S0037">seems there's been loads of like</u>
<u n="29" who="S0115">looks like a cross between uh an electron</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="30" who="S0037">so was that you know that stargazing thing? That Brian Cox thing?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0037">has that finished now then?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0115">I don't know uh <pause dur="short"/> I watched it last week and it was uh two or three episodes and <pause dur="short"/> I think it was just a one-off yeah it was just three episodes of uh and it had uh Dara O'Briain in it and they went out and</u>
<u n="34" who="S0037">D'you think this? Sorry</u>
<u n="35" who="S0115">it was pretty good but</u>
<u n="36" who="S0037">D'you think this aubergine's alright it looks a bit brown?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0115">I don't know what it means if it's brown uh I</u>
<u n="38" who="S0037">I'm not sure</u>
<u n="39" who="S0115">depends what you're doing it are you gonna  are you gonna  boil it or?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I was just gonna chuck it in there for the meal</u>
<u n="41" who="S0115">uh just just throw it in the pan and</u>
<u n="42" who="S0037">D'you think? Think it'll be alright? Or <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="43" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I mean I had some of it earlier <pause dur="short"/> it tastes the same as before</u>
<u n="44" who="S0037">oh right</u>
<u n="45" who="S0115">well it did to me I mean</u>
<u n="46" who="S0037">I'll just chuck it in</u>
<u n="47" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's not <trunc>brill</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> I don't really like it uncooked very much but</u>
<u n="48" who="S0037">I don't know if you're supposed to have it uncooked are you?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I dunno but</u>
<u n="50" who="S0037" trans="overlap">are you just eating things <vocal desc="laugh"/> From out of the fridge?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it's one of the things that's not like like a mushroom <pause dur="short"/> not many people eat raw mushrooms do they?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0037">no I suppose not</u>
<u n="53" who="S0115">uh <trunc>p</trunc> perhaps because like they release all the  all the  juice</u>
<u n="54" who="S0037">when they're cooked?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you know when when they're cooked so you're probably not getting the most out of it if you have it raw</u>
<u n="56" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0115">but I don't think it's one of those things that's poisonous <pause dur="short"/> or you're not supposed to have like a potato you're not really supposed to have that raw are you?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0037">are you not?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0115">I thought it</u>
<u n="60" who="S0037">are you not supposed to have them raw?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0115">potato?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you know crazy  you know crazy  Jim?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0115">no</u>
<u n="64" who="S0037">you do <pause dur="short"/> jim <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>ma</trunc> Jan and Jim</u>
<u n="65" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0037">he eats like potatoes like apples like <event desc="sound of makes crunching"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0115">wow that's really strange <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and onions which is less strange but still a bit strange</u>
<u n="69" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well onions a lot of people eat raw onions although it's a bit of a</u>
<u n="70" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but not like an apple not like</u>
<u n="71" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's a bit  it's a bit  much to eat a whole onion raw isn't it cos it sort of stings you a bit</u>
<u n="72" who="S0037">but not like a banana <trunc>sk</trunc></u>
<u n="73" who="S0115" trans="overlap">get get that <trunc>fee</trunc> get that dry feeling like a yeah like with a banana or or black tea where it gets the gets your mouth and you sort of</u>
<u n="74" who="S0037" trans="overlap">banana skin <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0115">your tongue sort of sticks to the um roof of your mouth a bit um</u>
<u n="76" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0115">and that uh so no I I I thought I read somewhere that a potato is um not not optimal when it's raw but</u>
<u n="78" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I always <pause dur="short"/> as well like you know like green bit when potatoes are green like what does that mean? Does that mean that you shouldn't eat them?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0115" trans="overlap">just they're just <trunc>ro</trunc> uh overly raw aren't they?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0037">is that right though? D'you ever get like a crisp that sometimes green?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0115" trans="overlap">ah well that's something like uh</u>
<u n="82" who="S0037">is that something different?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0115">uh no I I think that's just one that's escaped through their through the system but um sometimes they have like brown pigmentation in crisps which is um it's bitter or something and they're trying to GM genetically modify <trunc>crisp</trunc> well potatoes to get rid of the brown bit of uh pigmentation <pause dur="short"/> or something <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="84" who="S0037" trans="overlap">really? God like of all the uses for genetically modified?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0115">they'll do it they'll do a lot of things I mean <pause dur="short"/> but if it's a company then they'll provide funding um to <pause dur="short"/> I think they're probably I haven't had a bitter crisp so they probably already have done that I think</u>
<u n="86" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0115">but but when you say genetically modified I mean cos partly it's just breeding isn't I mean</u>
<u n="88" who="S0037" trans="overlap">do they not have to say on the packet?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0115" trans="overlap">if you've got a bitter batch of <pause dur="short"/> if you get potatoes um and that particular family of potatoes that you're growing uh did have a lot of this bitter pigmentation or something then you could uh obviously just not um you know not not reuse that uh configuration you know</u>
<u n="90" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I suppose yeah like genetically modifying a potato's a bit different to like genetically modifying a baby <pause dur="short"/> slightly</u>
<u n="91" who="S0115">well uh yeah for I think it needs need uh turning up maybe but</u>
<u n="92" who="S0037" trans="overlap">what do you uh want with this? Like rice or? I have yeah <pause dur="short"/> um rice or? Or like noodles or what?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0115">uh probably noodles I think</u>
<u n="94" who="S0037">where's the other? Ah where's the other pan?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0115">the uh well I can empty that cos that's uh this this one here's um there's not much there's only one round in that well not even a round just one single</u>
<u n="96" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> I looked at it this morning and I thought like oh I should've thinned that soup out earlier in the week</u>
<u n="97" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's not a problem but uh just put it on here</u>
<u n="98" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0115">and uh well that's probably a bit much for one but</u>
<u n="100" who="S0037">no well</u>
<u n="101" who="S0115">well a bit less for two though so</u>
<u n="102" who="S0037">no it's not that's normally where it goes up to like up to that line <pause dur="short"/> that's normally how much</u>
<u n="103" who="S0115">think that's quite feels like quite a big one but yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="104" who="S0037">did you like that soup? I thought it was a bit weird <pause dur="short"/> I know I made it but</u>
<u n="105" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh this one? I mean yeah well I don't</u>
<u n="106" who="S0037">dunno</u>
<u n="107" who="S0115">sort of it's sort chicken and uh <pause dur="short"/> but you put quite a bit of some herb in there was it? I think it was uh <trunc>fen</trunc></u>
<u n="108" who="S0037" trans="overlap">coriander it was cos it was</u>
<u n="109" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah that's that's fine I I like it <pause dur="short"/> I don't have a problem with with that soup at all um</u>
<u n="110" who="S0037" trans="overlap">maybe we'll use that butternut squash then for the soup next week?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0115">we didn't put an extra stock in there cos <trunc>n</trunc> normally we put in um</u>
<u n="112" who="S0037">oh no <pause dur="short"/> we'll have to <trunc>st</trunc> use them ones out of the freezer they've taken so much room</u>
<u n="113" who="S0115" trans="overlap">an extra <pause dur="short"/> the last ones we had were ham <pause dur="short"/> it was ham ones</u>
<u n="114" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> they that was so salty</u>
<u n="115" who="S0115">oh yeah well <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> two sort of uh</u>
<u n="116" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but um <pause dur="short"/> I've ordered that haggis then for for Friday <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0115">um oh you've  oh you've  put an order in for from Sainsbury's?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0115" trans="overlap">are the Sainsbury's about to deliverer a haggis or? What d'you want in this one then?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0037">uh can you put some water in him for the noodles?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0115">is this thing turned up?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0037">yeah I dunno <trunc>d</trunc> it's just <pause dur="short"/> I think it's cos we've got since we've got that new pan it's like <pause dur="short"/> cos it's a bigger pan it takes ages</u>
<u n="123" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I would say it certainly takes longer to</u>
<u n="124" who="S0037">I said happy birthday to uh Claire on Facebook today <pause dur="short"/> d'you wanna <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="125" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="126" who="S0037">you'll have to maybe</u>
<u n="127" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="128" who="S0037">I know you don't check it very often</u>
<u n="129" who="S0115">right <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0037">no no I mean <pause dur="short"/> don't have to <pause dur="short"/> it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s birthday actually last yesterday or the day before</u>
<u n="131" who="S0115">oh was it? Um</u>
<u n="132" who="S0037">it's</u>
<u n="133" who="S0115">I don't know there's there's a few people round I know aren't there?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0037" trans="overlap">there's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s is on</u>
<u n="135" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0037">Monday I think <pause dur="short"/> something like that <pause dur="short"/> it's useful that bin at me nana bought isn't it?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there's the what the pan? What?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0037">no like the little box</u>
<u n="139" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I like the box yeah that's good</u>
<u n="140" who="S0037">I have to transfer them out of there</u>
<u n="141" who="S0115">yeah you got a lot of uh recipes in it and</u>
<u n="142" who="S0037">one of the problems is like I I get them sometimes I just get them off the internet and then make then and then forget where I've got them from so</u>
<u n="143" who="S0115">right <pause dur="short"/> I didn't use to <trunc>u</trunc> really use recipes I just used to throw everything in in uh</u>
<u n="144" who="S0037">I think they're good for like if you run out of ideas so like I just tend to cook the same things like all all <trunc>o</trunc> over and over again</u>
<u n="145" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh I think you learn <pause dur="short"/> you learn from them don't you?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0037">I think I've cut too many carrots <pause dur="short"/> um yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0115">uh</u>
<u n="148" who="S0037">oh yeah anyway I was gonna say about that Brian Cox thing?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0115">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0037">like the funniest thing about that I thought was like when they were like Here we are live in Devon and we're gonna turn all the lights off <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> And then it was like the cloudiest night of the year</u>
<u n="151" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="152" who="S0037">it wouldn't have mattered if all the lights had been on</u>
<u n="153" who="S0115">oh yeah uh <pause dur="short"/> I would've <pause dur="short"/> it would've been very good if that had worked cos you'd have <pause dur="short"/> but it seemed like <pause dur="short"/> it seemed a bit pointless actually</u>
<u n="154" who="S0037">it's quite clear here though the skies and I I think they're quite good <pause dur="short"/> although d'you remember in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="155" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they're alright <pause dur="short"/> not as good as <anon type="place"/> but</u>
<u n="156" who="S0037">D'you remember in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0115">um which time?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0037" trans="overlap">when we were when we went on that walk and through the forest and that <pause dur="short"/> but the bit before that when like you could see like all the Milky Way and stuff</u>
<u n="159" who="S0115">yeah um</u>
<u n="160" who="S0037">ooh ooh turn that off</u>
<u n="161" who="S0115">it is good to be able to see that uh <pause dur="short"/> I'm not really very good at recognizing what the uh constellations are but</u>
<u n="162" who="S0037">na <pause dur="short"/> I know like three <pause dur="short"/> like The Plough <pause dur="short"/> the Disputed North Star <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0115">the</u>
<u n="164" who="S0037">uh</u>
<u n="165" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> north one is just to follow from uh The Plough and then</u>
<u n="166" who="S0037">Orion's Belt and that's about it</u>
<u n="167" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I can't <trunc>reme</trunc> uh yeah there's probably <pause dur="short"/> I mean uh some familiar shapes but uh</u>
<u n="168" who="S0037" trans="overlap">those ones what's that one that's like a square that's a famous one as well</u>
<u n="169" who="S0115">is that the Pegasus that's a big square?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah I think so <pause dur="short"/> yeah because they say that was what they were doing on that programme like counting how many stars you could see inside like the Square of Pegasus</u>
<u n="171" who="S0115">oh yeah to measure how</u>
<u n="172" who="S0037" trans="overlap">there's like a light pollution measurement thing</u>
<u n="173" who="S0115">yeah wasn't there that that programme was good cos uh they sort of did a lot of uh <trunc>astronom</trunc> astronomical cosmological stuff like they talked about black holes on one of them and uh <pause dur="short"/> that was kind of interesting</u>
<u n="174" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think <pause dur="short"/> cos it was quite good as well it wasn't <pause dur="short"/> cos sometimes I think some of the science stuff like is a bit too <pause dur="short"/> what you doing?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I just turned it up</u>
<u n="176" who="S0037">oh right <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> I think some of the science things are a bit too um like babyish or like basic?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0115">yeah and that that didn't</u>
<u n="178" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like This is the human body like Robert Winston like pointing to an arm going This is an arm like</u>
<u n="179" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="180" who="S0037">it's just a bit oh yawn yawn sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> but that this one was quite good <pause dur="short"/> I thought it was quite good</u>
<u n="181" who="S0115">yeah well it was going it was going into quite a lot of detail but they had  they had  uh Brian Cox <trunc>d</trunc> uh this series doing all the all his theories and or theoretical cosmology and stuff but then there was uh Dara O'Briain was there to sort of balance that with the comedy end a bit <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="182" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I bet like <pause dur="short"/> but I think like <pause dur="short"/> I bet real like real physicists if you like get really annoyed by him <pause dur="short"/> d'you not think?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0115">real <trunc>physi</trunc> you think are not uh?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you know like real inverted commas physicists</u>
<u n="185" who="S0115" trans="overlap">probably some of them are I mean like <pause dur="short"/> they might <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="186" who="S0037">you know when he's just like look at the stars like</u>
<u n="187" who="S0115" trans="overlap">they might think he's not as good <trunc>a</trunc> as they are cos he spends it he's more sort of for publicizing in trying to advertise <pause dur="short"/> trying to get people to become uh</u>
<u n="188" who="S0037" trans="overlap">scientists?</u>
<u n="189" who="S0115">to become um cosmologists <pause dur="short"/> it's at the back</u>
<u n="190" who="S0037" trans="overlap">hey where's the honey? Have you seen it? Where? In the back at the top or?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0115">no at the back</u>
<u n="192" who="S0037">oh</u>
<u n="193" who="S0115">behind that cabbage</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="194" who="S0037">sorry <pause dur="short"/> yeah but</u>
<u n="195" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but so I don't really know <pause dur="short"/> uh but I mean we've got that book A Brief History of Time haven't we? And <pause dur="short"/> and that's a bit sort of uh</u>
<u n="196" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh that's so hard though</u>
<u n="197" who="S0115">some of the stuff you don't know how true it is and um <pause dur="short"/> I remember talking about black holes actually on the show</u>
<u n="198" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's the thing with anything <pause dur="short"/> anything that's theoretical though it's just like <pause dur="short"/> how <trunc>w</trunc> it's just an idea isn't it really?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0115">well I don't know <pause dur="short"/> uh it's hard to sort of see how much is um definitely true and how much is um conjecture and how much uh is <trunc>w</trunc> how to what extent is it true sort of</u>
<u n="200" who="S0037">mhm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0115">I mean to what extent is it backed up by uh findings <pause dur="short"/> who believes in it and who doesn't? Well problem with  problem with  the <trunc>co</trunc> cosmology is that they have to fit everything in with their  with their  theories with the model the Standard Model</u>
<u n="202" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0115">and everything <pause dur="short"/> they've gotta fit all the um <pause dur="short"/> all their observations have to fit into the the sort of complex network of uh</u>
<u n="204" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0115">uh theories and um rules that they've got so <pause dur="short"/> they may be a bit restricted in some ways um in what they how they can explain things <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="206" who="S0037">I think it's quite</u>
<u n="207" who="S0115"><trunc>I</trunc> it's <trunc>ha</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> but it doesn't cos physics doesn't fully work together cos uh <pause dur="short"/> cos the sort of the small uh quantum physics doesn't fully um go together with the the larger Einstein uh relativity</u>
<u n="208" who="S0037" trans="overlap">big physics yeah</u>
<u n="209" who="S0115">so that uh <pause dur="short"/> um they they have to kind of just uh come up with ways to try and unify them</u>
<u n="210" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0115">um but at the moment they they don't know <pause dur="short"/> so that's a big <pause dur="short"/> that uh there was a lot of mysteries there then a lot to be found out <pause dur="short"/> um so that's why they need people like Cox to get people to join up sign up and uh um start theorizing and</u>
<u n="212" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I suppose he's promoting it <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> getting them into <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm not sure like</u>
<u n="213" who="S0115">it's like the big  the big  bang the big big bang theory it's a bit like uh um that's sort of really really theoretical actually a lot of the stuff they talk about isn't it?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0037">well it's quite good though I suppose for making it for popularizing it</u>
<u n="215" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like yeah <pause dur="short"/> and um <pause dur="short"/> the</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="216" who="S0115">the all the characters are funny I mean that's it's just funny and people don't watch that really for</u>
<u n="217" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0115">oh d'you mean uh the big bang or the</u>
<u n="219" who="S0037">hm?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0115">do d'you mean Big Bang Theory or d'you mean uh</u>
<u n="221" who="S0037">what d'you mean?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0115">Cox's programme <pause dur="short"/> big</u>
<u n="223" who="S0037">oh well I was talking about big <trunc>ba</trunc> big bang but yeah both of them really</u>
<u n="224" who="S0115">big Bang <pause dur="short"/> but I dunno if that popularizes physics but it</u>
<u n="225" who="S0037">oh no science I suppose</u>
<u n="226" who="S0115">sort of <pause dur="short"/> yeah I suppose</u>
<u n="227" who="S0037">and being a geek like</u>
<u n="228" who="S0115">yeah <trunc>bi</trunc> geekiness it popularizes sort of <pause dur="short"/> sort of glamorizes being geeky doesn't it? Uh <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>sel</trunc> Sheldon</u>
<u n="229" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but that really came in though didn't it like? Like that whole um <pause dur="short"/> like recently all the cool kids or whatever so I'm told uh been wearing like you know like those glasses really came in didn't they?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0115" trans="overlap">who's these cool kids? What? Glasses?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0037">like last year <pause dur="short"/> You know those like they're like National Health glasses <pause dur="short"/> jarvis Cocker kind of Graham Coxon</u>
<u n="232" who="S0115">bit sort of square glasses?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0037">you know they're really black like black rimmed thick ones <pause dur="short"/> like geek</u>
<u n="234" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well my dad's got some <trunc>s</trunc> funny glasses but they're more sort of</u>
<u n="235" who="S0037">no not not not not exactly like that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="236" who="S0115">big ones like the <trunc>Deir</trunc> Deirdre Barlow glasses</u>
<u n="237" who="S0037">those are like Miami Vice glasses <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0115">um or Ben Elton from the eighties <pause dur="short"/> ben Elton with his  with his  jacket rolled up and uh</u>
<u n="239" who="S0037">Deirdre Barlows <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0115">you know there's his rolled up  rolled up  jacket</u>
<u n="241" who="S0037">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> blazer yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0115">um uh and uh big Deirdre Barlow glasses and</u>
<u n="243" who="S0037">Deirdre Barlow <pause dur="short"/> deirdre Barlow's still in it I think</u>
<u n="244" who="S0115">yeah does she still have the same?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Ken Barlow is <pause dur="short"/> ken Barlow's been in right from the start you know? He's just got like one thing on his CV like Coronation Street <pause dur="short"/> but um</u>
<u n="246" who="S0115">he doesn't need to have a <trunc>s</trunc> CV or <pause dur="short"/> it's just Ken</u>
<u n="247" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Just a picture of his face?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's just Ken Barlow with a signature across his photograph</u>
<u n="249" who="S0037" trans="overlap">signed photo?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0115">you know he doesn't  he doesn't  really <pause dur="short"/> I mean people would <pause dur="short"/> he doesn't have to <pause dur="short"/> he wouldn't have to get another job unless they  unless they  discontinued um</u>
<u n="251" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Coronation Street?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0115">that probably wouldn't happen within his sort of working uh working life I would have thought</u>
<u n="253" who="S0037">did? I've told you haven't I that me</u>
<u n="254" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Cos until all the viewers sort of gradually begin to die out I don't think there'll be any sign of uh the end of Coronation Street but</u>
<u n="255" who="S0037">I've told you haven't I like that that the uh that me nana used to have a picture of like all of her grandchildren and the cast of Coronation Street?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0115">signed?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like not not one picture <pause dur="short"/> like a picture of me a picture of our Tom a picture of all my cousins <pause dur="short"/> and just nestling in with those a picture of the cast of Coronation Street like <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> If they were similar of similar importance</u>
<u n="258" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That's uh Phyllis isn't it?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0037" trans="overlap">she's bonkers <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> bonkers</u>
<u n="260" who="S0115">so she preferred <pause dur="short"/> but she also watched Eastenders didn't she?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0037">she preferred Corrie and Emmerdale <pause dur="short"/> but not <trunc>w</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> like she didn't like it that they were making it all like sexy and that</u>
<u n="262" who="S0115" trans="overlap">neighbours? Well older people don't normally like that sort of thing do they?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="264" who="S0115">I mean <pause dur="short"/> not on the TV</u>
<u n="265" who="S0037">I mean she did like Big Brother and that</u>
<u n="266" who="S0115">yeah I mean that could be filthy couldn't it I mean in terms of the language and <pause dur="short"/> well just everything about it really is uh</u>
<u n="267" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0115">I mean it's so sort of like it's sort of breaking a lot of conventions in in decency you know decency's just gone hasn't it sort of on on on that I mean <pause dur="short"/> but uh</u>
<u n="269" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I haven't watched it like for ages really</u>
<u n="270" who="S0115">that was uh <unclear/> shocking thing</u>
<u n="271" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but anyway I was saying so them glasses you know the you know which ones I mean? The really black ones?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0115">uh National Health glasses you said <pause dur="short"/> so</u>
<u n="273" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so like they <trunc>w</trunc> got really popular again <pause dur="short"/> and also like like <pause dur="short"/> as a bit of a cross uh</u>
<u n="274" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is that just for? Amongst um</u>
<u n="275" who="S0037">I dunno like cool people</u>
<u n="276" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is it  is it  that <trunc>Chri</trunc> was it is his name from uh uh the the IT Crowd um <pause dur="short"/> his name's something Ayounde?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0037">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> he was the Footlights thing here wasn't he?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is his name um Richard or Chris or something?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah yeah Richard <pause dur="short"/> the other one's called Chris O'Dowd</u>
<u n="280" who="S0115">so I think he wears a pair of thick-rimmed uh glasses black glasses</u>
<u n="281" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he does yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0115">so um he might've helped that's it</u>
<u n="283" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and also</u>
<u n="284" who="S0115">so it's become more popular to be geeky but it's also becoming more popular to be a criminal I think as well so there's this well there's always a</u>
<u n="285" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="286" who="S0115">you know the it's not  it's not  sort of</u>
<u n="287" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and <pause dur="short"/> but <trunc>als</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> also those like jumpers you know like the Kurt Cobain jumpers?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0115">yeah I think it's <trunc>prob</trunc> probably more popular to look sort of grungy or whatever uh</u>
<u n="289" who="S0037" trans="overlap">loads of them in Primark</u>
<u n="290" who="S0115">which which um? Were?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I remember like sitting on Facebook like our Amy had written something like No you're not cool you're just a slag in a rubbish jumper <vocal desc="laugh"/> like <pause dur="short"/> you know all those like kind of you know girls who wanna be like <pause dur="short"/> You know in the town?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that's the the sort of um <pause dur="short"/> you mean the the sort of holey gungy green jumpers</u>
<u n="293" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah like looking really distressed and like Hey man this is from a charity shop <pause dur="short"/> No it's not it's from Primark <pause dur="short"/> You know what I mean?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0115">fair enough</u>
<u n="295" who="S0037">there's <trunc>s</trunc> that amused me <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> it's quite funny</u>
<u n="296" who="S0115">although I prefer jumpers to sort of some of the other things that you know local people wear <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="297" who="S0037">what d'you mean?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0115">more sort of</u>
<u n="299" who="S0037">tracksuits and that?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0115">well them sorts of <trunc>w</trunc> bling like with clowns on it <pause dur="short"/> and stuff</u>
<u n="301" who="S0037">ah I love them <pause dur="short"/> they're hilarious like <pause dur="short"/> the ones <pause dur="short"/> like from a bit of Elizabeth Duke <vocal desc="laugh"/> D'you know Elizabeth Duke?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="303" who="S0037">maybe <trunc>y</trunc> maybe <trunc>un</trunc> like maybe that that that's just <trunc>show</trunc> I'm showing my chav self there</u>
<u n="304" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I <trunc>do</trunc> I think  I think  you might've mentioned it before but uh</u>
<u n="305" who="S0037">Elizabeth Duke uh the jewellery range <trunc>fr</trunc> by Argos</u>
<u n="306" who="S0115">yeah I think you've mentioned that</u>
<u n="307" who="S0037">and like <pause dur="short"/> they have you know like nine carrot gold teddy bears with jewels <pause dur="short"/> and like rubies for eyes and like sapphires for <pause dur="short"/> You know</u>
<u n="308" who="S0115">better better to stick with the jumper I think</u>
<u n="309" who="S0037">ay?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0115">better to stick with the jumper</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="311" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="312" who="S0037">I never make enough sauce</u>
<u n="313" who="S0115">they they have much uh bling then?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0037">oh loads <pause dur="short"/> sovereigns you know Um <pause dur="short"/> oh where was I? Oh I was in  I was in  New York Matt and I saw like um <pause dur="short"/> they had loads of stuff there on one of the streets near where the office was <pause dur="short"/> um they sold like loadsa like fake stuff <pause dur="short"/> oh can I have a bit of that? Sold loadsa like fake stuff and um <pause dur="short"/> one of the things that they sold then in this window was like loads of like um that <trunc>h</trunc> sort of horrible bling like massive chains with like things on the end <trunc>al</trunc> all made out jewels <pause dur="short"/> and one of the things they had was Jesus's face <pause dur="short"/> like made out of jewels <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Well now you reminded me of the the that Mexican um</u>
<u n="316" who="S0037">thank you</u>
<u n="317" who="S0115">that programme about Mexico that I watched uh</u>
<u n="318" who="S0037">which one?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> well it's sort of uh</u>
<u n="320" who="S0037">ah the one about the dead?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0115" trans="overlap">some aspect of Mexican culture where they they have a festival of the dead or something like that <pause dur="short"/> or they have like shrines to the dead but they sort of have a lot of um <pause dur="short"/> yeah a lot of models a lot of uh</u>
<u n="322" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0115">are they called graven images or something um uh?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0037">I don't know</u>
<u n="325" who="S0115">various uh  various uh  little um</u>
<u n="326" who="S0037">ah I know what you mean that's I can't remember the word</u>
<u n="327" who="S0115" trans="overlap">little uh idol <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>I</trunc> not not exactly idol that's a sort of a biblical word but yeah but <trunc>i</trunc> images basically of uh of people and um</u>
<u n="328" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh it's on the tip of me tongue</u>
<u n="329" who="S0115">so there's a bit of a similarity with that I think</u>
<u n="330" who="S0037">yeah like Jesus's face made out of jewels though like how stupid?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0115">they uh <vocal desc="laugh"/> But <trunc>d</trunc> can you get  can you get  a stick of rock with uh with Jesus on it I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="332" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I can get you one for Christmas if you want one you know? From the Vatican maybe aye</u>
<u n="333" who="S0115">mm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0037">they have all that kind of stuff there</u>
<u n="335" who="S0115">have you ever found the one of those uh you know the face of the Virgin Mary in a  in a in a  carrot or something like?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0037">not not as yet</u>
<u n="337" who="S0115">maybe you weren't looking hard enough or</u>
<u n="338" who="S0037">I know I'll have to keep me eyes peeled</u>
<u n="339" who="S0037">what's that thing called though that's that's the name for it when you see faces in things?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0115">oh yeah um I've forgotten what that's called</u>
<u n="341" who="S0037">where did I read that?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0115">I told you about it <pause dur="short"/> it was in the New Scientist</u>
<u n="343" who="S0037">oh right</u>
<u n="344" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> that was in on a uh thing about um sort of explaining the unexplained with science</u>
<u n="345" who="S0037" trans="overlap">excuse me <pause dur="short"/> oh that's right no I read it  no I read it  it's in  it's in  the bathroom</u>
<u n="346" who="S0115" trans="overlap">which is called uh para something</u>
<u n="347" who="S0037" trans="overlap">about <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos they were saying about those like glowing orbs were just actually like um mist steam and that kind of thing? On the lens?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah that's um <pause dur="short"/> yeah that's there was a term for that when when you think</u>
<u n="349" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't believe in any of that sort of supernatural stuff</u>
<u n="350" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so there was yeah they were talking about uh photos and and where you see yeah uh they had say maybe ten different uh effects that people mistake for</u>
<u n="351" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0115">ghosts or some other kind of um</u>
<u n="353" who="S0037">I remember</u>
<u n="354" who="S0115">supernatural uh being and uh there were different tricks and they include things like uh <trunc>go</trunc> uh uh like if you got a glass window in front and and it would create a kind of a phantom sort of figure on the in the glass and then</u>
<u n="355" who="S0037" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> reflective the photographer in it?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0115">the other one is if you got water on the lens it can create little little spots which can shine and look like uh a</u>
<u n="357" who="S0037">they're supposed to be orbs of energy</u>
<u n="358" who="S0115" trans="overlap">orbs of energy or UFOs or something</u>
<u n="359" who="S0037">oh me mam believes in all that kind of bollocks like</u>
<u n="360" who="S0115" trans="overlap">also saw a programme around the same time about uh <pause dur="short"/> that that was the Cox and uh <pause dur="short"/> that was the Cox programme actually</u>
<u n="361" who="S0037">oh when he was <unclear/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the where they did the little little thing about UFOs</u>
<u n="363" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh cos they <trunc>d</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> that's right <pause dur="short"/> that's right</u>
<u n="364" who="S0115">and um sort of uh they obviously Professor Brian Cox is a bit sceptical about UFOs</u>
<u n="365" who="S0037">oh right of course</u>
<u n="366" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh the the existence I mean</u>
<u n="367" who="S0037" trans="overlap">D'you want any green beans?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0115">I think if you're intelligent enough to get to Earth</u>
<u n="369" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0115">then you'd be intelligent enough not to reveal yourself in a clumsy sort of wabbling uh nineteen fifties looking black and white saucer</u>
<u n="371" who="S0037">should buy more <pause dur="short"/> should order some more green beans <pause dur="short"/> will you write  will you write  it on the list?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0115">uh what?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0037">I've had like an annoying sort of thing all day like <pause dur="short"/> You know when you're talking and you can feel like your throat clogging up?</u>
<u n="374" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="375" who="S0037">and then you've gotta go like that?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0115">oh you mean phlegm</u>
<u n="377" who="S0037">lovely <pause dur="short"/> yes I mean phlegm <vocal desc="laugh"/> But you know what I mean? I was on the phone earlier and I was like <vocal desc="cough"/> every <trunc>f</trunc> like few minutes I was like I'm really sorry about this <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="378" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no I didn't know that uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah well if you  if you  mean something's gone down the wrong way</u>
<u n="379" who="S0037">maybe it was after that like choking fit that I had <trunc>u</trunc> other day</u>
<u n="380" who="S0115">A choking fit <vocal desc="laugh"/> uh</u>
<u n="381" who="S0037">I was like standing over the uh corridor <pause dur="short"/> I'd ate something out the pan and I was like <vocal desc="cough"/> like for ages and ages</u>
<u n="382" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> that's um</u>
<u n="383" who="S0037">I was like The Heimlich <pause dur="short"/> doctor Heimlich <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> And and <trunc>y</trunc> you you that was when you were making that soup <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="385" who="S0037">I know</u>
<u n="386" who="S0115">the the chicken soup <pause dur="short"/> you'd you'd made the soup</u>
<u n="387" who="S0037">choked on soup</u>
<u n="388" who="S0115">and then tested it and then nearly killed yourself with the soup <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="389" who="S0037">doctor Heimlich <pause dur="short"/> have you seen that Eddie Izzard sketch?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> I think so <pause dur="short"/> I think I've seen almost all of Eddie Izzard</u>
<u n="391" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and he's like trying to invent something and he's like Ah I will invent a manoeuvre <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0037">D'you remember?</u>
<u n="394" who="S0115">well he's just  he's just  sitting in his studio artist's studio?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0037">no he's a doctor doctor Heimlich</u>
<u n="396" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and uh oh he he was thinking</u>
<u n="397" who="S0037">he was trying to invent something um like he and he's had a lot of money but <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0115">to get  to get  oh yeah to get uh fame?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> exactly</u>
<u n="400" who="S0115">just uh</u>
<u n="401" who="S0037"><unclear/></u>
<u n="402" who="S0115">did you say that it's quite brutal the Heimlich and that you can end up with a broken rib?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0037">oh yeah but I think it doesn't matter <pause dur="short"/> you'd happily break all your ribs rather than choke wouldn't you? Well most people would</u>
<u n="404" who="S0115">suppose so yeah <pause dur="short"/> I guess but if you were the  if you were the  person doing the manoeuvre you you might be afraid that you didn't want to like break a rib you know cos it might have a do something</u>
<u n="405" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you don't <pause dur="short"/> you don't do it with children</u>
<u n="406" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0037">with children you you just like dangle them upside down</u>
<u n="408" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="409" who="S0037">actually if they're little enough you're supposed to</u>
<u n="410" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so maybe that would work if it was a small person as well</u>
<u n="411" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you're supposed to hold them by the legs with one hand and then like wallop them on the back with the other hand</u>
<u n="412" who="S0115">right <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> okay I'll bear that in mind so if you've got a choking child grab the child and and shake it upside down</u>
<u n="413" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like if they're a baby <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> whack them hardly a <trunc>far</trunc> firmly in between the shoulder blades</u>
<u n="414" who="S0115">it's the same procedure as if you'd trapped something inside an inanimate which you could pick up</u>
<u n="415" who="S0037" trans="overlap">this is very very true <vocal desc="laugh"/> Or if you're trying to get some sauce out of a tomato ketchup bottle</u>
<u n="416" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> yeah or although that's normally you would  you would  hit it on the base but</u>
<u n="417" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No that doesn't work <pause dur="short"/> I've I've have you tried that?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0115" trans="overlap">is there not?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0037">well it does work eventually but hitting it on  hitting it on  a side to side motion as opposed to an up and down motion is much more effective</u>
<u n="420" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah you just whack it <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> normally I would shake it actually or get a knife and the knife will uh do some kind of scientific process that I don't know the name of and pull draw it down</u>
<u n="421" who="S0037">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> suction?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="423" who="S0037">some sort of suction surely</u>
<u n="424" who="S0115">it's not <trunc>i</trunc> it's some it's to do with the <trunc>war</trunc> the the ketchup following the the knife or something</u>
<u n="425" who="S0037">oh right</u>
<u n="426" who="S0115">or <trunc>i</trunc> or not <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> could be</u>
<u n="427" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ooh I've got a bit of a headache <pause dur="short"/> ah still a bit crispy <pause dur="short"/> were you supposed to throw it on the wall? Hooray must be done <pause dur="short"/> that's what they say isn't it?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0115">it's really sticky <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0037">yeah I've just really cooked it <vocal desc="laugh"/> I've overcooked it so it's like glue pasta <pause dur="short"/> still tastes a bit hard to me</u>
<u n="430" who="S0115">so d'you wanna mix the</u>
<u n="431" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0115">noodles in with the vegetables?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> wish we had a proper draining thing</u>
<u n="434" who="S0115">need that <pause dur="short"/> you can use a <unclear/> for what <trunc>w</trunc> what were you what sort of drainer would've</u>
<u n="435" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I I meant like for the dishes not for like draining these noodles</u>
<u n="436" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah the uh a drainer yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0037">oh I've made too many haven't I?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> no that's alright</u>
<u n="439" who="S0037">can leave some for tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> or later <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="440" who="S0115">if if they make it through to tomorrow yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I've made some extra sauce <pause dur="short"/> I never make enough I just can't seem to get it right in me mind how much sauce to make</u>
<u n="442" who="S0115">so this is uh you got what uh honey and soy?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0037">mm <pause dur="short"/> soy five spice</u>
<u n="444" who="S0115">mix in sauce there</u>
<u n="445" who="S0037">bit of lemon juice <pause dur="short"/> bit of chilli</u>
<u n="446" who="S0115" trans="overlap">should put put a bit of uh bit of water in with that or?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0037">if you want to there's some juice in the fist</u>
<u n="448" who="S0115">right</u>
<u n="449" who="S0037">so <pause dur="short"/> could put that in</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="450" who="S0037">I'm aware of making it too runny though cos that's the <trunc>prob</trunc></u>
<u n="451" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no I don't think that would happen with the uh</u>
<u n="452" who="S0037">noodles?</u>
<u n="453" who="S0115" trans="overlap">with this one cos think there's a lot of noodles so like they'd absorb it</u>
<u n="454" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0115">un and it's a</u>
<u n="456" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it is a bit of a habit of mine though <pause dur="short"/> there's always like a watery sort of</u>
<u n="457" who="S0115">well no I think <trunc>th</trunc> that's your style isn't it? You like to make a watery watery sauce</u>
<u n="458" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> it's not supposed to my <trunc>st</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's not supposed be my style <pause dur="short"/> it's just an unfortunate</u>
<u n="459" who="S0115" trans="overlap">sort of a broth <pause dur="short"/> like a <trunc>b</trunc> like a <trunc>b</trunc> a minestrone like a a cross between a minestrone and uh like spaghetti Bolognese</u>
<u n="460" who="S0037">ah it's not supposed to be though <pause dur="short"/> see what this tastes like</u>
<u n="461" who="S0115">but in this case think the pan's hot so it's gonna evaporate <pause dur="short"/> well so we watched uh</u>
<u n="462" who="S0037">mm <pause dur="short"/> tastes nice</u>
<u n="463" who="S0115">it's <trunc>y</trunc> you been <trunc>w</trunc> you'd been wanting to watch Masterchef hadn't you so?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0037">I know it was good</u>
<u n="465" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="466" who="S0037">tonight it's the thingy bob challenge where they cook like um</u>
<u n="467" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that was <pause dur="short"/> oh is it it is on again <pause dur="short"/> it's always on again</u>
<u n="468" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's always on it's great <pause dur="short"/> it's where they cook like um</u>
<u n="469" who="S0115">I think they're gonna replace like BBC News with uh like BBC Food News or something</u>
<u n="470" who="S0037">aha I think that would be <trunc>f</trunc> perfectly fine</u>
<u n="471" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um</u>
<u n="472" who="S0037">they're gonna do like a mass cooking challenge tonight where they've gotta cook for like soldiers or like a group of whoever like a big group of people anyway <pause dur="short"/> d'you know what I need? I need some tongs like <pause dur="short"/> it gets on my nerves</u>
<u n="473" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="474" who="S0037">maybe I'm just</u>
<u n="475" who="S0115">ah fork and spoon <vocal desc="laugh"/> Just use a fork and spoon</u>
<u n="476" who="S0037">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/> Thanks</u>
<u n="477" who="S0115"><unclear/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0037">I don't wanna use a fork and spoon</u>
<u n="479" who="S0115">yeah if you  if you  use a fork and spoon you're sort of putting a sort of clasp the the uh the spoon and the fork together</u>
<u n="480" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> No you can't <pause dur="short"/> you just want to say that over and over again <pause dur="short"/> I actually didn't make as much as I thought <pause dur="short"/> I think it just looked more than that</u>
<u n="481" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh <pause dur="short"/> so I used to do that <pause dur="short"/> uh you could do it with a salad you get get your fork get your spoon</u>
<u n="482" who="S0037">no I'm not very good at it <pause dur="short"/> careful this pan's hot</u>
<u n="483" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> sort of get them but using them a little bit like together in one hand a bit like where where you use like a</u>
<u n="484" who="S0037">chop <pause dur="short"/> chopstick?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0115" trans="overlap">chopstick and then sort of grab the uh item with the fork and spoon</u>
<u n="486" who="S0037">ah <pause dur="short"/> thanks very much <pause dur="short"/> which one do you want? This one?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0115">uh <trunc>ei</trunc> either I think they're quite similar aren't they?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0037">there's two fish <pause dur="short"/> ooh sorry can you move that off the hob? Bits of fish like they always I always seem to defrost two where one's like a mighty whale and one's like a goldfish size <vocal desc="laugh"/> <vocal desc="misc"/> like a <pause dur="short"/> never mind <pause dur="short"/> right shall we? D'you wanna eat this?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0115">yep yep uh thanks for making it</u>
<u n="490" who="S0037">no probs d'you wanna?</u>
</body>
</text>
