<text id="SQ2W">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:30:21</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-28</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0439 S0441</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Bedroom and Kitchen</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>sport, food, friends, catch-up, ex-boyfriends, family, work, house</topics>
		<activity>Catch-up with housemate after holiday</activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, requestion, inviting, announcing, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0439">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern - Non-accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Project Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0441">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridgeshire - Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Mental Health Nurse</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0439">we have to like move out of this house</u>
<u n="2" who="S0441">no <unclear>we just</unclear></u>
<u n="3" who="S0439" trans="overlap">no no not move out of the house we have this viewing on this Saturday? <pause dur="short"/> it's really inconvenient <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0441"><unclear/> <unclear>you</unclear> can call them back and say so</u>
<u n="5" who="S0439">oh er are you here this weekend?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0439">oh I am here it's just <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s here as well that's all</u>
<u n="8" who="S0441">oh</u>
<u n="9" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0441">is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear>here all</unclear> weekend?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0439">er no I don't think so I think she's only here gonna be here on the Saturday</u>
<u n="12" who="S0441">okay</u>
<u n="13" who="S0439">that's annoying</u>
<u n="14" who="S0441">we can change it if you want?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0439">no it's fine it's just annoying just so soon</u>
<u n="16" who="S0441">I know but that but she did say that if they can find someone then we can <unclear/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0439">oh I see that'd be better wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0441">yeah unless we say <unclear/> <unclear>can't make it today but if they want to move in they can</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> or we could ring the estate agent and just say that we're happy to <unclear>move out in December</unclear></u>
<u n="19" who="S0439">yeah before Christmas <pause dur="short"/> yeah that'd be okay</u>
<u n="20" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="22" who="S0441">as long as it's basically as long as she's got someone to pay basically <unclear>the rent it doesn't matter</unclear></u>
<u n="23" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0441">she doesn't mind who who it is <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0439">yeah yeah yeah fair enough will they have they put the rent back up do you know? don't know? it's eight hundred not that it's much extra is it? but</u>
<u n="26" who="S0441">I'd imagine she probably would</u>
<u n="27" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I think they probably just gave it to us because we wanted it</u>
<u n="28" who="S0441">I don't think they'd had much interest last time did they?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0439">no so <trunc>ha</trunc></u>
<u n="30" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0439">so she's got one viewing this weekend?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0441">no there's like loads of people that wanna come and see it</u>
<u n="33" who="S0439">good <vocal desc="laugh"/> didn't <unclear>realise it was that</unclear> popular</u>
<u n="34" who="S0441">neither did I because the woman that we that showed us round said that we were the only ones didn't she?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0441">like she hadn't had anyone else</u>
<u n="37" who="S0439">mm okay well</u>
<u n="38" who="S0441">weird</u>
<u n="39" who="S0439">yeah that's fine I think we'll just have to we'll just we'll have to make sure that they know that the <trunc>f</trunc> some of the furniture is ours and some of it's</u>
<u n="40" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0439">so they'd have to get themselves</u>
<u n="42" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0439">yeah no if they wanted to move in earlier I guess then they could move in earlier couldn't they?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0441">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0439">mm yeah</u>
<u n="46" who="S0441">we could pay December's rent and then</u>
<u n="47" who="S0439">yeah cos what I'm <trunc>conv</trunc> I think that that'd mean November'll be the last payment wouldn't it? November the sixteenth would be the last <pause dur="short"/> pay we wouldn't pay on December the sixteenth</u>
<u n="48" who="S0441">well er er we'd probably move out before <unclear/> the sixteenth</u>
<u n="49" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah that works for me <pause dur="short"/> cos that's still like the last week before Christmas and I'm not working the week after so I don't need to be here</u>
<u n="50" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="51" who="S0439">means I can find somewhere to <trunc>g</trunc> move into after Christmas</u>
<u n="52" who="S0441">yeah I guess cos you'll be away anyway won't you?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0439">yeah be away for two weeks so yeah that works fine</u>
<u n="54" who="S0441">okay when she rings me back it's at ten till twelve on Saturday</u>
<u n="55" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="56" who="S0441">when she rings me back I can either say not then or I I guess actually <unclear/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0439" trans="overlap">well no it's okay I think I've got a netball match at that time anyway so erm I won't be here can just make sure that everything's clean and tidy <pause dur="short"/> well the vacuum cleaner still doesn't work very well but I guess we could try again couldn't we? mm okay didn't know they had loads of people interested</u>
<u n="58" who="S0441">yeah I didn't think it'd be so soon either but <unclear/> I suppose these things take time don't they?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0439">but also that means no one's gonna be here we've got to be here to to show them round haven't we? yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0439">okay</u>
<u n="62" who="S0441">that's the downside of having an estate agent in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0439">yeah <unclear>I guess so yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="64" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <unclear>what on earth</unclear> possessed her to do that <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0439" trans="overlap">probably cheaper isn't it? probably cheaper to have like an external well not external but like estate agent that works just by phone and email</u>
<u n="66" who="S0441">yeah yeah yeah true I suppose</u>
<u n="67" who="S0439">rather than like having to come out all the time</u>
<u n="68" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0439">yeah no that's okay then yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0441" trans="overlap">well if I say to them <pause dur="short"/> we'll pay our last rent in November and then be <trunc>mov</trunc>moved out by the next <unclear>rent on the</unclear> sixteenth of December</u>
<u n="71" who="S0439">yeah that works gives me an extra erm four hundred or three hundred and seventy-five pounds</u>
<u n="72" who="S0441">plus deposit we'll get back</u>
<u n="73" who="S0439">plus deposit that can all go back into my savings <unclear>actually yeah</unclear> plus erm we don't have to pay bills and stuff that month or do we still have to?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0441">I don't know how that works is it the first?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh unless we contacted the bills company like in October and told them that our <trunc>l</trunc> when our last date was then we can organise all our final bills then</u>
<u n="76" who="S0441">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we we wouldn't have to pay water would we? cos I suppose that's <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <unclear>I don't even know</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0439">yeah that means the next people are gonna get a fucking massive water bill which isn't theirs</u>
<u n="78" who="S0441"><unclear/> it won't be much will it? cos it'll be just one month one month</u>
<u n="79" who="S0439">yeah but my point is that if we don't pay it if we we've only paid one water bill from January through to June or July whenever and then if we don't get another water bill until like until if they don't get another bill until like January</u>
<u n="80" who="S0441"><unclear>oh yeah I see</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that's gonna be our water bill isn't it?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0441">unless we ring up the water <unclear>board</unclear> <unclear/> <unclear>water company</unclear></u>
<u n="83" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> or just sneak off and don't leave a <vocal desc="laugh"/> no I'm kidding let's not do that firstly cos it's in my name</u>
<u n="84" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0439">and I really really don't want that against my credit rating <pause dur="short"/> yeah well if we ring them up in October cos then we can get the internet cancelled we can get the</u>
<u n="86" who="S0441" trans="overlap">I don't think I'm gonna be able to get that cancelled I think there's a <unclear/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0439">oh</u>
<u n="88" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0439">can't we ask them if they want to keep the internet contract?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0441">I don't know how it would work though in terms of changing the names round and stuff</u>
<u n="91" who="S0439">well we could just ring up and change the names couldn't we? <pause dur="long"/> cos then again it saves them having to then get a new internet supplier</u>
<u n="92" who="S0441" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0439">which took us like a month</u>
<u n="94" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0439">we could say that to them</u>
<u n="96" who="S0441">true</u>
<u n="97" who="S0439"><unclear>like</unclear></u>
<u n="98" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <unclear>they have</unclear></u>
<u n="99" who="S0439"><unclear>if they want it you know</unclear></u>
<u n="100" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> let's try and make it as nice as possible so <unclear/> wants it</u>
<u n="101" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos that'd be really good actually cos that means we get our deposit back would be which is what? four hundred quid?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0441">yep</u>
<u n="103" who="S0439">and then our we don't have to pay rent that last month which would be another four hundred quid</u>
<u n="104" who="S0441">yep</u>
<u n="105" who="S0439">then we wouldn't have to pay council tax that month</u>
<u n="106" who="S0441">er <trunc>c</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc>what do we <unclear>do</unclear> council tax as?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0439">oh hundred and fifty quid</u>
<u n="108" who="S0441">how er how often though?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0439">every month</u>
<u n="110" who="S0441">oh it is monthly?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0439">if we paid it in November and then told them we were moving out in mid December they I think they reduce it or you don't have to</u>
<u n="112" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0441"><unclear>what else</unclear> <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and then electricity bill we can ring up and er can you give us a final bill?</u>
<u n="116" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="117" who="S0439">what else have we got? gas same</u>
<u n="118" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="119" who="S0439">just ask them for a final bill <pause dur="short"/> I think we have to pay like a five pounds exit fee but that's not bad</u>
<u n="120" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0439">er <pause dur="short"/> yeah no that's fine then actually saves us a bit of money in December doesn't it?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0441">it does</u>
<u n="123" who="S0439"><unclear>seeing that</unclear> it's Christmas month <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="124" who="S0441">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah er <pause dur="short"/> yeah because we've <pause dur="short"/> this'll be October won't it? October <unclear/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0441">we've only got two left <unclear/> if it works <unclear>out</unclear> I'm sure it <unclear>will</unclear></u>
<u n="127" who="S0439">yeah so I've already yeah I've already <trunc>tak</trunc> I take cos I get paid on the eighteenth of every month I've already taken my October rent out of this salary</u>
<u n="128" who="S0441">yeah so have I</u>
<u n="129" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0441">out of the one I just got paid</u>
<u n="131" who="S0439">yeah and then we've got so then in October <unclear>after that</unclear> so</u>
<u n="132" who="S0441">that'll go for November</u>
<u n="133" who="S0439">so yeah er that'll go for <trunc>Novem</trunc>November yeah <pause dur="short"/> so I won't actually have to pay rent in my November salary</u>
<u n="134" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="135" who="S0439">that'll be good</u>
<u n="136" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0439">and my December salary</u>
<u n="138" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0439">that's two salaries without having to pay rent <pause dur="short"/> boom love that idea <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>blimey</unclear> that's really good actually</u>
<u n="140" who="S0441">if it works like that</u>
<u n="141" who="S0439" trans="overlap">if it works like that</u>
<u n="142" who="S0441">let's not get our hopes up <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0439">still I'll be like ha ha ha that's <unclear>an extra like seven</unclear> hundred quid <unclear/> which I do not factor for mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0441">I I wouldn't I couldn't I I don't see why it wouldn't work like that if if we explain to them that if you can come to an arrangement with somebody who wants to move in that we'll move out by the sixteenth of December the fifteenth of December</u>
<u n="145" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0441">what's the weekend of that <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0439">but I guess it's probably it'll depend on whether somebody would want to move in half way through a month just before Christmas doesn't it?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0441">mm <pause dur="short"/> unless we moved in unless we just said the beginning of December</u>
<u n="149" who="S0439">yeah that doesn't bother me I don't mind driving to work for like I could easily like ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or something if I could stay with her or</u>
<u n="150" who="S0441">cos the sixteenth is a Wednesday <pause dur="short"/> so we'd either say the <pause dur="short"/> first or second week of December</u>
<u n="151" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0441">just pay a month's rent on the <pause dur="short"/> sixteenth of November</u>
<u n="153" who="S0439">well if we ask them on Saturday when they would like to <trunc>mo</trunc> or if like if they were interested when like when and what when are they looking to move in? and we could like negotiate from there maybe</u>
<u n="154" who="S0441">yeah we could <pause dur="long"/> it's good it's good that it's not so like</u>
<u n="155" who="S0439">imminent</u>
<u n="156" who="S0441">well I mean <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> quite <unclear/> so <unclear>we haven't</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0439">no that's good</u>
<u n="158" who="S0441"><unclear>that is quite</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0439">cos there's no point paying if we can there's no point paying for two weeks when we're not even gonna be living in the house so</u>
<u n="160" who="S0441"><unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0439">mm that'd work yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0441"><unclear>mm</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> she's very nice</u>
<u n="163" who="S0439">really?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0441">nicest one I've met when I spoke to them</u>
<u n="165" who="S0439" trans="overlap">that's good <unclear/> with the fucking lying shite</u>
<u n="166" who="S0441">yes</u>
<u n="167" who="S0439">well erm <pause dur="short"/> cos they said someone was coming over on Thursday for the fridge did they say what time <unclear>at all</unclear> <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0441"><vocal desc="yawn"/> <unclear>erm I'm</unclear> gonna be here though</u>
<u n="169" who="S0439">oh okay</u>
<u n="170" who="S0441"><unclear>she's not gonna</unclear> be here but I will</u>
<u n="171" who="S0439">she's just shit</u>
<u n="172" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0439">she's actually the shittiest shittiest shittiest estate agent in the entire western world</u>
<u n="174" who="S0441">I still don't understand why these companies as well like they ring you up and they're like okay so when do you want me to come? it's like <pause dur="short"/> well they say any weekday between nine and five it's like well</u>
<u n="175" who="S0439" trans="overlap">so any weekday <trunc>f</trunc> between nine and five when everybody else is working</u>
<u n="176" who="S0441">exactly I don't understand like er fair enough you have the same working hours as everyone else but you haven't <unclear/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0441">and I was like okay so morning then and she was like okay morning is between eight till one I'm like what the hell? do you expect me to factor that into my day? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah cos if you come at one o'clock you've just wasted my entire morning</u>
<u n="180" who="S0441" trans="overlap">for god's sake</u>
<u n="181" who="S0439">they're just shit</u>
<u n="182" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0439">they're really bad like I hate the the internet though we can come in the evening but you have to pay more it's like</u>
<u n="184" who="S0441"><unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="185" who="S0439">so you're gonna charge me to come at the most convenient time of day</u>
<u n="186" who="S0441">well that's just to complete the ploy though isn't it?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh yeah of course it is</u>
<u n="188" who="S0441">cos they know that everyone's gonna bloody well want to go in the evening</u>
<u n="189" who="S0439" trans="overlap">cos er yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0441" trans="overlap">it's an extra fifteen quid</u>
<u n="191" who="S0439">exactly it's just oh er yeah no okay we'll do some cleaning</u>
<u n="192" who="S0441">yep <pause dur="short"/> do you think they should come and actually touch it up a little bit? it's er looking very tatty and run down</u>
<u n="193" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it looks tatty it does look tatty like the paintwork really should be redone</u>
<u n="194" who="S0441" trans="overlap">the paintwork's shit</u>
<u n="195" who="S0439">and we've also got to get the single bed out of erm thingy bobby's <trunc>ga</trunc>garage</u>
<u n="196" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="197" who="S0439">hope it hasn't gone mouldy or anything</u>
<u n="198" who="S0441">ah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0439">what? is there a spider?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0439">I've got a <trunc>l</trunc> is it a massive massive spider? or just a?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0441">it's like one of those horrible outdoor spiders</u>
<u n="203" who="S0439">er let's have a look <pause dur="short"/> er this house is actually like full of spiders</u>
<u n="204" who="S0441">er</u>
<u n="205" who="S0439">it's actually the most disgusting thing I've like</u>
<u n="206" who="S0441"><unclear>daren't ever go</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0439">I know <trunc>t</trunc> <vocal desc="sigh"/> god</u>
<u n="208" who="S0441">oh</u>
<u n="209" who="S0439">I just hate spiders so much</u>
<u n="210" who="S0441">how was your weekend? <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0439">oh it was really good so</u>
<u n="212" who="S0441" trans="overlap">how was the theatre? <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0439">well <trunc>Sat</trunc> Friday night we'd booked to go for dinner with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0439">we took her to <trunc>s</trunc> to <anon type="place"/> in town like eleven ninety for a three course meal</u>
<u n="216" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh yeah I remember</u>
<u n="217" who="S0439">so I turned up at her house at half about <trunc>tw</trunc>twenty to six and she er she was like hi in her gym clothes I was like have you just been for a run? she's like yeah I was like so I'm guessing you haven't showered? she was like no and I was like well you have like <trunc>twe</trunc> fifteen minutes to get ready before we have to go out and she's like what the fuck?</u>
<u n="218" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0439">so she like quickly got ready and everything and then she didn't know what we were doing and she was like why are we going into a car park? I was like <pause dur="short"/> you'll see so</u>
<u n="220" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear>sorry</unclear> I'm just getting my tea I'm listening</u>
<u n="221" who="S0439">and so took her to the restaurant and she really liked that and she was so happy she was like I can't believe you did this it's such a good surprise</u>
<u n="222" who="S0441" trans="overlap">ah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0439">blah blah blah blah blah and we paid for like her dinner and stuff cos it was only like eleven quid so it's not breaking the bank balance and then I stayed over on Friday night and she was like oh I can't believe you surprised me last night you're so sneaky and I went into her room at nine o'clock in the morning I was like er by the way you've got an hour to get up cos then we're going to the train station she was like</u>
<u n="224" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0439">what the fuck?</u>
<u n="226" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0439">so we took her to <anon type="place"/> and she was like we're going to <anon type="place"/>? I was like yeah we are going to <anon type="place"/> she was like why are we going to <anon type="place"/>? I was like not gonna tell you</u>
<u n="228" who="S0441" trans="overlap">who were you with?</u>
<u n="229" who="S0439">just me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0441" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="231" who="S0439">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then so we got to <anon type="place"/> and she was like she said are we going to the <anon type="place"/>? I was like no and she was like oh okay</u>
<u n="232" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0439">I was like damn it</u>
<u n="234" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0439">but no then we took her to the theatre and she was like she was so happy she absolutely loved it with</u>
<u n="236" who="S0441" trans="overlap">what did you see again?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0439">The Book of Mormon</u>
<u n="238" who="S0441">oh yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0439">oh it was amazing</u>
<u n="240" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0439">like I don't know if you'd like it it was like quite politically incorrect and dodgy in that respect like it's er <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>it's er like it's like it's like er</unclear> a select type of humour</u>
<u n="242" who="S0441">uhu <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0439">but it was really good really funny</u>
<u n="244" who="S0441"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="245" who="S0439">erm you could because it's written by the people who created South Park you can er while you're watching it you can imagine a South Park episode it's really it's really weird but it was really well done and the theatre like our seats weren't bad they were quite they were near the back but they weren't bad or any or anything and then we just came back here went to a pub and watched the rugby and then <pause dur="short"/> erm Sunday went to this country park fair thing at <anon type="place"/> country park and then went to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s and then took went to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s for dinner had dinner with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then I went to yoga</u>
<u n="246" who="S0441">nice</u>
<u n="247" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0441">busy</u>
<u n="249" who="S0439">it was erm like a weird feeling on Saturday we erm we were just going and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like oh yeah erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> one of the girls at <anon type="place"/> who I don't I like I don't really hang out with people at <anon type="place"/> to be honest but she's like yeah she's going out with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like they've been seeing each other for a while and I was like oh okay and she was like yeah I found out like a few weeks ago but I didn't wanna tell you I was like</u>
<u n="250" who="S0441" trans="overlap">why? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0439">yeah I was like why? and she was like I dunno <unclear>just I just</unclear> didn't know <unclear>if</unclear> I should tell you I was like <pause dur="short"/> that's weird then I <trunc>r</trunc>realised when I went out for dinner with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> last Friday she said that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was seeing somebody</u>
<u n="252" who="S0441">then she must've known as well</u>
<u n="253" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and er so she knew and didn't <unclear>tell me</unclear></u>
<u n="254" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear>that's</unclear> weird</u>
<u n="255" who="S0439">but I was just like why does it matter? then for some reason I was a bit sad <trunc>ab</trunc> like not sad about it but just you know when you're just like a bit when you feel a bit weird about it? and I think it's because <anon type="place"/> is so like incestuous and so tangled I was like I hope he doesn't like say anything about me to her or like</u>
<u n="256" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0439">and then like er awkwardly enough she was there at the rugby</u>
<u n="258" who="S0441">oh</u>
<u n="259" who="S0439">and I was just like and like apparently they've been seeing each other for a while and I'm just like why why suddenly do I <trunc>f</trunc> like find out in a really weird way?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="261" who="S0439">erm for some reason I felt a bit weird about it I don't know why it's not that I even liked him that's the weird thing he's a bit of a weirdo but <pause dur="short"/> er yeah that was weird</u>
<u n="262" who="S0441">always weird I suppose isn't it?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0439">yeah the person that you were seeing starts seeing somebody else</u>
<u n="264" who="S0441">yeah doesn't necessarily mean that you like them but I suppose it's just a bit like oh</u>
<u n="265" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="267" who="S0439">just puts you in a bit of a weird mood</u>
<u n="268" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0439">cos it's not like I didn't really want him well I didn't want to be with him I <trunc>d</trunc> I didn't want him <pause dur="short"/> erm but it's still kind of weird knowing that like someone else like he's got</u>
<u n="270" who="S0441" trans="overlap">someone else wants him</u>
<u n="271" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0439">it's like ah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0441">was I missing something? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah was I did I miss <unclear/> am I just a failure at relationships?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0439">is it me? I bet it's me</u>
<u n="278" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0439">like it's not it wasn't me and like I feel fine now but</u>
<u n="280" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <unclear>wasn't you</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> I think I think that's a <pause dur="short"/> good dodge <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0439">yeah yeah oh definitely yeah like I <trunc>reali</trunc> like when you said to me it was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know when I told you that I ended things with him? you were like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I don't think you actually spoke about him once and I was like</u>
<u n="282" who="S0441" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="283" who="S0439">no no I didn't then I realised then because I was kind of embarrassed about it</u>
<u n="284" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0439"><unclear/> <unclear>like we're really awkward when we're</unclear> out together I'm like yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's cos I'm probably embarrassed to actually admit that I know you</u>
<u n="286" who="S0441">it's not very nice that I hate that feeling</u>
<u n="287" who="S0439">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0441">that that's when you know it's not right</u>
<u n="289" who="S0439">mm I was like</u>
<u n="290" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/> embarrassed to be around someone</u>
<u n="291" who="S0439">I just I <unclear/> never like introduce him to any of my friends from home</u>
<u n="292" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="293" who="S0439">I would never take him to like a barbecue with our friends like</u>
<u n="294" who="S0441" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="295" who="S0439">it would have just been <trunc>aw</trunc> it would have been horrible</u>
<u n="296" who="S0441">that's sort of what I felt about when I was dating <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well just just a bit like <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>oh</unclear></u>
<u n="297" who="S0439">and I just feel horrible er you don't mean to be rude but I was just like</u>
<u n="298" who="S0441">I <trunc>w</trunc> I would've been quite embarrassed <unclear>to have erm</unclear> like brought him round</u>
<u n="299" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0441"><unclear/> you know? like just</u>
<u n="301" who="S0439">and I don't know why like</u>
<u n="302" who="S0441" trans="overlap">no there's no reason</u>
<u n="303" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/> like he was like</u>
<u n="304" who="S0441"><unclear>there's</unclear> nothing wrong with him <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0439">he was a nice guy just a bit weird <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0441" trans="overlap">just weird <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0439">and just a bit like camp and just a bit like just not me and I was just like yeah <pause dur="short"/> some of the things he did I was just like why are you doing that?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0439">I'm so confused <pause dur="short"/> but apparently he's dating <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> now so that's all good</u>
<u n="310" who="S0441">well that's good at least he's over it</u>
<u n="311" who="S0439">yeah like I <trunc>s</trunc> I did send him a message on the Saturday cos I was just like cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was just being a bit weird with me she kept calling me darling</u>
<u n="312" who="S0441" trans="overlap">oh god</u>
<u n="313" who="S0439">why are you calling me darling? firstly you're northern and no one in the north says darling like they say darling but they don't say darling</u>
<u n="314" who="S0441">and she was actually saying darling?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0439">yeah like darling like</u>
<u n="316" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0439">and she was like touching my arm and stuff I was like who the fuck are you?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0441">oh god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0439">why are you?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0441" trans="overlap">she's trying way too hard <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0439">yeah I was like who are you even? like and she kept like being like talking to me about rugby I'm like why are you even talking to me? I don't know you and I know that you know who I am because you're sleeping with the person I was sleeping with <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="322" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0439">so <unclear>I sent him this message I'm like</unclear> oh I heard you're going out with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm I just wanted you to know like I don't if we're ever out together like I don't want there to be any weirdness or awkwardness or anything like that</u>
<u n="324" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0439">erm you know I hope you have a good time and stuff and then I <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was really horrible</u>
<u n="326" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0439">I kind of like slipped in</u>
<u n="328" who="S0441">oh god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="329" who="S0439">like someone said like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was like well I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> thinks it's kind of serious because like they're apparently exclusive and stuff</u>
<u n="330" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear>right</unclear></u>
<u n="331" who="S0439">and I was like okay so <vocal desc="laugh"/> I wrote in the text message I hear you're pretty serious so erm it's nice to know that you got over your commitment issues</u>
<u n="332" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0439">and I did it as a joke but I was like</u>
<u n="334" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="335" who="S0439">if he doesn't think they're serious</u>
<u n="336" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0439">he definitely knows that she thinks they're serious <vocal desc="laugh"/> I realise that was a very harsh thing to do but I was like</u>
<u n="338" who="S0441" trans="overlap">did he reply?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0439">no</u>
<u n="340" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0439">but I didn't no but I left it like <trunc>rea</trunc> it was like a really closed message there was no like it wasn't a message</u>
<u n="342" who="S0441" trans="overlap">no questions <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0439">looking for a reply it was like I hope you're okay I know this and then it was like if we bump into each other you know if we don't bump <trunc>int</trunc>into each other before you go back to er <anon type="place"/> I hope you have like a good time and then like</u>
<u n="344" who="S0441" trans="overlap">is he going back there forever?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0439">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh okay</unclear></u>
<u n="347" who="S0439">he's moving back to <anon type="place"/> <trunc>t</trunc> for his job and I was like and I hope you enjoy your new job like it was a really closed message it wasn't like a I want to start a conversation with you it's a I know this I don't wanna be weird</u>
<u n="348" who="S0441" trans="overlap">statement of fact <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0439">let's leave it there shall we? <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> yeah and then er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> understood why I was feeling a bit weird and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was just like I don't get it</u>
<u n="350" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0439">so so I just didn't mention it and then like I went back to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s in the evening and we were chatting about it and she goes well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s just added <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on Facebook</u>
<u n="352" who="S0441">oh</u>
<u n="353" who="S0439">and I feel weird too I was like that's okay we can feel weird together <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="354" who="S0441">poor <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="355" who="S0439">I know she was like I don't understand why I'm feeling weird about the fact that he's added this girl who he's been dating on Facebook <pause dur="short"/> and she I was like well it's kind of because</u>
<u n="356" who="S0441">you want to be that girl <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0439">yeah or you now know that like they're more than just <pause dur="short"/> texting each other</u>
<u n="358" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0439">they're like they're now like</u>
<u n="360" who="S0441" trans="overlap">actual Facebook friends <unclear>now</unclear></u>
<u n="361" who="S0439">yeah that's so stupid though isn't it? like</u>
<u n="362" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear>that is so stupid</unclear></u>
<u n="363" who="S0439">being Facebook friends means something</u>
<u n="364" who="S0441" trans="overlap">that is er that's that is the next step though I think</u>
<u n="365" who="S0439">yeah it is yeah like I don't have people if I'm dating somebody I don't have them on Facebook for ages</u>
<u n="366" who="S0441" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="367" who="S0439">unless they <trunc>invi</trunc> unless they add me <pause dur="short"/> yeah so I think she was just like why have they gone to the next step? I was like</u>
<u n="368" who="S0441" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0439"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's fine like he's <trunc>be</trunc> he's away for like three weeks two weeks like</u>
<u n="370" who="S0441">exactly he'll miss you</u>
<u n="371" who="S0439" trans="overlap">and your brother's gonna be here</u>
<u n="372" who="S0441">has she gone now?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0439">no she's going tomorrow so I'm popping round tonight just to say goodbye give her a birthday card and I've got to take some of her clothes back</u>
<u n="374" who="S0441"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0439">erm</u>
<u n="376" who="S0441">when's her actual birthday? <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0439">next <trunc>Wedn</trunc> no wait it's the seventh next Wednesday</u>
<u n="378" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="379" who="S0439">erm</u>
<u n="380" who="S0441">well she'll've had her birthday with the bake off <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="381" who="S0439">yeah with birthday cake but no</u>
<u n="382" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0441">can't happen <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0439">no I think she's having a wedding dress fitting on er not a wedding a bridesmaid's fitting on the seventh on her birthday so <pause dur="short"/> yeah she's just like <unclear/> I'm gonna be away for three weeks and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gonna be here and what if he forgets me? I'm like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> he is not going to forget you</u>
<u n="385" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he's not gonna forget you</u>
<u n="386" who="S0439">like</u>
<u n="387" who="S0441">he'll miss all the little things that she does</u>
<u n="388" who="S0439">exactly it'll be like <trunc>y</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> she'll be but why doesn't he want me? I'm like I don't know</u>
<u n="389" who="S0441">he might not know it yet maybe</u>
<u n="390" who="S0439">maybe he just <trunc>d</trunc>didn't wanna like ruin their friendship or something yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0441" trans="overlap">ruin their friendship yeah true</u>
<u n="392" who="S0439">I don't know but <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> don't know</u>
<u n="393" who="S0441">it's so hard</u>
<u n="394" who="S0439">yeah relationships are too hard and such effort</u>
<u n="395" who="S0441">massive effort</u>
<u n="396" who="S0439">talking about relationships and so much effort how was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="397" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0441">such an effort <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="399" who="S0439">such an effort <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0441">no it was really lovely <unclear>though</unclear></u>
<u n="401" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0441">just wandered round</u>
<u n="403" who="S0439">mm did you go into <anon type="place"/>? or?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="405" who="S0439">oh did you book those tickets for the Month of the Dead thing <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0441">no</u>
<u n="407" who="S0439"><unclear>okay</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0441">I don't know if I'm gonna be able to afford it</u>
<u n="409" who="S0439">ah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0441">I hate money so damn much</u>
<u n="411" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I know it's shit isn't it?</u>
<u n="412" who="S0441" trans="overlap">it's <unclear>like <trunc>m</trunc></unclear></u>
<u n="413" who="S0439">like even the odd ten pounds here ten pounds there adds up doesn't it?</u>
<u n="414" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's like my tyres obviously I had those to pay for</u>
<u n="415" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="416" who="S0441">which is a hundred and eighty pounds which isn't that bad <pause dur="short"/> but still like</u>
<u n="417" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="418" who="S0441"><unclear/> out of my my wages</u>
<u n="419" who="S0439">yeah if I suddenly had a hundred and eighty pounds coming out of my wages I'd be fucked</u>
<u n="420" who="S0441">and I'm trying to not that I'm making excuses but I'm trying to before I start saving I'm trying to cancel out all the debts I have</u>
<u n="421" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="422" who="S0441">so I'm trying to put <unclear>money</unclear> to all my debts <unclear>it's really fun</unclear></u>
<u n="423" who="S0439">what debts do you have?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0441">just <unclear>that</unclear> credit card</u>
<u n="425" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="426" who="S0441">that I haven't paid off yet because it's interest free so</u>
<u n="427" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0441">what's the rush? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0439">I've got I've got a <trunc>cre</trunc> an interest free credit card that I'm paying off every month</u>
<u n="430" who="S0441">mm that and I've got <pause dur="short"/> new Look store card which is almost paid off anyway</u>
<u n="431" who="S0439">how much did you spend in New Look? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0441">not much like it's only a hundred quid like</u>
<u n="433" who="S0439" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0441">not not a lot</u>
<u n="435" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0441">the the credit limit's only the credit limit is only a hundred and fifty pound</u>
<u n="437" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="438" who="S0441">but I've just been paying off like ten pounds a month so it's just taken like</u>
<u n="439" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0441">fifty thousand million years to <vocal desc="laugh"/> to to pay off <pause dur="short"/> I'm just like putting chunks to it now</u>
<u n="441" who="S0439">yeah that's what I'm gonna do with my Nationwide like once I've paid off my John Lewis credit card</u>
<u n="442" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0439">that's the one I use like every month to put like flights on and stuff</u>
<u n="444" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="445" who="S0439">like I don't want to put flights and stuff on a on on a <trunc>b</trunc> debit card so I put that on my John Lewis card</u>
<u n="446" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="447" who="S0439">and then when I had to pay for my car and for my bed I put that on a fifteen month credit card and I have like I think it's got something like six hundred pounds left to pay off but once my I've paid off my flights for Lapland and stuff I'll just pay off the <trunc>Na</trunc> the Nationwide card with like <unclear>eighty</unclear> quid a month</u>
<u n="448" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="449" who="S0439"><unclear/> hundred quid a month and just pay it off quickly <pause dur="short"/> cos once it gets to like a manageable chunk of like two hundred quid</u>
<u n="450" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0439">you can just pay it off can't you?</u>
<u n="452" who="S0441" trans="overlap">exactly it's just yeah <pause dur="short"/> they're too easy</u>
<u n="453" who="S0439">oh credit cards are ridiculously easy to put money onto</u>
<u n="454" who="S0441">crazy</u>
<u n="455" who="S0439">I'm really really trying this month to not put anything on my John Lewis credit card</u>
<u n="456" who="S0441">yeah</u>
<u n="457" who="S0439">it's just like little things like thirty pounds of petrol oh I'll put that on my credit card</u>
<u n="458" who="S0441" trans="overlap">exactly <unclear/> credit card oh but it soon adds up remember</u>
<u n="459" who="S0439">yeah shit</u>
<u n="460" who="S0441" trans="overlap">jesus <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="461" who="S0439">I remember once I bought something and I didn't know that the my month cut off was the fifth I thought it was the thirty-first</u>
<u n="462" who="S0441">oops</u>
<u n="463" who="S0439">or the thirtieth so I put like a hundred and fifty pounds onto my credit card</u>
<u n="464" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0439">and realised that I had to pay it off the next month instead of the month after I was fuck my life <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0441">oops</u>
<u n="467" who="S0439">I had a credit card card bill of like four hundred quid I was like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's not what you want</u>
<u n="469" who="S0439">I was not a happy bunny that month <pause dur="short"/> no my credit card bill this month was quite expensive but it's because of all my flights and my holidays and stuff but it's fine <unclear/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0441">it's worth it</u>
<u n="471" who="S0439">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="472" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="473" who="S0439">it's <unclear>only</unclear> like a hundred odd quid so</u>
<u n="474" who="S0441"><unclear>fun</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> what are you doing for New Year? <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0439">no idea</u>
<u n="476" who="S0441">no me neither <unclear/> we were gonna go out with go away with his friends and their girlfriends</u>
<u n="477" who="S0439">that sounds like <unclear/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0441">I know well <pause dur="short"/> I'm trying really hard to cos I haven't actually seen them since we got back together</u>
<u n="479" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="480" who="S0441">so I need to sort of make an effort with his friends really and <pause dur="short"/> he wants to be able to like go out with them and he wants <trunc>n</trunc> me to not feel like <pause dur="short"/> excluded I suppose so he wants me to meet the girls so I know the girls which is fine but I just don't like girls really</u>
<u n="481" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh my god that sounds like the shittiest thing I've ever heard in my life</u>
<u n="482" who="S0441">but I'm doing it so it's fine</u>
<u n="483" who="S0439" trans="overlap">I hate girls</u>
<u n="484" who="S0441">me too <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0439">girls actually just make me wanna like stab my own face</u>
<u n="486" who="S0441">me too</u>
<u n="487" who="S0439">well obviously not you and like girls I like but most girls if someone genuinely threw me into a room with a bunch of girls I'd like oh <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="488" who="S0441" trans="overlap"><unclear>help</unclear> me</u>
<u n="489" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="490" who="S0439">like why are they doing this to me? they're just so <pause dur="short"/> dull</u>
<u n="491" who="S0441">I mean <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s girlfriend seems really nice actually</u>
<u n="492" who="S0439">oh okay</u>
<u n="493" who="S0441">so</u>
<u n="494" who="S0439"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0441">I think I like her</u>
<u n="496" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="497" who="S0441">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s girlfriend <pause dur="short"/> even <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't like her she went to our uni to be fair but she's really like I haven't actually met the girl so <unclear>I'm er I'm</unclear> being very judgemental here but</u>
<u n="498" who="S0439" trans="overlap">it's fine you can be judgemental <unclear>I don't care</unclear></u>
<u n="499" who="S0441"><vocal desc="sigh"/> I just get the impression she's very not me</u>
<u n="500" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="501" who="S0441">like got like <trunc>s</trunc> loads of money so money's really important to her and stuff like that so</u>
<u n="502" who="S0439">so that rules us out</u>
<u n="503" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="504" who="S0439"><unclear>well I mean she er</unclear> what I hate is when you like you're out with somebody and they're like oh yeah no let's go here and you're like and they like drop like a hundred quid in a bar and you're just like I don't even have a hundred pounds to spend this weekend</u>
<u n="505" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="506" who="S0439">let alone on one night out</u>
<u n="507" who="S0441">one buy one get one free shot please <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0439">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0441">that's me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0439" trans="overlap">cocktails two for one? I'll have ten <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0441" trans="overlap">let's go <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh</u>
<u n="512" who="S0439">yeah <trunc>h</trunc> I know</u>
<u n="513" who="S0441">so I don't think I'll have anything in common with her really at all</u>
<u n="514" who="S0439">mm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0441">she's just opened her <trunc>n</trunc> her own shop</u>
<u n="516" who="S0439">oh for fuck's sake</u>
<u n="517" who="S0441">because her dad helped her</u>
<u n="518" who="S0439">oh I hate <unclear/></u>
<u n="519" who="S0441">she already wasn't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and her already didn't get on at all so that's awkward enough</u>
<u n="520" who="S0439">why not? just</u>
<u n="521" who="S0441">they just didn't I think she's er obviously like must take is a bit of a psycho must take things like really seriously because this is so petty once we were on a night out and she was there because her best friend used to go out with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as well</u>
<u n="522" who="S0439">oh okay</u>
<u n="523" who="S0441">they broke up <pause dur="short"/> I liked her she was nice <pause dur="short"/> erm they were friends and</u>
<u n="524" who="S0439" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="525" who="S0441"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s girlfriend was seeing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at this time</u>
<u n="526" who="S0439" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="527" who="S0441">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said something to her but she obviously took it the complete wrong way and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was drunk so he like reacted to what she was saying</u>
<u n="528" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0441">they had like a <unclear>mini</unclear> little argument in in this club and they never spoke again like it was really that bad I mean he would try obviously cos he is that type of person</u>
<u n="530" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0441">like he's not gonna let you know <unclear>he would try and talk to her</unclear></u>
<u n="532" who="S0439" trans="overlap">one drunken argument yeah</u>
<u n="533" who="S0441">yeah she just was never interested and always used to say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like why does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hate me? and just making it so difficult like <unclear/></u>
<u n="534" who="S0439">girls do that girls like seriously hold onto grudges</u>
<u n="535" who="S0441" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="536" who="S0439">so badly</u>
<u n="537" who="S0441">she I mean the next time she saw him she could've been like oh you know that was really silly</u>
<u n="538" who="S0439">yeah <unclear>it was pretty</unclear> shit sorry about that like <unclear/> happened</u>
<u n="539" who="S0441" trans="overlap">or just laugh about it do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0439">yeah</u>
<u n="541" who="S0441">god <pause dur="short"/> so that's all all really awkward <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> then there's the <vocal desc="laugh"/> there's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s girlfriend I've not I don't know anything really about her I'm sure she'd be very nice but I keep wanting to call her <pause dur="short"/> oh god what's her name? so I think her name's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the ex girlfriend was called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I really keep wanting to call her <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="542" who="S0439" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="543" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0439">okay don't call her <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="545" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I keep saying this to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he said literally being like <vocal desc="laugh"/> don't you dare call her <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos that would just be the worst</u>
<u n="546" who="S0439">yeah hi <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hi <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="547" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh god so it's just gonna end badly <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="548" who="S0439">I I sense this is er gonna end badly yeah</u>
<u n="549" who="S0441">anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/> we might not do that so it's fine cos they can't decide what they want to do</u>
<u n="550" who="S0439">yeah I have no idea what to do for New Year's I wanna do something</u>
<u n="551" who="S0441">you love New Year</u>
<u n="552" who="S0439">I do love New Year mum and dad I think might be going to Denmark with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> so I don't think we'll be going to Germany although I've already booked a flight to Germany but it was only thirty quid so I don't really care not doing it <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="553" who="S0441">mm <pause dur="short"/> I'm er I'm working anyway in the day so it's not worth <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>just quickly going</unclear> somewhere I <vocal desc="misc"/> I think we might go and stay somewhere <unclear>to be fair</unclear> just me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="554" who="S0439">I'm not gonna lie that sounds like the most tedious New Year's ever</u>
<u n="555" who="S0441">we're both not really that bothered though we did that last year and it was fine</u>
<u n="556" who="S0439"><unclear>yeah I do</unclear> I went to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house party last year and that was quite fun</u>
<u n="557" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="558" who="S0439">don't like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but <unclear>he throws a good</unclear> party</u>
<u n="559" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/> fun minus him</u>
<u n="560" who="S0439">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was there</u>
<u n="561" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="562" who="S0439"><unclear>I just ignored her</unclear></u>
<u n="563" who="S0441">did actually post a very nice photo of a sunset today</u>
<u n="564" who="S0439"><unclear>don't care</unclear></u>
<u n="565" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="566" who="S0439">I think I actually unfriended her</u>
<u n="567" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="568" who="S0439"><unclear>or if</unclear> not I really should</u>
<u n="569" who="S0441" trans="overlap">she's quite annoying she is quite annoying <unclear/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0439">she's annoying in general she's an annoying person</u>
<u n="571" who="S0441">mm I haven't seen her for absolutely years</u>
<u n="572" who="S0439">sadly I have</u>
<u n="573" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="574" who="S0439">no but it's just like I'm not rude to her I just can't be bothered to be fake with her mm</u>
<u n="575" who="S0441">can't tolerate her</u>
<u n="576" who="S0439">yeah I just don't want to talk to her</u>
<u n="577" who="S0441"><vocal desc="yawn"/> mm</u>
<u n="578" who="S0439">I'm not gonna apologise for that I don't have to talk to her</u>
<u n="579" who="S0441">no you don't have to talk to her <unclear>you've not got</unclear> to talk to anyone</u>
<u n="580" who="S0439"><unclear>okay</unclear> just sit alone in my room all the time</u>
<u n="581" who="S0441"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="582" who="S0439">never talking to anybody</u>
<u n="583" who="S0441">become a recluse</u>
<u n="584" who="S0439">I think I might do</u>
<u n="585" who="S0441"><unclear>no good</unclear></u>
<u n="586" who="S0439">no <pause dur="short"/> sometimes it's just nice to have time on your own though</u>
<u n="587" who="S0441">oh yeah I'm all for that</u>
<u n="588" who="S0439">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="589" who="S0441">mm</u>
<u n="590" who="S0439"><vocal desc="yawn"/> I'm so tired but <pause dur="short"/> I don't wanna go to sleep <unclear/> <unclear>a little</unclear> nap <unclear>need</unclear> a cup of tea need a cup of tea</u>
<u n="591" who="S0441">I'll have a cup of tea too</u>
<u n="592" who="S0439">tea I love tea so much <unclear>I'm</unclear> so bad</u>
<u n="593" who="S0441"><unclear/></u>
<u n="594" who="S0439">okay say hi to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for me</u>
<u n="595" who="S0441"><unclear/> didn't say anything so <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="596" who="S0439">she just rang you and didn't say anything?</u>
<u n="597" who="S0441">I think <unclear>I don't think the signal was very good</unclear></u>
<u n="598" who="S0439">oh I see okay well okay</u>
<u n="599" who="S0441"><unclear>oh</unclear></u>
<u n="600" who="S0439"><unclear>I have</unclear> a message</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
