<text id="SQ37">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:01:25</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-11-18</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0282 S0650</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Home of ANON in Oval, Lambeth, South London</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Birth of grandchild. Being born abroad. What things are like in France: property, enterprise, land, anarchists and bureaucrats, French visitors to London. Chichester Cathedral spire collapsing. Architect called Porden. Open day and photo exhibition. Art competition. Argument about bollards. Local housing management: failings of new landlord. Book being written by speaker no 2. British Library. Philip of Spain and Mary Tudor: experience of visiting Spanish archives. Austrian battleship disaster. Historians. </topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about Europe, history and local concerns</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussingm explaining, inquiring, advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0282">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Stratford-upon-Avon</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>self employed</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0650">
				<exactage>80</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>80_89</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Westminster</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>21 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0282">erm two recordings at the moment I've on my phone this is not very handy my phone because the technology of a smart phone</u>
<u n="2" who="S0650">yes</u>
<u n="3" who="S0282">is not particularly compatible with the</u>
<u n="4" who="S0650">what the equipment they use?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0282" trans="overlap">with the MP3 and the other</u>
<u n="6" who="S0650" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="7" who="S0282" trans="overlap">sort of software that you have</u>
<u n="8" who="S0650">yes</u>
<u n="9" who="S0282" trans="overlap">to record music and stuff like that because erm they're you know they're all Apple people</u>
<u n="10" who="S0650">yes</u>
<u n="11" who="S0282" trans="overlap">those people they like Apple better</u>
<u n="12" who="S0650">oh</u>
<u n="13" who="S0282">they don't like all the</u>
<u n="14" who="S0650">oh</u>
<u n="15" who="S0282" trans="overlap">Microsofts and the <unclear/> etcetera</u>
<u n="16" who="S0650">yes</u>
<u n="17" who="S0282">but erm so the idea is just that we kind of chat away</u>
<u n="18" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah right fine no problem</u>
<u n="19" who="S0282">so erm erm probably erm so erm you it's your your daughter that you went out to see when they she had her babies wasn't it? you were going out to see</u>
<u n="20" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="21" who="S0282">to see babies</u>
<u n="22" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="23" who="S0282" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="24" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes that's right yes she erm had her first baby er exactly <vocal desc="laugh"/> just almost to the day that they had to leave Berlin and then and move into the house in Brussels and er er we went over <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had to come over to London to have the child erm in the typically erm I suppose it's a reprehensible way I put my foot down and said my grandson is going to be born in this country</u>
<u n="25" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and I'm not having any kraut <vocal desc="laugh"/> grandchildren thank you and er so she came over here and gave birth erm er in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="27" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="28" who="S0650" trans="overlap">erm well what's it called? er it was <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0282">oh I don't know actually</u>
<u n="30" who="S0650" trans="overlap">it was well it's <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="31" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0650">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0650">yeah erm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0282" trans="overlap">so I don't know how that works though because my my nephew was born in Bahrain and erm and I was never sure whether that meant that there was some kind of question mark over his I mean both his parents are British but</u>
<u n="36" who="S0650" trans="overlap">if</u>
<u n="37" who="S0282">you know if you're born overseas I don't know where that leaves you whether there's the kind of there's just that little trace there in your heritage where people say</u>
<u n="38" who="S0650" trans="overlap">you you you you</u>
<u n="39" who="S0282">oh you know</u>
<u n="40" who="S0650">you'll have to be careful you will have to make sure that the er er British authorities know when it happened</u>
<u n="41" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0650">and so you have to tell the local consul</u>
<u n="43" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="44" who="S0650">and so on unless they've changed it or unless the the rules in the European Union may be different but it was essential that er <trunc>th</trunc>those two little children were born in England</u>
<u n="45" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="46" who="S0650">so that they could <trunc>ha</trunc><trunc>ha</trunc> where there wouldn't be any problem about them <trunc>beco</trunc> them becoming British subjects</u>
<u n="47" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0650">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0282">well I was yes I was slightly concerned with my sister as I thought you know actually erm you do find that people who are born and spend their early lives with their peripatetic parents sometimes don't develop roots</u>
<u n="50" who="S0650"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0282" trans="overlap">you know</u>
<u n="52" who="S0650">my second son <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was born in Paris his mother is French and erm she then she's quite a clued up lady erm she moved from Paris and worked for one of the er <trunc>dep</trunc>department authorities in southwest France</u>
<u n="53" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0650">and that's where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> first went to school then he came back to England and when he came back to England erm I had to er register him and take out British nationality for him and it I even <trunc>h</trunc> even had to go to the lengths of getting a copy of the his French birth certificate with my name on it</u>
<u n="55" who="S0282">oh really?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0650">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/> they may have changed all that this was in nineteen erm eight nineteen the nineteen eighties</u>
<u n="57" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0650">erm</u>
<u n="59" who="S0282">I wouldn't have thought it was easier now I would have thought it was more difficult now because there are so many</u>
<u n="60" who="S0650"><trunc>ye</trunc> I think it is more difficult</u>
<u n="61" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I mean and we are actually getting worse</u>
<u n="62" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="63" who="S0282">about even Europeans coming here aren't we?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0282" trans="overlap">don't know where all that's going to end I mean I know my mother when she first came to the country had to go to the police station every week and register</u>
<u n="66" who="S0650">where where had she come from?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0282" trans="overlap">well she's French</u>
<u n="68" who="S0650">oh she's French is she?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0650">from which part of France?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0282">well she was born in Toulouse</u>
<u n="72" who="S0650">oh right down there?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0650">at one part <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went to <anon type="place"/> or whatever it's called</u>
<u n="75" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="76" who="S0650" trans="overlap">in in in <anon type="place"/> and because of er the <anon type="place"/> work</u>
<u n="77" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and they they put a lot of money into all the educational facilities and he got an internship with <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0650">and from <anon type="place"/> he got himself a place at one of the London university colleges er it's a bit stupid I can't remember whether it's <anon type="place"/> or something like that but</u>
<u n="81" who="S0282" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="82" who="S0650">erm and he went to a London university but it was quite a business and while he was at the London university the I had to deal with the business of his citizenship</u>
<u n="83" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0650">but only when he was I dunno he must have been er seventeen or eighteen yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0282">whereas the French I was talking to my mother about this the other day you know I could get a French passport if I wanted one and erm and my siblings have done so erm but they all reported how snotty the people were at the <vocal desc="laugh"/> French embassy when you went there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0650">oh that's that's true</u>
<u n="89" who="S0282">so her</u>
<u n="90" who="S0650" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0282">and they were all sort of very disdainful and looked down their nose at you</u>
<u n="92" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and like</u>
<u n="94" who="S0650" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="95" who="S0282" trans="overlap">can I help you? what are you doing here?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0650" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="97" who="S0282">so I've always sort of put off the business of going to to get a French passport as well but there were various times when erm <unclear/> for example wrote to me and asked me if I'd like to vote</u>
<u n="98" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="99" who="S0282" trans="overlap">well I <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="100" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0282">er because erm obviously he felt that it would help his cause I suppose</u>
<u n="102" who="S0650">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0282">rather than his opponents'</u>
<u n="104" who="S0650">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0282">so but I think they seem to have a very different attitude to to us have you got property in France?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0650">no no no no I'm glad erm I wouldn't want to have either</u>
<u n="107" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="108" who="S0650">I I wouldn't want to live in France it's a nightmare country</u>
<u n="109" who="S0282">do you think so?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0650" trans="overlap">it's er oh gosh it's awful</u>
<u n="111" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0650" trans="overlap">you know no er I mean the only sensible thing that any French people do is come over over here why do you think there are so many people French over here?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0282">well I don't know I mean</u>
<u n="114" who="S0650" trans="overlap">well the <trunc>rea</trunc> I'll tell you exactly why if you've got any initiative at all er er you want to set up your own business for example</u>
<u n="115" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0650">or you go into a big firm like erm er Thomson-CSF which is the biggest armaments <trunc>com</trunc>company erm and erm <pause dur="short"/> you get very well trained up you <trunc>ha</trunc> they insist on you having all these qualifications and so on half of which you don't need</u>
<u n="117" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="118" who="S0650">erm and unless you have them you can't get a job</u>
<u n="119" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="120" who="S0650">erm and then if you want to set up your own because you can see all the the er on-cost of the bureaucracy which these large firms are stuck with the minute you set up a company you have to pay tax whether you've made a profit or not it stifles all initiative it's quite extraordinary</u>
<u n="121" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0650">and I'll tell you another thing if you have and this is from past experience if you have a house or a share in a house and you want to share that house you have to do it through a a er an agent appointed appointed not chosen by you appointed by the state</u>
<u n="123" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and he acts as a a erm a mediator and whoever is buying the you know er property has to use that person as well</u>
<u n="125" who="S0282">gosh</u>
<u n="126" who="S0650">and so if you erm say well you you think the man is getting it all wrong er firing the guy is well a very expensive job in in fact</u>
<u n="127" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0650" trans="overlap">it it their system of doing things is is weird</u>
<u n="129" who="S0282">they do have very</u>
<u n="130" who="S0650">mm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0282" trans="overlap">very strong protectionism my mother</u>
<u n="132" who="S0650">oh yes that's <unclear>it's beyond belief</unclear></u>
<u n="133" who="S0282" trans="overlap">my mother inherited her mother's house and</u>
<u n="134" who="S0650">mm</u>
<u n="135" who="S0282">erm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0650"><unclear/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0282" trans="overlap">she was obviously very <trunc>senti</trunc>sentimental about it and wanted to keep it but that <trunc>wa</trunc> this was in a suburb of Bordeaux</u>
<u n="138" who="S0650">mm</u>
<u n="139" who="S0282">so it wasn't it just wasn't feasible as a holiday house and er so she let it out and you're not allowed to evict any tenants between November and April because you're not allowed to evict tenants during the winter because of the potential hardship of the tenant</u>
<u n="140" who="S0650">oh</u>
<u n="141" who="S0282">so even if they're not paying you rent you're not allowed to evict them</u>
<u n="142" who="S0650">that is barmy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0282" trans="overlap">erm it all went so horribly horribly wrong over the years that and she got fleeced terribly by this this one man erm who really sort of took liberties and then when she came to sell it she had that same situation where you have the</u>
<u n="144" who="S0650" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="145" who="S0282">the person who brokers the sale</u>
<u n="146" who="S0650">yes</u>
<u n="147" who="S0282">and the only saving grace of it is that in order to avoid death duties and capital gains and stuff like they're they the the appointed agent will at some point or another leave the room whereupon packages of money are exchanged under the table <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0282" trans="overlap">between the <vocal desc="laugh"/> buyer and the seller because you have an official selling price</u>
<u n="150" who="S0650">mm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0282">which is sort of set a price where you know which is quite an innocuous sort of price</u>
<u n="152" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="153" who="S0282">that doesn't attract any attention from the authorities</u>
<u n="154" who="S0650" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and then there's the real sales price</u>
<u n="156" who="S0650" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="157" who="S0282" trans="overlap">which is negotiated privately on the side</u>
<u n="158" who="S0650">mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0282">so you know you have pieces of paper on the table</u>
<u n="160" who="S0650" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0282" trans="overlap">that says the house is being sold for X and then an envelope with</u>
<u n="162" who="S0650">yes</u>
<u n="163" who="S0282" trans="overlap">the balance of the money gets passed underneath the table while the guy is is is looking in the other direction erm so erm so the French have found a way around the bureaucracy</u>
<u n="164" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0282" trans="overlap">in fact I think really but but that's not to say that erm the state is not a bit erm oppressive in that <trunc>re</trunc> in that regard I suppose that's one of the reasons why they don't have the same problems in Paris that they do over here with this sort of young people trying to find rented accommodation because you you know there is not that property ownership thing there not a fetishistic thing</u>
<u n="166" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="167" who="S0282" trans="overlap">about property ownership</u>
<u n="168" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah it's true</u>
<u n="169" who="S0282" trans="overlap">there</u>
<u n="170" who="S0650">all and er all the land and I know that that but <unclear/> all the land in Paris belongs to the state</u>
<u n="171" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0650" trans="overlap">it doesn't belong to various individuals</u>
<u n="173" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0650">my aunt had a house er in er erm er <unclear>Montan</unclear> I <trunc>can</trunc> <unclear>Montan</unclear> and my great aunt also had a house down there as well erm and they were always having trouble with er getting permission to do this or having this that and the other done</u>
<u n="175" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and so on and you have to oil everybody's hands and</u>
<u n="177" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0650">otherwise you just never get anywhere er</u>
<u n="179" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> it is erm no my father was though is always that he wants to move there because erm they don't have oh well until recently they haven't had the same thing about speeding <pause dur="short"/> so you could drive how you wanted and however fast you wanted</u>
<u n="180" who="S0650" trans="overlap">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and you were okay and also you know he felt that erm oh he had a thing about David Blunkett introducing all these laws about gun owning guns and things like that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0650" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0282">so</u>
<u n="184" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0282" trans="overlap">he just <trunc>tha</trunc> the French are the French are more grown up and reasonable about about erm you know erm <pause dur="short"/> not erm infantalising I suppose people or</u>
<u n="186" who="S0650" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0282">seeking to be very parental about about how they live their lives and what they have and what they do and</u>
<u n="188" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0282">and so on but I don't I think the French are catching up with us in that regard actually</u>
<u n="190" who="S0650">their inheritance laws are are bizarre</u>
<u n="191" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0650">erm <pause dur="short"/> you can't make a will in a way that you can here</u>
<u n="193" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="194" who="S0650">I think is ridiculous</u>
<u n="195" who="S0282">no cos you can't it things get inherited by your children don't they not by your spouse?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0650">er that's correct and and also you can't erm er just er er write a will saying I leave all my property to a cats' home</u>
<u n="197" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="198" who="S0650">or I leave all my property to my second son</u>
<u n="199" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0650">not my first son and it doesn't matter if you put in the fact that you <trunc>s</trunc> first son has made a million anything like that oh no the law has to operate</u>
<u n="201" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="202" who="S0650">your</u>
<u n="203" who="S0282">so it's a feudal then really isn't it? or sort of</u>
<u n="204" who="S0650">well it's dictatorial and it's a totalitarian is sort of</u>
<u n="205" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0650" trans="overlap">er however you wanna call it</u>
<u n="207" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0650" trans="overlap">er</u>
<u n="209" who="S0282">but I suppose it's about you know perhaps it's about land perhaps it's about you know the family farm going down through the generations or something</u>
<u n="210" who="S0650" trans="overlap">mm I think er er er er I think it's a erm an intellectual approach I would say rather crudely that all French people suffer from the <trunc>pr</trunc> what I call the promised land syndrome</u>
<u n="211" who="S0282">oh yeah? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0650">er if you they all quote Rousseau at you</u>
<u n="213" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="214" who="S0650">erm about every man is free and all that sort of nonsense and erm <pause dur="short"/> er they entirely <trunc>o</trunc> they had this vision that they all had this vision of a perfect state where everybody is properly looked after and as some people here say everybody has a prize</u>
<u n="215" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0650">and so on they don't stop to think about the practicalities of it and the result of that is that they're for example their er farming agricultural industry is chronically inefficient</u>
<u n="217" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="218" who="S0650">because none of the units are the right size</u>
<u n="219" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="220" who="S0650">er they don't once you build up a a or you reach a what I think you call a critical mass on the farm for example you get the right amount of machinery and get it <pause dur="short"/> erm capitalised properly used properly so that it was worth spending money for example on a a forty thousand pound combine harvester and there's no point in having a piece of machinery like that if you've only got twenty acres</u>
<u n="221" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0650">but it once you get to the right level of saying five hundred acres or might probably be a thousand acres in fact erm er then when you die they will say oh no that's all got to be split up again and so they they're constantly destroying the <trunc>ec</trunc>economic base of their agriculture</u>
<u n="223" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0650">it's weird</u>
<u n="225" who="S0282">that is very weird isn't it?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0650" trans="overlap">it is yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0282">gosh I suppose they've got a lot of land though haven't they? perhaps er perhaps they're not they haven't got the same sort of the the panic about it that we do cos we're always sort of saying oh we're running out we're running out of land there's not enough room whereas France is very spread out and sometimes actually</u>
<u n="228" who="S0650" trans="overlap">it is yes</u>
<u n="229" who="S0282" trans="overlap">you look at the way the French sort of set things out and you think <pause dur="short"/> you're being very careless actually with your</u>
<u n="230" who="S0650">oh that's that's</u>
<u n="231" who="S0282" trans="overlap">with your countryside</u>
<u n="232" who="S0650">it's funny that you say that because erm French people coming over here erm we've er taken erm er <trunc>peo</trunc> like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her sister and so on down to <anon type="place"/> and the thing that they always say is oh the countryside in England is manicured</u>
<u n="233" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0650">er er which I find weird actually because when you drive around er the suburbs of Paris where there are gardens or in Normandy where there are good farms they look after them</u>
<u n="235" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0650">beautifully</u>
<u n="237" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0650">because they have this sense of style <vocal desc="laugh"/> or</u>
<u n="239" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0650" trans="overlap"><unclear>whatever it is</unclear> and everything has to be very presentable</u>
<u n="241" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0650">erm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0282">well even in the middle where there's very little and very few people</u>
<u n="244" who="S0650">yes</u>
<u n="245" who="S0282" trans="overlap">when you drive across it's all</u>
<u n="246" who="S0650">yes</u>
<u n="247" who="S0282">it's all you know you it's not like being in America where you've got the Badlands or wild quite wild country</u>
<u n="248" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0282" trans="overlap">that's not obvious that it belongs to anybody it's all terribly cultivated</u>
<u n="250" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0282">how strange <pause dur="short"/> gosh</u>
<u n="252" who="S0650">I'm sure you read about the guy who was not allowed to run a ski school</u>
<u n="253" who="S0282">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="254" who="S0650" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm his his mother erm finished up looking after one of the departments in the in the Pyrenees</u>
<u n="255" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="256" who="S0650">and as a result of that he got the opportunity to ski right through I think two or three winters and got himself qualified as a ski instructor</u>
<u n="257" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="258" who="S0650">but they <trunc>wo</trunc>won't allow <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for example is just as good if not better skier but he's not allowed to instruct at all</u>
<u n="259" who="S0282">because?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0650">because has hasn't gone through the rigmarole of taking all these exams</u>
<u n="261" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="262" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and erm this that and the other and so on</u>
<u n="263" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="264" who="S0650" trans="overlap">it's just childish really</u>
<u n="265" who="S0282">well I don't know I I often think the French are fifty percent of them are bureaucrats and the other half are anarchists</u>
<u n="266" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="268" who="S0650">yes that's just about true yes</u>
<u n="269" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and they kind of hold each other in a state of</u>
<u n="270" who="S0650" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes <unclear/> yes</u>
<u n="271" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>status</unclear></u>
<u n="272" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0282">my mother's definitely on er on the anarchic side actually</u>
<u n="274" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0282">she's she went to some you know if you have the misfortune to go into a courtroom with her or something and you stand up when the judge comes in my mother's sitting there starting to go I don't see why I should have to stand up for him he's only a human being like the rest of us</u>
<u n="276" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0650">er at one point erm I'm I I I had a heart attack and erm I thought while I while I was recovering I couldn't work I will erm er er brush up my German so I went to <anon type="place"/> college</u>
<u n="279" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="280" who="S0650">and er in and er it it it's a I think it's a a college of further education or whatever they call it anyway</u>
<u n="281" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="282" who="S0650">er it's very the language language department is very well run the head of the language department is a French lady</u>
<u n="283" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="284" who="S0650">and her sister she introduced me to her sister her sister is the most joyous individual she is one of the anarchists</u>
<u n="285" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="286" who="S0650">and you know erm in I think it was in Nicaragua</u>
<u n="287" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="288" who="S0650">erm or one of those Central American erm countries they what do they call the <trunc>com</trunc> <trunc>c</trunc> can you remember what they were called?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="290" who="S0650">contra something or other</u>
<u n="291" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yes yes yes yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0650" trans="overlap">mm anyway somehow she got herself into a position of editing the a book by one of these I wish I could remember what they're called erm they're <trunc>r</trunc><trunc>r</trunc><trunc>r</trunc>rebels against the Americans at any rate</u>
<u n="293" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0650">erm and er I got to know her quite well and she certainly had anarchist tendencies and on one occasion the book was being published in Paris and so</u>
<u n="295" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="296" who="S0650">she er was going backwards and forwards and er she was doing a job I think also I dunno if it was in <anon type="place"/> college but it was something to do with education anyway erm and er she went over to Paris and she came back absolutely knackered and I said</u>
<u n="297" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0650">what on earth? you know oh she said there was a <foreign lang="fre">manif</foreign> I said what? she said yes we there was a very good <foreign lang="fre">manif</foreign> on the Champs-Elysees what would be what she meant was there was a demonstration</u>
<u n="299" who="S0282">uhu <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0650">erm about something or other which something had done I said what was it all about? it took me about two hours to discover that she really hadn't a clue what the demonstration was about</u>
<u n="301" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but she joined in</u>
<u n="302" who="S0650">she joined in because it was a good party</u>
<u n="303" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0650">literally literally</u>
<u n="305" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's the most extraordinary performance to be fair at the end of it all she gave me a signed copy of the book which had been published <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="307" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="308" who="S0650">which was rather fun and it was all about smuggling things like bicycles</u>
<u n="309" who="S0282">smuggling bicycles okay</u>
<u n="310" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="311" who="S0282">uhu <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="312" who="S0650" trans="overlap">now into central America well I always thought central America was er you know straight up and down no <unclear>flatlands</unclear> at all but</u>
<u n="313" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="314" who="S0650">the thought of bicycling around Nicaragua oh I wish I could remember what they were called <trunc>th</trunc>these people</u>
<u n="315" who="S0282">oh no I my brain has gone as well now</u>
<u n="316" who="S0650" trans="overlap">but but the the sort of villain of the piece was a man called Noriega I think</u>
<u n="317" who="S0282">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that sounds familiar</u>
<u n="318" who="S0650">Confindustria er Confindustria for the Italian erm CPI not that <pause dur="short"/> contra something or other</u>
<u n="319" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="320" who="S0650">anyway</u>
<u n="321" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="322" who="S0650">it was quite a interesting experience</u>
<u n="323" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0650">er but I've got to know quite a lot of French people and really quite well and</u>
<u n="325" who="S0282">you seem to have a constant stream of French people actually</u>
<u n="326" who="S0650">we do yes because they like coming over here</u>
<u n="327" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="328" who="S0650">they live in Primark getting our our</u>
<u n="329" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh I know well the little girls we have at the <unclear>brics</unclear> who are all</u>
<u n="330" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="331" who="S0282" trans="overlap">all from this school in Bordeaux</u>
<u n="332" who="S0650">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0282">and we have a link with a school in Bordeaux because when I was growing up erm there was a young woman called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who used to come over in the holidays and look after us</u>
<u n="334" who="S0650">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and er she had a student she then went on to be a student and and</u>
<u n="336" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0282">this <trunc>stu</trunc> one of her students said to her I need a placement in England so <trunc>sh</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> phoned me up and said could you take a student? and then since then we've been taking two a year so we have <vocal desc="laugh"/> we had this sort of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who's a fellow trustee said erm oh yes I've just been looking at the people who have been visiting our website and looking at the statistics and strangely we seem to have a lot of people in Bordeaux looking at our website</u>
<u n="338" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so I said yes it's all the students that go to a particular school researching us</u>
<u n="340" who="S0650">oh right</u>
<u n="341" who="S0282">before they write to us and say can I come over and do two months' placement with you so erm so we have this ongoing link with erm with the students in Bordeaux but they all come over here and erm they're very naive really about what to expect when they get to London and some of them have the most horrible adventures with</u>
<u n="342" who="S0650" trans="overlap">oh lord <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0282" trans="overlap">rental properties and unscrupulous</u>
<u n="344" who="S0650" trans="overlap">oh lord yes</u>
<u n="345" who="S0282" trans="overlap">types and whatever</u>
<u n="346" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0282">so and they're cos they're always trying to economise by finding you know finding flats on the internet and you can't tell them that London's a big place and it's full of strangers and that that actually you can't trust anybody you meet on the internet and there's one girl</u>
<u n="348" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0282">in particular who got awfully stung and erm and er somebody took about two thousand euros off her in advance</u>
<u n="350" who="S0650">oh dear</u>
<u n="351" who="S0282" trans="overlap">er rental on a flat and turned out to be</u>
<u n="352" who="S0650" trans="overlap">god</u>
<u n="353" who="S0282" trans="overlap">a complete fake and the flat didn't exist and</u>
<u n="354" who="S0650">oh heavens</u>
<u n="355" who="S0282">I know</u>
<u n="356" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0282" trans="overlap">so they do they do actually fall er get themselves into trouble from time to time</u>
<u n="358" who="S0650">yeah I spent a day Bordeaux is a rather a nice place actually I think</u>
<u n="359" who="S0282">oh I hate it</u>
<u n="360" who="S0650">oh do you? oh I</u>
<u n="361" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0650">had very happy times there er when I was working in <anon type="place"/> cathedral they sent me to France to find out how they look after the cathedrals there</u>
<u n="363" who="S0282">oh yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0650">and er I was the the</u>
<u n="365" who="S0282" trans="overlap">they have a splendid cathedral</u>
<u n="366" who="S0650">er Bordeaux erm and the reason I was sent to Bordeaux was because it was English for such a very long time and they were actually keen to find out the the clerk of the works and his erm people in <anon type="place"/> were keen to find out whether er <trunc>anybo</trunc> there'd been any exchange of er craftsmen and technology between</u>
<u n="367" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="368" who="S0650">the British colony in Bordeaux</u>
<u n="369" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0650">and the er <trunc>Chi</trunc> two particular cathedrals Chichester and and erm Salisbury</u>
<u n="371" who="S0282">oh gosh</u>
<u n="372" who="S0650">I don't know if you've have you been to Chichester? the the the point</u>
<u n="373" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm no</u>
<u n="374" who="S0650">but it's it's as the cathedral is very interesting <vocal desc="laugh"/> one one of the most quirky and interesting things about it is that a man was in the nave with a box original box camera in eighteen sixty something when the spire imploded</u>
<u n="375" who="S0282"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0650">and he er he managed to take photographs of it actually happening</u>
<u n="377" who="S0282">oh my god</u>
<u n="378" who="S0650" trans="overlap">er and and they're really primitive pictures but you can see it's most interesting things because you can see that once the er <pause dur="short"/> the inner cement so to speak mortar mortar started to crumble the weight er you it it went like that er right down</u>
<u n="379" who="S0282" trans="overlap">like a sodden pudding</u>
<u n="380" who="S0650">yes</u>
<u n="381" who="S0282" trans="overlap">or something yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0650">yes er</u>
<u n="383" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="384" who="S0650">yes really strange and the other thing that</u>
<u n="385" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I had no idea that had happened</u>
<u n="386" who="S0650">erm the you can and well if you go there you will see the photographs</u>
<u n="387" who="S0282">wow</u>
<u n="388" who="S0650">at a tourist attraction</u>
<u n="389" who="S0282">wow</u>
<u n="390" who="S0650">and the other thing about er er Chichester is that there is still to this day erm they have a a a proper international stone yard er an awful lot of er churches in the south of England use quoin stone</u>
<u n="391" who="S0282">oh do they? oh</u>
<u n="392" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes uhu er and if for example Peterborough which is miles up er erm that's got</u>
<u n="393" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah no</u>
<u n="394" who="S0650" trans="overlap">a lot of French stone</u>
<u n="395" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yes absolutely I suppose</u>
<u n="396" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="397" who="S0282" trans="overlap">it's quite near the eastern coast if</u>
<u n="398" who="S0650" trans="overlap">oh yes it was</u>
<u n="399" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0650" trans="overlap">it would go up the River Nene in a</u>
<u n="401" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="402" who="S0650">in a barge</u>
<u n="403" who="S0282" trans="overlap">so perhaps it was that so you sort of went up that side of the country to get to</u>
<u n="404" who="S0650">any rate I I went er with the direct er directed by the clerk of the works in Salisbury erm to the people in Chichester and then I was sent off to Bordeaux to see whether there was any</u>
<u n="405" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="406" who="S0650" trans="overlap">any link</u>
<u n="407" who="S0282">and was there?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0650">there is of craftsmen erm it's quite limited</u>
<u n="409" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="410" who="S0650" trans="overlap">erm there's no what I call <vocal desc="laugh"/> what they quite heavy lifting erm they didn't er pick up any erm constructive technology from er Bordeaux</u>
<u n="411" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="412" who="S0650">no all of that came from <trunc>mm</trunc> er particularly from the Abbey at St Denis</u>
<u n="413" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="414" who="S0650" trans="overlap">actually erm and to Canterbury and so on</u>
<u n="415" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="416" who="S0650">erm</u>
<u n="417" who="S0282">but craftsmen individual craftsmen were going</u>
<u n="418" who="S0650" trans="overlap">individual craftsmen who would go and do for example <trunc>th</trunc>that they you must have seen bosses the stone bosses</u>
<u n="419" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="420" who="S0650" trans="overlap">which are beautifully carved and and some there was an interchange between craftsmen from France coming through England</u>
<u n="421" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0650">and vice versa</u>
<u n="423" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="424" who="S0650">but erm otherwise no not</u>
<u n="425" who="S0282">oh right yes</u>
<u n="426" who="S0650">nobody er nobody knows quite who was the engineering brain behind Salisbury cathedral because it it it's it is an engineering feat</u>
<u n="427" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0650" trans="overlap">there</u>
<u n="429" who="S0282">well then er they are just when you look at them and think about what the must have been involved in conceiving them and building them then I mean well it must have taken well it did take decades in some instances didn't it to put them up? there's that wonderful erm William Golding novel called The Spire</u>
<u n="430" who="S0650">oh yes that's right that's right absolutely you know</u>
<u n="431" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and I think it's an absolutely fantastic book</u>
<u n="432" who="S0650" trans="overlap">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0282" trans="overlap">a man of a man obsessed really <pause dur="short"/> yes we we managed to find something about the architecture of erm <anon type="place"/> for erm <pause dur="short"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s son <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was helping us out a bit</u>
<u n="434" who="S0650" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="435" who="S0282">and he did a bit of digging around and found out a bit more about our architect and it was the only the only building he ever <trunc>l</trunc>led on so he was part of architectural team with erm William Tite or something who was quite a famous architect of the time</u>
<u n="436" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="437" who="S0282">but he he only ever sort of led on one building which was our building</u>
<u n="438" who="S0650">really?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0282">but erm but you know he was erm he he got quite good press for it really in those days</u>
<u n="440" who="S0650" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0282">er but</u>
<u n="442" who="S0650" trans="overlap">but there was a street named after him</u>
<u n="443" who="S0282">yes the one opposite</u>
<u n="444" who="S0650">what was it called?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0282"><anon type="place"/> road yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0650"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="447" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0650" trans="overlap">is it? <anon type="place"/> yes</u>
<u n="449" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="450" who="S0650" trans="overlap">er yes</u>
<u n="451" who="S0282">so</u>
<u n="452" who="S0650" trans="overlap">but I've never found a I've never heard of any come across any other building that's put up by him</u>
<u n="453" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="454" who="S0650">I suppose that's right</u>
<u n="455" who="S0282">no he was</u>
<u n="456" who="S0650" trans="overlap">er</u>
<u n="457" who="S0282">there were some there were other churches he worked on as part of a team for a boss but <anon type="place"/> is his only his only <trunc>s</trunc>sole creation really</u>
<u n="458" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah oh</u>
<u n="459" who="S0282">so so that's it that was fun that was quite fun to find that out actually so we we this this open day thing was quite good for us it was it was</u>
<u n="460" who="S0650" trans="overlap">I'd noticed you'd put some lovely erm prints or drawings up as you go in at the bottom of the lift</u>
<u n="461" who="S0282">yeah yes</u>
<u n="462" who="S0650" trans="overlap">that's rather fascinating</u>
<u n="463" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0650" trans="overlap">or <trunc>pho</trunc>photographs of</u>
<u n="465" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no that's my little photographic expedition <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="467" who="S0282">all these photographs from the <anon type="place"/> archives</u>
<u n="468" who="S0650">yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0282">there's quite a that quite an amazing of the spire of <anon type="place"/> across the fields because it was there</u>
<u n="470" who="S0650" trans="overlap">oh yes yeah</u>
<u n="471" who="S0282" trans="overlap">before all the houses came so</u>
<u n="472" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="473" who="S0282">so it's sort of standing on its own in the middle of an orchard or something</u>
<u n="474" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0282">which is hard to imagine these days <pause dur="short"/> with er all that traffic rushing past us</u>
<u n="476" who="S0650">do you still have an annual art exhibition?</u>
<u n="477" who="S0282">we do</u>
<u n="478" who="S0650">yeah</u>
<u n="479" who="S0282">we do</u>
<u n="480" who="S0650">great</u>
<u n="481" who="S0282">so and actually <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who is the art teacher is now</u>
<u n="482" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="483" who="S0282" trans="overlap">now running classes on our building as well so so that's <trunc>actua</trunc> so I'm hoping that we're going to reposition ourselves and be a bit more artistic have a few more kind of</u>
<u n="484" who="S0650" trans="overlap">oh that's good</u>
<u n="485" who="S0282" trans="overlap">kind of of that sort of class going on</u>
<u n="486" who="S0650">yes</u>
<u n="487" who="S0282" trans="overlap">where people pay for it apparently erm</u>
<u n="488" who="S0650">there'll be er er on the twenty-ninth there'll be a girl erm there called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="490" who="S0650">I'll introduce you to her she works for <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0282">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="492" who="S0650">erm</u>
<u n="493" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="494" who="S0650">and erm well you might find it quite a useful link I don't know</u>
<u n="495" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0650">yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0650">er because they've got a lot er er a large educational programme</u>
<u n="499" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0650"><trunc>w</trunc> on <trunc>r</trunc></u>
<u n="501" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I think you were trying you there was somebody before wasn't there?</u>
<u n="502" who="S0650">yes there was yes there was</u>
<u n="503" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I mean years ago and didn't come off for some reason</u>
<u n="504" who="S0650" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="505" who="S0282">I can't remember what that was the</u>
<u n="506" who="S0650" trans="overlap">oh I think the reason it came <trunc>o</trunc> didn't come off was cos I think I got ill</u>
<u n="507" who="S0282">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="508" who="S0650" trans="overlap">erm erm and I had to postpone meetings I've I've I've er do remember that actually</u>
<u n="509" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="510" who="S0650">and <unclear/> that's what happened</u>
<u n="511" who="S0282">I think there might <trunc>ha</trunc> it was also there was something else as well I don't <trunc>remem</trunc> I think there was can't remember what the problem</u>
<u n="512" who="S0650" trans="overlap">I certainly arranged for somebody from the <anon type="place"/> to talk to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> actually</u>
<u n="513" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="514" who="S0650">that I know that that did come off erm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0282">oh I think but I think it might have been one of those things where there was one conversation and then one person said that I need to pass you on to another person and then as so often happens</u>
<u n="516" who="S0650">yes</u>
<u n="517" who="S0282">that's where it never quite</u>
<u n="518" who="S0650" trans="overlap">oh it</u>
<u n="519" who="S0282" trans="overlap">actually kind of comes about</u>
<u n="520" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes yes</u>
<u n="521" who="S0282" trans="overlap">despite good intentions on both sides and I I think</u>
<u n="522" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0282" trans="overlap">the timing the timing cos of the timing of the art competition or something it didn't work out I can't remember but erm <pause dur="short"/> no it's been it's been erm no we still do it and we still have our little French students helping us out it's a way of kind of marketing without marketing really</u>
<u n="524" who="S0650" trans="overlap">well yeah mm</u>
<u n="525" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but as the open day was a way of marketing</u>
<u n="526" who="S0650">mm</u>
<u n="527" who="S0282">cos that I think you know it has limited I don't know how we've we market ourselves I think the best way is to have people in the hall and saying you know oh what a lovely hall I think I might come back here</u>
<u n="528" who="S0650" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="529" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so so we're having all kinds of difficulties with er with er with the congregation again of course <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="530" who="S0650" trans="overlap">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> in what way?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0282">well we were having an argument er there was the most surreal argument at the AGM about the bollards <pause dur="short"/> because there was</u>
<u n="532" who="S0650" trans="overlap">outside the west end?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="534" who="S0650">mm</u>
<u n="535" who="S0282">because there were there was a few instants where the people who run the nightclub opposite were just taking over the car park at night and there were a couple of er attacks stabbings</u>
<u n="536" who="S0650">oh lord</u>
<u n="537" who="S0282" trans="overlap">where the perpetrators were loitering in our car park and jumping out on people in <anon type="place"/> and</u>
<u n="538" who="S0650">oh</u>
<u n="539" who="S0282" trans="overlap">stabbing them</u>
<u n="540" who="S0650">dear</u>
<u n="541" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and then jumping in the car and rushing off and there was also lots of drug dealing so we decided that that we were going to lock the bollards so we had a rather surreal conversation where we had a delegation from the church demanding that they be allowed to have a bollard please so given that we were reporting on the fact that our finances were up the creek at the time</u>
<u n="542" who="S0650">mm</u>
<u n="543" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and then they turned up and said yeah but yeah but can please can we have a bollard please? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="545" who="S0282">so as usual a completely disproportionate response to er</u>
<u n="546" who="S0650" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="547" who="S0282">so anyway so you've begun to when you retired you were going to sort of help the the the association round here but did you did your estate here get taken over in the end by an <anon type="place"/> or a whatever it was?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0650" trans="overlap"><trunc>ye</trunc>yes what happened er was that er the council erm they er wanted to get rid of responsibility for all their freehold on what was originally the <anon type="place"/> estate</u>
<u n="549" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="550" who="S0650">and erm</u>
<u n="551" who="S0282">I presume this was enough to <unclear>win a</unclear> bombsite or something</u>
<u n="552" who="S0650"><trunc>abso</trunc>absolutely</u>
<u n="553" who="S0282" trans="overlap">or did they knock it down <trunc>del</trunc>deliberately?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0650">no no</u>
<u n="555" who="S0282" trans="overlap">they didn't knock it down deliberately?</u>
<u n="556" who="S0650" trans="overlap">no no no it was it was it was</u>
<u n="557" who="S0282" trans="overlap">thank goodness for that</u>
<u n="558" who="S0650" trans="overlap"><trunc>fla</trunc>flattened and er well what er what then happened was that er the tenants and residents association erm put together a a a <trunc>sh</trunc> I think they called it a shadow regeneration board</u>
<u n="559" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="560" who="S0650">erm and I er er they erm er selected the they interviewed and <trunc>s</trunc> er and then selected a er housing association <anon type="place"/> housing <trunc>ass</trunc> <anon type="place"/> housing trust erm and at that point erm it this er there was a meeting of the tenants and residents association and a presentation was made by somebody from this shadow board and I started asking questions and erm I was asked to join the board</u>
<u n="561" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="562" who="S0650">and er er we were responsible for er putting together a package er which covered all the functions which er had been discharged by the council</u>
<u n="563" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="564" who="S0650">to service their tenants on this estate and that was er the the terms the legislation which provides for the transfer away from the council to a recognised housing</u>
<u n="565" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="566" who="S0650" trans="overlap">association and that has to be voted on</u>
<u n="567" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0650">and there was a <pause dur="short"/> a a a ballot er based on the proposals which the this shadow board had agreed erm and everybody mm by an an a marginal majority I don't think it was about <trunc>th</trunc> twenty votes so to speak I <trunc>d</trunc> two hundred and something erm they decided against it</u>
<u n="569" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="570" who="S0650">erm but yours</u>
<u n="571" who="S0282" trans="overlap">gosh</u>
<u n="572" who="S0650">yours truly being I was rather surprised from talking to people because I thought it would be passed on a nod almost</u>
<u n="573" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0650">I discovered that that the ballot had been rigged</u>
<u n="575" who="S0282"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="576" who="S0650">and that people had been going round erm er er er er saying er <trunc>ca</trunc> to people who in in the two <unclear>wings that are sheltered</unclear> that's all sheltered housing</u>
<u n="577" who="S0282">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="578" who="S0650" trans="overlap">at the far far end knocking on the doors and say oh give us your erm er er voting er card and we'll put it in the ballot ballot box and erm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0282">oh no</u>
<u n="580" who="S0650">they'd they'd either been telling people how to vote or they'd just not been putting the er papers in the ballot box</u>
<u n="581" who="S0282">oh no</u>
<u n="582" who="S0650">and the the the truth of it was that the electoral that the ballot was carried out by the I think it's called the electoral reform society</u>
<u n="583" who="S0282">it is yeah that's our</u>
<u n="584" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and they had been so slovenly er they they should</u>
<u n="585" who="S0282" trans="overlap">had they really? they should</u>
<u n="586" who="S0650" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="587" who="S0282" trans="overlap">they're supposed to be the people who are the example of how to do this</u>
<u n="588" who="S0650" trans="overlap">they were not they were just lazy</u>
<u n="589" who="S0282">really?</u>
<u n="590" who="S0650">idle and so we erm <trunc>w</trunc>we we had to go to get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to approach the minister of state who is a good lady called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="592" who="S0650">erm and er with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s help erm yours truly wrote to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and said can we please have a revamp? and that was the agreed the <trunc>gov</trunc> the department of the environment I think it was called</u>
<u n="593" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="594" who="S0650">ministry of housing erm</u>
<u n="595" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="596" who="S0650">they said yes and erm the second time round the offer made by erm metropolitan</u>
<u n="597" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="598" who="S0650">was accepted</u>
<u n="599" who="S0282">oh right okay</u>
<u n="600" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and then erm the offer was based on metropolitan spending twenty-four million pounds</u>
<u n="601" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="602" who="S0650">on the regeneration of the estate</u>
<u n="603" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="604" who="S0650">erm and er er the the board the shadow board was er er given permanent er status so to speak and er it it had to allow for a a rotation in membership</u>
<u n="605" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="606" who="S0650">and I er volunteered to stand down erm after the first I think it was two years erm and er <pause dur="short"/> it it had erm mm we had approved the initial essential work programme</u>
<u n="607" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="608" who="S0650" trans="overlap">the sort of urgent repairs that needed doing and then I stood down but just before I stood down er they came up they discovered there was er asbestos all over the place</u>
<u n="609" who="S0282">oh no</u>
<u n="610" who="S0650">yeah and erm <trunc>th</trunc>they the health and safety people moved in</u>
<u n="611" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="612" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and said you've got to take all this asbestos out and it was blue or brown or pink or I don't know what what it was and er</u>
<u n="613" who="S0282" trans="overlap">the harmful kind</u>
<u n="614" who="S0650"><trunc>y</trunc>yeah it was the harmful sort yeah</u>
<u n="615" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="616" who="S0650">erm and er er we were told that we if we had this could have it done for free</u>
<u n="617" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="618" who="S0650">erm and I said well that's fine but I <trunc>w</trunc> I want want a contract and so on and I said no can't do things for free that it's not like they could do things</u>
<u n="619" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="620" who="S0650">and the <anon type="place"/> was so slovenly and just generally uncooperative because they also at the same time erm were proposing to redo redo the rooves</u>
<u n="621" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="622" who="S0650">er of the houses er which had got asbestos in them and so we <trunc>sai</trunc> which er which was freehold which we all said well if you're going to do redo this those er rooves can't you do our rooves as well? they said oh no they said no and</u>
<u n="623" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="624" who="S0650">one way or another I just got and we all got completely fed up</u>
<u n="625" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="626" who="S0650" trans="overlap">with <anon type="place"/> I'm not quite sure where the problem lay but at at a higher level in the local <anon type="place"/> people because all the <anon type="place"/> people we'd originally been dealing with they suddenly they all resigned <pause dur="short"/> they vanished and we got a lot of people trying to run this replacement of the they are called fascia boards where the asbestos was er of <trunc>cour</trunc> didn't know their way round the estate they were er</u>
<u n="627" who="S0282">oh how <unclear/></u>
<u n="628" who="S0650" trans="overlap">er I think it it was very unsatisfactory the whole thing and er they'd been erm I'm out of it now but I I just got completely browned off</u>
<u n="629" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no I'm not surprised really</u>
<u n="630" who="S0650">er er it was really tiresome</u>
<u n="631" who="S0282" trans="overlap">not surprised and I think some of these <trunc>ass</trunc> that some of these housing associations claim they overreach themselves and</u>
<u n="632" who="S0650">yes</u>
<u n="633" who="S0282">got out of their depth</u>
<u n="634" who="S0650">yes</u>
<u n="635" who="S0282" trans="overlap">with all this stuff</u>
<u n="636" who="S0650">well they've got very weak management</u>
<u n="637" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="638" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and they don't pay attention to details they they <trunc>s</trunc>sent us round at the end of the <trunc>repl</trunc> the replacing of the fascia boards they gave us all erm a a letter er saying this is what we've done and it it it literally did not make sense it</u>
<u n="639" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="640" who="S0650">and so we had had to you know er er we get <anon type="place"/> to issue new letters and then erm it's in in the case of our house erm and it said that they had replaced the Vent-Axia erm the extractor fan they hadn't</u>
<u n="641" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="642" who="S0650">and er er and in one of the houses</u>
<u n="643" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="644" who="S0650">two two or three down that way erm fortunately er the the freeholder erm er noticed the work was being done when she was not aware it was about to be done and she she'd found that the guy who was doing the work had muddled up the numbers</u>
<u n="645" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="646" who="S0650">and he was doing work which should have been for</u>
<u n="647" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="648" who="S0650" trans="overlap">number eighty-four</u>
<u n="649" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="650" who="S0650">on number eighty-three and number eighty-four you know when you come up the street and the houses</u>
<u n="651" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="652" who="S0650" trans="overlap">on that side are completely different?</u>
<u n="653" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="654" who="S0650">there's a small dock which belonged to the council</u>
<u n="655" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="656" who="S0650">that's number eighty-four and they're</u>
<u n="657" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="658" who="S0650">early Victorian houses and he</u>
<u n="659" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="660" who="S0650" trans="overlap">should have been doing a job on that on the house over there</u>
<u n="661" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="662" who="S0650">and he was doing trying to do that sort of just didn't work at all</u>
<u n="663" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="664" who="S0650">er</u>
<u n="665" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I remember once getting a free boiler service like that</u>
<u n="666" who="S0650">mm</u>
<u n="667" who="S0282" trans="overlap">when somebody was supposed to be at somebody else's house but it's not very satisfactory is it really? that's bizarre isn't it? so erm have you lived here since it was new?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0650">since what?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0282">since this this was new this house?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0650" trans="overlap">no no the the houses were built in nineteen sixty-seven</u>
<u n="671" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="672" who="S0650">and er erm they were privatised by wait a minute <trunc>n</trunc> that's not no nineteen seventy-six that's</u>
<u n="673" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="674" who="S0650" trans="overlap"><trunc>ni</trunc> seventy-six and then Mrs Thatcher introduced the er sale of council houses and er er about er I think it's actually over fifty percent of the houses here <trunc>w</trunc> have been privatised</u>
<u n="675" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="676" who="S0650">yeah and this house was erm the tenant was a builder erm and he made various changes erm including disconnecting the house from the communal heating</u>
<u n="677" who="S0282">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="678" who="S0650" trans="overlap">erm which in fact was a erm a a really sensible thing to do</u>
<u n="679" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="680" who="S0650" trans="overlap"><trunc>bu</trunc>but it meant that we had extraordinary pipework erm sticking up into the kitchen this wall was about where you are now</u>
<u n="681" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="682" who="S0650">where you and I are now and there there was a a curious pipe connection sticking up into the middle of the kitchen it was really very very odd indeed</u>
<u n="683" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="684" who="S0650">but the <trunc>disconnect</trunc> the the discontinuance of the communal heating system was one of the erm jobs which er <anon type="place"/> was supposed to do erm and er they <trunc>m</trunc>made a Horlicks of that too they didn't realise that half of the estate is erm on the front level <unclear/></u>
<u n="685" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh oh really?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0650">and where that is the case the erm the houses are built in pairs in fact</u>
<u n="687" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="688" who="S0650">and underneath that wall and not under this this wall but under the next wall erm there was a a er like a er a solid wall</u>
<u n="689" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="690" who="S0650" trans="overlap">so that no water can pass through one to the other</u>
<u n="691" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="692" who="S0650">and</u>
<u n="693" who="S0282" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="694" who="S0650">erm just pipes and that's all and then the the wall here is is it isn't any longer but it was relatively it had a big hole in it in fact</u>
<u n="695" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="696" who="S0650">erm and there is a tunnel which you can er go through er which was built originally erm as a er er like a a test <unclear/> it's for it's you need to find out where the heating could go <trunc>wh</trunc>where</u>
<u n="697" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="698" who="S0650" trans="overlap">where there were other pipes and so on</u>
<u n="699" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="700" who="S0650">but when they when <anon type="place"/> discontinued the communal heating they didn't realise that er these walls must be replaced otherwise if there was a a the I think it's called the <anon type="place"/> river</u>
<u n="701" who="S0282">oh the <anon type="place"/> right it's here as well is it?</u>
<u n="702" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and if if there's if there's a very high tide</u>
<u n="703" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="704" who="S0650">the water backs up</u>
<u n="705" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="706" who="S0650">and the the erm</u>
<u n="707" who="S0282"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="708" who="S0650" trans="overlap">the the these er chambers cos they're they're not really like cellars you can't get into them</u>
<u n="709" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="710" who="S0650"><trunc>o</trunc>other than by going through a manhole</u>
<u n="711" who="S0282">right gosh</u>
<u n="712" who="S0650" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> any rate <pause dur="short"/> erm it was just another area where <anon type="place"/> were were being really stupid and another thing they did</u>
<u n="713" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="714" who="S0650">which infuriated <trunc>for</trunc>fortunately we weren't involved erm they were charging people for erm electric light and heating hot water and heating</u>
<u n="715" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="716" who="S0650">erm who who erm were not getting any</u>
<u n="717" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="718" who="S0650" trans="overlap">er it's quite extraordinary and er</u>
<u n="719" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="720" who="S0650" trans="overlap">they they let us know that they were going to disconnect the communal aerial there's a communal erm er a television aerial on the top of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="721" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0650">erm and er <trunc>w</trunc><trunc>w</trunc>we erm were sent a note saying this was going to be disconnected and we didn't think we <trunc>w</trunc> we were on it and so we asked them to check and they said oh no you're not on it and then there was a long pause and then about six months later erm our er television suddenly stopped working and we found <vocal desc="laugh"/> that they they'd when</u>
<u n="723" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="724" who="S0650">whether we were connected to it or not I don't really know but anyway they'd cut through some wires when they were disconnected that</u>
<u n="725" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and cut through our television</u>
<u n="727" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="728" who="S0650">aerial wire</u>
<u n="729" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="730" who="S0650">so we we sort of oh enough is a enough and we bought a a a saucer</u>
<u n="731" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="732" who="S0650">and a lot of other people have similar bought saucers</u>
<u n="733" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="734" who="S0650">but that's where <anon type="place"/> have been very unsatisfactory they pay no attention to detail at all</u>
<u n="735" who="S0282">no that's every exasperating isn't it?</u>
<u n="736" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="737" who="S0282" trans="overlap">very exasperating I mean are they they must be they sounds as if they're more exasperating than <anon type="place"/> in fact which</u>
<u n="738" who="S0650">well by quite honestly they are actually because at least <anon type="place"/> clean the streets</u>
<u n="739" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="740" who="S0650">and they also erm er <trunc>o</trunc>offered us and gave us a quarterly test inspection</u>
<u n="741" who="S0282">oh yeah</u>
<u n="742" who="S0650" trans="overlap">so and the <trunc>infesta</trunc> we had cockroaches or er whatever erm every quarter we could be certain that they would be extinguished or eradicated or</u>
<u n="743" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="744" who="S0650">you know</u>
<u n="745" who="S0282">that makes sense to do it</u>
<u n="746" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and they</u>
<u n="747" who="S0282">in advance doesn't it? rather than</u>
<u n="748" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes it does</u>
<u n="749" who="S0282" trans="overlap">wait till they've</u>
<u n="750" who="S0650" trans="overlap"><trunc>ab</trunc>absolutely</u>
<u n="751" who="S0282">especially with these modern builds where they've got</u>
<u n="752" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="753" who="S0282" trans="overlap">voids and passages and things</u>
<u n="754" who="S0650">yeah they</u>
<u n="755" who="S0282" trans="overlap">through the brickwork that you</u>
<u n="756" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="757" who="S0282">they pop up everywhere but</u>
<u n="758" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="759" who="S0282">have no idea</u>
<u n="760" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so our experience with <anon type="place"/> has not been very happy I'm afraid</u>
<u n="761" who="S0282">oh no that's</u>
<u n="762" who="S0650">yeah</u>
<u n="763" who="S0282" trans="overlap">that's sad really oh dear</u>
<u n="764" who="S0650">then erm there were er two councillors that were er on the <anon type="place"/> the the it's called <anon type="place"/> regeneration board and I got to know them one of them quite well one of them was a Liberal chap and I dunno what happened he lost his seat or something and the other one was a a Labour chap and he stayed on and I got to know him quite well and he was quite a conscious councillor dealing with local issues and so on</u>
<u n="765" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="766" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/> he wrote to me and said would I sponsor him in the last round of local elections</u>
<u n="767" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="768" who="S0650">and I I said I just wrote back and said no way er <vocal desc="laugh"/> he asked why and I said well <vocal desc="laugh"/> a man who <vocal desc="laugh"/> says that he's going to cap energy prices must be mad</u>
<u n="769" who="S0282">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="770" who="S0650">and said oh why I didn't know he was going to I it was it was the most <trunc>sh</trunc> awful experience with this guy who was</u>
<u n="771" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="772" who="S0650" trans="overlap">you know er standing as a Labour councillor hadn't a clue what the Labour</u>
<u n="773" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="774" who="S0650" trans="overlap">their policies were</u>
<u n="775" who="S0282">mm oh well</u>
<u n="776" who="S0650">anyway there you go</u>
<u n="777" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="778" who="S0650">mm</u>
<u n="779" who="S0282">I see</u>
<u n="780" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="781" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so oh it's a bit sad about the writing did you finish that book that you were working on when you were?</u>
<u n="782" who="S0650" trans="overlap">I've got up to I've got up to sixteen forty-eight</u>
<u n="783" who="S0282">right and how many how many <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="784" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="785" who="S0282">how much more have you got to go?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0650">er I'm erm er er er it goes up to nineteen eighteen</u>
<u n="787" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="788" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and I actually have read up up to nineteen eighteen</u>
<u n="789" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="790" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and it's just a question of sorting myself out and sitting down and and putting something down on paper but</u>
<u n="791" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="792" who="S0650">it takes quite a long time to do that and it I did too lame and too lazy to go what you have to do is to go every day to the British Library and</u>
<u n="793" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and <unclear/> do it</u>
<u n="794" who="S0650">er because to make a a book worth reading you have to contribute some sort of original view on subjects</u>
<u n="795" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="796" who="S0650">and erm <pause dur="short"/> the I suppose er just at the moment it's actually interesting because a whole lot of new material has come into the public domain erm whereas after the well the research work by one or two really erm well established historians</u>
<u n="797" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="798" who="S0650" trans="overlap">about the lead up to nineteen fourteen</u>
<u n="799" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="800" who="S0650">and why it happened</u>
<u n="801" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="802" who="S0650">erm and I was looking at a lot of those books and they are erm very interesting</u>
<u n="803" who="S0282">okay</u>
<u n="804" who="S0650" trans="overlap">very interesting indeed erm <pause dur="short"/> so I I shall go back to it and try and finish it off</u>
<u n="805" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="806" who="S0650" trans="overlap">I think</u>
<u n="807" who="S0282">you were right about general anaesthetics and things though I think you do get knocked sideways don't you by these things that come along and you think you can bounce back and young people think they can bounce back perhaps they can when they're younger but it's just takes longer</u>
<u n="808" who="S0650" trans="overlap">I think they can when they're younger yes I just found that after three hours in in the British Library if you you stop for a sandwich at lunchtime and you go back and sit down at two o'clock half past two I'm</u>
<u n="809" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="810" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/> falling asleep</u>
<u n="811" who="S0282">I know</u>
<u n="812" who="S0650" trans="overlap">but <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="813" who="S0282" trans="overlap">that's very sad isn't it? <vocal desc="gasp"/> how what is it?</u>
<u n="814" who="S0650" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="815" who="S0282">I've never been there actually I meant to join and er</u>
<u n="816" who="S0650" trans="overlap">oh it</u>
<u n="817" who="S0282" trans="overlap">I believe I could join but</u>
<u n="818" who="S0650" trans="overlap">it's it I think it's superb actually</u>
<u n="819" who="S0282" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="820" who="S0650">I think it's very good I I don't know what the er the the it's in two parts erm there are some nineteen seventy-five onwards</u>
<u n="821" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="822" who="S0650">and <trunc>ev</trunc>everything earlier than that and so erm er what's it called? I <trunc>thi</trunc> I I think they call it a a antique or something like that no <unclear>inch</unclear> I can't remember what they call it anyway erm rare books and something erm I always worked in that department</u>
<u n="823" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="824" who="S0650" trans="overlap">because the stuff that I've been looking at was published in the nineteenth century or <trunc>wha</trunc> eighteenth century and seventeenth century</u>
<u n="825" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="826" who="S0650">erm and it's very well equipped and the atmosphere is very you know you you you're not disturbed</u>
<u n="827" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="828" who="S0650">that's the beauty of the place is that it's quiet and er</u>
<u n="829" who="S0282">studious atmosphere</u>
<u n="830" who="S0650" trans="overlap">a studious atmosphere</u>
<u n="831" who="S0282">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's nice I find</u>
<u n="832" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah and there's plenty of room and the staff are extremely helpful</u>
<u n="833" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="834" who="S0650">they're very helpful indeed</u>
<u n="835" who="S0282">oh that's good</u>
<u n="836" who="S0650">I was amazed in fact because erm <pause dur="short"/> one of the things that happened was that I I went to the Spanish national archives in near Valladolid</u>
<u n="837" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="838" who="S0650">in a place called Salamanca and erm to my horror when I got there I found nobody but nobody could speak English</u>
<u n="839" who="S0282">ah</u>
<u n="840" who="S0650">and I also</u>
<u n="841" who="S0282" trans="overlap">you need to go away from the coast in Spain</u>
<u n="842" who="S0650">er <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was just that the there's got to be a er what surprised me even more there was no catalogue</u>
<u n="843" who="S0282"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="844" who="S0650">erm other than the catalogue which had been written by some er well I suppose amateur in eighteen nineteen or eighteen twenty</u>
<u n="845" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="846" who="S0650">and but all</u>
<u n="847" who="S0282" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="848" who="S0650">all the papers sort of period from fourteen seventy-seven to seventeen fifteen they're all located in this one place which actually makes it very easy</u>
<u n="849" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="850" who="S0650" trans="overlap">from the point of view of you know what you're looking for is there</u>
<u n="851" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="852" who="S0650">and and all the</u>
<u n="853" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="854" who="S0650">earlier documents I'd I'd not come across this before are not <trunc>w</trunc> not mm well not in this form they are all in tubes and these tubes go right back to the seventeenth century</u>
<u n="855" who="S0282">oh wow</u>
<u n="856" who="S0650">erm and you ask for a I the the lady who was sort of erm I don't know if she was appointed to look after them or somehow she she took to looking after me erm she couldn't speak English but she knew that Philip the second had been married to bloody Mary</u>
<u n="857" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="858" who="S0650" trans="overlap">which was what I was interested in</u>
<u n="859" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="860" who="S0650">and after talking to her <vocal desc="laugh"/> a lot of writing and drawing and <trunc>var</trunc></u>
<u n="861" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="862" who="S0650" trans="overlap">using a dictionary mainly cos er there's no electronics there's no you can't there's <trunc>n</trunc> you you can't use your erm laptop you can use an ordinary typing</u>
<u n="863" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="864" who="S0650" trans="overlap">but you can't use it for research at all because there's nothing is is <trunc>on</trunc>online</u>
<u n="865" who="S0282">how extraordinary</u>
<u n="866" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and erm anyway</u>
<u n="867" who="S0282">it has revolutionised things since this stuff</u>
<u n="868" who="S0650" trans="overlap">oh absolutely</u>
<u n="869" who="S0282" trans="overlap">when you put it online</u>
<u n="870" who="S0650">absolutely this good lady erm she's she eventually <trunc>sh</trunc> she <trunc>under</trunc>understood what I was interested in and she produced for me the inventory of erm Vladimir's household</u>
<u n="871" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="872" who="S0650">erm from a visit of er of Philip the second to</u>
<u n="873" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="874" who="S0650" trans="overlap">this country and it was er riveting erm it was one of these things that had been rolled up as if you</u>
<u n="875" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="876" who="S0650">quite a long thing</u>
<u n="877" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="878" who="S0650">and it listed literally every member of the staff</u>
<u n="879" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="880" who="S0650">and all their clothes</u>
<u n="881" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="882" who="S0650">and all their food allowance</u>
<u n="883" who="S0282">oh really?</u>
<u n="884" who="S0650">I'd never seen anything like it</u>
<u n="885" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh how exciting</u>
<u n="886" who="S0650">it's a masterpiece of bureaucracy</u>
<u n="887" who="S0282">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="888" who="S0650">incredible</u>
<u n="889" who="S0282">wow</u>
<u n="890" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="891" who="S0282">and that was the sort of was that the the big initial meeting between them when they were sort of circling each other and deciding whether they were going to have a a political union and a</u>
<u n="892" who="S0650">it well well</u>
<u n="893" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><unclear/>?</u>
<u n="894" who="S0650">yes I mean there were a lot of correspondences there before she got married</u>
<u n="895" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="896" who="S0650">and then there is his visit here</u>
<u n="897" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="898" who="S0650">and that was a thing which was I wanted to really to see what er I could find out</u>
<u n="899" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="900" who="S0650">but without having a really working knowledge of of Spanish and ancient Spanish Castilian erm I find it very very difficult indeed</u>
<u n="901" who="S0282" trans="overlap">wow yeah</u>
<u n="902" who="S0650">er so I have to rely on other people's erm</u>
<u n="903" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="904" who="S0650">er <trunc>f</trunc>first primary work</u>
<u n="905" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="906" who="S0650">there is a lot of primary work easily available</u>
<u n="907" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="908" who="S0650">and fortunately erm</u>
<u n="909" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but you've got er <trunc>t</trunc> it's the time isn't it to</u>
<u n="910" who="S0650" trans="overlap">it's the <trunc>ti</trunc> it's the time</u>
<u n="911" who="S0282" trans="overlap">to go through it</u>
<u n="912" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah absolutely right</u>
<u n="913" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="914" who="S0650">yeah</u>
<u n="915" who="S0282">it is amazing now with with Kew what you can get online and we were stumped in our with our family history there was one insuperable obstacle that we couldn't get past and then all of a sudden one day it just popped up online</u>
<u n="916" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="917" who="S0282">you know and then it's just simple</u>
<u n="918" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="919" who="S0282">it's straightforward all these other things fall immediately into place but you know until that point it was the sort of date we didn't know whether two individuals had got divorced and if so when it when it might be or where it might have taken place or whatever and so we <trunc>did</trunc> we couldn't work out where one of them had gone because we couldn't work out what you know where she had gone to afterwards</u>
<u n="920" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="921" who="S0282">and then and then erm just when you know <trunc>the</trunc>then all of a sudden somebody's done this work and has put it online and it's fantastic it opens these fantastic vistas</u>
<u n="922" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="923" who="S0282">that saved so much time it would have been otherwise would have been days and days and days and days and days at Kew going through</u>
<u n="924" who="S0650" trans="overlap"><trunc>ano</trunc> er er another er strange erm experience er pure coincidence er there will be a er a good lady erm with us on the twenty-ninth called</u>
<u n="925" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="926" who="S0650" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and she works for the BBC</u>
<u n="927" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="928" who="S0650">and erm I had</u>
<u n="929" who="S0282" trans="overlap">are they related to the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>? with</u>
<u n="930" who="S0650" trans="overlap">well it's spelt <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="931" who="S0282">oh right well obviously</u>
<u n="932" who="S0650" trans="overlap">it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="933" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh yeah no no no difference by then yes</u>
<u n="934" who="S0650">an Italian name</u>
<u n="935" who="S0282">yeah oh right</u>
<u n="936" who="S0650">she's not Italian at all but erm any rate erm I er met her when I went to <anon type="place"/> university</u>
<u n="937" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="938" who="S0650">she's er by training a erm a violinist and she's also the national UK national expert on Schoenberg does that mean anything to you? Schoenberg?</u>
<u n="939" who="S0282">vaguely I've heard of the name but I don't know er</u>
<u n="940" who="S0650" trans="overlap">he was a <unclear/></u>
<u n="941" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh really? oh right okay yes</u>
<u n="942" who="S0650">yeah anyway erm I made friends with her ages ago when she was a student and so on and I always kept in touch with her <pause dur="short"/> any rate it was you know two thousand I I wanted to look at some papers in the Hofburg which is the the equivalent of Buckingham Palace in Vienna</u>
<u n="943" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="944" who="S0650">and the there's a marvellous court library with the Hofbibliothek it's er in the building itself is fantastic and what's in it is equally fantastic</u>
<u n="945" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="946" who="S0650">and I er a lot of it is the national library and is open like the British Library is you just go in and say there's my British Library ticket which they accept and you just ask for what you want</u>
<u n="947" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="948" who="S0650">but there's part of it where all the very special erm delicate and erm er prized works are are</u>
<u n="949" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="950" who="S0650" trans="overlap">kept and they're all kept in <trunc>lo</trunc> under lock and key in this amazing erm er building</u>
<u n="951" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="952" who="S0650" trans="overlap">er designed by a man called Fischer von Erlach I don't know if you've heard of his but the leading block architecture er architect and er erm it was closed</u>
<u n="953" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="954" who="S0650">and er well and I I suddenly saw that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was with er two of her colleagues with a a camera and recording equipment er and I I'd</u>
<u n="955" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="956" who="S0650">I went over to her and I said hello <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what are you doing here?</u>
<u n="957" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="958" who="S0650">she said I'm making a programme</u>
<u n="959" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="960" who="S0650">and I said really? she said why are you here? and I said well I wanted to go and look into some papers in the <trunc>o</trunc>on Hofbibliothek and and actually I find it's closed oh she said no problem erm I</u>
<u n="961" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="962" who="S0650" trans="overlap">I I think I can sort that one out cos that's where we're making a programme you can become a member of the BBC staff for the day</u>
<u n="963" who="S0282">oh how wonderful</u>
<u n="964" who="S0650">and so</u>
<u n="965" who="S0282" trans="overlap">how wonderful</u>
<u n="966" who="S0650" trans="overlap">I got into this and and one of the things they were actually looking at er er concerts which were put on between nineteen hundred and nineteen fourteen</u>
<u n="967" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="968" who="S0650">and what was done to promote Schoenberg it</u>
<u n="969" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="970" who="S0650" trans="overlap">it was quite a an esoteric exercise</u>
<u n="971" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="972" who="S0650">but it coincided with and it er I think it's the year nineteen nineteen seven I <trunc>thi</trunc> about about then the first decade there was a a frightful winter</u>
<u n="973" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="974" who="S0650">and appalling floods</u>
<u n="975" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="976" who="S0650">in the Danube Basin and erm the people at the <trunc>m</trunc> there was a person working in the library who came up to me and she said I I was er er wanted to know about the mm er what had been the way in which the Austrian foreign ministry worked and thoroughly boring</u>
<u n="977" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="978" who="S0650" trans="overlap">academic stuff and this person came over and said what are <trunc>y</trunc> er can I help are you looking for something? and I said well I actually I want to know how much to what extent the emperor was involved over the Bosnia crisis in nineteen eight and so on oh he said that's the that's the erm the the the the year when there was this frightful weather come with me and I'll show you something interesting and he showed me this whole set of photographs</u>
<u n="979" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="980" who="S0650">which were taken of the the emperor going and visiting the villages which had been flooded</u>
<u n="981" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="982" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and I mean it was absolutely fascinating</u>
<u n="983" who="S0282">how amazing</u>
<u n="984" who="S0650" trans="overlap">erm they were quite informal and the other thing that this man said he said er this is the time when the Austrians decided that they needed to have a navy a proper navy they all</u>
<u n="985" who="S0282">uhu</u>
<u n="986" who="S0650" trans="overlap">that they ought to have a Dreadnought</u>
<u n="987" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="988" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and it there is a er a special exhibition on at the what they call the the <trunc>Au</trunc> er it's the <trunc>A</trunc>Austrian Army Museum</u>
<u n="989" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="990" who="S0650" trans="overlap">he said go there and you will see something which is really unique so I went and you had to book in and at eleven o'clock on er</u>
<u n="991" who="S0282"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="992" who="S0650">Friday morning and so on and <trunc>any</trunc>anyway went into it sat down in this tiny little theatre place with a er erm one of those er er cine camera things with two reels</u>
<u n="993" who="S0282">oh yeah</u>
<u n="994" who="S0650" trans="overlap">two big reels on the top</u>
<u n="995" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="996" who="S0650">and and you could hear it whirring away</u>
<u n="997" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="998" who="S0650">and what they'd got was the newsreel of the launch of er <trunc>th</trunc>this battle ship er at Pula and it er it it showed the awful blunder that they made</u>
<u n="999" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0650">the ship was constructed and up to er a hull the complete hull and first decking</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0650">erm in a dry dock and it was held in place by these enormous erm I suppose they were <unclear/> I don't know but er timber props</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0650">erm they are sort of the the the cross section of the hull</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0650" trans="overlap">there are these timber props</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0650">and to launch this ship they opened the the er lock gate at the bottom</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0650" trans="overlap">to the let water in</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0650">and they told the guys to knock the these great <trunc>pi</trunc> erm er props away</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0650">so that the ship would slide out into the into the into into the sea</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1016" who="S0650">what they didn't realise was that when the ship went into the er into the water it would cause an enormous displacement of water</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1018" who="S0650">into the dock</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0282">oh no</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and there were these poor people who were drowned</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0282"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1022" who="S0650">and it was all on the film</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0282">oh no</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yeah it was</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0282">oh my lord</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0650" trans="overlap">er quite extraordinary and horrifying</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0282">oh my word</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0650">and there was this stand you could see everything because it showed Franz Ferdinand and <trunc>h</trunc>his his would-be wife Sophie Hohenberg erm and all the other dignitaries er there to launch this ship and all that kind of thing and there were these poor people being drowned at their feet</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0282">oh my word <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0650" trans="overlap">horrifying</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0282">oh my word</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0650">yeah</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0282">that's shocking isn't it?</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0650">yeah</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0650">anyway <pause dur="short"/> it's produced some all of my activities looking work for the er researching for this book have led me to some weird places</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0282">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> it sounds like doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0650" trans="overlap">I've been been to the Ukraine</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1040" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and the problem is the problem <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> at the moment</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0282">yeah gosh</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0650">and <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1043" who="S0282">gosh well no it was always a hugely wide ranging piece of work</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0650">yeah so I dunno I hope I'll finish it</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0282">I don't know</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0650" trans="overlap">I should but</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0282" trans="overlap">have you thought about doing different volumes and?</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0650" trans="overlap">er I I've I showed the first half of the first part I've written to a publisher and <vocal desc="laugh"/> he was a bit dismissive erm he said what why did you write it? and I said well no it's er purely out of personal interest he said oh mm very good textbook <vocal desc="laugh"/> so anyway but a textbook is not a bad thing to have produced because of the fact it's bread and butter</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0282">well well quite</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0650" trans="overlap">and</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0282">I mean I find that there's</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0650" trans="overlap">if if if</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0282" trans="overlap">nothing wrong with textbooks I mean what is the historian to do without a textbook? and he</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0650" trans="overlap">well exactly yes we have to start somewhere</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0650" trans="overlap">then you build up on it yeah</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and things that aren't textbooks someone can be very suspect <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1058" who="S0650">yes exactly yes</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0282" trans="overlap">things written by journalists who</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1061" who="S0282">knew nothing about it last year</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0282">and now are experts</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0282">all these er my pet hates when you have people like Simon Schama or Andrew Marr who</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0650" trans="overlap">Andrew Marr is a mm <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0282">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1068" who="S0650" trans="overlap">he is not a historian</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0282" trans="overlap">but they sort of stride about and they say</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0650">yes</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0282">within fifty years the whole of Europe was Catholic</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0650">yeah</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0282">and you think</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0650">er</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0282" trans="overlap">er <trunc>n</trunc> really? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1076" who="S0650" trans="overlap">yes yes that's right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1077" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1078" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1079" who="S0282">I'm not that they were <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1080" who="S0650">that's right yes</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0282">or you know <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm you they just just great big swathes of history had quite big rows with with erm my husband's family about Simon Schama it's like isn't Simon Schama wonderful? no</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0650">no</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0282">don't think so no not really</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1085" who="S0282">and he might know a lot but how can you follow what he's talking about?</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1087" who="S0282">it doesn't make sense</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1089" who="S0282">or it makes sense in a spurious sort of way but but erm well there we are let me just see where we've got up to</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0650">yeah</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0282" trans="overlap">in terms of timing oh look we've done an hour and a minute</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0650">gosh that should be enough for</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah let's do that</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0650"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1095" who="S0282">stop <pause dur="long"/> are we stopping? what are we doing? <pause dur="short"/> stop</u>
<event desc="sound of audio"/>
<u n="1096" who="S0282">oh there we are <pause dur="short"/> there we are that did record? that's <trunc>han</trunc>handy</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0650" trans="overlap">oh good</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
