<text id="SQ3P">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:21:06</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-09-27</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0519 S0520 S0521</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Hunsonby, Cumbria</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>elderly grandma, care arrangements, business partners, Literary adaptations, grandchildren, jeans</topics>
		<activity>Family chat over peas and chips</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, requesting, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0519">
				<exactage>59</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>Irish</nat>
				<birthplace>Dublin, Ireland</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Ireland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Penrith, `</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>6 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Recently retired maths teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0520">
				<exactage>32</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birkenhead, UK`</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>India/Thailand/UK (Hunsoney</hab_city>
				<hab_country></hab_country>
				<hab_dur>3 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Transcriber, Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0521">
				<exactage>59</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Walsall, UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Penrith</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Former role as technical esport of development planning in oil industry</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0519">it's just that I don't think she has the</u>
<u n="2" who="S0520">what does she do then? just a sandwich?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0519">I think she just has like a boiled egg or some soup</u>
<u n="4" who="S0520" trans="overlap">especially now it's getting cold you really do need a warm meal it's kind of er <unclear/></u>
<u n="5" who="S0519">she complained that the the Wiltshire meals were too big for her as well and I said well serve yourself onto your plate what you want from it chuck the rest in the bin</u>
<u n="6" who="S0520" trans="overlap">in the bin</u>
<u n="7" who="S0519">that's what you do</u>
<u n="8" who="S0520">that's what I do with with er food like I just take</u>
<u n="9" who="S0519">you have what you like</u>
<u n="10" who="S0520">mm yeah you just have what you like and then you chuck it but</u>
<u n="11" who="S0519" trans="overlap">we learnt that didn't we? I I've learned that from you</u>
<u n="12" who="S0520">well yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I've learnt it from you in the sense of just like</u>
<u n="13" who="S0519">this is it now yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0520" trans="overlap">you know don't make a deal out of it</u>
<u n="15" who="S0519" trans="overlap">don't that's not that's right</u>
<u n="16" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0519">but yeah I think it came home to me with you</u>
<u n="18" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0519">that you know and to just look after yourself and have the thing you want</u>
<u n="20" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0519">and with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> when he's he had he's had lots of issues with food in the last years and</u>
<u n="22" who="S0520">I know</u>
<u n="23" who="S0519">we'd be going out for a meal or he'd be coming to us for a meal and he'd say of I don't know if I'm going to fancy it and I just say look you order exactly what you want and you eat two mouthfuls it's still worth it</u>
<u n="24" who="S0520">whatever you want mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0519">you just have two mouthfuls of what you want</u>
<u n="26" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="27" who="S0519">and that's all you need</u>
<u n="28" who="S0520">yeah it's all just different for grandma isn't it? and that is the is the sore point is that it's not how it was and it's not how she's used to it being still</u>
<u n="29" who="S0519">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="30" who="S0520">at ninety-two it's pretty hard to</u>
<u n="31" who="S0519">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we said we would let her know we were home</u>
<u n="32" who="S0521">right</u>
<u n="33" who="S0520">give her a cally</u>
<u n="34" who="S0521">I was just sending a mail to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> explaining more or less what we just discussed</u>
<u n="35" who="S0519">erm hang on a second cos there were a couple of things <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> asked us to do as well</u>
<u n="36" who="S0521">yeah I sent him a summary of that yesterday</u>
<u n="37" who="S0519">erm well he asked</u>
<u n="38" who="S0521">I summarised I said we've done the the bedroom</u>
<u n="39" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0521">we've done the erm fall fall detectors <unclear>advice</unclear></u>
<u n="41" who="S0520">was that broken?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0519">we don't know they they said they would send an engineer to look at it dad said my throwing it on the floor idea wasn't good enough</u>
<u n="43" who="S0520">what you didn't just chuck it on the ground see if it?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0519" trans="overlap">that's what <unclear/> for</u>
<u n="45" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0519">he said no I'm going to ring the people and ask properly</u>
<u n="47" who="S0521">well</u>
<u n="48" who="S0520">well it's a question of how sensitive it's supposed to be isn't it?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0521" trans="overlap">as discussed had it had it yes exactly had it worked we wouldn't have known if it normally worked had it not worked we wouldn't have solved anything</u>
<u n="50" who="S0519">no so anyway they're sending an engineer</u>
<u n="51" who="S0520">that sounds clever</u>
<u n="52" who="S0521">so</u>
<u n="53" who="S0519">that's very clever</u>
<u n="54" who="S0521">and the advert for the car we've done as well</u>
<u n="55" who="S0520">have you? mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0519">so there were couple of things</u>
<u n="57" who="S0521">hey <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0519">listen</u>
<u n="59" who="S0521">we had a valet they came out to the house and did it and it's magnificent isn't it?</u>
<u n="60" who="S0519">beautifully valeted</u>
<u n="61" who="S0520">what's a valet?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0519">you know for the car</u>
<u n="63" who="S0521">cleaning inside and out</u>
<u n="64" who="S0519">and we did ours while we were on</u>
<u n="65" who="S0520">did you? it needed it there's like coffee on the walls and stuff</u>
<u n="66" who="S0521"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0519">it was really gross in there it's absolutely beautiful now</u>
<u n="68" who="S0520">that's cool like proper polish and stuff?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0519">proper polish and a good scrub and everything erm so we did both cars that was cool so hang on erm it there were just some subtleties</u>
<u n="70" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0521">well if there's anything er I I can tell him now you're right</u>
<u n="72" who="S0519">there were a couple of subtleties so along with the bed moving</u>
<u n="73" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0519"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had asked us to ask you mum about having the single bed</u>
<u n="75" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0519">so we can say that erm we talked about that and said she said she would try it moved first that she didn't want to go <trunc>st</trunc> you know that it would be a phase down the line but we did discuss it with her but she she wanted to try out first of all moving it away from the wall which we did</u>
<u n="77" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yeah yeah I know I did mention that it was er okay couple of</u>
<u n="78" who="S0519" trans="overlap"><trunc>a</trunc>and the second one was that he asked me to look into a tabletop fridge</u>
<u n="79" who="S0520">yeah the fridge is so awkward to get at isn't it? down there</u>
<u n="80" who="S0521" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="81" who="S0520">even for me it's awkward</u>
<u n="82" who="S0519">it's really awkward it's extra especially awkward I've no idea why but ours is too you don't realise</u>
<u n="83" who="S0520">a little bit but it's smaller than yours</u>
<u n="84" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0520">it's underneath all of that</u>
<u n="86" who="S0519">stuff</u>
<u n="87" who="S0520">stuff and then next to it is the door another door</u>
<u n="88" who="S0519">mm I know it's really awkward so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had asked me to look into a and to talk to your mum about it and just to say that I've brought up the idea and told her that it would need to go at the that we would need to take one of the cupboards out and that it possibly it would have to go in front of the window</u>
<u n="89" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0519">and erm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0520">next to the sink</u>
<u n="92" who="S0519">next to the sink and she erm and that she listened</u>
<u n="93" who="S0521">do you mean</u>
<u n="94" who="S0519">and agreed that the other</u>
<u n="95" who="S0521">swapping sides then?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0519">sorry?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0521">swapping sides</u>
<u n="98" who="S0519">no swapping the fridge buying a tabletop fridge</u>
<u n="99" who="S0521">oh sorry can we just deal with the bed</u>
<u n="100" who="S0519">oh</u>
<u n="101" who="S0521">so with the bed</u>
<u n="102" who="S0519">she agreed to</u>
<u n="103" who="S0521">she's agreed to try it as it is now</u>
<u n="104" who="S0519" trans="overlap"><trunc>d</trunc> moved</u>
<u n="105" who="S0521">but we also discussed swapping sides</u>
<u n="106" who="S0519">we also discussed phase two if that didn't work would be to try swapping sides and third in line to the throat was swapping the bed to the single bed she would only consider that if none of the above worked</u>
<u n="107" who="S0520">because she can't get out of the bed? is it too high?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0519">no it's erm it has so it was <trunc>ha</trunc> the side that she's on in the furthest from the bathroom which you know but then having said that she hasn't always been on that side she used to be on the other side but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had the same hip thing as me</u>
<u n="109" who="S0520">oh really</u>
<u n="110" who="S0519">and he couldn't sleep on his hip so he that swapped sides</u>
<u n="111" who="S0520" trans="overlap">they swapped</u>
<u n="112" who="S0519">so she's not the furthest away from the bathroom and it was too close to the wall to get the walker in so she was just managing or not as the case may be so anyway we've moved it away from the wall so he can get the walker I erm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0521">right on the fridge we discussed desktop</u>
<u n="115" who="S0519">and erm and that it would <trunc>em</trunc> <trunc>am</trunc> a cupboard would need to come out and it could go in front of and it would have to go in front of the window was probably the simplest solution on the left-hand side looking out of the window</u>
<u n="116" who="S0520">right so have it on top of the counter?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0519">kinda</u>
<u n="118" who="S0520">mm yeah cos it'll open</u>
<u n="119" who="S0521">well the freezer's underneath</u>
<u n="120" who="S0519">the freezer's underneath and the fridge would go above if you like and we would have to take the left-hand cupboard out or it wouldn't be useful cos it would cover up that anyway just say we discussed a tabletop fridge and the possibilities and although she agreed that the current fridge was very awkward and she couldn't get stuff out of it erm she didn't agree to having the new fridge yet but that that was something to keep going on about <pause dur="long"/> erm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0521">good</u>
<u n="122" who="S0519">so what have you said about since we left we've been thinking about getting her talking to her about getting somebody to come and prepare meals for her</u>
<u n="123" who="S0521">just reflecting on the weekend mum was in a lot of pain barely able to get out of the chair we think she's close to not being able to or finding it too much effort to prepare her own meals we know she's just had a fall but we see her getting thinner and weaker</u>
<u n="124" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="125" who="S0519">as as they have done and they've said so you could perhaps put that in as in</u>
<u n="126" who="S0521">like you</u>
<u n="127" who="S0519">like you we have seen blah cos otherwise it's touchy feely</u>
<u n="128" who="S0520" trans="overlap">politics</u>
<u n="129" who="S0521" trans="overlap">it's <vocal desc="misc"/> we thought of this first</u>
<u n="130" who="S0519">we we're we're far more observant that you</u>
<u n="131" who="S0520" trans="overlap">oh no that's not how it should be is it?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0519">no</u>
<u n="133" who="S0520">disaster</u>
<u n="134" who="S0521">we think that having carers to prepare meals might be a good option what do you think?</u>
<u n="135" who="S0519">the carers to prepare a dinner or a cooked meal</u>
<u n="136" who="S0520" trans="overlap">one <trunc>si</trunc> one meal a day</u>
<u n="137" who="S0519" trans="overlap">once a day</u>
<u n="138" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0521">okay couple of other things on the bed mum said she would like to try the bed in its new positions before thinking of a new one we might also look at swapping sides to put her nearer to the bathroom</u>
<u n="140" who="S0520">that would make sense</u>
<u n="141" who="S0519">before looking into swapping to your one is really the thing <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="143" who="S0521">do you have any experience as a proofreader</u>
<u n="144" who="S0519">erm actually I do darling</u>
<u n="145" who="S0520">mum's just verbally editing your email <vocal desc="laugh"/> this is what I do as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="146" who="S0519">and you should say it like this and you want to say it like this</u>
<u n="147" who="S0521">on the fridge we discussed the tabletop and agreed the existing new one is very awkward</u>
<u n="148" who="S0519">however</u>
<u n="149" who="S0520">however it's just the beginnings of</u>
<u n="150" who="S0519">this is only the starting point that it's been raised really</u>
<u n="151" who="S0520">you can get very canny little fridges these days small ones well I guess she doesn't have a very small one</u>
<u n="152" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I looked at see what I would have and will have in my new house</u>
<u n="153" who="S0520">is a massive one with those ice machines</u>
<u n="154" who="S0519">oh yes I'll have that really but</u>
<u n="155" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0519" trans="overlap">if if I don't yeah but I'm definitely they're just so cool</u>
<u n="157" who="S0520">American fridge's yeah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0519">oh actually you're right that's what I will have but what they have now is erm for under table you can have them either side by side but say that's your countertop</u>
<u n="159" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="160" who="S0519">it's a a drawer</u>
<u n="161" who="S0520">drawer fridge</u>
<u n="162" who="S0519">a drawer fridge so you pull it out like a nice big deep draw and the bottles and everything just stand up in it so you just pick them out like that</u>
<u n="163" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm what about all your vegetables and things in baskets?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0519" trans="overlap">and you have a different drawer and you have them at different temperatures so you maybe have two drawers one for all your veggies and blah blah blahs and one for your other things and then two more drawers of freezer drawers you know and they all stack up in any way that you like</u>
<u n="165" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0519">isn't that just glorious</u>
<u n="167" who="S0520">it sounds fantastic</u>
<u n="168" who="S0519">and I so I sent they're about six hundred quid for two drawers but that wouldn't matter we just wouldn't have to tell <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> how much it cost erm so I sent <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a picture of them and he so if you had one on top of the other say where they are at the moment or even at the freezer position near the sink erm <pause dur="long"/> er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> still thought it would be too low</u>
<u n="169" who="S0520">yeah she doesn't want to have to bend down</u>
<u n="170" who="S0519">no I I just think if you're I know I'm small so I it doesn't but if you pull it out the thing that you can't do in a fridge is you have to do that</u>
<u n="171" who="S0520">mm yeah but not if it's at <trunc>bo</trunc>body height</u>
<u n="172" who="S0519" trans="overlap">but in the drawer you just have to do that</u>
<u n="173" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0519">but in the lower drawer you got to do that but it's <trunc>sti</trunc> you haven't got to look for it it's right there you can see it and you just got to lift it up</u>
<u n="175" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0519">but he said he thought it would be too low down anyway so</u>
<u n="177" who="S0520">I like the idea I think well if the if there was a fridge on top of the counter that would be sort of</u>
<u n="178" who="S0519">simple one</u>
<u n="179" who="S0520">arm height eye height you know like that</u>
<u n="180" who="S0519">yeah it's just it's going to look seriously ugly</u>
<u n="181" who="S0520">it's going to look ugly and it's gonna obscure the view of the garden isn't it?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0520">mm yeah there's nowhere else to really put it is there cos that counter on the left-hand side is really narrow</u>
<u n="184" who="S0519">that's right it's very narrow and erm</u>
<u n="185" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0519">yeah it needs to be right up in order for it to be <trunc>o</trunc> <trunc>a</trunc>an improvement on the one that's there already</u>
<u n="187" who="S0520">mm definitely grandma really cares how things look as well doesn't she? she wants it all to be</u>
<u n="188" who="S0519">she didn't want us to move the bed because it wouldn't look right</u>
<u n="189" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm yeah I understand</u>
<u n="190" who="S0519">and I I know that I get that but they all the carers were saying</u>
<u n="191" who="S0520" trans="overlap">you just want things to be practical yeah</u>
<u n="192" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I know it might not look quite as as nice but we're talking about your safety you know and your ease of use so the other thing you were saying what's wrong with her bed erm I think the mattress is quite cheap and it <trunc>sq</trunc>squashes</u>
<u n="193" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0519">so when you sit on the edge of it</u>
<u n="195" who="S0520" trans="overlap">lose balance mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0519">it squashes down so she slides off before she's got her feet round she's kinda sliding down it erm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0519">and she doesn't have any strength to well of course you can't hold yourself up on it because then it just squashes down when you're sitting on it</u>
<u n="199" who="S0520">they're the oldest mattresses in the world aren't they?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0519">I think they bought a new one for this new bed</u>
<u n="201" who="S0520" trans="overlap">oh they did</u>
<u n="202" who="S0519">that goes up and down the bed is super-duper</u>
<u n="203" who="S0521">this might be the er the <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> er don't don't spend much er</u>
<u n="204" who="S0520">no just er</u>
<u n="205" who="S0521">approach to life</u>
<u n="206" who="S0520">we slept in that bed <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I when we were kids that was like dipping in the middle and then as we grew older and older we just we couldn't resist the force of the dip it was like</u>
<u n="207" who="S0521"><unclear/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0519"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you just had to lie on top of each other</u>
<u n="209" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> a big hole in the middle of the bed it just had to so we would roll into it</u>
<u n="210" who="S0521">well actually <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I I remembered cos I actually made a remark that for at least ten years they slept on a bed which was held up by bricks</u>
<u n="211" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0519"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <trunc>a</trunc>admitted it she said oh yes we had those bricks for a very long time</u>
<u n="213" who="S0521" trans="overlap">she admitted it didn't she? yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> did you have a dippy bed as well?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0519" trans="overlap">and everywhere in the house</u>
<u n="216" who="S0520">did you have a dippy bed in that in that has that has that been changed as well?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0519">the little bed is now a proper bed as well</u>
<u n="218" who="S0520">the one you sleep is not dipping any more</u>
<u n="219" who="S0519">the the one we sleep in is not dipping bit it's pretty old it's a three and it's a three quarter bed I mean it's just the most annoying size</u>
<u n="220" who="S0520">that's small</u>
<u n="221" who="S0519">it's teeny</u>
<u n="222" who="S0521">it's quite uncomfortable as well isn't it? quite er</u>
<u n="223" who="S0519">extremely uncomfortable</u>
<u n="224" who="S0521" trans="overlap">unsupportive</u>
<u n="225" who="S0519">erm there's two like wafer thin pillows</u>
<u n="226" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0519">my <trunc>a</trunc> I I wake up my arms numb <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="228" who="S0521">well that's not as bad as me I have the clothes pinched off me</u>
<u n="229" who="S0519" trans="overlap">dad's got all the covers</u>
<u n="230" who="S0521">you go <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="231" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0519">I have to do that cos you allow them all to drift off onto the floor</u>
<u n="233" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> classic</u>
<u n="234" who="S0521">I just have my leg out <unclear/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0519" trans="overlap">you're you</u>
<u n="236" who="S0520">classic</u>
<u n="237" who="S0519">hoick them <trunc>ro</trunc> no it's the seriously you don't sleep for <unclear/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0520" trans="overlap">argument no it's not ideal is it?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0521">I didn't realise that little white plug in the living room actually goes through the wall into the kitchen</u>
<u n="240" who="S0519">the number of <trunc>plu</trunc> the number of electrical disasters in that house</u>
<u n="241" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="242" who="S0519">is beyond anybody's understanding</u>
<u n="243" who="S0521">it was a bit of a palaver <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because when the the people came to install the new lift</u>
<u n="244" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0521">they refused to do it on the one one the plug sockets</u>
<u n="246" who="S0519">they said it's been taken for here to there to everywhere</u>
<u n="247" who="S0521" trans="overlap">wasn't safe</u>
<u n="248" who="S0520">grandad's been doing his DIY</u>
<u n="249" who="S0519" trans="overlap">you couldn't he's been doing his DIY</u>
<u n="250" who="S0521">the best is the shed isn't it? the shed you go into the shed and then there's wires all over the place</u>
<u n="251" who="S0520">oh god</u>
<u n="252" who="S0521">and there's a switch right next to the door and you switch it on and nothing happens and it only after repeated trial and error do you find that in the middle of the shed there's a plug socket and if you switch the plug socket on all of the lights come on</u>
<u n="253" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh dear <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0519">he er he did</u>
<u n="255" who="S0520">so what did you have to get an electrician out to put a new plug in?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0519">no they they they found</u>
<u n="257" who="S0520" trans="overlap">they rejigged it</u>
<u n="258" who="S0519">one that they would accept and redid it from that</u>
<u n="259" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0519">erm but you find the most loving you know he's put up all these things to help grandma</u>
<u n="261" who="S0521">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="262" who="S0519">and mostly they're quite awkward</u>
<u n="263" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0519">erm and difficult looking</u>
<u n="265" who="S0521">did you like the toffee tin with a handle on it?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0519">but that's what I was just gonna say</u>
<u n="267" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0519">they <trunc>ha</trunc> the the toffee tin came out of the car so they had their little sweeties in the tin in the car</u>
<u n="269" who="S0520" trans="overlap">oh shame</u>
<u n="270" who="S0519">and it's a nice little tin with a lid you know and it was in the car door and he'd drilled holes into the end of it</u>
<u n="271" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0519">and bolted on a little make do handle so that grandma could pull it up and get the toffees out</u>
<u n="273" who="S0520" trans="overlap">so sweet</u>
<u n="274" who="S0521"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0519">it's just the nicest thing</u>
<u n="276" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0519">and <trunc>i</trunc> you know it'd probably be that they'd been out and say shall we have a toffee and she couldn't reach it</u>
<u n="278" who="S0520" trans="overlap">she couldn't reach it yeah</u>
<u n="279" who="S0519">and he'd bring it in and put a handle on it</u>
<u n="280" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> sweet</u>
<u n="281" who="S0519">oh dear <pause dur="short"/> it's absolutely lovely</u>
<u n="282" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="283" who="S0519">it's nice when we're there cos we have nice chats about him don't we?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> we do</u>
<u n="285" who="S0520">that's cool yeah</u>
<u n="286" who="S0519">that's the best bit really think she really enjoys talking about him</u>
<u n="287" who="S0521">and any number of gadgets he was mad about gadgets wasn't he? in the garage and they're some of them hadn't even really been taken out of the packet</u>
<u n="288" who="S0519">no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said the same</u>
<u n="289" who="S0520" trans="overlap">that's what I remember about him</u>
<u n="290" who="S0519">he got more and more that he kept ordering stuff and we didn't even know what most of it was did we?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0520" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0521">no</u>
<u n="293" who="S0520">he just one of the things I remember is those catalogues</u>
<u n="294" who="S0519">yes he loved them</u>
<u n="295" who="S0520">that he always looked through and bought like you know circled things and <unclear/> in and <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="296" who="S0521" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0520">don't know anyone else who has the you know who would shop in that way and just like funny things like</u>
<u n="299" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no no</u>
<u n="300" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="301" who="S0519">and I think the more they did it then the more little catalogues they got from various different places</u>
<u n="302" who="S0520" trans="overlap"><unclear/> and then they start to target you don't they?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0521" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0519">and they <trunc>do</trunc> they targeted them and there was there's one that I've enjoyed looking through they're absolutely fascinating and they're full of kind of age targeted gadgets you know</u>
<u n="305" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="306" who="S0519">there's</u>
<u n="307" who="S0520">things to</u>
<u n="308" who="S0519"><trunc>s</trunc> furry hot water bottle slippers and</u>
<u n="309" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0519">you know a a tray with a cushion and a you know everything targeted to that age and you go through and you're absolutely riveted at what you can do</u>
<u n="311" who="S0520">yeah the kind of stuff that they think of</u>
<u n="312" who="S0519" trans="overlap">the kind of stuff that people can think up</u>
<u n="313" who="S0520">that's what I remember about it as well</u>
<u n="314" who="S0519">and that you think you do not actually need a single thing from this book</u>
<u n="315" who="S0520">but it's quite fun</u>
<u n="316" who="S0519">but it's quite fun and I think he started to gradually order from that sort of thing</u>
<u n="317" who="S0521" trans="overlap">mm had you heard about the tray with the cushion? I mean you actually suggested it and mum said oh yes we've got one of those</u>
<u n="318" who="S0519">and they they've got four</u>
<u n="319" who="S0521">they've got four</u>
<u n="320" who="S0519" trans="overlap">but we don't know where they are</u>
<u n="321" who="S0520">a cushion that you put it on your lap yeah I've seen that that's quite cool</u>
<u n="322" who="S0519">and it's quite cool so grandma her knees don't you know</u>
<u n="323" who="S0521">she can't</u>
<u n="324" who="S0519" trans="overlap">so she can't rest the tray on her lap cos it just slides off</u>
<u n="325" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="326" who="S0519">so we've been sitting at the fire to have our meals and she said that that's what she does cos she can't sit on the chairs at the table cos they're too dangerous</u>
<u n="327" who="S0520">oh dear</u>
<u n="328" who="S0519">erm but she can't hold the tray up so she'd got the tray sort of balanced like that half on the arm and and that was worked better and you were saying oh that that works better with it a bit on the arm</u>
<u n="329" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0519">and then we both almost said together oh you can get those trays with a soft bottom and then you could get it you know sort of wedged in</u>
<u n="331" who="S0520" trans="overlap">properly wedged in yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0519">and she said oh we've got two of those well we bought two and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> gave us another two so we've got four where are they?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0520">where are they yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="334" who="S0519">oh dear did they give them away to somebody else they probably thought they were well they probably sat at the table still then</u>
<u n="335" who="S0520" trans="overlap">do you think so?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0519">I I don't know I they sat at the trolley for lunch</u>
<u n="337" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="338" who="S0519">whether they just sat at the table</u>
<u n="339" who="S0521">oh the old trolley</u>
<u n="340" who="S0519">the old trolley</u>
<u n="341" who="S0520" trans="overlap">the trolley <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0521">the liability trolley</u>
<u n="343" who="S0520">the classic trolley with the gold <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0519">the gold wheels that went</u>
<u n="345" who="S0520"><unclear>were all</unclear> wobble all over the place</u>
<u n="346" who="S0519">nothing was left on it by the time you got it to its place I bought well I found it I I I</u>
<u n="347" who="S0521">you did that's true</u>
<u n="348" who="S0519">I knew that erm it existed cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had one erm erm and I looked up the the hideous trolley which we knew <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would never agree to have erm and it's <trunc>y</trunc>you'll see it when you go you might have seen it it's like two plastic trays and a <trunc>f</trunc> a walking frame</u>
<u n="349" who="S0520">oh cool yeah handy</u>
<u n="350" who="S0519" trans="overlap">on big <trunc>l</trunc>like walking wheels</u>
<u n="351" who="S0520" trans="overlap">oh no when we when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I went last time it was the er it was the gold trolley cos grandma's trying to move it and she can't</u>
<u n="352" who="S0519">with no that's <trunc>wh</trunc> with the walking frame absolutely no</u>
<u n="353" who="S0520" trans="overlap">what's going on?</u>
<u n="354" who="S0519">so I bought <trunc>e</trunc> we thought what she'd had enough of us telling her what to do anyway so</u>
<u n="355" who="S0520">fair enough</u>
<u n="356" who="S0519">we just said look let's us buy it and give it to her at a present and she'll <trunc>ha</trunc>hate it but she she won't be able to say that she hates how it looks cos it looks like a you know for an old person</u>
<u n="357" who="S0521" trans="overlap">it looks like a cafeteria</u>
<u n="358" who="S0519">it and it doesn't look pretty like her gold trolley</u>
<u n="359" who="S0520" trans="overlap">no golden bits yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0519">and we were so thrilled then the next time we went she said I've done hundreds of miles with this trolley it's absolutely perfect</u>
<u n="361" who="S0520" trans="overlap">oh great</u>
<u n="362" who="S0521">she uses it a lot now doesn't she?</u>
<u n="363" who="S0519">like she uses it for everything</u>
<u n="364" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="365" who="S0521">every meal</u>
<u n="366" who="S0519">because the other <trunc>n</trunc> the nice thing with it is it's got the swivel wheels so you just can go either direction and so in the kitchen she like empties the dishwasher onto it and then pushes the stuff across and you know she can use it to move things round</u>
<u n="367" who="S0520" trans="overlap">ideal yeah</u>
<u n="368" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="369" who="S0519">as well as to carry them through for her dinner and it you can pull it right up so she can get her cup of tea off it and her plate off it and it's all</u>
<u n="370" who="S0521">I noticed the gold trolley is now in the lounge I <unclear>wonder</unclear> who did that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> probably was it? he's put it out of sight hasn't he?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I think I did I <trunc>di</trunc> I might have</u>
<u n="372" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> hide the gold trolley</u>
<u n="373" who="S0519" trans="overlap">not straight away of course cos that</u>
<u n="374" who="S0521" trans="overlap">oh you did it?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0519">I but I think once she decided that the other one was good</u>
<u n="376" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="377" who="S0519">erm I don't know I probably wouldn't have been cheeky enough to move it maybe it was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> but I was just happy that she wasn't using it any more</u>
<u n="378" who="S0520" trans="overlap">oh she yeah if she's not using it that's fine</u>
<u n="379" who="S0519">unless she <trunc>re</trunc>rebrought it in specially for you two</u>
<u n="380" who="S0520">I don't know yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> she definitely definitely had it out</u>
<u n="381" who="S0519">oh heck</u>
<u n="382" who="S0520">and erm well yeah that's the classic isn't it? when we used to arrive from Holland and late at night and then come out with the trolley with cheese and biscuits</u>
<u n="383" who="S0519" trans="overlap">that was the best thing wasn't it?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0521" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0520">it was the best thing</u>
<u n="386" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0520">cheese and biscuits sandwiches crisps <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0519">and the trolley is another one of your dad's specialities isn't it?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0520" trans="overlap">biscuits</u>
<u n="390" who="S0519">it's got bolts all over it</u>
<u n="391" who="S0521">it has yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's been going a long time as well I remember it from when I was I don't know if it's the same trolley but</u>
<u n="393" who="S0519">no they had an original</u>
<u n="394" who="S0521" trans="overlap">no the idea of it</u>
<u n="395" who="S0520" trans="overlap">I remember from when I was really small</u>
<u n="396" who="S0519">the the the gold one with the big wheel and the small wheel was later</u>
<u n="397" who="S0521">that goes back a long way that idea</u>
<u n="398" who="S0519">the they've always had a trolley</u>
<u n="399" who="S0520">yeah and like proper china tea cups</u>
<u n="400" who="S0521" trans="overlap">I remember dad came when dad came home at work from the chemist he was probably eight o'clock he would have tea on his own off the trolley</u>
<u n="401" who="S0520">would he?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="403" who="S0520">well so that's even further back</u>
<u n="404" who="S0519" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="405" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0519">em so we thought we would go out for tea</u>
<u n="407" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="408" who="S0519">be nice to have a break but would you like to ring your mum and just</u>
<u n="409" who="S0521">oh I forgot that so what's that corner doing on the table?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0519" trans="overlap">have you got the phone?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0520" trans="overlap">oh yeah I've got the phone</u>
<u n="412" who="S0521" trans="overlap">an uneaten uneaten corner</u>
<u n="413" who="S0520">it has actually been there for probably a little bit longer than it should have been</u>
<u n="414" who="S0521">oh dear <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0520">have to throw it away <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="416" who="S0519">chuck it in the bin erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0521">so we left her watching P and P</u>
<u n="418" who="S0519">yeah we got there was the six episodes</u>
<u n="419" who="S0520">oh it's a dream</u>
<u n="420" who="S0519" trans="overlap">oh it was a nightmare trying to</u>
<u n="421" who="S0520">set it up</u>
<u n="422" who="S0519">well just to show her how to press play</u>
<u n="423" who="S0521" trans="overlap">trying to get her to be able to use the video</u>
<u n="424" who="S0519">isn't it?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0520">I bet grandad did all of that stuff didn't he?</u>
<u n="426" who="S0519">he did everything</u>
<u n="427" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="428" who="S0519">she said I'm no good with remotes I was saying to dad cos he he got an earful from me when we got in the car cos he said oh it's like your dad and I said no my dad tries really hard and he's watched two matches on Sky Go which is the most difficult thing to use on a computer</u>
<u n="429" who="S0520">Sky is pretty confusing I also have problems with it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0519">no that's right and Sky Go is a joke and a half erm it's er Sky allow you to have two people who can use Sky Go on their computer or whatever</u>
<u n="431" who="S0520">oh right</u>
<u n="432" who="S0519">from your Sky account</u>
<u n="433" who="S0520" trans="overlap">your subscription yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0519">but they've made it the clunkiest most awkward it doesn't quite fit on the screen it's hard to sign into you have to scroll down the channels with a roller and a you have to be clicked on to that side or it doesn't move you know everything is awkward</u>
<u n="435" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm well I think anyone of that generation is forgiven for not being able to negotiate</u>
<u n="436" who="S0519">yeah but we we struggle with it but my dad has persevered it's to watch a football match</u>
<u n="437" who="S0521" trans="overlap">sheer determination</u>
<u n="438" who="S0520">yeah that's a pretty big motivation</u>
<u n="439" who="S0519">and he's persevered and its he's watched the two football matches he wanted to so I was telling dad off cos grandma can't even press play on a remote you know well my dad</u>
<u n="440" who="S0520" trans="overlap">oh that's cool <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0521">oh it's not giving any sound</u>
<u n="442" who="S0520" trans="overlap">she's not got as much confidence has she?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0519" trans="overlap">has it got a dial tone to start with?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0521" trans="overlap">no nothing completely blank unless it's on call length sixteen seconds it says</u>
<u n="445" who="S0519" trans="overlap">well it's er can well what</u>
<u n="446" who="S0521" trans="overlap">it's not even ringing</u>
<u n="447" who="S0520" trans="overlap">press the green oh</u>
<u n="448" who="S0519">l put put it down into its cradle and get the other phone</u>
<u n="449" who="S0521">reboot</u>
<u n="450" who="S0519">no it's probably run out of batteries</u>
<u n="451" who="S0520" trans="overlap">it may have run out of batteries sorry that's my fault again it's cos your peeps were phoning</u>
<u n="452" who="S0519">yes it's not been in its little home for a while</u>
<u n="453" who="S0521" trans="overlap">it's got battery it's got lights on it and actually make the call you're having a laugh</u>
<u n="454" who="S0520">I think mum might be right it hasn't been on the stand since yesterday</u>
<u n="455" who="S0519" trans="overlap">you're having a laugh okay <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you're having a laugh</u>
<u n="457" who="S0519">it's ringing now</u>
<u n="458" who="S0521">I did that before but it didn't give me any ring tone oh that's better</u>
<u n="459" who="S0520">dad <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0519">he's laughing at his mum press play</u>
<u n="461" who="S0521" trans="overlap">hallo mum did you did you just <trunc>ha</trunc> ring before? that's that's strange isn't it? cos it didn't ring my end at all anyway not the worry we've got we've got to you now yeah so we're back home it it was there was one stretch where it was completely slowed up there was er it seemed like somebody had er had er driven into the the central reserve yeah <unclear/> for about half an hour or so <unclear/> so it was okay so how are you doing? are you alright? did you actually watch it through? okay right yes it <trunc>be</trunc> get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to put the other disk in tomorrow that'd be nice wouldn't it? does it bring it all back again <vocal desc="laugh"/> yes it's a nice er nice production isn't it? yeah alright then mum so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s fine yes we'll probably go out for something to eat tonight but er and then we'll we'll get on the road again tomorrow it's nice to be able to break it up actually cos it's an awful long way from you of course so er well have a good night's sleep and get off tomorrow morning oh a <trunc>wa</trunc> a water? okay that sounds very modest yes okay alright then mum so er we'll keep in touch and we'll tell you what's going on with our move you too alright mm speak to you soon absolutely alright then mum bye bye now</u>
<event desc="begin overlap"/>
<u n="462" who="S0520"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sent me photos of the childers</u>
<u n="463" who="S0519">how are they doing? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="464" who="S0520">how cute is this boy? <unclear/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0519"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they're just adorable aren't they? look at them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0520">they have a lot of fun don't they? it's nice that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> always take them out</u>
<u n="467" who="S0519" trans="overlap">they do they do have a lot of fun</u>
<u n="468" who="S0520" trans="overlap">and do things they go to all those play parks and stuff</u>
<u n="469" who="S0519">they just think it's normal <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> asks to go to the zoo every time we come</u>
<u n="470" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what is that?</u>
<u n="471" who="S0519">it was glorious send them to me she better have sent the to me or I'll kill her</u>
<u n="472" who="S0520">she might have I can't tell you have to look at your own phone</u>
<u n="473" who="S0519">mm don't worry she'll have sent them to me <pause dur="long"/> that's nice and easy innit?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="475" who="S0519">how's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0520">not the best he's had all kind of difficulties of a practical nature with his business and his partner is being a bit rubbish</u>
<u n="477" who="S0519" trans="overlap">his</u>
<u n="478" who="S0520">his business partner</u>
<u n="479" who="S0519" trans="overlap">oh that's right</u>
<u n="480" who="S0520">so it's really stressing him out he's very busy so he has a lot to do and then there are like calamities because his partner lost the tablet that has all the inventory information things that are like annoying really annoying to him I'm if somebody for me of somebody loses something I'm fully sympathetic I'm just like yeah know what you know what like he doesn't ever lose anything and it's all on a list and it's all you know he's not stupid so he doesn't have tolerance for that type of disorganised chaotic way of <trunc>de</trunc> of living you know?</u>
<event desc="end overlap"/>
<u n="481" who="S0520">so he's having it's a stress because of that because he's just just er always you know? struggling against that the tide really and they they've decided not to erm I've been watching Great British Menu erm they've decided not to sign any contracts in terms of their partnership until in next year because this year he's been learning the ropes he's been trying things he hasn't made the business profitable which is quite a big erm factor in whether he to <trunc>sh</trunc> to show whether he's a suitable partner or not you know like they weren't making profit and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on his own is making enough profit to erm amply serve his lifestyle so his idea for having a business partner was to increase his profit</u>
<u n="482" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0520">and to make the business more viable for him and more flexible</u>
<u n="484" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="485" who="S0520">and to have more freedom</u>
<u n="486" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="487" who="S0520">and to able to eventually withdraw himself from the business that's was his that's his like long-term plan you know? to set up a business that's kind of self-sustaining</u>
<u n="488" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="489" who="S0520">so there's a bit of there's a litmus test isn't it? if you profit is going down because your partner is not able to even keep it at the same level as what it was you know?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="491" who="S0520">you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was working a couple of days a week in different markets and fairs and whatever selling the jewellery and making decent money because he was efficient because he's really good at it and because he knows what to do so anyway those are the things and also he's not entrepreneurial so he's not like coming up with ideas or like he's just he's more like a worker he really works hard and he grafts and he gets up and he works you know he's really he's not a lazy guy he's really like but he doesn't he just does the job that he's given you know he doesn't think how can I do this job better or</u>
<u n="492" who="S0519">mm no but you can't even learn that</u>
<u n="493" who="S0520" trans="overlap">he doesn't come up with new ideas you can't</u>
<u n="494" who="S0519">if you've not got it you've not got it</u>
<u n="495" who="S0520">that's what I said and I also said</u>
<u n="496" who="S0519">he could be a slave for somebody else</u>
<u n="497" who="S0520" trans="overlap">if someone is chaotic they can improve it like I have become more less chaotic more organised</u>
<u n="498" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm me too</u>
<u n="499" who="S0520">I'm able to plan things more but I'm still quite disorganised fundamentally because I don't care</u>
<u n="500" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="501" who="S0520">and it's a skill that you can learn to a degree but I'm never going to be <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or I'm never going to be <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's in their nature to</u>
<u n="502" who="S0519" trans="overlap">it's no it's it's a skill you can learn</u>
<u n="503" who="S0520" trans="overlap">you can learn the skill</u>
<u n="504" who="S0519">but it's not it's not a talent and that and they're and that's a different level so somebody like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they've actually <trunc>e</trunc><trunc>g</trunc>got a gift of seeing how to be that long-term and that planning and that how everything should fit together where to put the files how to make it all happen what sort of system to run that makes it all work</u>
<u n="505" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm it's all like coming inherently to him</u>
<u n="506" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I haven't got any of that</u>
<u n="507" who="S0520">like he</u>
<u n="508" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0520">thinks like that</u>
<u n="510" who="S0519">he thinks in that way</u>
<u n="511" who="S0520" trans="overlap">he want you know he</u>
<u n="512" who="S0519" trans="overlap">that's right</u>
<u n="513" who="S0520">he approaches a problem in that way</u>
<u n="514" who="S0519">mm that's right</u>
<u n="515" who="S0520">it's like that</u>
<u n="516" who="S0519">whereas you and me we can fight the</u>
<u n="517" who="S0520">fundamental tendency</u>
<u n="518" who="S0519" trans="overlap">general chaos</u>
<u n="519" who="S0520">yeah that's right whereas and this boy is more in that category you know he he works</u>
<u n="520" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="521" who="S0520">in a circular way and he he has other qualities like he's very personable he's very enthusiastic he's very very good at selling which is a key factor</u>
<u n="522" who="S0519">well that should be alright</u>
<u n="523" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="524" who="S0519">I was thinking maybe he wasn't</u>
<u n="525" who="S0520">no he's good at the actual selling part so that's a really big thing cos that's a that is a talent as well it's a different type of skill you know? erm so you know he her certain things but I said my <trunc>fe</trunc> my idea is that he would be better off in another position like in as as the retail manager of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s company but not as a partner to <trunc>hi</trunc> to his business because he's not got the entrepreneurial side and he's not got the vision and he's not got the efficiency to take that</u>
<u n="526" who="S0519" trans="overlap">so he can't take the business further</u>
<u n="527" who="S0520">yeah to take his side of the business to the level that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wants it to be at you know? and er</u>
<u n="528" who="S0519">or beyond</u>
<u n="529" who="S0520">if exactly</u>
<u n="530" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="531" who="S0520">if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was I mean the idea of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> taking a partner in business was to improve his life right?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="533" who="S0520">he was like I've reached a certain plateau in his business he had enough money but he didn't have loads of money and he didn't have a security for the future in terms of erm like a a long-term plan for the future where he could actually stop working at some point you know and whatever so he said right this is phase two of my business I've reached the top of my game I know how to do it I'll take a partner who expands all the retail side of it and brings in different wholesale partners and expands it and I will move only to production</u>
<u n="534" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="535" who="S0520">and eventually he can teach someone else his <trunc>pa</trunc> side of the company</u>
<u n="536" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="537" who="S0520">and Bob's your uncle if his life is not improving and is business is not improving there there is there is no reason in fact it's getting it's become harder in a way because he's constantly having to negotiate with this guy whereas before</u>
<u n="538" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm mm it was up to him</u>
<u n="539" who="S0520" trans="overlap">it was up to him and his <unclear/> is</u>
<u n="540" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I suppose you have to give him a decent time that's the only that</u>
<u n="541" who="S0520" trans="overlap">that's fine that's what they're doing erm but I think the longer it goes on the more personal obligations are created you know they are friends</u>
<u n="542" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="543" who="S0520">since a long time anyway and it's difficult to then say this is not working</u>
<u n="544" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm this is not working but I suppose he can</u>
<u n="545" who="S0520" trans="overlap">so but he's being honest and he's said look there's we're we're not signing a contract and this is reasons why and let's give it this amount of time and</u>
<u n="546" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="547" who="S0520">if it doesn't work then it's not going to happen</u>
<u n="548" who="S0519">it's quite stressful isn't it?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0520">it is stressful and it's stressful to deal with someone else's</u>
<u n="550" who="S0519">how's his?</u>
<u n="551" who="S0520">oh no actually I think it's still in the running</u>
<u n="552" who="S0519">that and his knee</u>
<u n="553" who="S0520">his knee well this is it it's like when you're a bit stressed then things tend to happen don't they?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="555" who="S0520">so now he's <trunc>fall</trunc> he knocked his knee on something and he's really straightened it suddenly and then he's really in pain and</u>
<u n="556" who="S0519" trans="overlap">oh darn oh god oh no</u>
<u n="557" who="S0520">he's doing a lot of complaining</u>
<u n="558" who="S0519">oh oh</u>
<u n="559" who="S0520">little <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="560" who="S0519">ah ah ah ah ah ah</u>
<u n="561" who="S0520">dad</u>
<u n="562" who="S0519">crisp man</u>
<u n="563" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so are we going to go to the shepherds?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0519">they look a big size</u>
<u n="565" who="S0521" trans="overlap">so she's erm she's come to the end of CD one apparently</u>
<u n="566" who="S0519">yes oh good</u>
<u n="567" who="S0521">and she wants she wants <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to set up CD two for her</u>
<u n="568" who="S0519">I did say that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'ll put CD two on</u>
<u n="569" who="S0520">oh I love it let's watch it</u>
<u n="570" who="S0519">mm I have</u>
<u n="571" who="S0520"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0519">we'll bring it back with us</u>
<u n="573" who="S0521">we've got it in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="574" who="S0519">or we'll watch it while we're in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0520">it's the best</u>
<u n="576" who="S0519">we've got a telly about that big</u>
<u n="577" who="S0520">you should look at Colin Firth now he's very old-looking</u>
<u n="578" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0521">is he?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0520">well that was like twenty years ago</u>
<u n="581" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah oh it's only quarter to seven</u>
<u n="582" who="S0520">they <trunc>st</trunc> finish serving at eight don't they?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0521">are we going to walk?</u>
<u n="584" who="S0519">no</u>
<u n="585" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="586" who="S0519">this woman's in her pyjamas</u>
<u n="587" who="S0520">well I can put jeans on</u>
<u n="588" who="S0519">oh go show me your jeans</u>
<u n="589" who="S0520">right fashion show</u>
<u n="590" who="S0519">I'll ring the Shepherd's I've put them into my phone or maybe I didn't</u>
<u n="591" who="S0520">I'll just write to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0521">I made a joke <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when we arrived tonight I a said I expect you'll be doing some treasuring tonight</u>
<u n="593" who="S0520">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0521">she said yes I am</u>
<u n="595" who="S0519"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="596" who="S0520">it wasn't a joke</u>
<u n="597" who="S0521">can you believe it?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0520">I can actually yeah how was your practice?</u>
<u n="599" who="S0519">great</u>
<u n="600" who="S0520">was it?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="602" who="S0520">good</u>
<u n="603" who="S0519">okay well why have you got a little picture of a phone with a one next to it then</u>
<u n="604" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="605" who="S0519">foolish one</u>
<u n="606" who="S0520">suss out dad two Ss or one?</u>
<u n="607" who="S0521">suss</u>
<u n="608" who="S0520">suss it out</u>
<u n="609" who="S0521">I'd say two</u>
<u n="610" who="S0520">mm you'd be right I had a to look it up</u>
<u n="611" who="S0519">suss out</u>
<u n="612" who="S0520">it's not in the erm Word dictionary suss</u>
<u n="613" who="S0519">no it's casual causal language</u>
<u n="614" who="S0520" trans="overlap">sussing out is no but I think they should have words like that to be honest some quite surprising sometimes the words they don't have in the dictionary</u>
<u n="615" who="S0521">I thought that was in the Greater Oxford</u>
<u n="616" who="S0520">no doubt it is I'm talking about the Word dictionary you know when you do</u>
<u n="617" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="618" who="S0520">a spell check and they mark it as a spelling mistake but the Oxford English dictionary is much wider has all the slang in it as well</u>
<u n="619" who="S0519">I have none of your service</u>
<u n="620" who="S0520">is there such a word as fettle?</u>
<u n="621" who="S0521">would you like another one?</u>
<u n="622" who="S0519">yes</u>
<u n="623" who="S0520">fetter</u>
<u n="624" who="S0521">would you like another one</u>
<u n="625" who="S0520">what is it Scottish?</u>
<u n="626" who="S0519">fettle</u>
<u n="627" who="S0520">no thank you</u>
<u n="628" who="S0521">fettle good fettle</u>
<u n="629" who="S0519">no it's good</u>
<u n="630" who="S0520">condition</u>
<u n="631" who="S0521" trans="overlap">good condition</u>
<u n="632" who="S0519">it's good condition</u>
<u n="633" who="S0521">it's good condition</u>
<u n="634" who="S0520">yeah I've never heard it before this woman was saying today</u>
<u n="635" who="S0521" trans="overlap">it's actually a it's usually applied to health I'm in good fettle</u>
<u n="636" who="S0520">yeah the woman said how are the ex-family doing? and the other woman said erm they're fettle they're doing fettle would you say? what did she say?</u>
<u n="637" who="S0521">no they're in good fettle</u>
<u n="638" who="S0520">they're in good fettle yeah that's what she said I thought it might be Scottish slang and it <trunc>wa</trunc> yeah they were all in good fettle <pause dur="long"/> nice word <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0521">yeah brought it all back watching the beginning of P and P</u>
<u n="640" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I've seen it so many times</u>
<u n="641" who="S0521">Mr Darcy</u>
<u n="642" who="S0519">was she alright then did she say anything?</u>
<u n="643" who="S0521">yeah she said she just had er she just had a packet of crisps and a glass a water sounded like that's what she was having for tea</u>
<u n="644" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she's always had her little <pause dur="short"/> just just the one just a little for me <pause dur="short"/> two thousand and five oh not that was the movie nineteen ninety-five dad we're talking twenty years ago</u>
<u n="645" who="S0521" trans="overlap">twenty years</u>
<u n="646" who="S0520">so I reckon Colin Firth must have been</u>
<u n="647" who="S0521">thirty-five</u>
<u n="648" who="S0520">thirty odd mustn't he then so now he's fifty-five</u>
<u n="649" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="650" who="S0520">yeah still handsome but a little bit more squidgy looking <vocal desc="laugh"/> it took him that long to</u>
<u n="651" who="S0521" trans="overlap">I was just commenting on</u>
<u n="652" who="S0520" trans="overlap">be called anything but Mr Darcy</u>
<u n="653" who="S0521">I was just commenting that I was asking about Jane cos she's not nearly a pretty as Lizzy in the</u>
<u n="654" who="S0520">no I know she's meant to be</u>
<u n="655" who="S0521" trans="overlap">where apparently in the story it's the other way around d</u>
<u n="656" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="657" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="658" who="S0520">yeah she's not well she if you look at her face sometimes you see like those old portraits you know she has that kind of classical look about her dome's she? like very long neck and erm very big eyes</u>
<u n="659" who="S0521" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="660" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="661" who="S0520">and a certain type of face shape that you would that is kind of appropriate to that like when I've seen movies or <trunc>ma</trunc> remakes of other Jane Austen books erm with modern actresses in it sometimes it's not it doesn't feel quite right</u>
<u n="662" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="663" who="S0520">because their face is is not suited for it not classically beautiful you now whereas Jane has this handsome look hasn't she?</u>
<u n="664" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="665" who="S0520">but yeah she's meant to be much more beautiful than Lizzy in the book that's well her mum always goes on about how beautiful she is</u>
<u n="666" who="S0521">doesn't quite work does it yeah</u>
<u n="667" who="S0520"><trunc>Ja</trunc> er Lizzy's supposed to be pretty but more</u>
<u n="668" who="S0519" trans="overlap">hello could I book a table for three for this evening please?</u>
<u n="669" who="S0521">have you ever seen Jennifer Ehle in real life?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0519" trans="overlap">about half last seven quarter to eight something like that</u>
<u n="671" who="S0520">she's blonde</u>
<u n="672" who="S0521">blonde and American she doesn't have any trace of American accent does she?</u>
<u n="673" who="S0520">she hasn't she's excellent in it? I think she has English ancestry</u>
<u n="674" who="S0519" trans="overlap">lovely see you then bye bye</u>
<u n="675" who="S0521">okay</u>
<u n="676" who="S0520">or like she lived in England for a while or something where it's you can understand why it's so flawless cos most of the time you can tell can't you? if somebody's</u>
<u n="677" who="S0521">yes</u>
<u n="678" who="S0520">from the other side it's like Hugh Laurie as well when he does House</u>
<u n="679" who="S0521">Hugh Laurie with his American yeah</u>
<u n="680" who="S0520">like people in America think he's American</u>
<u n="681" who="S0521">they don't know he's</u>
<u n="682" who="S0520">they're convinced yeah and when he speaks in English it's very posh isn't it?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0521">Stephen Fry said that sometimes he talks in American without realising it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="684" who="S0520">he talks in American without realising?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0521">with an American accent without realising it cos of course he's he does it so much</u>
<u n="686" who="S0520">so used to being over there yeah yeah she's good Jennifer Ehle she's in a lot of theatre she does a lot of a theatre apparently</u>
<u n="687" who="S0521" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="688" who="S0520">well nothing has come even close to that in terms of an adaptation of Jane Austen in my opinion</u>
<u n="689" who="S0521"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="690" who="S0520">yeah Keira Knightley was in it the movie as Lizzy I was like no no no</u>
<u n="691" who="S0519" trans="overlap">it was horrible I watched part of it I wanted to cry</u>
<u n="692" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she's a she's fine but she's not Lizzy Bennett</u>
<u n="693" who="S0519">no way Jose</u>
<u n="694" who="S0520">no way Jose</u>
<u n="695" who="S0519">but you can imagine her wanting to do it</u>
<u n="696" who="S0520">well she's always given those parts she's been <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in Zhivago</u>
<u n="697" who="S0519">that was the worst film I've ever seen in my entire life</u>
<u n="698" who="S0520" trans="overlap">and she's been Anna Karenina</u>
<u n="699" who="S0521">Anna Karenina as well I was just thinking that</u>
<u n="700" who="S0519">no it was that was the worst</u>
<u n="701" who="S0521">that was that was poor wasn't it?</u>
<u n="702" who="S0519">I haven't seen the Lara I couldn't cope</u>
<u n="703" who="S0521" trans="overlap">compared with the</u>
<u n="704" who="S0520">oh it's nothing compared to the book it's more like a kind of er inspired but the book thing you know it's not even the right story</u>
<u n="705" who="S0519" trans="overlap">yeah it was a load of nonsense</u>
<u n="706" who="S0520">and stuff</u>
<u n="707" who="S0519">no it was awful</u>
<u n="708" who="S0520">Kitty and Levin weren't even in it</u>
<u n="709" who="S0519">that's the whole thing</u>
<u n="710" who="S0520">it's very choreographed isn't it? they keep dancing all the time it's weird</u>
<u n="711" who="S0519">mm erm yes all fine <pause dur="short"/> but England were beaten at the rugby by Wales</u>
<u n="712" who="S0520">oh I know now it's all depression they were beaten by three points in fairness so why they have to say that it's the end of the line</u>
<u n="713" who="S0519" trans="overlap">but they were the better team and it was just naughtiness they were they gave away some penalties near the end and Wales kicked the penalties in</u>
<u n="714" who="S0520">does that mean they're not going through?</u>
<u n="715" who="S0519">no they've got unless they can if they can beat Australia</u>
<u n="716" who="S0521" trans="overlap">not yet not yet</u>
<u n="717" who="S0520" trans="overlap">they have to beat Australia</u>
<u n="718" who="S0519">which is pretty unlikely but never mind</u>
<u n="719" who="S0520">are Australia the top team?</u>
<u n="720" who="S0521">no New Zealand</u>
<u n="721" who="S0519" trans="overlap">one of them no</u>
<u n="722" who="S0520">New Zealand yeah</u>
<u n="723" who="S0519">New Zealand South Africa and Australia will be the three</u>
<u n="724" who="S0521">the southern hemisphere</u>
<u n="725" who="S0519">erm</u>
<u n="726" who="S0520">the South African's won</u>
<u n="727" who="S0519" trans="overlap">so Andy can quite rightly lay <trunc>i</trunc> lay it on you've got to watch out</u>
<u n="728" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah you've got better watch out</u>
<u n="729" who="S0521">I didn't get any text message yet</u>
<u n="730" who="S0519">mm you didn't look probably</u>
<u n="731" who="S0520" trans="overlap">SA well they won theirs by quite a quite a way didn't they?</u>
<u n="732" who="S0521" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said that the first match they played all the black people cos you South African government wanted more black people on the team</u>
<u n="733" who="S0520">I've heard this erm from</u>
<u n="734" who="S0519">some sort of quota system</u>
<u n="735" who="S0520">there's a positive discrimination system in South Africa in everything so they do put black people in erm they have to have fill a quota don't they? it's also the same for jobs and university positions as well which is all fair enough to be honest but it might not</u>
<u n="736" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="737" who="S0521">I think they probably thought never mind the Japanese they're hopeless we'll just put in the B team</u>
<u n="738" who="S0519">well that's really what happened is they played the B team rather than the black team</u>
<u n="739" who="S0520">well they'll be fine they'll win</u>
<u n="740" who="S0521">well I didn't mean it like that but that's that's what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said</u>
<u n="741" who="S0519" trans="overlap">they just happen to be black</u>
<u n="742" who="S0520" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> of course no no it's a source of great erm pain for the South African's I think</u>
<u n="743" who="S0519" trans="overlap">it is it is cos they love</u>
<u n="744" who="S0520">because they they're team you know they have such pride of that</u>
<u n="745" who="S0521">I think it's the same as the cricket hardly any black people</u>
<u n="746" who="S0519">there's hardly any black people doing sport which is the biggest ludicrous <trunc>trav</trunc>travesty</u>
<u n="747" who="S0520" trans="overlap">no they're athletic do athletics don't they?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0519">no but the South Africa aren't that big on</u>
<u n="749" who="S0520" trans="overlap">on in South Africa mm no that's right no I mean of course there's always an it's always a difficult thing positive discrimination isn't it?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="751" who="S0520">but at the end I think it's the right thing</u>
<u n="752" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="753" who="S0520">it's what they did in Norway to get women into parliament</u>
<u n="754" who="S0521">did they?</u>
<u n="755" who="S0520">fifty fifty that's the law</u>
<u n="756" who="S0521">wow</u>
<u n="757" who="S0520">so they just put a lot of women in who weren't necessarily as well qualified or as well sort of er</u>
<u n="758" who="S0521">well that's what James James Corbyn has done with his cabinet</u>
<u n="759" who="S0520">well he's just put all the crap jobs</u>
<u n="760" who="S0521">the crap jobs he's given to women</u>
<u n="761" who="S0520" trans="overlap">to the women <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="762" who="S0521">there's an uproar about it actually he's he satisfied the quota it's more than fifty percent women but</u>
<u n="763" who="S0520">it's a bit insulting to be honest isn't it?</u>
<u n="764" who="S0519">the Times cartoon</u>
<u n="765" who="S0520">you might as well just put one</u>
<u n="766" who="S0519">one at the top</u>
<u n="767" who="S0520">one at top</u>
<u n="768" who="S0521">where can we give the women jobs?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0519">the Times erm did you see the cartoon? said er</u>
<u n="770" who="S0521">oh the one about the polishing the flag yeah</u>
<u n="771" who="S0519" trans="overlap">here you are erm now your job is the iron the red flag</u>
<u n="772" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="773" who="S0520">he could have known that that would have been <trunc>con</trunc> erm controversial couldn't he?</u>
<u n="774" who="S0521">I think he's a bit inadequate as a a public figure</u>
<u n="775" who="S0520">he's not very convincing but I think he'll learn the ropes won't he? like if you look at</u>
<u n="776" who="S0519" trans="overlap">but he's been a politician for ninety-nine years he's not like</u>
<u n="777" who="S0520">not but that's a different thing I mean as a leader figure</u>
<u n="778" who="S0519" trans="overlap">twenty-seven</u>
<u n="779" who="S0521" trans="overlap">entirely different though</u>
<u n="780" who="S0520">and someone who has to speak to the media all the time and stuff you know</u>
<u n="781" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="782" who="S0521">he's just found fault with the Labour party the entire time</u>
<u n="783" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="784" who="S0519">that's all he's done isn't it?</u>
<u n="785" who="S0520">it's not very encouraging is it? the way he his mannerisms and the way he erm addresses things like the way he narrates things and stuff</u>
<u n="786" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="787" who="S0521">I read Matthew Parris yesterday my</u>
<u n="788" who="S0520">Mr Matt</u>
<u n="789" who="S0521">he said er the Labour party would be entirely inward looking for the next five years erm</u>
<u n="790" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm trying to define itself yeah</u>
<u n="791" who="S0521" trans="overlap">and that's probably right because they've got to have a sort out their own differences he said that if you look at it they've had half a million votes to choose the <trunc>p</trunc> the <trunc>le</trunc> the leader and they've got to win at least twelve million to er win an election</u>
<u n="792" who="S0520">yeah I don't see that happening</u>
<u n="793" who="S0521" trans="overlap">erm it's very misleading to think that they suddenly have got a Labour party full of lefties</u>
<u n="794" who="S0520">yeah</u>
<u n="795" who="S0521">or that the voters will vote for them</u>
<u n="796" who="S0520">mm I don't think I would</u>
<u n="797" who="S0519">not at present</u>
<u n="798" who="S0521">you're not you're not alone</u>
<u n="799" who="S0520" trans="overlap">no not that I've ever voted I said this to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I was explaining it to him and then I said and I I mean I wouldn't vote for him blah and then he was like have you ever voted? and I was like no but <vocal desc="laugh"/> I have an opinion</u>
<u n="800" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="801" who="S0520">I've never lived here so it's not really close to my heart</u>
<u n="802" who="S0519" trans="overlap">I didn't vote in any of the years we lived in Holland</u>
<u n="803" who="S0520">no you just don't feel close enough to it do you?</u>
<u n="804" who="S0519" trans="overlap">people used to send their postal vote in</u>
<u n="805" who="S0521" trans="overlap">postal vote yeah</u>
<u n="806" who="S0520">I could understand that if you'd come away from three years and you it's still your country and you should be influencing the future but if you were <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and you and never intended to go back why should you have a</u>
<u n="807" who="S0521"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="808" who="S0520"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> classic</u>
<u n="809" who="S0521" trans="overlap">gosh she was a bit of a strange type wasn't she?</u>
<u n="810" who="S0520">a bit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="811" who="S0519"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="812" who="S0521">she did nothing but complain about being in Holland</u>
<u n="813" who="S0520">did she? oh</u>
<u n="814" who="S0521">it was quite monotonous the way she went on she'd only been living there for twenty years</u>
<u n="815" who="S0520">she wasn't fully in her right mind as I remember</u>
<u n="816" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="817" who="S0520">she used to leave our class for like eighty per cent of it just go off to the staff room have</u>
<u n="818" who="S0521">very odd wasn't she?</u>
<u n="819" who="S0520">coffee</u>
<u n="820" who="S0519">have a coffee and bring it back</u>
<u n="821" who="S0520">we'd be like where's our teacher gone</u>
<u n="822" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="823" who="S0519">you're supposed to be doing chapter seven which was get on with it</u>
<u n="824" who="S0521">she used to say she longed to go and live in her house in France</u>
<u n="825" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="826" who="S0521">for god's sake do it then</u>
<u n="827" who="S0520" trans="overlap">go and do it yeah crikey</u>
<u n="828" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="829" who="S0520">nobody's that bothered</u>
<u n="830" who="S0519"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="831" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="832" who="S0519">funny <pause dur="long"/> yeah</u>
<u n="833" who="S0520">alight so what time is dinner?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0519">erm</u>
<u n="835" who="S0521">and we're not walking is that what you're saying?</u>
<u n="836" who="S0519">I'm not walking biff come on</u>
<u n="837" who="S0520">you've just been on the M6 for hours</u>
<u n="838" who="S0519">I'll drive</u>
<u n="839" who="S0521">I I <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was just saying it it's it's the you know the M6 now has got to the situation you can't you know any time of day</u>
<u n="840" who="S0520">why do they not just deal with that problem?</u>
<u n="841" who="S0521" trans="overlap">any time of day it seems like you're liable to get a queue</u>
<u n="842" who="S0520">well this is why we decided not to go on Wednesday cos it's the stress of if we're in a queue and we've got to pick <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> up and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s in the car it's like</u>
<u n="843" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="844" who="S0521"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'d like it</u>
<u n="845" who="S0520">but we'll go on Sunday</u>
<u n="846" who="S0521">keeps on saying tractor</u>
<u n="847" who="S0520">he likes it for about ten minutes and then he starts to go crazy</u>
<u n="848" who="S0519">we had such a lovely time with them but then we took them to the park</u>
<u n="849" who="S0520">oh yeah you picked em up from school didn't you?</u>
<u n="850" who="S0521" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="851" who="S0519">yeah and then</u>
<u n="852" who="S0521"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had a bit of a turn</u>
<u n="853" who="S0519" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was having the ball having the time of his of life <trunc>j</trunc> on everything running about scootering everything and he loved trying to go down the fireman's pole from the slide er rather er <trunc>w</trunc> <trunc>up</trunc> the steps</u>
<u n="854" who="S0521" trans="overlap">the one in Kingsley</u>
<u n="855" who="S0519" trans="overlap">and then down the fireman's pole and he was absolutely over the moon but he was making us stand back I'm doing it myself and then crashing to the floor</u>
<u n="856" who="S0521">he had a very near miss actually</u>
<u n="857" who="S0519">he had a very near miss er cos you have to your it's for a much bigger person and you had to lean out grab the pole and jump and wrap your legs round it you know so it's quite</u>
<u n="858" who="S0520" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="859" who="S0519">anyway erm so then one time you tried to help him just the last time just tried to stand near and he just started sort of there was a strange wailing moan</u>
<u n="860" who="S0521" trans="overlap">a moaning noise yeah</u>
<u n="861" who="S0519"><vocal desc="misc"/> and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was peeping at him through the holes of the slide which made him more mad so he just goes <vocal desc="misc"/> and he wouldn't stop</u>
<u n="862" who="S0521">wouldn't stop</u>
<u n="863" who="S0520">what is that?</u>
<u n="864" who="S0519">and he just wouldn't stop and you lifted him out eventually we said come on come down the pole go down the slide de de <vocal desc="misc"/> and then you lifted him up and carried him erm and we got to the end of the path and put him down and he ran back and climbed back in and we thought well he'll go down the pole and that'll be the end of the story</u>
<u n="865" who="S0520" trans="overlap">the end of the moany bit</u>
<u n="866" who="S0519">no he just sit sat in the bit where he was sitting and carried on going <vocal desc="misc"/> so you had to pick him up and carry him all the way back the car and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s just chatting away erm and we're carrying the scooter and him and the whole thing</u>
<u n="867" who="S0520">mm he's a bit of a one isn't he? suddenly just loses the plot</u>
<u n="868" who="S0519">he loses it doesn't he?</u>
<u n="869" who="S0520">and then he just is a nightmare</u>
<u n="870" who="S0519">and we got him back and he was fine</u>
<u n="871" who="S0520">was he?</u>
<u n="872" who="S0521">but this is a good one this is good one <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we we so we were in the in the in the living room</u>
<u n="873" who="S0519" trans="overlap">oh yes that was quite funny</u>
<u n="874" who="S0521">with all the chaos and the toys get tipped everywhere</u>
<u n="875" who="S0520">yeah they do</u>
<u n="876" who="S0521">and er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was in the corner</u>
<u n="877" who="S0519">no I and I called them for tea didn't I?</u>
<u n="878" who="S0521">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came why she does it I don't know she came and put the <trunc>te</trunc> little table right next to him and started doing the Lego on it</u>
<u n="879" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah she's yeah she doesn't learn</u>
<u n="880" who="S0521">I mean what could be asking for it more than doing that?</u>
<u n="881" who="S0520">yeah it's like when she did the erm there's a den</u>
<u n="882" who="S0519">it was right next</u>
<u n="883" who="S0520">and she does it right there and then she goes I've got my own den nobody else is allowed in it so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> immediately was perfectly fine but then immediately goes over and I want to be in the den</u>
<u n="884" who="S0519" trans="overlap">dives on it</u>
<u n="885" who="S0521" trans="overlap">of course of of course</u>
<u n="886" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="887" who="S0520">it's as if she kind of wants to create the problem yeah</u>
<u n="888" who="S0521" trans="overlap">as if she wants wants to provoke something anyway the thing so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said he's got to go and have a bath or something like that</u>
<u n="889" who="S0519">it was dinnertime yeah</u>
<u n="890" who="S0520">yeah dinnertime yeah</u>
<u n="891" who="S0521">and so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> went over the table and started smashing the Lego and saying we need we need to clear this away</u>
<u n="892" who="S0520">oh dear</u>
<u n="893" who="S0519">we need to clear this away it's dinner time</u>
<u n="894" who="S0521" trans="overlap">has has has <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> ever said that to you before?</u>
<u n="895" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="896" who="S0521">we need to clear it away</u>
<u n="897" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="898" who="S0521">and so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was absolutely beyond</u>
<u n="899" who="S0519" trans="overlap">boiling</u>
<u n="900" who="S0521">beyond reproach</u>
<u n="901" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah she gets mad doesn't she?</u>
<u n="902" who="S0519" trans="overlap">screaming and banging things</u>
<u n="903" who="S0521" trans="overlap">and she sort of stomped out the room and went right up went to her bedroom and then we could hear her stomping on the flow in the bedroom</u>
<u n="904" who="S0520" trans="overlap">yeah tantrum</u>
<u n="905" who="S0519">so I I told you to to go up</u>
<u n="906" who="S0521">so I went up</u>
<u n="907" who="S0520" trans="overlap">this is the classic</u>
<u n="908" who="S0521">and he said er</u>
<u n="909" who="S0519">she said</u>
<u n="910" who="S0521" trans="overlap">she said he's er my brother is the worst brother in the world I hate him</u>
<u n="911" who="S0520" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="912" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="913" who="S0520">I think every day they have the same situation at that time you know just</u>
<u n="914" who="S0519">it's hilarious well that was the other trouble <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had emailed and said she couldn't come home on time so they neither of them got there till half six did they? so by then it was meltdown brigade</u>
<u n="915" who="S0520">every day</u>
<u n="916" who="S0519">we just went here you go bye</u>
<u n="917" who="S0520">see you later</u>
<u n="918" who="S0519">and we were off</u>
<u n="919" who="S0520">I'm going yeah it's a bit of a drama between the two of them isn't it?</u>
<u n="920" who="S0519">but then you stayed upstairs with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and read her Esio Trot</u>
<u n="921" who="S0521">I did</u>
<u n="922" who="S0520">that's cool I like that book it's the best way at that point of the day to try and separate them I think</u>
<u n="923" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="924" who="S0520">cos when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got your attention she's happy and okay</u>
<u n="925" who="S0521" trans="overlap">she's completely different isn't she? you just sort of sit her down and read a book and she's</u>
<u n="926" who="S0519">completely in her element</u>
<u n="927" who="S0521">absolutely nothing like</u>
<u n="928" who="S0520" trans="overlap">and in fact <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s the same although he's can have a turn if you're just with him</u>
<u n="929" who="S0519">he's <trunc>ju</trunc> he's completely happy</u>
<u n="930" who="S0520">and you're fully engaged in whatever he's doing like you if you're ready to dig</u>
<u n="931" who="S0521">play me grandad play me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="932" who="S0520">play me grandad</u>
<u n="933" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="934" who="S0520">yeah must be really tiring to go through that day after day</u>
<u n="935" who="S0519">I love the bit where we pick him up from school and he gives you a hug and then he walks back with us and holds our hand</u>
<u n="936" who="S0520">yeah he's sweet</u>
<u n="937" who="S0519">points everything out doesn't he?</u>
<u n="938" who="S0521">oh yes</u>
<u n="939" who="S0519">this is the prickly bush</u>
<u n="940" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="941" who="S0519">now walk on the path safely</u>
<u n="942" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="943" who="S0519">the cars are on the road oh there's more cars and more cars</u>
<u n="944" who="S0520">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="945" who="S0519">right <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> clothing</u>
<u n="946" who="S0520">yes don't you like my pyjama slipper combo?</u>
<u n="947" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no it's not looking like we're getting to a glass of wine any time soon please get some clothes</u>
<u n="948" who="S0521" trans="overlap">are we going to have a fashion demo?</u>
<u n="949" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's all about the wine</u>
<u n="950" who="S0519">it's all about the wine sack the food I've eaten enough <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="951" who="S0520">okay I'll shall demonstrate my jeans to here's what's happened I've bought two pairs one of which I</u>
<u n="952" who="S0519" trans="overlap">don't tell dad anything</u>
<u n="953" who="S0520">mean to return</u>
<u n="954" who="S0519">just which ones he likes best</u>
<u n="955" who="S0520" trans="overlap">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="956" who="S0521">okay <pause dur="short"/> all things considered <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="0520 leaves"/>
<u n="957" who="S0519">crisps and water what's that?</u>
<u n="958" who="S0521">just simple</u>
<u n="959" who="S0519">no it's not food</u>
<u n="960" who="S0521">no it's not food <pause dur="short"/> I wouldn't be surprised if that's her tea</u>
<u n="961" who="S0519">course it is <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="962" who="S0521">good job she's eaten well this weekend <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="yawn"/> so you don't like this article about selfies do you?</u>
<u n="963" who="S0519">I I didn't agree with him</u>
<u n="964" who="S0521">what the idea of laughing at people?</u>
<u n="965" who="S0519">the idea of laughing at people who died is a little harsh they're foolish and stupid and if they've fallen down the stairs and hurt themselves but when you have to say what are people doing it you see falling down the stairs at the Taj Mahal is not the same as standing in front of a train that's approaching you to try and get a selfie</u>
<u n="966" who="S0521" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="967" who="S0519">is it? I mean that is <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="968" who="S0521">no that's just completely ridiculous</u>
<u n="969" who="S0519">er that is a a deliberately putting yourself at risk</u>
<u n="970" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="971" who="S0519">whereas the somebody who fell down the stairs was just not thinking what he was doing and had an accident but to to lose your life for it is not what you've got in mind is it really? erm</u>
<u n="972" who="S0521">have you do you read his stuff cos he he's always a bit on the edge you know?</u>
<u n="973" who="S0519">yeah I I I</u>
<u n="974" who="S0521">with what's okay to say</u>
<u n="975" who="S0519">yeah no I don't normally I don't think? is it Giles Coren?</u>
<u n="976" who="S0521">Giles Coren yeah</u>
<u n="977" who="S0519">yeah mm no I think I've only ever got half way through most of it</u>
<u n="978" who="S0521">yes what what's her name the</u>
<u n="979" who="S0519">the yes the other Coren one</u>
<u n="980" who="S0521" trans="overlap">Victoria Coren's husband no her brother he brother the one that does the quiz programme</u>
<u n="981" who="S0519">yeah they're both very clever aren't they? <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s complaint is we've got no full length mirrors in this house</u>
<u n="982" who="S0520">alright</u>
<u n="983" who="S0521">okay <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> let's see it</u>
<u n="984" who="S0520">just a second</u>
<u n="985" who="S0519">have to adjust them</u>
<u n="986" who="S0520">this is pair number one</u>
<u n="987" who="S0519">oh beautiful</u>
<u n="988" who="S0520">ooh</u>
<u n="989" who="S0519">oh do the zip up for goodness sake and tuck the erm</u>
<u n="990" who="S0521">mm that's nice</u>
<u n="991" who="S0520">this is to go with it</u>
<u n="992" who="S0519">oh this is beautiful <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="993" who="S0520">nice it's really long</u>
<u n="994" who="S0519" trans="overlap">absolutely gorgeous yes</u>
<u n="995" who="S0520">for India as well covers your bum</u>
<u n="996" who="S0521">yes I like that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="997" who="S0519">lovely</u>
<u n="998" who="S0520">so that's pair number one now the only problem with them is</u>
<u n="999" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0521">no pockets</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0520">they're a little bit short</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0519">teensy bit short I would have said that</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0520">this is the long</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0519">and when they shrink</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0520">they're supposed to be long they're a long length jean</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0519" trans="overlap">jean</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0521">oh right</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0520">but unfortunately</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0519">they're only just making it</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0521">yes you wouldn't know that you wouldn't know that they were long length</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0520">you wouldn't would you? and I think it's because I've got an eight on</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0519" trans="overlap">when you put boots on you won't see them</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0520">which I've never been an eight but in this particular store I am not telling you where</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0520">and erm</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0519">too short slightly</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0520">I think because they pull up here maybe</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0519">yes</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0519">erm</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0520">so but I would wear them with boots mostly</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0519" trans="overlap">but with boots it won't it won't make any difference</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0520">if I wore them with boots they'd be like this</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0519">mm they'll be fine with boots</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0520">and in the summer I will just roll them up</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0519">and have them as slightly shorter</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0520">and have them as like ankle ones</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0519">yes they're lovely</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0520">okay so that's pair number one</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0519" trans="overlap">very nice</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0521">pair number one</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0519">okay <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1033" who="S0521">what are you smiling at me for is there a story here?</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0519">well only one pair is meant to be kept</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0521">okay she has to make the choice</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0519">mm <pause dur="short"/> and one is much dearer than the other this is the thing that we I was not going to tell you</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0521">I guessed that might be the case the way you said it</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0519">so we're supposed to see if we can tell the difference is it worthy of the difference?</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0519">which one's just better if you don't even know</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0521">regardless of cost</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0519">regardless of cost <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1043" who="S0521">those look quite velvety those actually</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/> this is pair number two</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0521">oh I see what you mean yes</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0520">dad probably can't tell that I've got new jeans on erm they're a <trunc>li</trunc></u>
<u n="1047" who="S0519">tiny bit longer</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0520">longer they're also a long length</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0521">right</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0520">they're a little bit more roomy on the bum</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0521" trans="overlap">so if you don't mind me saying so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1052" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0521">I think it's apples and pears the first pair is clearly more expensive and it looks nicer</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0520" trans="overlap">what do you think?</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0519">first pair is nicer</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0520">these are the more expensive ones</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0521">oh</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0520">three times more expensive</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0521">oh</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0519">interesting</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0520">isn't it? because they do I mean the thing here is that they're a little bit higher</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0521">they fit you better yes</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0520">here so that fits better</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0519">yes</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0521">yes</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0520">and yet I don't feel that this bit was quite as flattering somehow maybe it's because you know sometimes skinnies can make you knees look a bit chubby</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0519">that's what I felt with you know the cheap ones that I had I think they accentuated my chubby knees whereas these black ones seem to make them disappear</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0520" trans="overlap">it doesn't always yeah the grey the first pair were are the same as the blue ones that I have exactly the same but for some reason they fall much shorter</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0519">probably being the eight</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0520">no both of them are the same size</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0519">see when you pulled them up I didn't I didn't even think they were as nice at the top</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0520">I think the problem with these might be that they they'll become a bit too baggy saggy here</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0520">and you don't want any feeling of that bulge bulging where you bulge</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0519">mm mm</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0520">so you think the first ones are nicer? cos that was my conclusion but I can't see</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0521">I think the first ones are</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0519">I think the first ones are nicer</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0520">love it twenty pounds sixty-nine pounds we love it you kind of</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0519" trans="overlap">no doubt <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> would have a different opinion</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0520">no it's not necessarily the case</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0519">but I actually really liked the first pair</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0520">the thing about these jeans <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> introduced me to them the Next ones they do petite short length regular long in all the sizes</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0519">mm</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0520">and they're really got a lot of elastic in them so they're comfortable you don't you know?</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0519">I wonder why these ones this one's more?</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0520" trans="overlap">partly it's the label</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0519" trans="overlap">do they not do extra long?</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0520">they do in some I'll have to check on line erm they partly it's the label is more a posh label that J in JLs and this is from them as well and I really like it</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0519">that's beautiful</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0520">but erm they're they do feel slightly softer and nicer material but I don't know if it's all just psychosomatic I wasn't even going to order them</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm soon as you told me they were the nicer ones I start looking at them in more detail</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0520" trans="overlap">now you're like so did I and the length is a little bit better for me</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0519">the length is slightly better but I think I actually just preferred the colour the of the other ones</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0521">me too me too</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0520" trans="overlap">I think that's me too dad <vocal desc="laugh"/> dad's on a fashion</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0519">done</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0520">no I'm happy because that was the conclusion I came to but I can't I can't see them in a mirror</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0519">er to be honest the thing will probably be will be that the other</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0520" trans="overlap">I'll be happy to return them</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0519">yeah will the others will wear out quicker but then just buy some more</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0520">no what well exactly but what I've noticed</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0519">or buy two pairs of the others have two colours and feel like you've got a bargain</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0520" trans="overlap">well that's why I was buying them in the first place bias I got a blue pair and I and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then said if it's twenty pounds and they do the in other colours</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0519">buy them</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0520">and you like them</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0521">half a dozen</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0520">just buy yeah they have a dark very dark blue the grey and they have washed kind of a black but this is a nice light grey</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0519">it's a lovely grey I liked the grey</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0520">done</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0521">excellent</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0519">done excellent right let's go get them off</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0520" trans="overlap">right well it's free deliveries and free returns with this company so I haven't lost anything</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0519">no everything is I I love Next</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0520" trans="overlap">and it was next day free next day delivery</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0519">even if you order it at like six in the afternoon</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0520" trans="overlap">at midnight and then you just put it in their <unclear/> and they give you a</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0519">an envelope</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0521" trans="overlap">it's like Bangkok</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0520">an envelope to put it in</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0519">no</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0521">like Bangkok</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0519">and I've done a couple of those envelope returning malarkeys</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0520">well yeah so that's good I've got one more erm</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0519">did you get any jumpers I'll tell you what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you me and the gatepost will have a an <anon type="place"/> John Lewis</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0520">I've got one more parcel form John Lewis so <unclear/> but I can bring it up show you and</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0519">and we can always change it</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0520">and we can do the same like I bought two and one of them is quite expensive but <unclear/> erm you know jumpers I don't like acrylic</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0519">no</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0520">and <unclear/> wool so I bought it but you can't know until you try like sometimes</u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="1133" who="S0520">so I think I might wear those then <pause dur="long"/> erm I need a deodorant I think I left my deodorant in erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="1134" who="S0520"><unclear/> because people just want erm I need a <unclear/></u>
<u n="1135" who="S0519">okay I've got two</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0520">that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="1137" who="S0519">I might have taken yours <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos <unclear/></u>
<u n="1138" who="S0520"><unclear/> I think I left mine at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="1139" who="S0519">if they were an inch longer they'd be</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0520">I think I'll wear my or shall I wear them or shall I try and get a longer one?</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0519">try and get a longer just in case I mean they're perfect and as you say I the summer you can roll them up and but if they were if they were an inch longer they'd be even more perfect</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0520"><unclear/> I'm looking at them there and I <unclear/></u>
<u n="1143" who="S0519">now if you just do that they they look slightly <trunc>ski</trunc> skimpier</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0520" trans="overlap">no the colour is nicer</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0519">the colour is nice have two lots and next time buy the posh ones</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0520">I don't even want to buy the posh ones though <unclear/></u>
<u n="1147" who="S0519">no</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0520">normally I would just buy the posh ones by default but <unclear/></u>
<u n="1149" who="S0519">no you can see that they're now when you do that they're better quality now that I know <vocal desc="laugh"/> I can't believe I I wasn't able to spot the expense that's really tragic</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0521">did you think the first ones were dearer then?</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0519">I thought the first ones were going to be the more expensive ones</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0521">me too</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0519">the others looked a little bit erm</u>
<u n="1154" who="S0521">looked a bit ordinary</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0519"><trunc>chep</trunc> ordinary material didn't they?</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0519">now you are also on a mission to get some more trousers and shirts while we're upon <anon type="place"/> cos the shopping's much better in <anon type="place"/> I have to tell you</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0521">so Australia won sixty-five three against Uruguay</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0519">I looked up that up yeah they only got one <trunc>bo</trunc>onus point I don't know why we've got two do you get a bonus point for being within a certain number of the you know maybe if you're within five of the team that beat you</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0521">yeah could be</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0519">you get a bonus because we only got one for the original match and we've now got two</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0521">yeah and Scotland had a big win against erm United States</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0519">good</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0521">so they're top of their table</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0521">ahead of South Africa <pause dur="long"/> Ireland's at the top of their table <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1167" who="S0520">what time have we got to be erm?</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0519">half seven to quarter to eight</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0521">it's half seven now <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1170" who="S0519">come on then</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0520">these are the same ones in blue</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0520">see how much longer they are</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0519">yeah they're really longer</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0520">mm</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0519">and let me have a look are they XL ex long</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0520">no eight long same size it's quite annoying isn't it?</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0519">mm very</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0520">sometimes it's just the individual jean as well like you would get another jean same size and it would have the extra</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0519" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0520">especially when they're manufactured en mass in a slave camp in China somewhere</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0519">I know that's what you're paying for</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0520">you say that but it's not necessarily true unless you buy from like Marks and Spencer or somewhere with like an ethical</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0519">no I know</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0520">policy</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0521">so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do you know a guy called Giles Coren</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0520">Giles? should I? is he famous?</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0521">do you know Victoria Coren?</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0520">mm Coren?</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0521">yeah</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0520">no</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0519">no come on biff</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0521">have we got to go?</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0519">yeah</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0521">I'll explain to you when we get the pub because it it's er actually quite a an interesting story</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0519">is it? I thought you were just going to say he writes in the Times</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0521">mm</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0519">have you got money darling?</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0521">I've got my wallet I never have any money you know that</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0520"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
