<text id="SQ63">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:15:41</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-19</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0486 S0536</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>In the ticket office at the TME working party near Taunton.</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Aquaintences</relationships>
		<topics>Successful career inventing and marketing printing systems.  Working in Germany at exhibitions.</topics>
		<activity>Talking while taking a break from the TME working party near Taunton.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, Explaining, Inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0486">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English</nat>
				<birthplace>Well, Somerset</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England/Wales</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>I may have a slight Somerset accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Taunton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>40 years on and off</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southwest</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>retired artist and antique dealer/gallery owner</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0536">
				<exactage>74</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Guiseley</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>General English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Axminster</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20 years +</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0486">be careful you don't fall off the back there won't you're right on the edge</u>
<u n="2" who="S0536">I've got cramp <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0486" trans="overlap">have you? oh right</u>
<u n="4" who="S0536">and I just thought I'd er</u>
<u n="5" who="S0486" trans="overlap">alright <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0536" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="7" who="S0486" trans="overlap">let me move those around</u>
<u n="8" who="S0536" trans="overlap">yeah that's it yeah</u>
<u n="9" who="S0486">do you get cramp often?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0536">erm er fairly frequently yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0486">do you?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0536"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0486"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well <trunc>w</trunc>well for the tape we're sitting in a very small <trunc>sig</trunc> erm ticket office here at the model engineers and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is with me this morning and he's going to talk about well why are you a model engineer?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0536">I think it's an engineering background my father was</u>
<u n="15" who="S0486" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0536" trans="overlap">a civil engineer</u>
<u n="17" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="18" who="S0536">and erm I studied <trunc>u</trunc> er engineering at at college actually and then erm went into engineering initially as a <trunc>po</trunc> as a post as a erm graduate apprentice for <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right right</u>
<u n="20" who="S0536">erm ending up at their applied research laboratories at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="21" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="22" who="S0536" trans="overlap">and er working on just er to start with guided weapons and then on er satellite communications</u>
<u n="23" who="S0486">very interesting</u>
<u n="24" who="S0536">then I erm formed a company with a couple of friends and erm we sold printing equipment all over the world <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0486">right printing equipment?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0536">yeah we actually modify we actually produce modifications for existing equipment</u>
<u n="27" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="28" who="S0536">erm we'd all worked for one company who was at the time was a majorly a brand leader in the area and we produced electronics for the print industry</u>
<u n="29" who="S0486">right right because erm in the in the I I worked for newspapers for quite a long time for about sixteen years I worked for the <anon type="place"/> and did you do anything at all with with the <anon type="place"/> the <anon type="place"/> press?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0536">I I never really used to <trunc>sp</trunc> <unclear>most</unclear> most of my time was spent in the laboratory I</u>
<u n="31" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="32" who="S0536">I I ran the R and B department</u>
<u n="33" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right right</u>
<u n="34" who="S0536">and erm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0486" trans="overlap">erm right so you were research and development and erm really you're the boffin behind the the engineering not not the sales person or the</u>
<u n="36" who="S0536">no occasionally we we'd <trunc>g</trunc>go out to see customers when there was</u>
<u n="37" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="38" who="S0536">a particular <trunc>k</trunc> a particular problem the company was small enough so that you erm er everybody had a go at everything practically</u>
<u n="39" who="S0486">right right and how many people were there in your company?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0536">er the maximum it was about thirty</u>
<u n="41" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="42" who="S0536" trans="overlap">but most of the time it was about twelve fifteen something like that</u>
<u n="43" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right right and erm you must have seen a lot of changes with printing techniques over the years</u>
<u n="44" who="S0536">erm yes erm the er I worked for <trunc>t</trunc>two companies erm before <trunc>b</trunc> going independent one was <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="45" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="46" who="S0536">and so I saw the development of the scanner from the early analogue scanners to the later digital scanners and so on</u>
<u n="47" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="48" who="S0536">and then it moved to <unclear>a liner type</unclear> and produced one of their <trunc>desi</trunc> er or designed one of their miniature scanners which er was the er sort of last generation before the desktop really took over and er</u>
<u n="49" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="50" who="S0536" trans="overlap">people started using small flatbeds</u>
<u n="51" who="S0486">yes I remember the erm in there was a sort of like a it was like a piece of cardboard er was it called <unclear>Dycron</unclear>? <trunc>Di</trunc> er er er a system where it was impressed on a piece of card and then that was impressed onto a roll that was put on a roll and then it was rolled out what</u>
<u n="52" who="S0536" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="53" who="S0486" trans="overlap">was that method called? that came somewhere in the middle</u>
<u n="54" who="S0536"><trunc>y</trunc>yes I've I I well I never worked on the press side so I I</u>
<u n="55" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh you didn't well they adopted</u>
<u n="56" who="S0536" trans="overlap">it was purely</u>
<u n="57" who="S0486" trans="overlap">that method at one stage and what the the card the residue cardboard that they left behind I used to paint on I used to sort of try and</u>
<u n="58" who="S0536"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0486">bend it back the other way and paint on the back</u>
<u n="60" who="S0536">yes</u>
<u n="61" who="S0486" trans="overlap">but that was very interesting</u>
<u n="62" who="S0536">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0486" trans="overlap">I wish I hadn't got rid of some of those though they were er they might be worth something today erm but er a lot of erm these processes they're good for a while and then they just go don't they?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0536">they do yes I mean the the although some of the high quality work is still done on the kind of scanners</u>
<u n="65" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0536" trans="overlap">I worked on</u>
<u n="67" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="68" who="S0536">most of it's now gone to the flatbeds which you put on your desktop</u>
<u n="69" who="S0486">yes yeah in the metallic printing erm they've still got in <anon type="place"/> university and a lot of the universities now and in the art departments they use old printing blocks</u>
<u n="70" who="S0536">yes</u>
<u n="71" who="S0486">a lot of the time and they put</u>
<u n="72" who="S0536" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0486">you see it <trunc>in</trunc>integrated in art and erm I have erm two blocks that I use for my initials when I do a painting I frequently you ink them up and stick them on at the bottom if they're in a piece of abstract work I mean it's not relevant in something that's smaller but er yeah so erm and and now you've retired and erm have <trunc>ha</trunc> er what have you got on the go as far as engines concerns er any engines at all?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0536">er yes I tend to build things in parallel because I like</u>
<u n="75" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="76" who="S0536" trans="overlap">to be able to swap between different scales and</u>
<u n="77" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0536" trans="overlap">different sizes</u>
<u n="79" who="S0486">oh right</u>
<u n="80" who="S0536">and so I'm building a two and a half inch gauge model of one of the American er wartime austerity locomotives</u>
<u n="81" who="S0486">oh right</u>
<u n="82" who="S0536">a five inch gauge Manning Wardle</u>
<u n="83" who="S0486">oh right</u>
<u n="84" who="S0536">and a seven and a quarter inch gauge Hunslet</u>
<u n="85" who="S0486">not much then <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0536">no no just just enough to keep me happy</u>
<u n="87" who="S0486"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so how much time do you spend in the workshop every day do you think?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0536">erm it obviously varies but er erm I quite often spend the whole day in the workshop</u>
<u n="89" who="S0486">do you?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0536" trans="overlap">cos it's</u>
<u n="91" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah yeah and do you find that if you don't get your model engineering done it <trunc>ma</trunc> it impacts on your erm er humour?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0536">not particularly no but I I do <trunc>s</trunc> yes I I you do suffer from withdrawal symptoms</u>
<u n="93" who="S0486"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0536">if you don't er <vocal desc="laugh"/> get your fix occasionally</u>
<u n="95" who="S0486">it yes erm I notice erm obviously cos I live with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I I I notice that he he gets he <trunc>does</trunc> he he never gets cross but he he does get slightly irritated I think if he can't get and do what he wants to do he feel he he's in a middle of a project and he wants to and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was saying the same you know he he he just gets very disgruntled if he can't get on with it</u>
<u n="96" who="S0536">I think probably we <trunc>a</trunc> we all tend to feel that way yes</u>
<u n="97" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0536" trans="overlap">but er</u>
<u n="99" who="S0486">and I'm the same with my art if I've got to if I'm diverted by doing housework or things that I really don't want to do I I do get grumpy</u>
<u n="100" who="S0536">yes</u>
<u n="101" who="S0486" trans="overlap">and I need to get erm I do I actually get very temperamental altogether so I've just got to get in there and do it you you see so you've been coming on these working parties now for how long?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0536">virtually since I joined the clubs</u>
<u n="103" who="S0486">really?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0536" trans="overlap">about five years</u>
<u n="105" who="S0486">five years? yeah yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0536" trans="overlap">one one time there were only three of us who normally turned up</u>
<u n="107" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="108" who="S0536">erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and myself</u>
<u n="109" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="110" who="S0536">and so erm I also edit the magazine so I'm dubbed as the three musketeers</u>
<u n="111" who="S0486">oh right</u>
<u n="112" who="S0536">er er how did it work out? <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0486"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0536"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0486">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0536">yes</u>
<u n="117" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes I like it erm cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> did <anon type="place"/> for a while didn't he?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0536">he did yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0486" trans="overlap">and now you're doing it</u>
<u n="120" who="S0536">yes I do it</u>
<u n="121" who="S0486">so I was I was going to I know that I'm too late for this edition er but I want to put a little thank you in <anon type="place"/> to everybody who's erm who's you know given their fifteen minutes to</u>
<u n="122" who="S0536">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0486">and also at the same time put something in to ask if there are any other members who would like to talk at some time when I come back</u>
<u n="124" who="S0536">mm yes</u>
<u n="125" who="S0486">so erm so how are you finding the challenge of doing <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0536">oh it's interesting yes</u>
<u n="127" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0536" trans="overlap">I quite enjoy it yes</u>
<u n="129" who="S0486" trans="overlap">you do? yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0536" trans="overlap">yes I think it I think it's getting to the point having done it for now about three or four years I that it's er time that I</u>
<u n="131" who="S0486">oh <trunc>ri</trunc></u>
<u n="132" who="S0536" trans="overlap">hand it over to somebody else</u>
<u n="133" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="134" who="S0536" trans="overlap">for them to er</u>
<u n="135" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh so now you've been doing it for three or four years and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was before you was he? or</u>
<u n="136" who="S0536" trans="overlap">he he was yes</u>
<u n="137" who="S0486" trans="overlap">he was yes so I'm right out of date because</u>
<u n="138" who="S0536" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="139" who="S0486">isn't it funny how the years go on and you still think oh it's still think it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and in fact it's yourself so</u>
<u n="140" who="S0536" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="141" who="S0486">dreadful so you you how much time does that take up?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0536">erm it takes up most of a week basically</u>
<u n="143" who="S0486">does it?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0536" trans="overlap">to put each er</u>
<u n="145" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0536">each edition together</u>
<u n="147" who="S0486"><trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="148" who="S0536">erm</u>
<u n="149" who="S0486">that's a big contribution as a volunteer isn't it really?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0536">er yes it is er</u>
<u n="151" who="S0486">but it's your hobby as well</u>
<u n="152" who="S0536" trans="overlap">it that's right it is</u>
<u n="153" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah yeah but erm have you ever thought of having a woman's page in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0536">erm I've never had a contributor <vocal desc="laugh"/> who give me any any contribution but I'd welcome it yes anything new I mean it's</u>
<u n="155" who="S0486" trans="overlap">anything new</u>
<u n="156" who="S0536">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0486">I was actually thinking about this erm show you're planning next year and erm thinking of having <trunc>s</trunc> I mean I I'm a member of the model engineers because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> always pays for me to be a member I wonder how many other of the ladies are <trunc>me</trunc> actual members and if they are erm whether we ought to have some sort of contribution in there because we are actually members and I sometimes think</u>
<u n="158" who="S0536" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="159" who="S0486"><trunc>noth</trunc>nothing big just just you know just some lines every now and then would be nice <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0536">well we do have contributions from the various sections</u>
<u n="161" who="S0486">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0536" trans="overlap">of the at the <anon type="place"/> library</u>
<u n="163" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0536" trans="overlap">erm occasionally from the <unclear>tickers</unclear> and erm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="166" who="S0536">so yes it was no real reason why there shouldn't be a section</u>
<u n="167" who="S0486">no I</u>
<u n="168" who="S0536" trans="overlap"><trunc>e</trunc>even put something in from the nomads occasionally</u>
<u n="169" who="S0486">do you? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0536"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0486">yeah so erm erm when you were doing your job originally looking back at the beginning of your career after you left university erm did you did you sort of fall into that erm way of working or did or was it something that you really wanted to do?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0536">oh no I I knew I wanted to go into design and development</u>
<u n="173" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="174" who="S0536" trans="overlap">into R and D right from the start</u>
<u n="175" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0536">and erm say I although I've erm I er well <trunc>whe</trunc> we started the company I was a director of the company so I had <trunc>re</trunc>responsibilities</u>
<u n="177" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="178" who="S0536" trans="overlap">as a director</u>
<u n="179" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="180" who="S0536" trans="overlap">but erm I was always involved the technical side yes</u>
<u n="181" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right what would you say over the years was the most satisfying project you worked on?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0536">oh that's difficult erm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0486">or one of them you know</u>
<u n="184" who="S0536">erm well in some respects the the well when we were working when we were er became independent erm we erm produced an interface between the established erm graphic art scanners</u>
<u n="185" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="186" who="S0536" trans="overlap">er and the desktop</u>
<u n="187" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="188" who="S0536" trans="overlap">and we were virtually the first people in the world to do this so we</u>
<u n="189" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="190" who="S0536" trans="overlap">erm one year</u>
<u n="191" who="S0486" trans="overlap">that was an achievement yes</u>
<u n="192" who="S0536">yeah one year we exported ninety-two percent of our product</u>
<u n="193" who="S0486">really?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0536">and we got a Queen's Award for Industry for it</u>
<u n="195" who="S0486">my goodness</u>
<u n="196" who="S0536">erm so it was that was perhaps the most in some respects the most interesting</u>
<u n="197" who="S0486">yeah erm erm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0536" trans="overlap">and so</u>
<u n="199" who="S0486" trans="overlap">where were where did you export it?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0536">erm we a lot went er to the States</u>
<u n="201" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="202" who="S0536">erm one of the directors was married to a Japanese lady</u>
<u n="203" who="S0486">oh right</u>
<u n="204" who="S0536" trans="overlap">and we exported quite a lot to Japan</u>
<u n="205" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="206" who="S0536">erm and in and the rest of Europe in general</u>
<u n="207" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="208" who="S0536" trans="overlap">we had quite an active agent in Germany</u>
<u n="209" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="210" who="S0536">and erm so virtually the whole of the world</u>
<u n="211" who="S0486">the but it because you were more er you were obviously research and development did you you did get sometimes obviously a chance to go to these places did you? or or travel at all?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0536">er yes in erm er my wife had a a horse and we had a horse box</u>
<u n="213" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="214" who="S0536">so the my company car was a erm a Discovery</u>
<u n="215" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="216" who="S0536">and that was used to tow the company's trailer whenever we went to a show</u>
<u n="217" who="S0486">right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0536">and so I often ended up driving the thing down the autobahns to Dusseldorf or somewhere <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right oh I see</u>
<u n="220" who="S0536" trans="overlap">loaded with er</u>
<u n="221" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="222" who="S0536">all sorts of bits and pieces for the show</u>
<u n="223" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah yeah they're very fast those autobahns aren't they? well erm we lived in Germany for a while and erm I think it was before we really had very many motorways er it was nineteen <trunc>f</trunc> I'm talking nineteen fifty-eight</u>
<u n="224" who="S0536">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0486" trans="overlap">and erm in those days I remember travelling on the autobahn and thinking well was it in nineteen fifty or? I went back to Germany in erm nineteen sixty-seven as well so it could have been nineteen sixty-seven but they <trunc>s</trunc> their roads seemed to be far more far faster and bigger than than what we had in England but it may be just me mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0536">yes I no I just took them <vocal desc="laugh"/> took them my stride yes</u>
<u n="227" who="S0486" trans="overlap">you just er <trunc>y</trunc>yeah you do really just er</u>
<u n="228" who="S0536" trans="overlap">with three tonnes behind and a Land Rover</u>
<u n="229" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0536">you're not gonna go very quickly anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="231" who="S0486" trans="overlap">no no and so when you were there and <trunc>th</trunc>these exhibitions you were talking to people as well were you?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0536">yes</u>
<u n="233" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0536">in fact the idea for the interface really we we first put out at a a show just to sort of see what the kind of response would be</u>
<u n="235" who="S0486">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0536">and erm we got people from all sorts of parts of <trunc>th</trunc> of the er show</u>
<u n="237" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="238" who="S0536">coming from other companies saying</u>
<u n="239" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="240" who="S0536" trans="overlap">this would be interesting so that was really what er pushed us into doing it</u>
<u n="241" who="S0486">absolutely I mean I've been to with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to <anon type="place"/> er <anon type="place"/> where they do the huge erm industrial show for the railways and also I went to <anon type="place"/> with him in fact trying to find him the place the site was so big that trying to find <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> on the site was really difficult erm</u>
<u n="242" who="S0536" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0486">and it took so long to get there and I used to find I'd get there and find he was deep in conversation with a potential customer and which I of course wouldn't wouldn't even wink at him you know</u>
<u n="244" who="S0536">mm</u>
<u n="245" who="S0486">erm and then I'd have to find all my way back <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0536"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0486">so erm it was a bit of a shame really and erm you know there you go but erm and that's over now and that twenty years of that erm yes it's it's over he was there a lot longer so erm did you meet your wife at work? or</u>
<u n="248" who="S0536">yes I did yes</u>
<u n="249" who="S0486" trans="overlap">you did?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0536">yes</u>
<u n="251" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="252" who="S0536">erm I got a er call from one of the other secretaries saying that erm I knew her vaguely but not very well</u>
<u n="253" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="254" who="S0536">and er saying that she'd broken down</u>
<u n="255" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="256" who="S0536">and erm since I was er interested in cars then I got er it <trunc>w</trunc> it was suggested we were working late and erm I think we were about the only people around</u>
<u n="257" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="258" who="S0536" trans="overlap">and er so suggested we went out and rescued her so</u>
<u n="259" who="S0486" trans="overlap"><trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="260" who="S0536" trans="overlap">two of us went out</u>
<u n="261" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="262" who="S0536" trans="overlap">and er we <trunc>m</trunc> er sort of struck up a friendship after that</u>
<u n="263" who="S0486">oh right oh that's a very nice story</u>
<u n="264" who="S0536"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0486">yeah that's a very nice story erm so erm do you have any other hobbies mm er besides engineering? I <trunc>mea</trunc> you probably don't have time but do you have anything at all that you're interested in apart?</u>
<u n="266" who="S0536">erm I although I haven't sailed much recently I</u>
<u n="267" who="S0486" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="268" who="S0536" trans="overlap">sail erm I erm restore historic cars as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0486">oh right okay</u>
<u n="270" who="S0536">erm again it's probably <trunc>se</trunc> rather taken a back of a seat recently</u>
<u n="271" who="S0486">yes</u>
<u n="272" who="S0536">erm <pause dur="short"/> oh travel all sorts of things</u>
<u n="273" who="S0486">what historic car have you got at the moment?</u>
<u n="274" who="S0536">erm I've got a Healey Silverstone which is</u>
<u n="275" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh have you?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0536" trans="overlap">the <trunc>m</trunc> the most interesting</u>
<u n="277" who="S0486">oh wow</u>
<u n="278" who="S0536">and erm I've got the I built the last ever kit TVR</u>
<u n="279" who="S0486">right</u>
<u n="280" who="S0536" trans="overlap">and I've still got that as well</u>
<u n="281" who="S0486" trans="overlap">right oh right</u>
<u n="282" who="S0536">so that's two of them though <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="283" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yeah that's erm er and and do you go to shows with them at all or?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0536">erm I I haven't done recently</u>
<u n="285" who="S0486">no</u>
<u n="286" who="S0536" trans="overlap">but I have done occasionally in the past yes</u>
<u n="287" who="S0486">it's quite nice isn't it in the summer? you <trunc>ge</trunc> you know when you can get the if you've got a a convertible or or any car really to go out and go to a show and walk round and have a look it's quite nice</u>
<u n="288" who="S0536">yes my I infected my son and erm</u>
<u n="289" who="S0486">oh right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0536" trans="overlap">he owns a TVR and we took one on a rally in Spain</u>
<u n="291" who="S0486">oh right</u>
<u n="292" who="S0536" trans="overlap">a couple of years ago which was</u>
<u n="293" who="S0486" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="294" who="S0536" trans="overlap">quite fun</u>
<u n="295" who="S0486">oh right goodness erm I I think erm I I used to know someone with a TVR years ago he lived over in <anon type="place"/> er he ended he he got rid of it eventually and bought and E-Type</u>
<u n="296" who="S0536">uhu</u>
<u n="297" who="S0486">and I was saying this morning to erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that erm I er when I had my car accident and I was nearly burnt to death er afterwards I went out <vocal desc="laugh"/> my car was obviously burnt <trunc>t</trunc> completely and I went out and bought erm an MG Midget and a fur coat <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0536"><vocal desc="laugh"/> why not?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0486"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it was sort of it was sort of protest really you know erm as er to you know to say look right here I'm back in the world you know I may not have my looks</u>
<u n="300" who="S0536" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="301" who="S0486" trans="overlap">back for a while but I've got my fur coat and my MG</u>
<u n="302" who="S0536">yes why not?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0486">and erm you know there there you are</u>
<u n="304" who="S0536"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="305" who="S0486" trans="overlap">I think you you've got to do that erm it's very important so erm have you had a holiday this year? or</u>
<u n="306" who="S0536">erm no</u>
<u n="307" who="S0486">ah</u>
<u n="308" who="S0536">but erm we I we normally go skiing in the winter</u>
<u n="309" who="S0486">oh do you?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0536">er so</u>
<u n="311" who="S0486" trans="overlap">oh right</u>
<u n="312" who="S0536" trans="overlap">we our holiday is booked for the end of January</u>
<u n="313" who="S0486">oh right</u>
<u n="314" who="S0536">so we're going</u>
<u n="315" who="S0486" trans="overlap">very nice</u>
<u n="316" who="S0536">yes</u>
<u n="317" who="S0486">we we're going to <anon type="place"/> for Christmas so er</u>
<u n="318" who="S0536">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0486">yeah are you erm er I I I can't help getting the analogy out of my my mind about <trunc>Ang</trunc>Angela Merkel who was described in the newspaper as a skier going down a slope without any any form of stopping or</u>
<u n="320" who="S0536"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0486">or something like that and I <vocal desc="laugh"/> now every time somebody mentions skiing I see Angela Merkel going down a slope because she invited all these people to go to her country and yet didn't realise I mean it's never ending at the moment</u>
<u n="322" who="S0536">yes</u>
<u n="323" who="S0486">erm it's a big problem erm but erm well we collectively have done fifteen minutes so okay?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0536"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes that's <trunc>f</trunc></u>
<u n="325" who="S0486" trans="overlap">thank</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
