<text id="SQ6L">
<header>
		<rec_length>0:39:22</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-04-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Linguistics, research, holidays</topics>
		<activity>ANON and ANON talking while making tea</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0037">did you see this thing? Have I showed you this before?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0115">no what is it?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0037">it's a word cloud</u>
<u n="4" who="S0115">oh yeah taken from your own that's your own corpus that you made is it?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no it's my thesis</u>
<u n="6" who="S0115">oh thesis itself <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0037">I thought I might frame it or something as a little reminder</u>
<u n="8" who="S0115"><anon type="place"/>'s the biggest then data then dialect then English then uh construction um</u>
<u n="9" who="S0037" trans="overlap">eG's quite big</u>
<u n="10" who="S0115">but they haven't got n-grams and if they did there'd probably be in terms of like about uh</u>
<u n="11" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you can <pause dur="short"/> you can  you can  add them <pause dur="short"/> I thought about doing that this was me first go <pause dur="short"/> cos you can add in terms of and you <trunc>c</trunc> like you you separate them with what's that symbol called? It looks like this</u>
<u n="12" who="S0115">it'd be better if they did that and then made it like um like a classifier classified it in terms of where they are</u>
<u n="13" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0115">merge in the n-grams <pause dur="short"/> so like you could  you could  deselect uh like you could say in terms of is okay but it's it's not a content is it?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0037">I should definitely put that in it'll probably come out like massive won't it?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0115">doesn't like so you've got like <trunc>S</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that that's uh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like obviously it's a named entity d'you what I mean like if you  if you  semantic tagged it</u>
<u n="17" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and <anon type="place"/> is in there cos <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but it's interesting I mean <pause dur="short"/> cos cos <anon type="place"/> is in there but it's obviously from like <anon type="place"/> like the all the references are in there <pause dur="short"/> which I should've probably put in</u>
<u n="18" who="S0115" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> so this is the sort of language app that I think people would pay for isn't it?</u>
<u n="19" who="S0037">well it's free it's online</u>
<u n="20" who="S0115" trans="overlap">perhaps <pause dur="short"/> I mean</u>
<u n="21" who="S0037">I put the Bible in as well just to see</u>
<u n="22" who="S0115">oh that'd be really <trunc>inter</trunc> you know I'd really like to do more work with other corpora like obviously I'm doing my own stuff now like</u>
<u n="23" who="S0037">so not not just because I'm <trunc>j</trunc></u>
<u n="24" who="S0115">you could use like  you could use like  K F N-gram to get uh</u>
<u n="25" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0115">to get your <trunc>l</trunc> the n-gram list <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah I was wondering if you could um do another one on the <trunc>G</trunc> German uh half of the uh half of the corpus uh</u>
<u n="27" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> just send me the file I'll I don't mind doing it <pause dur="short"/> of course <pause dur="short"/> but um</u>
<u n="28" who="S0115">Cos uh yeah for that thing I was telling you yesterday <pause dur="short"/> I I decided that it would be easiest to do a find and replaced string thing after Berkeley yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0115">is to change it after directly after Berkeley</u>
<u n="31" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0115">then um uh as soon as  as soon as</u>
<u n="33" who="S0037">ah your problem with the thing</u>
<u n="34" who="S0115">yeah that that means that I would wanna change it as soon as Berkeley splits it out <pause dur="short"/> like so that  so that  it doesn't get cause any further problems and like can nip it in the bud as soon as it's out of Berkeley so I wonder if string find and replace but</u>
<u n="35" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well that's alright I mean</u>
<u n="36" who="S0115">I need unfortunately I need a list of every single word so that I can swap them</u>
<u n="37" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well that's okay I can do that <pause dur="short"/> uh anyway yeah so</u>
<u n="38" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it will probably come in handy later actually I imagine that list <pause dur="short"/> so this is like basic language model but</u>
<u n="39" who="S0037">so but you can add in like um n-grams by you know that  you know that you know that you know that  thing?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah and semantic tagging?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0037">what's that symbol that looks like that? Like that?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0115">A tilde</u>
<u n="43" who="S0037">A tilde <pause dur="short"/> but it's not a hat tilde it's just a normal character</u>
<u n="44" who="S0115">yeah in mathematics does it mean approximately or something?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0037">I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> anyway so you can put those in then you can it generates n-grams <pause dur="short"/> but yeah so I put the Bible in just to see what it would be <pause dur="short"/> and like it was Lord was the biggest one and then unto was the next one</u>
<u n="46" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think you've used the King James one there and not the um you've not used the modern</u>
<u n="47" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I did use the King James one well done <pause dur="short"/> well no I was just  I was just  on</u>
<u n="48" who="S0115" trans="overlap">could use the Tyndale one</u>
<u n="49" who="S0037">and I put like um Sense and <trunc>Sensibil</trunc> uh Pride and Prejudice in</u>
<u n="50" who="S0115">hey I tell you I can tell you two people who'd be quite interested in seeing that I mean</u>
<u n="51" who="S0037">well I'll do one for when they come round and then</u>
<u n="52" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I know they they cos like these sorts of things um really is the the sort of way isn't it?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well it's just all it's just free it's called Wordle online and you just  you just  well you can either link to a webpage and it'll um tell you all of the things or you can just paste in loads of text and I pasted my whole thesis in so <pause dur="short"/> that's obviously like</u>
<u n="54" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0037">I'll not say how many thousand words cos that's contentious <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0115">well how can a number how can a count of anything be contentious?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0037">well because it was a little bit under what it should've been wasn't it?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0115">I dunno I mean I I never officially counted it myself but I can only</u>
<u n="59" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh did you not? I counted it with</u>
<u n="60" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um I can only speculate them</u>
<u n="61" who="S0037">well it was  it was  just about on the lower limit but I counted like every scrap of text like all of the bibliography and everything</u>
<u n="62" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0037">that was a bit naughty <pause dur="short"/> so it was a little bit underweight but you know it's what you write not how much you write isn't it?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0115">it's what you <pause dur="short"/> yeah of course because because you could waffle on and on in a really big <trunc>f</trunc> you know flabby sort of text</u>
<u n="65" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0115">which uh you know sometimes I suppose some of the constructions you used were maybe a bit more verbose than they could've been but uh</u>
<u n="67" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well you you tried to root those out</u>
<u n="68" who="S0115">but I the key thing with your one was getting the SVO order and getting the verb early</u>
<u n="69" who="S0037">yeah I know I'm like a non-native speaker <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="70" who="S0115" trans="overlap">getting the finite gotta get that finite verb early so that <trunc>s</trunc> the person knows what the tense is early and they know what the</u>
<u n="71" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="72" who="S0115">I dunno I suppose in German they they always put the finite verb it can can end up right at the very end</u>
<u n="73" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah maybe I'm more German than you think <pause dur="short"/> no I mean maybe maybe it's like</u>
<u n="74" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0037">maybe I just <pause dur="short"/> I dunno where I got that writing style from</u>
<u n="76" who="S0115">no because you don't speak like that that's the thing</u>
<u n="77" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="78" who="S0115">I think you're just trying to overwork <pause dur="short"/> trying to over-academicize your work maybe <pause dur="short"/> should be more perhaps more informal</u>
<u n="79" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well that's <pause dur="short"/> maybe <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> maybe I shoulda been <pause dur="short"/> I never mastered it like I never got the hang of that</u>
<u n="80" who="S0115">on the subject of PhDs someone had to resign didn't they <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0037">who?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0115">uh the President of <trunc>Har</trunc> uh Hungary</u>
<u n="83" who="S0037">president of Hungary?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0115">he's had to resign</u>
<u n="85" who="S0037">why?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0115">because his PhD thesis was fake</u>
<u n="87" who="S0037">was it? Like Gillian O'Keith's? Gillian McKeith's?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0115">I don't think hers was fake I think it just wasn't a thesis I think she just paid money and got a PhD</u>
<u n="89" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well she bought it didn't she? She looks at turds anyway <pause dur="short"/> you don't need a thesis to do that</u>
<u n="90" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> on the contrary I'm sure there's lots of interesting things you can do with that but um</u>
<u n="91" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0115">no someone else was accused of it <trunc>u</trunc> uh Alan Greenspan was accused of it</u>
<u n="93" who="S0037">aha</u>
<u n="94" who="S0115">but no no he <pause dur="short"/> no he was accused of getting other people to write it for him <pause dur="short"/> that's a different like</u>
<u n="95" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and actually <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>magra</trunc> not Magrahi <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="96" who="S0115" trans="overlap">in fact you've got <pause dur="short"/> this is is what we were on about like with the text <pause dur="short"/> like it's <trunc>alwa</trunc> it's a bit controversial <pause dur="short"/> like I I does it  does it  mean plagiarized as in simply cut and paste or does it mean that you paid and bought someone else's after they'd done it or something?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0037" trans="overlap">excuse me <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> well it has to be your own work doesn't it? In fact you sign a declaration</u>
<u n="98" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh his name was Pal Schmidt</u>
<u n="99" who="S0037">Ohh <pause dur="short"/> you sign a declaration <pause dur="short"/> a declaration? You sign the declaration saying like this is all my own work <pause dur="short"/> what what are they for?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I was wondering</u>
<u n="101" who="S0037">for the dinner for the sauce?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0115">like d'you want that or do you want uh um something more spicy?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0037" trans="overlap">uh I dunno what we gonna have? <trunc>Pas</trunc>? Pasta? Pasta?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> like Italian? We could have like Italian sort of we've got <pause dur="short"/> we've got like chives and parsley haven't we that I've planted so?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that's what  that's what  my idea was yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah so well I'll just uh just do that then</u>
<u n="107" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I can go and get some <pause dur="short"/> but we're not having that for a while though if we're gonna have those pasties <pause dur="short"/> I'll not be able to eat like</u>
<u n="108" who="S0115">ah well you know I was just sort of getting things <unclear/> started and I'll just um</u>
<u n="109" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah right no we'll <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah no we'll get it on <pause dur="short"/> yeah no that's fine <pause dur="short"/> did the kettle  did the kettle  boil?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0115">it it did actually um</u>
<u n="111" who="S0037">so</u>
<u n="112" who="S0115">so so yeah I mean so there's a lot of things you can do <pause dur="short"/> phDs I mean so they they do tend to uh like check <pause dur="short"/> but actually Al Greenspan's PhD like um there's only two copies in the world or something</u>
<u n="113" who="S0037">how can that even be the case?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0115" trans="overlap">there's only his copy which he he doesn't want anyone to see <pause dur="short"/> and like the the the reviewer's copy</u>
<u n="115" who="S0037" trans="overlap">the one in the <trunc>univers</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> no the university will hold one</u>
<u n="116" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah yeah the university's copy yeah <pause dur="short"/> that was those are the only two copies that there were</u>
<u n="117" who="S0037">yeah but you can request to see it can't you?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but um and someone someone from paper or some blog had managed to you know do some research work and get and obtain the other copy</u>
<u n="119" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0115">uh it was an economics paper like uh maybe Bloomberg or something I dunno <pause dur="short"/> um they read you know they read it but it's a  it's a  proper economics PhD so</u>
<u n="121" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="122" who="S0115">it was difficult had a lot of formulas and that's always suspicious it's um you know?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0037">yeah overly difficult</u>
<u n="124" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like if you're using extra formulas to try and sort of confuse people but uh</u>
<u n="125" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0115">I think he Greenspan's was uh was was okay it's just that I think he <trunc>d</trunc> he'd released them all as papers like he he got like <pause dur="short"/> but he was doing loads of other stuff at the like he was working whilst doing it</u>
<u n="127" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0115">he was just <pause dur="short"/> he was a bit of a celebrity I think already before it had even come out <pause dur="short"/> um but he ended up being uh head of the Chairman of the <trunc>Fed</trunc></u>
<u n="129" who="S0037">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0115"> eral Reserve Bank thing</u>
<u n="131" who="S0037">have you still not eaten that chocolate from the other day?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0115">yeah this is from  this is from  uh it's from Saturday this is innit</u>
<u n="133" who="S0037" trans="overlap">God I dunno how you can <pause dur="short"/> I would've just been <pause dur="short"/> I would've eaten it straight away <pause dur="short"/> I'm can't help meself</u>
<u n="134" who="S0115">and Friday <pause dur="short"/> I've still got Friday's in there <vocal desc="laugh"/> There's not loads but some of it went in Saturday's meal</u>
<u n="135" who="S0037" trans="overlap">D'you know what man if you don't eat that it'll <trunc>mag</trunc> the the chocolate fairies'll get it</u>
<u n="136" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Ah I think I'd like to to do a bit of like uh what do they call it when uh countries are hoard masses of gold and what is it yeah what are must be stockpiling of commodities</u>
<u n="137" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah stockpile? You you're like panic buying <vocal desc="laugh"/>?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well just just saving just refusing to to actually spend <trunc>ea</trunc> eat consume any of the uh commodity</u>
<u n="139" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh that's alright it's <trunc>f</trunc> I shouldn't have bought any more should I if you've still got that</u>
<u n="140" who="S0115">it's funny with gold cos you can't really eat it well you can like uh you can have gold leaf yeah but it would take you quite a long time to eat your way through like a whole</u>
<u n="141" who="S0037" trans="overlap">there is edible gold leaf <pause dur="short"/> I saw like a <pause dur="short"/> bar?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0115">the problem with that is that you're sort of destroying the gold aren't you cos like once you've eaten it it's not really possible to <trunc>re</trunc> to <trunc>r</trunc> <trunc>re</trunc> to retrieve the</u>
<u n="143" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but does it come out though? It can't just like <pause dur="short"/> it can't just hang out in your body</u>
<u n="144" who="S0115" trans="overlap">your uh your word cloud on this is gonna be good isn't it?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0037">me what?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0115">you know <trunc>y</trunc> <trunc>y</trunc> the uh</u>
<u n="147" who="S0037" trans="overlap">on this conversation?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0115">the yeah if you stick it through there it's gonna come out with like Alan Greenspan and like uh</u>
<u n="149" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0115">uh eating gold and retrieving the gold after it's been eaten</u>
<u n="151" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> these are all valid questions</u>
<u n="152" who="S0115">I I dunno how much gold gold leaf you could get out of uh</u>
<u n="153" who="S0037">where's your cup</u>
<u n="154" who="S0115">like I wonder how many miles or sort of square metres of gold leaf you can get out of like a <trunc>w</trunc> one um</u>
<u n="155" who="S0037" trans="overlap">A bullion? One bullion thing?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0037">no it'll be on the <unclear/> I saw a thing that Michel Roux Junior made where he put like <trunc>e</trunc> he put like gold leaf on something and it kind of makes me feel that I wouldn't wanna eat it that it might jangle on me fillings</u>
<u n="158" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't  I don't  think I'd ever want to eat it I think um <pause dur="short"/> I don't wanna know what it tastes like but I imagine it tastes of metal <pause dur="short"/> like hard</u>
<u n="159" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't really like gold anyway <pause dur="short"/> like I don't like the <trunc>m</trunc> like I don't like it aesthetically</u>
<u n="160" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you mean the like the look of it?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0037">sorry <pause dur="short"/> what am I doing? I'm trying to put this over there <vocal desc="laugh"/> Um no I mean I don't mind it <pause dur="short"/> it's a bit like I dunno I associate it with older people like gold like nanas</u>
<u n="162" who="S0115">uh darts darts presenters</u>
<u n="163" who="S0037">darts presenters definitely <pause dur="short"/> and chavs</u>
<u n="164" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0037">chavs like gold</u>
<u n="166" who="S0115"><unclear/> not using a <trunc>s</trunc> a class based slur against Britain's um Britain's uh</u>
<u n="167" who="S0037">no I'm just  I'm just  saying what it reminds me of <pause dur="short"/> I'm not saying that all all this do that or uh everyone like that likes this <pause dur="short"/> loads of people like gold obviously I mean</u>
<u n="168" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0037">I'm just saying I don't because I think it reminds me of nanas and chavs <pause dur="short"/> which is a</u>
<u n="170" who="S0115">was was it you who <trunc>d</trunc> pointed out the uh that that those those golden um necklaces they have with a clown</u>
<u n="171" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah I think we were talking about it the other day</u>
<u n="172" who="S0115">yeah that's pretty uh</u>
<u n="173" who="S0037">clowns?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0115">and like the idea of getting that I guess it comes from America I mean</u>
<u n="175" who="S0037" trans="overlap">they were really big when I was at school <pause dur="short"/> I sort of wanted one in some ways <pause dur="short"/> I told you one that I saw in New York that had like Jesus's face on it?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0115">one what?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0037">it was <vocal desc="laugh"/> I've got the picture still <pause dur="short"/> like one of them clown necklaces but it wasn't a clown it was Jesus's face</u>
<u n="178" who="S0115">that's tremendous</u>
<u n="179" who="S0037">with diamantes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0115">those are fake diamonds right?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> dimonesque <pause dur="short"/> dimonique <pause dur="short"/> et cetera</u>
<u n="182" who="S0115"><trunc>Dimur</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> dimunique</u>
<u n="183" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but um <pause dur="short"/> I dunno like I really do like jewellery but um it just doesn't agree with me very much</u>
<u n="184" who="S0115">yeah no it doesn't with me</u>
<u n="185" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> don't be silly <pause dur="short"/> no I mean like I really like earrings and <pause dur="short"/> uh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wears really nice earrings like always <trunc>h</trunc> and <trunc>ac</trunc> in fact <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does they always have like really nice matching outfits with earrings and dangly sparkly ones</u>
<u n="186" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0037">unusual ones and stuff but they just itch my ear so much <pause dur="short"/> they never used to <pause dur="short"/> then I stopped wearing them and now I can't wear them again</u>
<u n="188" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> that is</u>
<u n="189" who="S0037">bit of a shame</u>
<u n="190" who="S0115">kind of even <pause dur="short"/> but gold shouldn't you know because it's cos it's um</u>
<u n="191" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no it's it's not the  it's not the  material it's the um it's having something in me ear in my ear holes if you know what I mean</u>
<u n="192" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0037">so yeah there's that and then um I've never liked like floppy like you know bracelets and stuff?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah yeah like um loose loose ones sort of thing</u>
<u n="195" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I like a bangle but I don't like a  I don't like a  like a floppy one that much</u>
<u n="196" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> I do like rings but they're <trunc>of</trunc> like I do like sort of ones that you buy for a pound and in fact I've got a lot of them sort of ones but they do turn me fingers green <pause dur="short"/> so I can't wear them for any length of time</u>
<u n="198" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah is that like what what do you reckon that's made of?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0037">I think it's nickel</u>
<u n="200" who="S0115">producing producing some copper sulphate or something?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0037" trans="overlap">or copper probably the <trunc>s</trunc> quality jeweller that I buy <pause dur="short"/> I dunno what it's doing but it's uh</u>
<u n="202" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like cupronickel uh whatever it's called <pause dur="short"/> got copper in it yeah produces like copper oxide which is green yeah?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0037">it does turn them green yeah <pause dur="short"/> and like that one that I had on at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s wedding d'you know which one I mean? It's got like a blue sort of <trunc>s</trunc> turquoise stone in it <pause dur="short"/> it's really big and like covers the whole bit of your finger there? D'you know which one I mean?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0115">I think so</u>
<u n="205" who="S0037">it's a bit sort of um Bollywood inspired</u>
<u n="206" who="S0115">right</u>
<u n="207" who="S0037">it um that turned me whole finger green <pause dur="short"/> which is lovely</u>
<u n="208" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah that's quite a  quite a  good buy that actually</u>
<u n="209" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="210" who="S0115">it's uh interesting how it goes from being you know such a <trunc>d</trunc> you know from one colour to such a different colour?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but some people do it deliberately like they wear those copper bangles don't they for like rheumatism and stuff</u>
<u n="212" who="S0115" trans="overlap">to dye  to dye  the <pause dur="short"/> oh oh alright <pause dur="short"/> does that actually work then?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0037">well I don't know it's just one of these like</u>
<u n="214" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="215" who="S0037">you know things that people do <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if it works <pause dur="short"/> I haven't got rheumatism or whatever thing they're doing it for <pause dur="short"/> but apparently like um you can get these ones that you wear for sea sickness</u>
<u n="216" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0037">but it's not made of copper but it has like pressure points</u>
<u n="218" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0037">I don't know if they work either though</u>
<u n="220" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't <trunc>th</trunc> I don't know if you can cure <pause dur="short"/> take these out and then put them over there</u>
<u n="221" who="S0037">am I in the way is this what you're saying?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0115">no no no no <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="223" who="S0037">was it a speech act?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0115">not at all <pause dur="short"/> that wasn't <pause dur="short"/> I was like explaining <pause dur="short"/> that was the the thing where you hear it <pause dur="short"/> that's where you hear something that wasn't <pause dur="short"/> you overanalyse you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no no no <pause dur="short"/>No I'm not <pause dur="short"/> I was only asking</u>
<u n="226" who="S0115">your uh pragmatic module is uh</u>
<u n="227" who="S0037">ooh the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> you didn't tell me this had arrived <pause dur="short"/> ah you did</u>
<u n="228" who="S0115">that's cos it's totally</u>
<u n="229" who="S0037">you did</u>
<u n="230" who="S0115">utterly</u>
<u n="231" who="S0037">it's the the dead one</u>
<u n="232" who="S0115" trans="overlap">that was Saturday <pause dur="short"/> we we we talked about that on Saturday</u>
<u n="233" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I thought it was the <anon type="place"/> um whatever it's called <pause dur="short"/> so I bought some  I bought some  schneidy um Boot's um shampoo and conditioner look <pause dur="short"/> can you tell what it's supposed to be?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0115">ah so you mean it's uh?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0037">look</u>
<u n="236" who="S0115">made um a copy <trunc>br</trunc> a copy brand sort of thing? Pro Vitamin ah it does look a bit like Pantene</u>
<u n="237" who="S0037">yeah it's like Schmantene <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but it says uh pro vitamin on it</u>
<u n="239" who="S0037">they had all of them <pause dur="short"/> they had like ones that looked like Herbal Essences and they've gone down the Aldi route</u>
<u n="240" who="S0115">yeah well you got to cos in this you know in this <trunc>cl</trunc> in this economic climate</u>
<u n="241" who="S0037">pardon?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0115">in this economic climate you know</u>
<u n="243" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0115">you've got to appeal to the  to the  the cheapskate and the you know</u>
<u n="245" who="S0037">well it's just the same juice inside I don't care what it says in the bottle really</u>
<u n="246" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the <trunc>Bri</trunc> the British poor <pause dur="short"/> the poor the <trunc>un</trunc> the un-flash <pause dur="short"/> the tight-fisted</u>
<u n="247" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="248" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> uh yeah so I read about like a lot of um like German solar solar powered computer just in Germany</u>
<u n="249" who="S0037">solar power? Why?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="251" who="S0037">are them things in the oven done?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like <pause dur="short"/> yeah probably are actually uh <pause dur="short"/> quite urgently</u>
<u n="253" who="S0037">na they take ages to heat through a lot of the time</u>
<u n="254" who="S0115">yeah I reckon they're done now</u>
<u n="255" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> you could just turn that off for now and we can eat these in there</u>
<u n="256" who="S0115">uh yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0037">if you want</u>
<u n="258" who="S0115">yeah no problem</u>
<u n="259" who="S0037">just close the window for a while</u>
<u n="260" who="S0115">oh yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> no that's fine yeah <pause dur="short"/> I don't <trunc>w</trunc> I don't um don't really need it <pause dur="short"/> there's your Cornish pasty</u>
<u n="261" who="S0037" trans="overlap">should I bring? Ah can I have  can I have  some tomato sauce?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0115">could eat it on the <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah it's in the fridge</u>
<u n="263" who="S0037">um</u>
<u n="264" who="S0115">so you don't like eating pasties standing like at a Gregg's?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> if I'm at Gregg's but if I'm in me own house with the benefit of sitting on the sofa with me cup of tea then I'd rather</u>
<u n="266" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> of yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0037">but yeah <pause dur="short"/> it'll have to be cold pasties from now on anyway</u>
<u n="268" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Could maybe um yeah <trunc>m</trunc> more people are buying pasties</u>
<u n="269" who="S0037">sorry?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0115">like um <pause dur="short"/> maybe more people are <trunc>g</trunc> actually gonna buy pasties because</u>
<u n="271" who="S0037">it would raise the</u>
<u n="272" who="S0115"><trunc>Part</trunc> partly panic buying and also like just to raise the awareness of pasties</u>
<u n="273" who="S0037" trans="overlap">to raise the profile? That's what they say isn't it like that um any publicity's good publicity</u>
<u n="274" who="S0115">yeah except like Bin Laden or something</u>
<u n="275" who="S0037" trans="overlap">D'you wanna come through or? Shall I just?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0037">they'll be alright</u>
<u n="278" who="S0115">well um I'll leave them on <pause dur="short"/> I'll</u>
<u n="279" who="S0037">I dunno if I can carry that and that</u>
<u n="280" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I'll take  I'll take  that <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah no <pause dur="short"/> extra</u>
<u n="281" who="S0037" trans="overlap">come back for it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="282" who="S0037">have I left the remote <trunc>contr</trunc> here y'are I'll do it</u>
<u n="283" who="S0115">hold that I'm just getting the salt actually</u>
<u n="284" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'm sorry</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="285" who="S0037">I wonder if <trunc>s</trunc> Come Dine With Me's on</u>
<event desc="sound of bang"/>
<u n="286" who="S0037">oh <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="287" who="S0115">sorry not Scum Dine With Me</u>
<u n="288" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> come Dine With Me</u>
<u n="289" who="S0115">I think that's really really loud on the uh recording when it it tips over</u>
<u n="290" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> never mind <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>s</trunc> accident</u>
<u n="291" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well <trunc>Sc</trunc> Scum Dine With Me is like a maximum security prison cooking programme</u>
<u n="292" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> That's funny <pause dur="short"/> what channel is it normally on? Or should I put the radio on?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0115">um think with the number four innit?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0037">oh it's not on <pause dur="short"/> it's not on Four yet <pause dur="short"/> one <trunc>b</trunc> fourteen</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="295" who="S0037">Matt?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="297" who="S0037">what you doing?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0115">just sorting out <unclear/></u>
<u n="299" who="S0037">pardon</u>
<u n="300" who="S0115">just uh sorting out these onions</u>
<u n="301" who="S0037">shall I press pause?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0115">uh no I <unclear/></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="303" who="S0037">Matt? You're not sorting out onions</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="304" who="S0037">you want me to press stop?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0115">uh no no I'm alright I'll just get <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah right uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah cos they were  they were  on quite high anyway so</u>
<u n="306" who="S0037">I picked up that bit of pasty to have a bite of and like every single bit of filling fell out the middle</u>
<u n="307" who="S0115">oh right <pause dur="short"/> you know I mean that that always happens when you eat pasties</u>
<u n="308" who="S0037">it's quite peppery it's nice <pause dur="short"/> so what d'you think we should do at Easter?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0115">well um yeah we need to go to a trip somewhere um so I thought</u>
<u n="310" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0115">Ely but also um <pause dur="short"/> uh mm could try and get to the um go to London or um on the coast</u>
<u n="312" who="S0037">oh that might be nice <pause dur="short"/> although I watched the weather forecast this morning <pause dur="short"/> it said it's gonna snow on Wednesday</u>
<u n="313" who="S0115">what here?</u>
<u n="314" who="S0037" trans="overlap">here</u>
<u n="315" who="S0115">it's gonna snow in in April?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0037">apparently</u>
<u n="317" who="S0115">mm</u>
<u n="318" who="S0037">apparently it's snowing in Scotland at the moment</u>
<u n="319" who="S0115">oh <pause dur="short"/> it's not exactly what I</u>
<u n="320" who="S0037">no <pause dur="short"/> had envisaged <pause dur="short"/> maybe it won't</u>
<u n="321" who="S0115">but the the yeah I mean <pause dur="short"/> it can  it can  really fast <pause dur="short"/> I guess it just depends like if the wind sort of changes and you get like Arctic winds coming through</u>
<u n="322" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> well the wind's supposed to be blowing from the Northeast like tomorrow <pause dur="short"/> like Norway</u>
<u n="323" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well well beyond that uh yeah yeah like the top of Norway yeah Lapland</u>
<u n="324" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I know <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0115">yeah cos we're it seems very precarious like I think a few  a few  of the wrong you know butterflies flapping their wings or whatever</u>
<u n="326" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0115">and <trunc>y</trunc> yeah the total like you know polar like cyclone'll just</u>
<u n="328" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0115">appear on top of the country <pause dur="short"/> and we'll be like plunged to minus fifteen</u>
<u n="330" who="S0037">well it is supposed to be like storms and hailstones and stuff <pause dur="short"/> well it's not brilliant</u>
<u n="331" who="S0115">so um need to do more technology to improve uh the ability to control the weather</u>
<u n="332" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> in Japan though have they not done a <pause dur="short"/> in China actually <pause dur="short"/> when they had the Olympics on did they not do a thing where they they managed to stop it from raining like avoid the rain? I'll have to look it up</u>
<u n="333" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um yeah I think there there are things that can sort of</u>
<u n="334" who="S0037">they put like hot air <trunc>u</trunc> like they blasted hot air up in the air or cold air or</u>
<u n="335" who="S0115">basically just a big fan that just blows blows the clouds away?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> they did something</u>
<u n="337" who="S0115">I guess you could <trunc>de</trunc> dehumidify</u>
<u n="338" who="S0037">or did they make it rain so that it wouldn't be as pollution-y</u>
<u n="339" who="S0115">yeah that that may well have been um</u>
<u n="340" who="S0037" trans="overlap">can't remember <pause dur="short"/> something about that</u>
<u n="341" who="S0115">basically just blow the bad um air away</u>
<u n="342" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0115">replace it with good air</u>
<u n="344" who="S0037">are you looking forward to the Olympics this time?</u>
<u n="345" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> it's not something that I think about a lot like</u>
<u n="346" who="S0037">is it not?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0115">in in you know my dreams or anything but uh</u>
<u n="348" who="S0037">it's not in my dreams either but</u>
<u n="349" who="S0115">I think it could be entertaining and</u>
<u n="350" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I sort of like anything that goes on like that for a while you know like Six Nations or the World Cup or <pause dur="short"/> euro Twenty-Twelve</u>
<u n="351" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah I've gotta get <trunc>in</trunc> involved in it and like <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="352" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0115">sort of extensively <pause dur="short"/> like like <trunc>w</trunc> watching spending time watching the <unclear/> and just leaving it on in the background and stuff</u>
<u n="354" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0115">sort of not watching anything else just that <pause dur="short"/> that that could happen</u>
<u n="356" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> the good thing about it being here is that like it'll be at the right time like <pause dur="short"/> in China they were always like in the middle of the <trunc>m</trunc> like really early in the morning and stuff</u>
<u n="357" who="S0115">oh yeah yeah I mean obviously with <trunc>w</trunc> taking place in that part of the world over there I mean it's pretty much out of synch obviously here we're <pause dur="short"/> we're gonna get everything right exactly when when we want it</u>
<u n="358" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="359" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I mean if you're asking which meridian uh is the best for the most people um</u>
<u n="360" who="S0037">well</u>
<u n="361" who="S0115">which which um you know</u>
<u n="362" who="S0037">line of latitude <pause dur="short"/> whatever it is</u>
<u n="363" who="S0115">which line of um</u>
<u n="364" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><trunc>Long</trunc> <trunc>lat</trunc> latitude or longitude?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0115">uh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0037">I never remember the difference</u>
<u n="367" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> the <pause dur="short"/> which which latitude is the best um?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0037">time zone?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Cos that's it which latitude has the most people on it? Which time zone has the most people?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0037">well let's think <pause dur="short"/> so GMT goes through</u>
<u n="371" who="S0115">um probably the one that goes all the way down Africa</u>
<u n="372" who="S0037">that's GMT isn't it goes through like</u>
<u n="373" who="S0115">oh um</u>
<u n="374" who="S0037">goes through Lisbon doesn't it? And Dublin?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0115">no I think it comes out over the the round part of Africa I mean <pause dur="short"/> you know Western</u>
<u n="376" who="S0037" trans="overlap">doesn't it? Oh does it? Maybe European Central Time then?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0115" trans="overlap">or <pause dur="short"/> hold on cos like where cos where's Spain it's sort of above Morocco isn't it? And the Gibraltar part <pause dur="short"/> strait of Gibraltar</u>
<u n="378" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0115">then if you're going down through through Spain then kinda cut through the round you know Maghreb West African bit</u>
<u n="380" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0115">if you wanna get it right down like you know from from yeah from like  from like  <trunc>l</trunc> like Egypt down through Sudan through everything</u>
<u n="382" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but then America I mean <pause dur="short"/> so is there more people there or is there more people in the <trunc>w</trunc> line that goes right down the middle of America to like through South America?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0115" trans="overlap">into South Africa</u>
<u n="384" who="S0037">obviously it can't go through the middle of America but South America but you know what I mean</u>
<u n="385" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh you could  you could  try and get which one like with a one with a lot of cities on them</u>
<u n="386" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="387" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="388" who="S0037">it lists don't it like on my phone when you wanna change the time zone it lists like the options</u>
<u n="389" who="S0115">you could try and get Mexico City and like <pause dur="short"/> perhaps Mexico and California</u>
<u n="390" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0115">and <pause dur="short"/> but then then you've got <pause dur="short"/> you've not got much like below Mexico sort of</u>
<u n="392" who="S0037" trans="overlap">in fact I think ours does</u>
<u n="393" who="S0115">isn't that? I dunno if that goes down to to like if you get Buenos Aires and like in terms of time zones I mean</u>
<u n="394" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> not sure</u>
<u n="395" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="396" who="S0037">was that pasty nice?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0115">there are a lot of people in like you got west coast and east coast of America probably got a lot of people in there but also</u>
<u n="398" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0115">but perhaps China and India could could um produce Bangladesh or Indonesia or something like that <trunc>tho</trunc> those sorts of <pause dur="short"/> perhaps they would in terms of time zones perhaps</u>
<u n="400" who="S0037">have more?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0115">um perhaps you could get like a <trunc>mulli</trunc></u>
<u n="402" who="S0037" trans="overlap">dunno <pause dur="short"/> I bet that someone's already worked that out</u>
<u n="403" who="S0115">oh yeah they will have <pause dur="short"/> yeah they they will uh</u>
<u n="404" who="S0037" trans="overlap">definitely</u>
<u n="405" who="S0115">um well so it's like a pub quiz question innit?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0037">yeah it is <pause dur="short"/> like a <anon type="place"/> pub quiz question</u>
<u n="407" who="S0115" trans="overlap">which uh <pause dur="short"/> like you gotta take um you gotta use guestimates haven't you?</u>
<u n="408" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no the <anon type="place"/> pub quiz question would be like Which line of latitude contains no it'd be like Which is the second largest capital city in terms of GDP located along the line of latitude with the most people in? That would be the sort of <anon type="place"/> one where you need to know like twelve facts to get to the one where you get a point</u>
<u n="409" who="S0115">yeah some of it's a bit crazy I mean <pause dur="short"/> but a lot  a lot  of it's interesting like um you know Greg was saying about like how much does France make on cheese a year?</u>
<u n="410" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0115">that's great <vocal desc="laugh"/> what a  what a  question <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="412" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's silly <pause dur="short"/> have you heard much from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="413" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> uh uh not not recently <pause dur="short"/> he's very busy so um with his uh with his baby so</u>
<u n="414" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> bambinos</u>
<u n="415" who="S0115">um you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="416" who="S0037" trans="overlap">hm? Not fond of that name</u>
<u n="417" who="S0115">you've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> haven't you?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0115">and I think there may be more <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>s than you  than you  realize like sorry <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0037">mm don't like it</u>
<u n="421" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="422" who="S0037">but I'm glad that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <trunc>tri</trunc> changed his name ideas</u>
<u n="423" who="S0115">oh yeah so he's moved from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hasn't he?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0115">so</u>
<u n="426" who="S0037">but he's gonna call her <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think</u>
<u n="427" who="S0115">fair enough <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>th</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> Girl <pause dur="short"/> you know that song?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0037">what?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0115">is that that song?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0037">what song?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0115">is it the one that goes uh <pause dur="short"/> that song that <pause dur="short"/> that film or um with uh</u>
<u n="432" who="S0037">I need a bit more</u>
<u n="433" who="S0115">ah <trunc>G</trunc> uh Walking down the street so fancy free you know it just goes</u>
<u n="434" who="S0037">what?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0115">hey there <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> girl or something <unclear/> walking down the street so fancy free it's it's one of the uh Redgraves isn't it?</u>
<u n="436" who="S0037">I don't know</u>
<u n="437" who="S0115">ah it's a sixties  it's a sixties  film</u>
<u n="438" who="S0037">oh</u>
<u n="439" who="S0115">I don't know if it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or like something else um</u>
<u n="440" who="S0037" trans="overlap">have to look it up</u>
<u n="441" who="S0115">are those onions alright?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0037">I think they'll be fine yeah <pause dur="short"/> the heat's not on them is it?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0115">yeah that's why I was checking it <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="444" who="S0037">is it like number one though?</u>
<u n="445" who="S0115">it's it's okay yeah <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> uh they're that so yeah that's uh um <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0037" trans="overlap">hey that aloes come looks really good doesn't it? Looks better than it was before I knocked him spectacularly</u>
<u n="447" who="S0115">yeah um <pause dur="short"/> uh I I thought he was dead I nearly threw him away actually um</u>
<u n="448" who="S0037">I need to change the soil though you said it was a bit stinky</u>
<u n="449" who="S0115">it's mouldy it's like um</u>
<u n="450" who="S0037">smell <pause dur="short"/> has it have you been overwatering them though?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0115">well they it just the soil just had that in it and <pause dur="short"/> would be it once it's  once it's  got into the soil then it would be there</u>
<u n="452" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0115">so it'd still have that smell uh even if it's  even if it's  really dry or even if it's not it'd still have that smell <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="454" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="455" who="S0115">same thing yeah so if we went to the coast where would we  where would we  go?</u>
<u n="456" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I dunno cos I've never  I've never  been round here before like <pause dur="short"/> we would have to <trunc>st</trunc> would we have to stay over though? How far?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0115">might have to stay a night</u>
<u n="458" who="S0037" trans="overlap">dunno if I've got <pause dur="short"/> dunno if we can really afford it this month really <pause dur="short"/> spent you know as usual money at the start of the month</u>
<u n="459" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well um <pause dur="short"/> but we've got you know a bit more coming in uh</u>
<u n="460" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah we have actually that's true</u>
<u n="461" who="S0115">um hopefully hopefully in the near future</u>
<u n="462" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well maybe we should <pause dur="short"/> although they'll they'll jack the prices up won't they with it being Easter that's the annoying thing</u>
<u n="463" who="S0115">well I dunno I mean depends where you</u>
<u n="464" who="S0037">where were you thinking of?</u>
<u n="465" who="S0115">oh uh this was just <trunc>p</trunc> pure sort of you know</u>
<u n="466" who="S0037" trans="overlap">conjecture <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <unclear/> I mean and we we would</u>
<u n="468" who="S0037" trans="overlap">shall I put this light on actually?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0115">I mean you want somewhere like uh in the uh in <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> you know <anon type="place"/> </u>
<u n="470" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but I've never ever been</u>
<u n="471" who="S0115">that's all the more reason to go then isn't it?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well it is <pause dur="short"/> I think you're right</u>
<u n="473" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> cos you've got <pause dur="short"/> I mean I think there probably would be some quite cheap places around there I mean <pause dur="short"/> they'd be just be glad to have anyone uh <pause dur="short"/> you know some of them have been putting putting the prices down because of the putting the prices down to just try and desperately get more um</u>
<u n="474" who="S0037" trans="overlap">could go to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> norwich <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Could go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0115"><anon type="place"/> or Norwich?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="477" who="S0115">well I think Norwich sounds like the the less rougher of those two</u>
<u n="478" who="S0037">well I've never been</u>
<u n="479" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="480" who="S0037">Liz went to uni there I'll ask her</u>
<u n="481" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Cos it's south <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> is it?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0037">UAE Norwich</u>
<u n="483" who="S0115">Norwich yeah <pause dur="short"/> and that that's interesting uh Brighton Brighton's expensive</u>
<u n="484" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's got like a <trunc>ca</trunc> a cathedral hasn't it <pause dur="short"/> brighton is expensive</u>
<u n="485" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um you actually have been there haven't you?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0037">I have been there</u>
<u n="487" who="S0115">and I only very very briefly have been there <pause dur="short"/> and um but London as well I mean</u>
<u n="488" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0115">that's probably the one of the most obvious ones uh could go to like a part of London that we haven't seen</u>
<u n="490" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="491" who="S0115">as much <trunc>li</trunc> like um uh Chelsea like Chelsea uh</u>
<u n="492" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but it's it's <trunc>exa</trunc> it's as expensive as here I mean</u>
<u n="493" who="S0115">like um</u>
<u n="494" who="S0037">maybe</u>
<u n="495" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> some of the parts of London</u>
<u n="496" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I dunno we went there not long ago though <pause dur="short"/> I'd rather go like somewhere different I think</u>
<u n="497" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well yeah I was just thinking that there's a lot of different bits of London to see aren't there?</u>
<u n="498" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no no I know <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but we might go <pause dur="short"/> I said like to Chris we might go and see him at some point so</u>
<u n="499" who="S0115">yeah well uh good to um maximize the London experience</u>
<u n="500" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I still forget that like it's just down the road</u>
<u n="501" who="S0115">I mean part of the <pause dur="short"/> yeah part of the problem with going to um some of the places are the expensive fares but I think London <pause dur="short"/> places you can get to on the bus like London are likely to be reasonably priced</u>
<u n="502" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well maybe I'll have a look at the bus and see if there's any others</u>
<u n="503" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so it's only um <pause dur="short"/> what is it fifteen pounds to London?</u>
<u n="504" who="S0037">mm depends when you go less <pause dur="short"/> I think there was only twelve last time</u>
<u n="505" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um the bus that's really  that's really  pleasantly cheap but uh</u>
<u n="506" who="S0037" trans="overlap">return?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="508" who="S0037">yeah six pounds</u>
<u n="509" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the train  the train  would be uh one would be uh <pause dur="short"/> so if there were the buses were going to other towns then we might've been able to consider that as well <pause dur="short"/> and sort of possibly the day trips</u>
<u n="510" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'm sure they do <pause dur="short"/> we could go to Oxford maybe <pause dur="short"/> I know the <anon type="place"/> goes there <pause dur="short"/> from just along there</u>
<u n="511" who="S0115">yeah we can that'd be that wouldn't take too long would it or?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0037">Don't think so <pause dur="short"/> an hour and a half or something</u>
<u n="513" who="S0115">no it's okay I mean <pause dur="short"/> london's shorter isn't it but</u>
<u n="514" who="S0037">well only cos we get off early <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="515" who="S0115" trans="overlap">were are you a bit sick of you a bit bored of London?</u>
<u n="516" who="S0037">oh I don't I think you can't be bored of London can you really?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0115">yeah cos I was just think you know like he who tires of London tires of life or whatever</u>
<u n="518" who="S0037">exactly</u>
<u n="519" who="S0115">I mean <pause dur="short"/> so I was thinking</u>
<u n="520" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no but I just mean it's good to go I've seen a bit of London <pause dur="short"/> it'd be good to see a bit of Oxford or</u>
<u n="521" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0037"><anon type="place"/> or <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah <anon type="place"/> does sound rough doesn't it? Maybe we should go there</u>
<u n="523" who="S0115">no it just sounds it sounds rough but I don't know if it is</u>
<u n="524" who="S0037">what are them places by the sea called like <anon type="place"/>? <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's near <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's in <anon type="place"/> isn't it uh? <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0037" trans="overlap">should see where the train  the train  goes <pause dur="short"/> oh <anon type="place"/> sounds like my sort of place</u>
<u n="527" who="S0115">it's got a sea life centre</u>
<u n="528" who="S0037">excellent <pause dur="short"/> I had a dream about I was in a</u>
<u n="529" who="S0115"><anon type="place"/> is the one just next to that</u>
<u n="530" who="S0037">is it a port?</u>
<u n="531" who="S0115">yeah it's a  it's a  ferry thing <pause dur="short"/> I I got it wrong in a pub quiz question</u>
<u n="532" who="S0037">oh did you? <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="533" who="S0115">painfully <pause dur="short"/> uh I mixed it up with uh</u>
<u n="534" who="S0037"><anon type="place"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0115">I think that was no that was it was that <anon type="place"/>? So I've mixed them up again</u>
<u n="536" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="537" who="S0115">I've forgotten</u>
<u n="538" who="S0037">Don't know</u>
<u n="539" who="S0115">where's <anon type="place"/>? Is that in <anon type="place"/> as well?</u>
<u n="540" who="S0037">well it's along that way because that the sign's like when we come if we came off the M6 to come here the signs say like <anon type="place"/> a hundred million miles or however far it is <pause dur="short"/> probably not a hundred million</u>
<u n="541" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="542" who="S0037">that sounds like a little bit of a long estimate</u>
<u n="543" who="S0115">hm <pause dur="short"/> then the other was uh <pause dur="short"/> there's another one that I I was mixing up as well uh you know Folkestone <pause dur="short"/> that's in that's in I mean that's in Kent isn't it?</u>
<u n="544" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ah yeah <pause dur="short"/> no Folkestone's that's is that not where you get on the Channel Tunnel?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's it's it's Kent yeah it's um near by near <trunc>D</trunc> near Dover I think</u>
<u n="546" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0115">um and it's and it might be near Hastings I'm not sure</u>
<u n="548" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="549" who="S0115">you know probably <pause dur="short"/> uh so so <anon type="place"/> is in <anon type="place"/> then is it?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0037">I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> as I say I really <pause dur="short"/> this is the furthest like <anon type="place"/> I've been if you know what I mean</u>
<u n="551" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="552" who="S0037">but I do like the East</u>
<u n="553" who="S0115">so uh d'you wanna do you want me to turn off them onions and?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0037">no <trunc>th</trunc> we'll go through there if you want yeah <pause dur="short"/> ah could do with a nice biscuit to <trunc>di</trunc> dip in me tea maybe</u>
<u n="555" who="S0115">yeah I've actually got a Nice biscuit here</u>
<u n="556" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I've got a nice Nice biscuit</u>
<u n="557" who="S0115">I guess you're supposed to say neece</u>
<u n="558" who="S0037">that's what me nana always said but then you said nice so I thought it was nice <pause dur="short"/> cos it's usually me who says things wrong</u>
<u n="559" who="S0115" trans="overlap">nice <pause dur="short"/> yeah so Nice <pause dur="short"/> good place to go <pause dur="short"/> bit expensive</u>
<u n="560" who="S0037">that would be nice Nice <pause dur="short"/> waay <pause dur="short"/> that'd be neece <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="561" who="S0115">oh that's actually your accent isn't it?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0037">no I'd never say that</u>
<u n="563" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's actually uh how people speak in the uh the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> you know did you know about these before?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0037" trans="overlap">nice is gonna come out as a collocate of Nice isn't it?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0115">what?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0037">we said them in a row too many times</u>
<u n="567" who="S0115">oh right yeah <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> when you have <trunc>t</trunc> it's for transcribing uh</u>
<u n="568" who="S0037">capital N for Nice though isn't it?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="570" who="S0037">ooh they're not gonna last very long <pause dur="short"/> maybe they are</u>
<u n="571" who="S0115">they're sorta shortbread aren't they?</u>
<u n="572" who="S0037">very sweet <pause dur="short"/> nice though <pause dur="short"/> yeah I like that card</u>
<u n="573" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> oh you <trunc>y</trunc> yeah your one from uh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that's <pause dur="short"/> which has um you know an incredible amount of stuff piled into one card</u>
<u n="574" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Good isn't it?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0115">I don't think you could seriously have driven with a dog like <trunc>w</trunc> with its lead like that</u>
<u n="576" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he's got a little his lead's attached yeah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0115">but when it falls off with the momentum like the dog's gonna get dragged behind it like</u>
<u n="578" who="S0037">mm <pause dur="short"/> poor little thing <pause dur="short"/> what kind of a dog's that then?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well I think it they I think they're just  I think they're just  um well looks like a type of terrier doesn't it?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0037">no it's got curly  it's got curly  hair</u>
<u n="581" who="S0115">yes um don't some terriers have that?</u>
<u n="582" who="S0037">do they? Is it not like a poodle-y thing?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> I don't think</u>
<u n="584" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I like its  I like its  hairdo whatever kind of dog it is</u>
<u n="585" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I'm not  I'm not  sure actually you'd have to we'd have to get the smartphone <pause dur="short"/> can I check that one?</u>
<u n="586" who="S0037">ooh I'm sorry <pause dur="short"/> actually it might <unclear/></u>
<u n="587" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no I reckon they set that photo up just for the <unclear/></u>
<u n="588" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well of course they did</u>
<u n="589" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> excuse me</u>
<u n="590" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's not some picture of someone like driving down the street is it?</u>
<u n="591" who="S0115">well it might've been they might've found it in an archive</u>
<u n="592" who="S0037" trans="overlap">duh</u>
<u n="593" who="S0115">it might've been in an archive somewhere</u>
<u n="594" who="S0037">I very much doubt it</u>
<u n="595" who="S0115">they uh spent ages uh</u>
<u n="596" who="S0037">so what's going in?</u>
<u n="597" who="S0115" trans="overlap">we could look look look for clues in uh in the photo to see it's a modern thing</u>
<u n="598" who="S0037">I don't know</u>
<u n="599" who="S0115">this is like carrot <trunc>n</trunc> going in there</u>
<u n="600" who="S0037">oh right</u>
<u n="601" who="S0115">although</u>
<u n="602" who="S0037">yeah no carrot's okay I normally</u>
<u n="603" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it seemed to just go with like a sort of Holy Trinity thing</u>
<u n="604" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's fine no put it in yeah that's good</u>
<u n="605" who="S0115">um we don't have any celery <pause dur="short"/> uh did anything exciting happen today?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0037">mm <pause dur="short"/> na not really <pause dur="short"/> usual</u>
</body>
</text>
