<text id="SQ82">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:35:08</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-02-11</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0607 S0644</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Driving through Oregon, USA, on holiday</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Religion; private school; studying at university; religion versus science. </topics>
		<activity>Car journey discussion about religion, private school and university.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0607">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Pembury, England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern/ 'BBC' English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Battle</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 month</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Translator/Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Italian -- level unspecified; French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0644">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English/British</nat>
				<birthplace>Enfield, UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London/ South-East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>36 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Office worker (temp)</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Brazilian Portuguese -- basic</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0607">knowing our luck</u>
<u n="3" who="S0644">isn't it your point though?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0607" trans="overlap">sorry</u>
<u n="5" who="S0644">what you were saying earlier like you're not even allowed to say anything</u>
<u n="6" who="S0607">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/> you're not allowed to say anything without having to apologise</u>
<u n="7" who="S0644">this this is it's not a I don't think it's a <pause dur="short"/> experiment in oh maybe it is I don't know it's more linguistics I think rather than</u>
<u n="8" who="S0607">yes</u>
<u n="9" who="S0644">rather than a study of cultural beliefs <unclear/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0607" trans="overlap">they're not supposed to be easily offended</u>
<u n="11" who="S0644">no</u>
<u n="12" who="S0607">you can't not not not be offended or whatever it was you said last night <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah you don't have a right not to be offended you don't have a right not to be offended</u>
<u n="14" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yes I get it now when you said it last night I think I was too tired</u>
<u n="15" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="16" who="S0607">but I knew what you meant but I couldn't get the sentence</u>
<u n="17" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0607">but by the way erm <pause dur="short"/> I'm <trunc>com</trunc> I feel like I'm quite lucky because I believe in God but I don't believe all these strict things that these other Christians believe</u>
<u n="19" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="20" who="S0607">erm but that but I do think that everyone can believe what they want like people can be really strict to the letter of the Bible if they want</u>
<u n="21" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="22" who="S0607">erm in their lives</u>
<u n="23" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="24" who="S0607">erm <pause dur="short"/> and I also but because I don't think that you have to be strict to the letter of the Bible cos I believe that life has moved on since then and things are different erm <pause dur="short"/> wait there there was there was a point there was a really good point</u>
<u n="25" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0607" trans="overlap">er because I because I <pause dur="short"/> yeah because I believe that</u>
<u n="27" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="28" who="S0607">it makes me think are there people who might believe in God if they thought that it could be a bit erm <pause dur="short"/> elastic like like me like or or does some people get put off cos they think it's all like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="30" who="S0607">cos I I don't think like her</u>
<u n="31" who="S0644">no well that's this is the whole topic</u>
<u n="32" who="S0607">and there are all sorts of different types of Christian churches and erm whether or not they're really strict or erm</u>
<u n="33" who="S0644">this is actually the problem with religion <pause dur="short"/> this is actually the problem with religion but it's because <pause dur="short"/> you will never get everyone to agree on everything all the time and nor should you want to do it</u>
<u n="34" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="35" who="S0644">nor should it be like that</u>
<u n="36" who="S0607">maybe it should be a private thing cos I actually don't really like it when people ask me about my religion cos I'm like well what's it got to do with you? you know it's my own private thing and it usually gets people worked up if you talk about religion</u>
<u n="37" who="S0644">well they shouldn't ask you then</u>
<u n="38" who="S0607">no</u>
<u n="39" who="S0644">can't ask someone and then get annoyed with their opinion</u>
<u n="40" who="S0607">but do you know what I think is really bad is that erm usually most of the time if you're English and you you admit that you believe in God people look at you weird and I think that's really poor</u>
<u n="41" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0607">I think that's really poor</u>
<u n="43" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0607">they'll like go they'll like go really?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0607"><trunc>rea</trunc> oh I didn't think that about you I didn't think you would be like that like what? you know it's like you're a fucking pariah or something</u>
<u n="47" who="S0644">what's a pariah?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0607">don't know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="50" who="S0607">I think it means that you're somebody who's like out of society someone who's like a leper</u>
<u n="51" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like a leopard</u>
<u n="52" who="S0607">shall we look that up later? <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0644" trans="overlap">leopard</u>
<u n="54" who="S0607">and I think that's really rude and I think people should bloody <pause dur="short"/> be a bit more <pause dur="short"/> I should go and you don't?</u>
<u n="55" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0607">you bloody weirdo what's wrong with you?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0644" trans="overlap">you're gonna burn in hell <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0607">so it means that like my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has to like keep it to herself because <pause dur="short"/> erm of the way people are about it they think you're odd and I don't think that's right oh and there's another thing I almost daren't bring this up though because if I had a discussion with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about this and we disagreed and it really left me in a bad mood for about four days so I'm worried that if I bring it up</u>
<u n="59" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0607">but this is the other thing my dad said to me you can't talk about things where people don't agree with you you get so enraged you know when I was at home going I can't talk about skinny people</u>
<u n="61" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0607">I just can't even talk about it even if you're agreeing with me because it's so upsetting <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0644">no you can't go through life like that you can't</u>
<u n="64" who="S0607" trans="overlap">but the but this topic is a bit of a hot one I'm not sure I should bring it up <pause dur="short"/> but the point of the topic was the way that people immediately judge you for one thing and I find it very narrow-minded and shitty</u>
<u n="65" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0607">what erm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><trunc>i</trunc>is it that you can't say what the one thing is?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0607">it's the fact that I went to private school <pause dur="short"/> a lot of people</u>
<u n="69" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="70" who="S0607">are really shitty about it and <unclear/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0644" trans="overlap">that's just dumb though</u>
<u n="72" who="S0607">I actually think that the next person who's shitty with me about it I'm gonna punch them in the face</u>
<u n="73" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0607">or the verbal equivalent if I could get the verbal equivalent of the <trunc>pun</trunc> you know obviously</u>
<u n="75" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0607">I don't punch people in the face</u>
<u n="77" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0607">erm but I'm gonna bite their head off basically because I'm sick of it and I was really disgusted cos my really good friend at work who's gay</u>
<u n="79" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="80" who="S0607">and I'm totally fine with that</u>
<u n="81" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="82" who="S0607">so if I'm fine with that can't he be fine with me going to private school? when he worked</u>
<u n="83" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0607">when he realised it no no no I don't think he had <trunc>reali</trunc> this is the cool thing right if you haven't told people and this topic comes up</u>
<u n="85" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0607">they'll say all this stuff about it and then you go <pause dur="short"/> I went to private school <vocal desc="gasp"/> and then they're all like so super shocked and embarrassed</u>
<u n="87" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="88" who="S0607">and and that that's what happened with my gay friend at work he went on a</u>
<u n="89" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh did he?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0607">rant about erm how outrageous it is for anybody to go to a private school and I let him go on and on and on about what bastards we all are and then I went yep I went to private school I won a scholarship actually <pause dur="short"/> and erm and what I really hate is that <trunc>w</trunc>winning a scholarship like excuses me for having gone to a private school so I think I'm gonna stop saying it</u>
<u n="91" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0607">because it's actually like an excuse</u>
<u n="93" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0607">like it's not my fault I was just so clever that I got in on a scholarship</u>
<u n="95" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="96" who="S0607">do you know what I mean? and it and I realised that I actually mention it for that reason I'm not now I'm not gonna mention it not gonna give them that satisfaction</u>
<u n="97" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0607">I'm gonna go yeah I went cos I'm really privileged</u>
<u n="99" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="100" who="S0607">and you all lost out and I it was so unfair cos I got a much better chance in life than you and er and yet here we all are in the same job so I don't know why you're so upset erm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0607">erm but no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went on and on about it she couldn't stop it worked her up so much cos she said erm it's not fair that some people should be able to go and some people shouldn't</u>
<u n="103" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0607">and I and I just kept yelling that I won the scholarship</u>
<u n="105" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0607">and <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and then oh yeah oh but then she apart from the fact that it's not fair it's also not better</u>
<u n="107" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0607">so I was like well if it's not better how is it unfair? so it's like there's no need to go because it's not even better so it's like so therefore it's fair erm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0607">and then and then I said to her erm <pause dur="short"/> the classes are a lot smaller that's why it's better</u>
<u n="111" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0607">and I'm not even gonna go into any other reasons but I'm just telling you</u>
<u n="113" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="114" who="S0607">why it's better so you had thirty people in your class and I had six so</u>
<u n="115" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0607">you get individual attention <pause dur="short"/> but of course what you just said is true it's not better so but therefore it's fair and it got really really heated and everything and</u>
<u n="117" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="118" who="S0607">and I'm I'm some privileged arsehole who should feel bad erm and I was just like well I'm I'm afraid I said to her if I could afford to send my kids to private school I would</u>
<u n="119" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0607">but one of them's probably gonna have to win the scholarship because it's very very expensive <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0644" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0607">and you have to earn a lot to</u>
<u n="123" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0607">erm to go there</u>
<u n="125" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0607">and <pause dur="short"/> erm but I just find it I find it outrageous how people judge that that one thing</u>
<u n="127" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0607">it's almost worse than being a Christian if you've been to private school <pause dur="short"/> I was really <trunc>sho</trunc> I wish I could remember some of the things that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said at work about it cos I was really like but I actually did really enjoy him not knowing that I'd been and then and then saying it</u>
<u n="129" who="S0644" trans="overlap">telling you</u>
<u n="130" who="S0607">and his face</u>
<u n="131" who="S0644" trans="overlap">was he embarrassed?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0607">yeah really embarrassed</u>
<u n="133" who="S0644">oh <pause dur="short"/> what did he say after?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0607" trans="overlap">I find that I've rarely had that pleasure</u>
<u n="135" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> what did he say after about it?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0607" trans="overlap">I can't I can't remember isn't it annoying?</u>
<u n="137" who="S0644">cos it's it's when they</u>
<u n="138" who="S0607" trans="overlap">I can't remember</u>
<u n="139" who="S0644">change people's minds or not</u>
<u n="140" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="141" who="S0644">erm</u>
<u n="142" who="S0607">but I would think that they would know that I went to private school cos he's one of the people cos he's like a supervisor he would have seen my CV and do you think if you saw on a CV <anon type="place"/> school wouldn't you think that's <vocal desc="laugh"/> a private school?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="144" who="S0607">I dunno maybe it doesn't but to me it always sounded like a private school</u>
<u n="145" who="S0644">I think no I mean there's probably loads of schools</u>
<u n="146" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0644">erm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0607">to me it like sticks out like a sore thumb you know</u>
<u n="149" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> school <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0607" trans="overlap">head of house I I don't have that on my CV any more</u>
<u n="151" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0607">but when I was younger you know when you haven't got anything on your CV except your education?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0607">so <trunc>every</trunc> was like head of house games captain</u>
<u n="155" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0607">I thought that would be quite obvious</u>
<u n="157" who="S0644" trans="overlap">a giveaway maybe to someone who is au fait with things like that</u>
<u n="158" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="159" who="S0644">but someone like me will just go and <unclear/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0644">and get it</u>
<u n="162" who="S0607">also not only private schools have houses but I do think it's a bit of an antiquated thing</u>
<u n="163" who="S0644">there was this woman so one of our discussions when I was doing my <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>stud</trunc> last uni and I really loved it cos it was all about things like this it was all about what's right and what's wrong and what's this and you've got to really reconsider things like just when you thought your mind was made up about something someone would give you another opinion</u>
<u n="164" who="S0607" trans="overlap">makes you think</u>
<u n="165" who="S0644">yeah and it was really really really good so there was this and this particular erm semester all these this lectures that I was going to were all about real life scenarios so there was one MP English MP and</u>
<u n="166" who="S0607" trans="overlap">sorry what was your course called?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0644">er it was legal and political theory</u>
<u n="168" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="169" who="S0644">it was very good because</u>
<u n="170" who="S0607" trans="overlap">did you enjoy it?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0644">I love it I loved it I loved it I loved it</u>
<u n="172" who="S0607" trans="overlap">was it a fulfilling year?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="174" who="S0607">oh</u>
<u n="175" who="S0644">I didn't want to leave I was gutted that it was only one year I loved it I loved it I loved it but not just the not just the studying</u>
<u n="176" who="S0607">everything</u>
<u n="177" who="S0644">everything it was just brilliant the place was fantastic the uni was fantastic</u>
<u n="178" who="S0607" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0644">the little cafeteria was fantastic the student uni <pause dur="short"/> oh brilliant</u>
<u n="180" who="S0607" trans="overlap">was it difficult? like was it was there in any way the possibility of like?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0644">not passing?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0644">do you know this is it's the story of my life <unclear/> that clever really if I actually applied myself on top of being clever I'd do really well</u>
<u n="184" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0644">but I can't really apply myself so there you go I'd rather go to the pub this is the whole thing erm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0607">but it wasn't like oh my god I'm so out of my depth I don't understand what's going on? <pause dur="short"/> or</u>
<u n="187" who="S0644" trans="overlap">er <pause dur="short"/> somehow do you know I was looking last just as I was clearing out some stuff before I came away here I was trying to get rid of some stuff the joy process you know?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0607">yes</u>
<u n="189" who="S0644">and I was looking through some of my essays cos I really like reading some of my essays and I mostly got Bs and I'd never really really put myself out <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0607">excellent no that's brilliant</u>
<u n="191" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I mostly got Bs and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was who's very clever she was much worse she'd be up the night before every time and she got quite I think she got a couple of As really thrown in or very high Bs B plus</u>
<u n="192" who="S0607">this is an interesting thing in itself by the way because I always killed myself with things like that like literally had a nervous breakdown erm over it</u>
<u n="193" who="S0644" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0607">and got top marks but which it what you know it could say</u>
<u n="195" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I think that is a gift in itself though I think that's</u>
<u n="196" who="S0607" trans="overlap">is it better to just enjoy it and get a B?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0644">no cos it's always the same</u>
<u n="198" who="S0607" trans="overlap">erm <pause dur="short"/> and actually be able to relax and not kill yourself do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0644">do you know what the problem is? I've never been able to go when I was occasionally I did like really really work on something and at uni as well like really enjoyed something and went out of my way</u>
<u n="200" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0644" trans="overlap">but most of the time it was like I could have done better than that I could have done why didn't you just try? if I'd actually tried and it's you get sick of yourself saying that to yourself like oh yeah I could have done better <unclear/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0607" trans="overlap">but maybe <pause dur="short"/> maybe you should erm try and erm accept it like live with it</u>
<u n="203" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0607">and enjoy the fact that you didn't have to kill yourself because I think with me it was actually that I cannot live with that I can't live with knowing that I</u>
<u n="205" who="S0644" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0607">haven't done my best that's a real <trunc>s</trunc> erm not a scar what is it? a erm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0607">what's the word I mean? it's a a burden</u>
<u n="209" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="210" who="S0607">what what was what was the word? a erm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0607">it's a <pause dur="short"/> a thing around your neck it's a</u>
<u n="213" who="S0644">weight</u>
<u n="214" who="S0607">it's a yeah it's a</u>
<u n="215" who="S0644" trans="overlap">it's a</u>
<u n="216" who="S0607">it has a real <pause dur="short"/> crap what's the word? it's a really simple word <vocal desc="laugh"/> as well it's a real</u>
<u n="217" who="S0644">like a burden or a scar or a</u>
<u n="218" who="S0607">yeah <pause dur="short"/> not a scar but a something that weighs you down it's a real cross to bear no anyway doesn't matter</u>
<u n="219" who="S0644">it'll come to us</u>
<u n="220" who="S0607">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you know cos then you you can't ever just go</u>
<u n="221" who="S0644">relax</u>
<u n="222" who="S0607">and it was the same when I was applying for my own job all the time you know I nearly killed myself three times trying to apply for my own job and it was like but but because I had said to myself I'm gonna die if I don't get this job</u>
<u n="223" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="224" who="S0607">cos I want it so bad so therefore</u>
<u n="225" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0607">I have to like do my best and I know that if I do my absolute best they're totally gonna pick me</u>
<u n="227" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0607" trans="overlap">so I have to do my best and if I don't and then my friend erm <pause dur="short"/> who was also applying we were both applying for our job</u>
<u n="229" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0607">and erm she sort of like spent about half the time I did erm maybe even less</u>
<u n="231" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0607">erm <pause dur="short"/> and what happened was that <pause dur="short"/> I came so that time that other woman got the job you know the woman who was like in her fifties and got a lot more experience then I came second so I got a temporary position</u>
<u n="233" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0607">and my friend came third</u>
<u n="235" who="S0644">right</u>
<u n="236" who="S0607">so if I hadn't killed myself</u>
<u n="237" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0607">my friend would have come second</u>
<u n="239" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0607">possibly</u>
<u n="241" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="242" who="S0607">so it was worth it but was it?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="244" who="S0607">you know cos</u>
<u n="245" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0607">I did and my and she I I did think I actually think that's right because I knew how much time she had spent and</u>
<u n="247" who="S0644" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="248" who="S0607">I knew how much time I had spent but in reality we're both as good as each other</u>
<u n="249" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0607">but I just went the extra mile eight hundred times and she just sort of went oh do you know what? I wrote my admission essay last night and I but the thing is I looked at her and I envied her</u>
<u n="251" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="252" who="S0607">because I thought <vocal desc="laugh"/> I spent two months writing it do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0607">honing it and honing it and then so two hundred and fifty people applied right? and my boss said that I mine was the best essay now that's wonderful right but I said to her I should bloody think so</u>
<u n="255" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="256" who="S0607">because seriously I nearly killed myself and I think that's a curse wouldn't you rather be you or my friend who's like right I'm gonna I've gotta do this but I'm not gonna make myself ill over it do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0644">I dunno I dunno what's there ain't there ain't really a right or wrong with it again is there? it's just cos I I've spent my life saying I could if I really tried I could do this</u>
<u n="258" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0644">if I actually really tried I could do this but just don't get round to really trying any of it</u>
<u n="260" who="S0607" trans="overlap">and I've I've spent my life going I've done that but nearly killed me though</u>
<u n="261" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="262" who="S0607">and my mum actually said to me recently she was like you've done too much you</u>
<u n="263" who="S0644">ah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0607">you need to stop it cos it's all been too much and I and I think she's right do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0644" trans="overlap">naked in the woods book reading Feb twenty-second at seven PM</u>
<u n="266" who="S0607">what day is it today?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> luckily it's not February the twenty-second</u>
<u n="268" who="S0607">no I really wanna do it</u>
<u n="269" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0607">shall we come back? oh no we'll be on like some <unclear/> island</u>
<u n="271" who="S0644">naked in the woods book reading</u>
<u n="272" who="S0607">that's so my kind of thing</u>
<u n="273" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0607">although do you think if you got there it would be like weirdos?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="276" who="S0607">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah did you not see that?</u>
<u n="278" who="S0607" trans="overlap">I really wanna do that</u>
<u n="279" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> would you really?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0607" trans="overlap"><unclear/> be cold in February though to be naked in the woods?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0644">apparently not</u>
<u n="282" who="S0607">do you remember how cold <vocal desc="misc"/> sorry pardon me how cold it was in the in the erm?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0644">greasy spoon café</u>
<u n="284" who="S0607">actual spoon <vocal desc="laugh"/> how cold it was in the erm whatchamacallit woods?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0644">what woods? in the in the red forest?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0607">the redwood oh it's difficult for me to say anything cos I was like coffee house greasy spoon safari ah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0644">see these little towns are wicked these little places I could stop at every single one</u>
<u n="290" who="S0607">I wish I could remember where</u>
<u n="291" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><unclear/> only be in California though wouldn't it? <unclear/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0607">I need to remember whether <anon type="place"/> is before or after where we're going I can't remember <pause dur="short"/> but anyway so going back to your this is how we got onto this <trunc>mm</trunc>me telling you about <unclear/></u>
<u n="293" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh can I just tell you though?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0607">it was your uni</u>
<u n="295" who="S0644">no yeah but about the dissertation so I got by with mostly Bs and the odd C</u>
<u n="296" who="S0607">that's great</u>
<u n="297" who="S0644">it was good until it got to the dissertation where you're supposed to you have it's like ten thousand words it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="298" who="S0607" trans="overlap">it's the hardest the hardest part the dissertation</u>
<u n="299" who="S0644" trans="overlap">you have to start planning it months before</u>
<u n="300" who="S0607">was it a masters?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="302" who="S0607">this is the problem isn't it?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0644">and I</u>
<u n="304" who="S0607" trans="overlap">don't you sometimes think I'd rather just have a diploma because <vocal desc="laugh"/> then I wouldn't have to do the dissertation?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0644" trans="overlap">no this this was the best example I thought cos I really loved the subject and what I was doing I really loved it</u>
<u n="306" who="S0607" trans="overlap">oh what was your subject?</u>
<u n="307" who="S0644">it was about animal rights and how</u>
<u n="308" who="S0607">oh of course</u>
<u n="309" who="S0644">it's gonna evolve</u>
<u n="310" who="S0607">fantastic</u>
<u n="311" who="S0644">erm and no is animal <trunc>right</trunc> and there was a really excellent erm lecture that we had on terrorism all about terrorism</u>
<u n="312" who="S0607">wow</u>
<u n="313" who="S0644">and it was so fascinating erm and I decided to do a bit of a combination of terrorism and animal rights and the rest of it <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember what it was anyway it was really fascinating brilliant brilliant brilliant subject but with propensity already to not do the work when you're supposed to do it plus around that time I met that young chap</u>
<u n="314" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0644">and ended up chasing him about for about three weeks before</u>
<u n="316" who="S0607" trans="overlap">which one?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0644">the</u>
<u n="318" who="S0607">oh the uni one</u>
<u n="319" who="S0644">the uni one yeah he was lovely</u>
<u n="320" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0644">so the last few weeks revolved around hanging not hanging about with him I only went out with him on like a few dates <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was terrible though <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="322" who="S0607">but was it fun?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0644">it was loads of fun it was so much fun he was lovely he's he's really smart he's on Youtube erm someone told me cos he's erm doing really really well with his stuff</u>
<u n="324" who="S0607">ah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0644">erm <pause dur="short"/> anyway so that just through an absolute spanner in and by the time it got round to doing the work I got fifty percent which is the minimal pass you can get <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0644">so but and the reason I got that partly is cos you know they do plagiarism now? like they can scan your work to see if it's plagiarised mine was forty percent plagiarised which again was the maximum</u>
<u n="328" who="S0607" trans="overlap">oh no</u>
<u n="329" who="S0644">yeah it was the maximum but I was doing it the night before the night before I was an absolute wreck <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for once couldn't even do it and she erm <pause dur="short"/> forwent the you know if you hand it in a week late but they automatically deduct ten percent</u>
<u n="330" who="S0607">ah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0644">have you heard of that? so she had to do that <pause dur="short"/> erm and I <trunc>rea</trunc> that's the thing I was most gutted about because that dissertation I really really really wanted to do well and just couldn't seem to manage it I was too busy chasing after that</u>
<u n="332" who="S0607">good that you passed though</u>
<u n="333" who="S0644">by the skin of my teeth I passed that</u>
<u n="334" who="S0607">I also only just passed my masters because of one thing that I got fifty percent on that was like interpreting</u>
<u n="335" who="S0644">really?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0607">and erm cos I couldn't do the interpreting er let's just recap that I was the best one at the translating</u>
<u n="337" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="338" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but the interpreting I couldn't I just couldn't do it at all</u>
<u n="339" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="340" who="S0607">it's so difficult and then the exam <pause dur="short"/> the exam came and I basically so they called my teacher called me up about the result I didn't know what the result was yet</u>
<u n="341" who="S0644" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0607">she called me up and she went just to let you know what's happened erm <pause dur="short"/> there's been some complaints about the exam</u>
<u n="343" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0607">now I didn't realise this because I couldn't do it anyway</u>
<u n="345" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="346" who="S0607">but the exam was completely wrong</u>
<u n="347" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="348" who="S0607">they had used a text that was written and you can't do that you have to have a spoken text</u>
<u n="349" who="S0644" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="350" who="S0607">so they had or something like that they'd read out a completely outrageous text that would be difficult for anybody to interpret</u>
<u n="351" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0607">because it wasn't a <trunc>spoke</trunc> a proper spoken text</u>
<u n="353" who="S0644">right</u>
<u n="354" who="S0607">so they'd completely fucked up which by the way I find absolutely inexcusable</u>
<u n="355" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0607">to not even be able to get off your arse and find the proper text for an exam</u>
<u n="357" who="S0644" trans="overlap">it's pretty bad</u>
<u n="358" who="S0607">which affects the rest of our lives</u>
<u n="359" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0607">so anyway she called me up and she went erm there's been an enquiry into the exam</u>
<u n="361" who="S0644">right</u>
<u n="362" who="S0607">and it's been found that it was completely <trunc>unacc</trunc> completely er not unacceptable er inappropriate</u>
<u n="363" who="S0644" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="364" who="S0607">test material</u>
<u n="365" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0607">erm and therefore everybody's been bumped up five percent</u>
<u n="367" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="368" who="S0607">and therefore you've got fifty percent</u>
<u n="369" who="S0644">so you passed it?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0607">yeah but only because the</u>
<u n="371" who="S0644" trans="overlap">the because of that?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0607">but the thing is I I sort of like couldn't stop laughing that day because I was like I hadn't passed it but I did because of the thing but actually you could say I would have just scraped it if the text had been correct</u>
<u n="373" who="S0644">right</u>
<u n="374" who="S0607">do you see what I mean? so like I was</u>
<u n="375" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="376" who="S0607">I was proper borderline and they used a shit text</u>
<u n="377" who="S0644">and that helped</u>
<u n="378" who="S0607">so I went down five percent</u>
<u n="379" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0607">so either way I guess I would have been dead on fifty</u>
<u n="381" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0607">and when she after I put the phone down I was just like oh my god thank god</u>
<u n="383" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0607">because I would have failed my masters because of interpreting and and the reason I did both was to find out which one I wanted to do you know?</u>
<u n="385" who="S0644" trans="overlap">to do <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0607">and erm luckily I had the other half that could do erm but so it's amazing when you get that fifty</u>
<u n="387" who="S0644">well I thought to myself as diabolical as it is it is a pass</u>
<u n="388" who="S0607">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="389" who="S0644" trans="overlap">if they if they could have failed me they would have failed me or</u>
<u n="390" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0644">if they should have done they would have done so it is a pass but it's more the fact that I was embarrassed cos I that really was poor I was up the night</u>
<u n="392" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0644">I was up till five o'clock or six o'clock in the morning copying somebody else's work <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="394" who="S0607">did <trunc>s</trunc> did some fun stuff happen with that boy?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="396" who="S0607">oh good</u>
<u n="397" who="S0644">oh yeah he was <trunc>lo</trunc> he was really nice</u>
<u n="398" who="S0607">well I vaguely remember about him</u>
<u n="399" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="400" who="S0607">but can I ask you? so I wanna go back to your course</u>
<u n="401" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="402" who="S0607">but also can I ask you? so your friend what's her face from Ghana she</u>
<u n="403" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="404" who="S0607">you met her the first uni?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0644">no no no no so I finished the masters degree and then had to go back to work and went to <anon type="place"/> and met her there</u>
<u n="406" who="S0607">ah okay okay cos I cos I got confused earlier thinking you've known about the theory of everything since you were eighteen</u>
<u n="407" who="S0644">oh no</u>
<u n="408" who="S0607">no</u>
<u n="409" who="S0644">no no no no no</u>
<u n="410" who="S0607">erm but <trunc>sh</trunc> so erm so your friend what's her face from Ghana erm miss thingy</u>
<u n="411" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0607">is a Christian</u>
<u n="413" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="414" who="S0607">like proper majorly</u>
<u n="415" who="S0644">hell hell fire type Christian</u>
<u n="416" who="S0607">now that I like that because now I can say to you when you meet people and they announce that they're Christian do you think flipping heck?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0607">so you know you've got me and her I don't know if you've got anyone else</u>
<u n="419" who="S0644">well no</u>
<u n="420" who="S0607" trans="overlap">it doesn't sound like you're that judgemental cos otherwise you wouldn't be friends with her right?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0644">erm I think that would be see that's <pause dur="short"/> I dunno if it's right so <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0607">cos some people just think you're a nutter by default then?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I used to be a bit like that I used to be a little bit like that and it's not that I would ever try and change someone else's views</u>
<u n="424" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="425" who="S0644">but I might used to think to myself <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> you know it ain't true like we know that ain't true</u>
<u n="426" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="427" who="S0644">you've got science you've got <pause dur="short"/> you've got all this stuff you know it ain't true but then I learned about the theory of everything</u>
<u n="428" who="S0607" trans="overlap"><unclear/> mm</u>
<u n="429" who="S0644">and now <pause dur="short"/> I see the importance of it</u>
<u n="430" who="S0607">so really the the key to everything is</u>
<u n="431" who="S0644" trans="overlap">the theory of everything</u>
<u n="432" who="S0607">the acceptance of other people's erm like you do what you want there's the buffet</u>
<u n="433" who="S0644">well I've got a really good it I need a pen and paper but I'll I'll show you later what how it makes sense and it might it might sort of help but I wanted what I wanted to tell you first <pause dur="short"/> oh you see there was loads of subjects just there</u>
<u n="434" who="S0607">I know</u>
<u n="435" who="S0644">there's loads of subjects</u>
<u n="436" who="S0607">I think that we shouldn't be trying to persuade each other to to come round to the other way of thinking but you can have</u>
<u n="437" who="S0644">you can have a discussion with people</u>
<u n="438" who="S0607" trans="overlap">discussions</u>
<u n="439" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0607">but I don't think it's right for either you or Miss thingy to be trying to force the other one</u>
<u n="441" who="S0644">no</u>
<u n="442" who="S0607">to think differently</u>
<u n="443" who="S0644">no</u>
<u n="444" who="S0607" trans="overlap">but it's an interesting discussion do you think that could be a key thing? cos I think that's a key thing because erm people should just bloody leave you alone if you don't believe in God or leave her alone if she does erm like nobody should be saying you're wrong you shouldn't be thinking that because everybody's different</u>
<u n="445" who="S0644" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> of course exactly that's that's the whole point is that you <pause dur="short"/> I'll give you a good example as well recently there were some parents it was on the radio there were some parents that wrote into the school and said no our children will not be joining you on their trip to it was either a mosque or a church or a it didn't matter which cos they were total atheists they they just say their opinion was that it <trunc>cau</trunc> it's more trouble than it's worth it's caused so many <unclear/> along those lines yeah so they said no we don't want our kids to go to any religious erm <pause dur="short"/> things we're not we are not religious we don't want them being brought up religious</u>
<u n="446" who="S0607" trans="overlap"><unclear/> deciding for their children already but hang on it depends how old they are I think when you're getting into teenager years</u>
<u n="447" who="S0644"><unclear/></u>
<u n="448" who="S0607" trans="overlap">or when you get older you decide your own that stuff don't you?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0644">well as parents you you do decide cos you that's your job</u>
<u n="450" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0644">when it until they're old enough so you have to do that but but what I said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was erm <pause dur="short"/> it's it feels almost it feels as bad to me to say we will not tolerate any religion as it as it does to say you must <trunc>toler</trunc> you must believe our religion it seems</u>
<u n="452" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0644">it's <pause dur="short"/> it's all extremism it's just extreme <pause dur="short"/> nothingness if you see what I mean</u>
<u n="454" who="S0607">people need to just learn to <trunc>co</trunc>coexist without you know <pause dur="short"/> cos also what I don't like is so there's one thing is erm you hurting people because their their beliefs are different</u>
<u n="455" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="456" who="S0607">another <trunc>i</trunc> another is judging them so me judging you cos you don't believe and you judging me cos I believe I I think that's wrong too and I'm terrible at judging people</u>
<u n="457" who="S0644">no but this is the good thing about that is that you can't <pause dur="short"/> when people say about don't judge this and don't judge that all you're saying really <pause dur="short"/> to an extent is an opinion cos everyone is entitled to their own opinion</u>
<u n="458" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="459" who="S0644">so you you've gotta not care what other people think if you if you've gotta have strong enough erm <pause dur="short"/> strength of mind yourself to say well that is what I think and if you don't like it get on with it</u>
<u n="460" who="S0607" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="461" who="S0644">you've gotta not worry about what other people think and if they're that <trunc>ups</trunc> offended by what you think then they're not people you're supposed to hang about with</u>
<u n="462" who="S0607">no cos I don't judge people who don't believe in God and so I don't see why they should jump to conclusions about me because I do but again who cares what they think?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0644">yeah you can't <trunc>s</trunc> you can't say</u>
<u n="464" who="S0607" trans="overlap">arseholes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0607">oh sorry no judgement</u>
<u n="467" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/> isn't it difficult?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0644" trans="overlap">no but you couldn't have erm</u>
<u n="470" who="S0607" trans="overlap"><unclear/> thirty-six and don't know how to behave</u>
<u n="471" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/> or think or anything</u>
<u n="473" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="474" who="S0607">have to start again aren't I?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="476" who="S0607">from scratch</u>
<u n="477" who="S0644">no cos it's constantly erm <pause dur="short"/> evolving isn't it? your thoughts about things as I was gonna that's what I was gonna say to you about religion I used to think I wouldn't actively I would never pick on someone or <pause dur="short"/> tell them off</u>
<u n="478" who="S0607" trans="overlap">but would you rule them out?</u>
<u n="479" who="S0644">I just think I don't see how you can think like I wouldn't be able to relate to it I wouldn't like <pause dur="short"/> you know you've got geology? just just as a small example</u>
<u n="480" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="481" who="S0644">you know you've got geology and that tells you how old everything is and how and it's it's sort of it's evidence</u>
<u n="482" who="S0607">yeah but this goes back to the whole thing of erm how some people listen to the Bible down to the letter and others don't like you know I don't think it necessarily means that the world was created in that day</u>
<u n="483" who="S0644" trans="overlap">but that was always <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s <pause dur="short"/> that was always <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s thing she said it is true it's in the Bible</u>
<u n="484" who="S0607" trans="overlap">she's a traditionalist yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0644">it's in the it it's was written thousands of years ago it's true</u>
<u n="486" who="S0607">she's the proper old school Christian type who you know er taking it all literally</u>
<u n="487" who="S0644">well I think that's that is frightening because that's that shows how <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> myopic their your view is like it cannot be swayed you are so and no matter what anything no matter what anyone says or anything that happens you you can't take into account the possibility that maybe something was not quite so this is what I was gonna say</u>
<u n="488" who="S0607">can you <trunc>ca</trunc> this is an irritating thing to say can you take into account the possibility that she's right?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0644">yeah she can be right for all I care if you see what I mean like she's totally entitled to</u>
<u n="490" who="S0607" trans="overlap">like could be could be that her version is true</u>
<u n="491" who="S0644">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="492" who="S0607">I do think that you see this is why I quite like my situation because I I don't sort of like feel like the science and the religion conflict with each other cos I'm not such a traditional er by the book</u>
<u n="493" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0607">Christian type so it doesn't actually have a conflict</u>
<u n="495" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="496" who="S0607">I don't sit there worrying about that</u>
<u n="497" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="498" who="S0607">and what I thought was really maybe this is going too far if you're not a a religious person but erm <pause dur="short"/> I hardly ever go to church and erm when I lived in Turin there's that Turin shroud</u>
<u n="499" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="500" who="S0607">erm do you remember what it is? it's where</u>
<u n="501" who="S0644">a face imprinted on it yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah so it's you in theory it's the thing that Jesus was wrapped up in</u>
<u n="503" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="504" who="S0607">and when my mum and dad came to visit me and we were doing touristy things we went to see the Turin shroud</u>
<u n="505" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="506" who="S0607">and I forget this is <unclear/> thing but usually the real shroud is not there</u>
<u n="507" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="508" who="S0607">it's erm kept because otherwise it would be like disintegrated if it was constantly out</u>
<u n="509" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="510" who="S0607">I'll have to check with dad I think it was out when we were there so that's why we went because it was like for one month the real shroud</u>
<u n="511" who="S0644">was there</u>
<u n="512" who="S0607">can be seen and it's only in this one church this really small church</u>
<u n="513" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="514" who="S0607">not in the centre of town</u>
<u n="515" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="516" who="S0607">and erm so we went and we're not fanatical so we had our doubts you know we were like what do you reckon? do you think it's true? and all this stuff and erm so we <trunc>a</trunc> my dad asked the priest and he said erm <pause dur="short"/> so you know what about all this carbon dating and things like that like</u>
<u n="517" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="518" who="S0607">is it really true?</u>
<u n="519" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0607">and the priest I won't be able to my dad can tell this story better I won't be able to say what he said as well as he did</u>
<u n="521" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="522" who="S0607">but the priest said <pause dur="short"/> but we don't need to we're not bothered about all of that erm all of those arguments are we? because we just believe and we were all like yay we just believe</u>
<u n="523" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0607">and it was so he was so holy that guy he just made us feel wonderful</u>
<u n="525" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0607">and and I agreed with him like but that's what it's about for us</u>
<u n="527" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="528" who="S0607">and for people who don't believe in God they're interested in the carbon dating</u>
<u n="529" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="530" who="S0607" trans="overlap">erm whereas to us it doesn't really matter whether the carbon dates back to then or not kind of thing</u>
<u n="531" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="532" who="S0607">erm and I thought that was really wonderful how he kind of</u>
<u n="533" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="534" who="S0607">and we and we went off going yay</u>
<u n="535" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0607">erm but I actually can't remember all the stuff about the carbon dating it's really interesting about the shroud but I actually can't remember the facts to tell you</u>
<u n="537" who="S0644">well the thing is <pause dur="short"/> erm what was I gonna say? <pause dur="short"/> oh there's so much to say</u>
<u n="538" who="S0607">also</u>
<u n="539" who="S0644">I love the discussion on religion</u>
<u n="540" who="S0607">yeah also I do think science erm <pause dur="short"/> is generally reliable but could also be wrong about many things</u>
<u n="541" who="S0644">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> right and</u>
<u n="542" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0644">and these erm <pause dur="short"/> cos I said to her look you've got a thing called empirical evidence erm which is you've got one theory I've got another let's test it by means of which we both agree on and therefore we will be able to get a result on something</u>
<u n="544" who="S0607" trans="overlap">flipping heck</u>
<u n="545" who="S0644">that's science innit?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0644">and she said yes but these methods that you're talking about so say I said geology and therefore you can tell how old this rocks are and and when life began on earth and all that kind of caper she said yeah but these are man made machines and <unclear/> systems and all that sort of thing you know of course they're gonna be designed to do that because the devil wants you to and I'm thinking oh I give up <unclear/></u>
<u n="548" who="S0607" trans="overlap">well she's very old school</u>
<u n="549" who="S0644">yeah but this is the point of it is it doesn't matter because she's perfectly entitled she's</u>
<u n="550" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="551" who="S0644">totally totally totally entitled to it and the world would not be complete without it the world would not be like</u>
<u n="552" who="S0607">I wouldn't go with the devil theory I was gonna say erm what annoys me about science is I watch a lot of erm</u>
<u n="553" who="S0644">Bank of America</u>
<u n="554" who="S0607">oh where?</u>
<u n="555" who="S0644">left</u>
<u n="556" who="S0607">left here?</u>
<u n="557" who="S0644">yeah what I'd do turn round here right</u>
<u n="558" who="S0607">go right yeah</u>
<u n="559" who="S0644" trans="overlap">well you could do</u>
<u n="560" who="S0607">yeah oh well done</u>
<u n="561" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> fitness training</u>
<u n="562" who="S0607">where is it? I can't even see it</u>
<u n="563" who="S0644">it's right next to that car <pause dur="short"/> right behind that car I should say</u>
<u n="564" who="S0607">oh fantastic yeah no what I was gonna say is I watch loads of erm you know I love all these detective dramas and stuff</u>
<u n="565" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="566" who="S0607">and it drives me insane because one of them I watch is called The Good Wife it's basically lawyers</u>
<u n="567" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="568" who="S0607">and erm so each team of lawyers the defence and the prosecution always have scientific evidence and it always has completely opposite er findings</u>
<u n="569" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="570" who="S0607">so one that one of them will get a scientist who'll say that this happened</u>
<u n="571" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="572" who="S0607">because based on this er</u>
<u n="573" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="574" who="S0607">testing and then the opposite will will find a scientist who believes the opposite <unclear/></u>
<u n="575" who="S0644" trans="overlap">mm mm mm hm</u>
<u n="576" who="S0607">and then that that does throw me for a loop cos</u>
<u n="577" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="578" who="S0607">I'm not even thinking about religion when I'm watching these at all</u>
<u n="579" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah just goes to show how</u>
<u n="580" who="S0607">I'm not thinking oh this proves about God or anything</u>
<u n="581" who="S0644">no</u>
<u n="582" who="S0607">I'm just thinking how oh everything is completely erm <pause dur="short"/> messed up so you can't actually <trunc>ha</trunc> what you know?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="584" who="S0607"><trunc>o</trunc>obviously some some lawyers are really erm morally erm have no morals and they just pay somebody to say something</u>
<u n="585" who="S0644">mm mm</u>
<u n="586" who="S0607">but I mean aside from that</u>
<u n="587" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="588" who="S0607">it's really upsetting that so cos I also find science to be very like you know ah we know this and we know that but then</u>
<u n="589" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="590" who="S0607">when I watch those programmes which admittedly are just stupid box sets</u>
<u n="591" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> well no they're based on erm</u>
<u n="592" who="S0607" trans="overlap">but it's <pause dur="short"/> they're based on real life right?</u>
<u n="593" who="S0644">well the idea has come from real</u>
<u n="594" who="S0607" trans="overlap">it's really realistic <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="595" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="596" who="S0607">but you know so then so then what? you know it's like</u>
<u n="597" who="S0644" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="598" who="S0607">wouldn't you like to know more about science and stuff and and be involved? not really erm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="599" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I'm not very scientific I never really got it</u>
<u n="600" who="S0607">maybe animals you know like finding out about how whales this that and the other you know whales the animals not the country</u>
<u n="601" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah I'd have liked to of been a animal studier</u>
<u n="602" who="S0607" trans="overlap">marine biologist</u>
<u n="603" who="S0644">sort of thing</u>
<u n="604" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="605" who="S0644">but then I say that I could have done well it's another one of those things where I could I could have done that if I'd tried harder</u>
<u n="606" who="S0607">where do I go?</u>
<u n="607" who="S0644" trans="overlap">could have done <unclear>it</unclear> chuck a left <anon type="place"/> so there is Bank of America on your left</u>
<u n="608" who="S0607">I still can't see it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="609" who="S0644">it's a bit worrying <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="610" who="S0607">here where the dog thing is?</u>
<u n="611" who="S0644">er <pause dur="short"/> well pull up anywhere you can basically cos it's about thirty second walk</u>
<u n="612" who="S0607">but I just can't see it anywhere</u>
<u n="613" who="S0644">it's right there man</u>
<u n="614" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0644">it's probably best to walk from here</u>
<u n="616" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="617" who="S0644">yeah <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="618" who="S0607">this is sort of breaking up a a conversation but it's too good to miss seeing a Bank of America</u>
<u n="619" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="620" who="S0607">well done you're so erm <pause dur="short"/> you're <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
