<text id="SQ93">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:31:46</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-04-18</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0390 S0391 S0392</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>refueling, ambulances, past week, spirituality, food and drink, eat-by dates, cricket, illness, news, supermarkets, foreign languages, education, literature, text messages</topics>
		<activity>Grandmother’s visit</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, advising, requesting, anecdote telling, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0390">
				<exactage>76</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>70_79</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kendal</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>British</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Near Thirsk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>12 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0391">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Darlington</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>British</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>County Durham</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Near Thirsk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>15 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0392">
				<exactage>15</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>11_18</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Newcastle-upon-time</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Northern/Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Near Thirsk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>15 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Full-time education</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0390">I went to Tesco's where I've gone for n number of years and probably been hundreds of times and I'm filling up as usual and suddenly instead of going to the car the petrol squirted came right up and then</u>
<u n="2" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so had you pressed the thing that makes it come out?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0390">yeah I was filling the car the petrol was the pump was working</u>
<u n="4" who="S0392">yeah <trunc>an</trunc>and did it come out the the spout into the tank sort of thing?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0390">the tank was filling as per normal but all of a sudden there was a huge pressure on my hand and the pump almost jumped out of the car you know where you put it and the petrol squirted up</u>
<u n="6" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yes</u>
<u n="7" who="S0390">and the petrol spurted up</u>
<u n="8" who="S0392">gosh but had you filled your tank already or?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0390">no I'd only got eleven pounds worth in and it takes forty pounds</u>
<u n="10" who="S0392">gosh</u>
<u n="11" who="S0390">so they were very I sort of staggered oh I staggered across the road and somebody said are you alright?  no I'm not no I can't see I couldn't see out of my left eye at all and I could hardly see out of my right eye <pause dur="short"/> it was horrible</u>
<u n="12" who="S0392" trans="overlap"><trunc>s</trunc>so what did they do to you then?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0390">well they took me into a little place and they washed my eye out with water just with water because they hadn't got anything else at that time and I think I was shouting all the time ah ah oh ah you know and then they called for the ambulance <pause dur="short"/> I said I didn't want the ambulance but apparently it is part of health and safety but maybe half an hour later the ambulance came they'd had to come from <anon type="place"/> but they were lovely they took me into the ambulance and washed my eye out again</u>
<u n="14" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/>  <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and so you did go in the ambulance?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0390">no it was static</u>
<u n="16" who="S0392">what?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0390">it was static</u>
<u n="18" who="S0392">so you went in the ambulance they sorted you out</u>
<u n="19" who="S0390">yes and then they took me back to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="20" who="S0392">oh is that where you'd come from?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0390">no I <trunc>ca</trunc> ah it was easier than taking me home because <trunc>I</trunc><trunc>I</trunc>I'd rang <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he'd come over and taken the car and my pullover and stuff that was oh they were absolutely stinking I had to wash them out three times</u>
<u n="22" who="S0392" trans="overlap">oh right okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I see yeah <pause dur="short"/> gosh</u>
<u n="23" who="S0390">so that's my saga for the weekend I don't want any more thank you</u>
<u n="24" who="S0392"><vocal desc="laugh"/> gosh that must've been a bit <pause dur="short"/> so you must've got your petrol free then surely?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0390">oh I offered to pay for it and the lady on the till was going to take some money and the manager said oh no</u>
<u n="26" who="S0392">she was going to take the money blimey</u>
<u n="27" who="S0390" trans="overlap">the lady on the till she didn't know any better</u>
<u n="28" who="S0392">oh dear</u>
<u n="29" who="S0390">she's just the the person who takes the money but the manager said no that's all so I got it erm <pause dur="short"/> thirteen pounds worth of petrol but some of it was on the courtyard because as soon as the petrol hit me I dropped the pump</u>
<u n="30" who="S0392">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> so you must get some compensation for that surely?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0390">well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thinks so I'm going to write and see I don't know it's kind of in the air <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> because I get my petrol every time at the same place but I will think about compensation I'm supposed to write but I haven't done it yet</u>
<u n="32" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah we'll do that as soon as possible <pause dur="short"/> what else has happened in your week then?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0390">well you ask me that question and I always have to dive into my handbag and get my diary out because I</u>
<u n="34" who="S0392">was there nothing very memorable then that's happened?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0390">well it can't be can it?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0392">oh you must've just</u>
<u n="37" who="S0390">oh I've had a very good weekend</u>
<u n="38" who="S0392">yeah?  did you win something on the Grand National or something?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0390">no I didn't I went up to <anon type="place"/> on a course</u>
<u n="40" who="S0392">oh yeah</u>
<u n="41" who="S0390">on <anon type="place"/> and it was brilliant absolutely brilliant</u>
<u n="42" who="S0392">was it good?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0390">mm the people in the group were good and they had lots of talks lots of prayers lots of things</u>
<u n="44" who="S0392">so what sort of form did it take? did you all go there?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0390">well there were fifteen from around the country</u>
<u n="46" who="S0392">yeah what whereabouts were they from?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0390">er Norfolk London Wales erm one or two from Yorkshire and various places oh it were quite a <trunc>lad</trunc> a couple a very nice couple from Manchester <pause dur="short"/> that was we met you know in the normal meeting and greeting and talking and introducing</u>
<u n="48" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but then is it silence after that?</u>
<u n="49" who="S0390">no there was no silence we talked and we even had a bar at night</u>
<u n="50" who="S0392" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> oh in one of those rooms?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0390">yeah have you been to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0392">I have yeah</u>
<u n="53" who="S0390">have you been to the <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0392">yes</u>
<u n="55" who="S0390">that's lovely that's where the bar is just a little cupboard and you go and help yourself</u>
<u n="56" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's like a little room isn't it?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0390">well I always</u>
<u n="58" who="S0392" trans="overlap">like the size of an airing cupboard maybe</u>
<u n="59" who="S0390">airing airing cupboard plus size</u>
<u n="60" who="S0392">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0390">yeah <unclear/> it's good</u>
<u n="62" who="S0392">I wonder at <unclear/> erm the that lemonade in the fridge must've been there years though surely?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0390">oh don't I got it changed you know</u>
<u n="64" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah did you check the date before you drunk it?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0390">no I don't ever do that I opened a tin of oh I can't think what they were oh peaches the other day at home when I got home and it was two thousand and eight and it was perfect</u>
<u n="66" who="S0392" trans="overlap">peaches? oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> blimey <pause dur="short"/> how do how do you er how well have you kept it for that long without noticing it?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0390">oh I don't know don't ask me</u>
<u n="68" who="S0392">where was it?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0390">in the larder on the shelf</u>
<u n="70" who="S0392">and it had been there since two</u>
<u n="71" who="S0390"><unclear/> but</u>
<u n="72" who="S0392">blimey</u>
<u n="73" who="S0390">did I tell you a while ago I saw a programme on TV where they had found these Heinz erm Christmas puddings from Scott's Antarctic expedition? and they ate them all those sort of forty fifty years I think no sixty years later so two thousand and eight it is not going to <unclear>kill me</unclear></u>
<u n="74" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="75" who="S0390">I don't look at dates</u>
<u n="76" who="S0392">no I think people take them too seriously don't they? <pause dur="short"/>  like</u>
<u n="77" who="S0390">I suppose it's good business if I'd have thrown that tin away I would have had to buy another one</u>
<u n="78" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well the idea is it's to stop you suing them saying I got food poisoning whereas the dates so they've got to be really careful and haven't they just in case something happened?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0390">I don't know I don't I don't go into those sort of things</u>
<u n="80" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that said it will be fine it doesn't instantly overnight just turn does it?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0390">well your nose generally tells you</u>
<u n="82" who="S0392">yeah oh your eyes?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0390">er no normally it's your nose you know if it's a tin and either you are pulling it or you are putting a a tin opener in there's a <pause dur="short"/> if it's if it's off you know because it smells horribly</u>
<u n="84" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="85" who="S0390">and what have you been up to this week?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0392">erm on Monday I <pause dur="short"/> nothing in particular Tuesday well that was quite interesting I had there was I was a a bit stuck on Tuesday because I didn't know what was going to happen whether I was going to be going to the area cricket trials in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0390" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> and did you?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0392">I didn't no I had to go somewhere else instead I had to go to Ripon with the music department to pick up this violin off the lady you know sort of near Morrisons so we went there</u>
<u n="89" who="S0390" trans="overlap">eurgh <pause dur="short"/> so that was the lady <trunc>wha</trunc></u>
<u n="90" who="S0392">you know I told you about</u>
<u n="91" who="S0390">yes</u>
<u n="92" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0390">tell me again I keep forgetting</u>
<u n="94" who="S0392">well she her husband had died and she was full of this violin that he had I talked to her about how good it was and then we had to collect that off her because she was giving it to us</u>
<u n="95" who="S0390" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> mm mm <pause dur="short"/> your mum or school?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0392">no me and the music teachers so I was a bit disappointed about that really</u>
<u n="97" who="S0390">why?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0392">because I could've been at the trials and playing for the area and I'd have got a little thing for my blazer that says cricket on it still never mind</u>
<u n="99" who="S0390">ah <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> well does this mean you won't get a chance again?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0392">it means I won't be able to play for but it doesn't bother me too much I mean I can play for clubs and schools and things so that doesn't matter I'm not too bothered about that but still we went to get the instrument from the lady in <anon type="place"/> it was quite fun the the journey and everything and erm getting there and she gave us it and she really enjoyed it and we asked her to come back to the the concert in summer and there we said you can have a bowl of strawberries <unclear/> I didn't know she was allergic to strawberries and we said you can have a bowl of raspberries and cream but she's allergic to cream so she so we are just going to get her a bowl of raspberries yeah and then she gave us all the stuff so I have to sort through that and the fiddle's is <unclear/> thing</u>
<u n="101" who="S0390" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> oh dear <pause dur="short"/> oh dear well <pause dur="short"/> is it music as well?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0392">yeah there's a bit of that which I'm going to see for the orchestra which they can have and there's a music stand as well but I've left that with them a tuning fork as well that I've kept and a couple of bows as well which are handy I suppose because you can I've always been worried about one of my bows breaking <pause dur="short"/> erm so if I've got a spare that's a lot easier and then Wednesday erm just a normal Wednesday really and yesterday we had a match after school against <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="103" who="S0390" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> mm mm mm mm <pause dur="short"/> ah <pause dur="short"/> cricket?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0392">yeah but that was really disappointing because our batsman didn't really get going at the start and the wicket was really hard to bowl off because it was just like a flat bit of carpet in the middle of a field where you're running in your spikes then all of a sudden half way through your run up there's like a carpet so you have to adapt to that so it's difficult to bowl on and plus they had this one person who looked about twenty-five he was <unclear/> hammered</u>
<u n="105" who="S0390" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> was he a sixth former?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0392">no no they had to he had to be in year ten but he looked about twenty-five he just <unclear>palmed him off somewhere</unclear> and he didn't really have any skill but he just had brute force that at <unclear> our age</unclear> that's all you need really</u>
<u n="107" who="S0390">well I wouldn't have thought that brute force would've enabled you to hit the ball yes when you've actually hit it</u>
<u n="108" who="S0392">yeah well that's the thing yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0390">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0392">and there were two of us who were bowling well but the other people didn't really and one of our players didn't turn up either so if we play them as our teacher said if we play them again we'd beat them every single time after that but it was just that first time they took us by surprise with it because just like the way they played and everything it was really different</u>
<u n="111" who="S0390">well they had the advantage it was their field</u>
<u n="112" who="S0392">well you don't really find that to be honest that's not really a <unclear/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0390">but you just said it was like a piece of carpet and you had to</u>
<u n="114" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah but they but they had to play off it as well so they had the difficulty</u>
<u n="115" who="S0390">but if it was theirs they're used to it</u>
<u n="116" who="S0392">no because we have a carpet at our school and we really hate it and it you you just can't get used to it I know what you mean but it's just impossible to get used to</u>
<u n="117" who="S0390">it's not an actual carpet is it?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0392">yeah it's a carpet</u>
<u n="119" who="S0390">or is it grass? you know artificial</u>
<u n="120" who="S0392">it's well it's like a carpet of green grass</u>
<u n="121" who="S0390">artificial?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0392">yeah so it's a carpet</u>
<u n="123" who="S0390">mm mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0392">we've got one at our school and you never get used to it plus you're playing away all the time at proper pitches and with the club you playing on a proper pitch as well so</u>
<u n="125" who="S0390"><trunc>w</trunc>which club?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0392">well any club that you play for they all have proper pitches</u>
<u n="127" who="S0390">and which clubs do you play for?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0392">I haven't really decided this year because there's some people wanted me to do one and some people wanted me to do the other</u>
<u n="129" who="S0390">and so</u>
<u n="130" who="S0392">yeah and I want to do one but then I feel sorry for the other so I'm just going to have to decide</u>
<u n="131" who="S0390">you can't play for both?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0392">no they play on the same night I'm afraid</u>
<u n="133" who="S0390">oh well</u>
<u n="134" who="S0392">and then today er we were discussing what had happened last night erm just having a laugh it was good fun though like the journey and scoring and everything because you get a lot of time when you're just sitting down when you're waiting for all the people to get back which is great fun</u>
<u n="135" who="S0390">so you go on a bus? oh that's good and mum and dad pick you up at the end?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0392" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> er no the bus brings you back to school</u>
<u n="137" who="S0390">that's what I mean and then your mum and dad have to come and pick you up</u>
<u n="138" who="S0392">yeah that's it <pause dur="short"/> well no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just came and got me</u>
<u n="139" who="S0390">right</u>
<u n="140" who="S0392">there were other people saying if they wanted to drop me off but no I said it's alright well nobody it would they would have to be going out of their way really</u>
<u n="141" who="S0390"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> and there's your poor mum with a twenty-four hour virus oh what a shame shame on you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="142" who="S0392">twenty-four hours she was better by then I think it mustn't have been too bad so it must be twenty-four hours</u>
<u n="143" who="S0390" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> I met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah I I met <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in Tesco's and oh it was such a <pause dur="short"/> you know Tesco's is built for big people and if there's anything on the top shelf I can't reach it</u>
<u n="144" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> you get those little stools though don't you?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0390">you're not allowed to I once did that and they <unclear>scurried</unclear> they are only for staff</u>
<u n="146" who="S0392" trans="overlap">that's a load of rubbish <pause dur="short"/> a load of rubbish just use it</u>
<u n="147" who="S0390">yeah but then they are not always there that's what we had in libraries those sort of stools but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was there when I wanted some jam from the top shelf and I wanted yogurt from the top shelf and she was there so she just came and helped me and your grandma was there</u>
<u n="148" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yogurt from the top shelf?  I thought it was all sort of down in the fridge?</u>
<u n="149" who="S0390">no this was the on offer yogurt in one of the sort of end aisles and it was right at the top and if it's a if it's a small thing I can get it down but if it's a big thing and I have one hand it might be</u>
<u n="150" who="S0392" trans="overlap">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="151" who="S0391">how many buns this size <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0390">so there you go</u>
<u n="153" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0391">three sausages <unclear/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0390">no I haven't had any</u>
<u n="156" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">two two</u>
<u n="157" who="S0391">two?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0390">talk about yesterday oh yes</u>
<u n="159" who="S0391">two with extra <unclear/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0392">did you see the the election debate last night? the opposition one?</u>
<u n="161" who="S0390">erm which one is that?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0392">where it was all the opposition leaders I think it was clever</u>
<u n="163" who="S0390">oh you mean it was the opposition as they are now?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> I think it was clever of the the media</u>
<u n="165" who="S0390">I thought you meant that personally you saw them as the opposition</u>
<u n="166" who="S0392">no no no it's the opposition erm I I saw it erm I found it clever how the media had branded it because originally it was going to be a normal leaders debate but then Cameron and Clegg didn't want to be in it but with it being the BBC well Cameron didn't want to be in it with it being the BBC they have to give everyone their own fair share point of view so for them they had to call it the <trunc>lead</trunc> an opposition leaders debate otherwise they wouldn't have been allowed to do it</u>
<u n="167" who="S0390" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> right I understand</u>
<u n="168" who="S0391">how many sausages would you like in how many buns?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0392">er I'll do it myself</u>
<u n="170" who="S0391">oh just to give me an idea two? three?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0392">erm two yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0391">two three?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0392">two</u>
<u n="174" who="S0391">two</u>
<u n="175" who="S0390">but one bun please</u>
<u n="176" who="S0391">are you sure?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0390">and two sausages</u>
<u n="178" who="S0391">right</u>
<u n="179" who="S0392">yeah yeah that's that's me as well isn't it?</u>
<u n="180" who="S0391">no you can have two buns you're a growing man</u>
<u n="181" who="S0392">am I? okay I'll have two buns</u>
<u n="182" who="S0391">I've got plenty of them</u>
<u n="183" who="S0392">okay</u>
<u n="184" who="S0390">you think we're alright then?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0391">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you can always come back for more</u>
<u n="186" who="S0390">that's all I want <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and no coleslaw please it doesn't agree with me anymore</u>
<u n="187" who="S0391">no I haven't got any would you like an egg and some chips?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0390">oh yes</u>
<u n="189" who="S0391"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="190" who="S0392">how long will it be?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0391">er oh twenty minutes</u>
<u n="192" who="S0392">okay can I just shut? <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="sound of door closing"/> cheers</u>
<u n="193" who="S0390">do you have you were you going to have a German exam?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0392">er I had it a long time ago</u>
<u n="195" who="S0390">no it's not that long ago</u>
<u n="196" who="S0392">I told you all about it didn't I?</u>
<u n="197" who="S0390">I don't remember</u>
<u n="198" who="S0392">maybe you're thinking about that person who had a cold?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0390"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I thought in all honesty right <vocal desc="laugh"/> no I'm not I'm thinking you know there was our little group up at <anon type="place"/> and there was a big parish from somewhere over in Cheshire I can't remember the name of the place and there was a German lady and she had very she had as much English as I have German we got on really well together <pause dur="short"/> she wasn't in our group</u>
<u n="200" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> really <pause dur="short"/> so did you speak in the <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0390">oh I spoke in German to her as best as best I could no don't don't you be just don't you start I know it is not as good as yours now you are miles ahead of me but I could still make her understand it might have been grammatically incorrect</u>
<u n="202" who="S0392" trans="overlap">oh gosh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but that's all as long as it's right do you know what I mean? the words are right they can</u>
<u n="203" who="S0390">as long as they understand it</u>
<u n="204" who="S0392">yeah I mean if I said to you tomorrow I go museum to</u>
<u n="205" who="S0390"><foreign lang="ger"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0392">no if I say in English tomorrow TV I watch you know what I mean wouldn't you? say an example in German if you said like they got words of it wrong</u>
<u n="207" who="S0390">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> now what's tomorrow again?</u>
<u n="208" who="S0392">well er <foreign lang="ger"/> I think</u>
<u n="209" who="S0390"><foreign lang="ger"/></u>
<u n="210" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0390"><foreign lang="ger"/>  or no that's the Italian sorry museum I can't remember</u>
<u n="212" who="S0392">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's just museum</u>
<u n="213" who="S0390">is it?</u>
<u n="214" who="S0392">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0390">it's Latin</u>
<u n="216" who="S0392">yeah well we're preparing for our English language not English language German writing now as well so hopefully that will be done soon</u>
<u n="217" who="S0390">so do you get your GCSE this year?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0392">no they only do some of it you only do like thirty percent this year or something yeah that makes sense thirty percent</u>
<u n="219" who="S0390">I think <unclear/></u>
<u n="220" who="S0392">yeah well he sort of has an advantage doesn't he so he's er is he doing all the year early within sort of being?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0390">German something and something</u>
<u n="222" who="S0392">Latin is it?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0390">Latin</u>
<u n="224" who="S0392"><unclear>then</unclear> doing that outside school you know?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0390">no it's inside school this time <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was outside school</u>
<u n="226" who="S0392">so is it on curriculum now?</u>
<u n="227" who="S0390">mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0392">blimey <pause dur="short"/> gosh</u>
<u n="229" who="S0390">mm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0392">I think by the time it's exams next year <vocal desc="misc"/> oh by the time it's exams next year I don't think I'll be doing any that I don't have a little bit I've already done you know what I mean? apart from probably maths which is easy anyway all the other ones I've done a little percentage of which is handy I think by the end of this year I would've done a percentage of most of them I'm just thinking yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0390" trans="overlap">yes very good yes <pause dur="short"/> mm mm <pause dur="short"/> well it gets you in <pause dur="short"/> it takes the fear away</u>
<u n="232" who="S0392">well it takes a lot of the pressure away as well</u>
<u n="233" who="S0390">yeah yes <pause dur="short"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="234" who="S0392">and it makes it more you work harder as well because you know that this stuff actually counts</u>
<u n="235" who="S0390">mm I mean we just had it all in one year</u>
<u n="236" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah for biology what I'm going to have to do is just <pause dur="short"/> wait until the half term or so before and then just learn all of it really because we don't really learn much to be honest because it's all just hard <trunc>I</trunc>I've noticed a lot of people have that problem all around the</u>
<u n="237" who="S0390">with biology?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0390">do you think it's the long names for all the?</u>
<u n="240" who="S0392">I think it's just like how there's so much stuff and it's all none of it's particularly inspiring that's on the curriculum nowadays it could it could be the best subject if you did what people like because everyone's interested in animals really aren't they? everybody loves animals people are interested in seeing plants and things but when you start talking about cells and bacteria I think that people don't really</u>
<u n="241" who="S0390" trans="overlap">no it's not no <pause dur="short"/> oh yes <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> I don't think we did that</u>
<u n="242" who="S0392">I mean cells it doesn't really matter to be honest</u>
<u n="243" who="S0390">but do you do human biology?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0392">do a little bit of it but it's never the interesting subjects it's always about how nervous system works and things</u>
<u n="245" who="S0390">I would think that would be quite useful</u>
<u n="246" who="S0392">not really</u>
<u n="247" who="S0390">well it</u>
<u n="248" who="S0392">motor neurones synapses</u>
<u n="249" who="S0390" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> oh dear yes</u>
<u n="250" who="S0392">and you've got to know how everything works</u>
<u n="251" who="S0390">do they ever have these sort of multiple choice questions still?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0392">they got rid of those about four years three or four years ago yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0390">never really?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0392">it's all written now and that's the problem because if you don't quite word your answer the way it's in the mark scheme then it's a big cross you can</u>
<u n="255" who="S0390" trans="overlap">that's wrong <unclear>if that's not right then</unclear></u>
<u n="256" who="S0392">there was a question suggest reasons and I put something I'd heard in the news that morning and obviously with it not being on the mark scheme I didn't get anything for it but I'm wise to that now I just stick to</u>
<u n="257" who="S0390">that that's not education that's just sort of regurgitating</u>
<u n="258" who="S0392">well at the this level they they don't really care if you think about the kind of people that write the exams or of that they'll all they'll say ah GCSE everyone does it sort of thing</u>
<u n="259" who="S0390">well we didn't have <pause dur="short"/> oh mine was O level but we didn't have multiple choice it was all sort of writing but when I used to mark maths you had to give marks for getting so far through to the answer</u>
<u n="260" who="S0392">yeah yeah we get you get like on maths it's a bit better because you get method marks accuracy marks and result marks sort of thing</u>
<u n="261" who="S0390" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes uhu</u>
<u n="262" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="263" who="S0390">so you know you could get the wrong answer but you could get two or three marks</u>
<u n="264" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah easy <pause dur="short"/> you could get four out of five well maybe three out of five</u>
<u n="265" who="S0390" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah three out of five sounds more like it</u>
<u n="266" who="S0392">it's about the way you do it isn't it it's a bit like physics as well that out of all the sciences at this level physics is probably the easiest because they just give you the equation and it's just about putting the numbers into it</u>
<u n="267" who="S0390">mm mm mm yes I understand</u>
<u n="268" who="S0392">whereas if you're learning all sorts of things the revision guides are handy though because they tell you everything in there</u>
<u n="269" who="S0390">the revision guides or guys?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0392">yeah the they're like guides it is like a little book A4 size and it just</u>
<u n="271" who="S0390" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> do the school give you those?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0392">we have to buy them for like three pound fifty or something</u>
<u n="273" who="S0390">well that's not bad that's money well spent</u>
<u n="274" who="S0392" trans="overlap">that's not too bad <pause dur="short"/> yeah because if you're not going to learn it in class and they don't really tell you exactly what you need to learn or anything physics do and chemistry do but somehow</u>
<u n="275" who="S0390">is it so far written down so that you can just rewrite it parrot fashion?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0392">how do you mean?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0390">well when I used to do exams especially with we got one on Greek and Turkish independence I think</u>
<u n="278" who="S0392">is that history?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0390">history yes and above my head when I'm thinking I can see my exercise book and I'm just writing the answers I'm just seeing it and copying down what I see in my mind</u>
<u n="280" who="S0392">really?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0390">yes and I can see when I turn over the page is that what you do?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0392">no not at all I erm</u>
<u n="283" who="S0390">different kind of do you remember things that you hear? cos I don't</u>
<u n="284" who="S0392">yeah I can remember anything I'm quite good with facts</u>
<u n="285" who="S0390">right I'm I see when it's written down it's it's not a good photographic memory but it's part of a photographic memory which it it helps at O level but it doesn't at A level you know you've got to start thinking</u>
<u n="286" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it would help at O level now or GCSEs either to be honest the way it works there's a lot more sciences themselves have even tried to help you sort or engage with the question if you know what I mean so <pause dur="short"/> give your own opinion positives and negative things to an extent obviously the most of the questions are</u>
<u n="287" who="S0390" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> well in that case if they're asking your opinion something you had read in the paper that day</u>
<u n="288" who="S0392">then it would get on that one yeah but on other ones if it was erm something I think it was something about statins or something <unclear/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0390" trans="overlap">it would it would <pause dur="short"/> oh right well yes that was facts they wanted</u>
<u n="290" who="S0392">give give two reasons why er some people don't want you to have them then they wanted to two hard facts and then I said that something about effectiveness that had come out in the news that morning that it wasn't too effective or something <pause dur="short"/> it was something <trunc>I</trunc><trunc>I</trunc>I don't really I can't remember really what it was</u>
<u n="291" who="S0390">right right <pause dur="short"/> do they tell you your results?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0392">yeah yeah you get told your results</u>
<u n="293" who="S0390">so you know</u>
<u n="294" who="S0392">what what do you mean?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0390">well how many marks you have got? how many percentages? you know if you've got a paper and it's going to count</u>
<u n="296" who="S0392">oh yeah all the papers you do those at the end of year eleven so</u>
<u n="297" who="S0390">yeah I know that but the things that you're doing now they count a certain percentage towards your final mark</u>
<u n="298" who="S0392">not on the papers and things that's only little essays that you write controlled assessments only they count</u>
<u n="299" who="S0390">okay</u>
<u n="300" who="S0392">we've only done about we've only done two things that count so far three things</u>
<u n="301" who="S0390" trans="overlap">well what were you telling me you got a hundred percent in? was it German?</u>
<u n="302" who="S0392">well I've got a hundred percent in everything so far</u>
<u n="303" who="S0390">oh dear I don't think I'd bother go back to school if I was you</u>
<u n="304" who="S0392"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> no so far we've done two English but I've only got the results for one of them a a German and a physics</u>
<u n="305" who="S0390">hang on what was the English? language or literature?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0392">er language but it was more like literature really what we're doing now is more like language and then the other one was literature so</u>
<u n="307" who="S0390">what is it? do you do a Shakespeare play?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0392">we've done a we've done that already you only do one</u>
<u n="309" who="S0390" trans="overlap">what was it?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0392">we did comparing Macbeth and Richard the third</u>
<u n="311" who="S0390">ah Macbeth is my one of my favourites</u>
<u n="312" who="S0392">I like Richard it's brilliant</u>
<u n="313" who="S0390">I like Richard the second</u>
<u n="314" who="S0392">oh yeah?  was that a play?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0390">well hang on is it the one with <unclear>time</unclear> old John O Gaunt <unclear/> Lancaster <unclear>has thou according to thine oath and band brought hither Henry Hereford</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0392">no that sounds that doesn't sound like what we're doing</u>
<u n="317" who="S0390">right so it's it's Richard the second I'm talking about because we had that for ours where you could there was there was you could choose and about six of us chose Richard the second and I think the other one was a sort of flowery</u>
<u n="318" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> like Othello or something?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0390">no it wasn't Othello erm and it wasn't Midsummer Nights Dream</u>
<u n="320" who="S0392">Romeo and Juliet?</u>
<u n="321" who="S0390">it could've been but I know it didn't appeal to me so I did Richard the second</u>
<u n="322" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> richard the third's really funny it some people call it a history like with it <unclear/> some people call it a tragedy with him dying at the end some people well no one calls it a comedy but it should be really because it's really funny in places some good puns in it</u>
<u n="323" who="S0390" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> is that the one with <unclear> crook back Nicky Dicky your son</unclear>?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0392">it could be it's now is the winter of our discontent</u>
<u n="325" who="S0390" trans="overlap">of our discontent</u>
<u n="326" who="S0392">but people think</u>
<u n="327" who="S0390" trans="overlap">made glorious by the son of York</u>
<u n="328" who="S0392">people think that now is the winter of our discontent is about like erm how it's the winter and everything's dark when actually if you read the full bit it it is saying now is this winter of this discontent being made glorious by</u>
<u n="329" who="S0390" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> being brought by this son of York</u>
<u n="330" who="S0392">and then that's a pun sun like the sunlight as the sun but it's the son of York so that's one pun there's loads of other ones as well</u>
<u n="331" who="S0390" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> I'd forgotten all that we used to do a Shakespeare play every year</u>
<u n="332" who="S0392">we only do one but it counts as twenty-five percent so that's a whole quarter done already</u>
<u n="333" who="S0390">well hang on did you not do them in your <trunc>fir</trunc> I say first year you say year seven?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0390">did you not do a <trunc>Shake</trunc>?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0392">no</u>
<u n="337" who="S0390">because we did As You Like It</u>
<u n="338" who="S0392" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> oh I like As You Like It I've seen that but I think we did one before maybe a little bit yeah we did a little bit of the Tempest in year eight which is second year</u>
<u n="339" who="S0390" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> have you have you been to the theatre when Shakespeare's on?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0392">I've seen As You Like It I'd like to see Richard though because it's so like</u>
<u n="341" who="S0390">I think it's good if you can see the one you're actually studying</u>
<u n="342" who="S0392">yeah if you if you know the story of it yeah</u>
<u n="343" who="S0390">mm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0392">we did a little bit of Twelfth Night last year as well which is quite fun</u>
<u n="345" who="S0390">brilliant <pause dur="short"/> well our <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he was only in year eight and he played Maria the <unclear>maid</unclear></u>
<u n="346" who="S0392">did he?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0390">I can remember <unclear>Cross Garcet</unclear></u>
<u n="348" who="S0392">oh that's in Twelfth Night</u>
<u n="349" who="S0390" trans="overlap">that's in <pause dur="short"/> twelfth Night yes erm</u>
<u n="350" who="S0392"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is one of them called?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0390">pardon?</u>
<u n="352" who="S0392">there's one called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yeah and then erm it is music with the food of love and then play on yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0390" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> mm mm <pause dur="short"/> and give me excess of this <pause dur="short"/> wow it's sixty years since I did that</u>
<u n="354" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I can't get over how we've already done it and it was just one little a couple of pages essay and it counts as twenty-five percent that's what struck me</u>
<u n="355" who="S0390">well that means it's got to be succinct you've got to get</u>
<u n="356" who="S0392">yeah we're only allowed four sides er four to six sides most of us did six sides</u>
<u n="357" who="S0390">well I don't think that that's very fair because a smaller writer can get so much more</u>
<u n="358" who="S0392">ah no no  that that was a guideline it wasn't really size of writing sort of thing if you'd written big then she'd of understood if you've gone over a bit more it was words really as a guide</u>
<u n="359" who="S0390">it was it was a word count in an undergraduate essay you are never allowed more than two thousand words I think I'm not sure but at one time it was that it was eight sides in handwriting</u>
<u n="360" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> what we've moved onto now is a lot more sort of language orientated so it's more looking at the way language works and collecting samples of text messages and things and thinking of</u>
<u n="361" who="S0390">it must've changed it must have how do you youngsters manage to spell things correctly when they're using text speak all the time?</u>
<u n="362" who="S0392" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> they're not though people never use text speak anymore that's what the what's what the investigation's into because it was written a lot of years ago like five years ago so when people did it absolutely nonstop but nowadays your phones most phones have got a full qwerty keyboard out you're not these days you're not you pay you've got a contract so it doesn't matter how many characters you use and if you spell something wrong like you miss out a letter it corrects it for you</u>
<u n="363" who="S0390" trans="overlap">really?<pause dur="short"/>  it's almost like a spellchecker on the computer</u>
<u n="364" who="S0392">yeah so nowadays</u>
<u n="365" who="S0390">very very good because the phone I've got when I text your mum it's always you know text speak as much as I can manage</u>
<u n="366" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah and if you write the letter u like for you it'll think you mean a like a the article if you're doing like a single vowel by itself so it will print you to a so it's a lot more easy just to type Y O U and have to go back and correct it</u>
<u n="367" who="S0390" trans="overlap">well if you've got that little keyboard</u>
<u n="368" who="S0392">just with your finger like just a little keyboard yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0390">mm mm whereas you know you've got to with my twelve year old phone</u>
<u n="370" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah<pause dur="short"/> well people still have those now</u>
<u n="371" who="S0390">I still use it</u>
<u n="372" who="S0392">yeah I know someone I know a lot of people who still use sort of ones with er one two three number layout</u>
<u n="373" who="S0390">mm mm</u>
<u n="374" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="375" who="S0390">and you put number four for for when you're saying for this for that and <unclear/></u>
<u n="376" who="S0392" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I'm I'm trying to remember what you call that it's something like a homophonic representation or something we've got to learn all the terms that people use so I think it's over <unclear> lexicalisation</unclear> or something is where if you say you know like when people go yeah and spell it Y Y Y E E E A A A A A H H H H H exclamation mark exclamation mark exclamation mark like that like when they really do you know I reckon we got</u>
<u n="377" who="S0390" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> no <pause dur="short"/> for yay I will put Y A H</u>
<u n="378" who="S0392">you know if you go I'm so tired they put loads of Os after it you know what I mean?  have you come across that before?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0390">no</u>
<u n="380" who="S0392">ah well some people do that if you put like if you want to show that you're screaming like ah you've got a load of As and loads of Rs Gs and Hs</u>
<u n="381" who="S0390">ah I would put A A A no just put ah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0392">because no if you it's like you're pretending to scream that sort of that's what you call an over <unclear>lexicalisation</unclear> and the whole idea of the task is to pretend er look at the ways that people try and recreate spoken language within written modern communications</u>
<u n="383" who="S0390" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> now you've just used another word I wouldn't I I know what it means by the context <unclear>lexicalisation</unclear></u>
<u n="384" who="S0392">over <unclear>lexicalisation</unclear> yeah so you're using over lexis more letters then you've got to we use things like <unclear>hedges off</unclear> which I think is where people sort <pause dur="short"/> oh what is that one or is it softeners? where you have things like maybe or to be honest or something to to make it sound like if you just said could I borrow your thing? then that's obviously a bit more harsh than please could I that would it be okay if I borrow or would it be okay if I</u>
<u n="385" who="S0390" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes yes mm mm <pause dur="short"/> is that to? well you would normally say please may I? <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> do you think I could possibly?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0392">yeah it's softening it</u>
<u n="387" who="S0390">mm</u>
<u n="388" who="S0392">and then you get the brevity measure brevity techniques which is where you keep things short like instead of because <unclear>cos</unclear></u>
<u n="389" who="S0390" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes and yes I understand mm great G R good G D</u>
<u n="390" who="S0392">that's not that's not so common nowadays it was though before</u>
<u n="391" who="S0390">oh I'm getting old you are making me feel old ah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0392" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> however things like lol laugh out loud</u>
<u n="393" who="S0390">laugh out oh</u>
<u n="394" who="S0392">yeah that's become a word really so people still use that as a word as in that's funny but not funny in a</u>
<u n="395" who="S0390">I didn't know that laugh out loud</u>
<u n="396" who="S0392">if something's if you want to show that you're laughing you can't laugh through a text message so you put a ha or a lol or a <trunc>sm</trunc> a little smiley face have you seen those little smiley faces?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0390" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> I've seen that lol <pause dur="short"/> yeah oh a smiley face?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0392">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0390">yes</u>
<u n="400" who="S0392">that was the problem with when David Cameron was sending text messages to Rebekah Brooks remember in the phone hacking scandal he put a lol thinking it was lots of love but it it turns out to be laugh out loud</u>
<u n="401" who="S0390" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> that's what I was when you were saying laugh out loud I was thinking that's not what I understand and my brain hadn't quite picked it up</u>
<u n="402" who="S0392" trans="overlap">but he thought it meant <pause dur="short"/> but he thought it meant lots of love so the messages he was putting lol David Cameron but if people who know it means laugh out loud what he's written before that became really ironic and funny thinking that he was putting laugh out loud at that</u>
<u n="403" who="S0391"><unclear/></u>
<u n="404" who="S0392">well we will have to go through now so</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
