<text id="SQ9R">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:58:38</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-02-09</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0607 S0644</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>in the car travelling in America on holiday</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Planning next few months; getting rid of possessions; doing too much; a theory of life.</topics>
		<activity>Car journey conversation about plans, tidying and doing too much</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, advising, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0607">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Pembury, England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern/ 'BBC' English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Battle</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 month</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Translator/Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Italian -- level unspecified; French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0644">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>English/British</nat>
				<birthplace>Enfield, UK</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>London/ South-East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>36 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Office worker (temp)</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Brazilian Portuguese -- basic</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0607">damn we just missed that <anon type="place"/> how many miles I was like looking and going? oh Smith River Brookings Portland oh I missed it erm okay</u>
<u n="2" who="S0644">I can't believe we're seeing signs for Portland</u>
<u n="3" who="S0607">look at this this is really great this road <pause dur="short"/> this is accidentally more trees</u>
<u n="4" who="S0644">aren't we sort of coming back a little bit like where we were though? I thought we were sort of having to go back to where we were to get back on the motorway</u>
<u n="5" who="S0607">well it doesn't feel like that does it?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0644">dunno</u>
<u n="7" who="S0607">it feels a bit like we're on a totally different road I wonder if we're on the right road</u>
<u n="8" who="S0644">oh smell the trees</u>
<u n="9" who="S0607" trans="overlap">oh it must be because it said Portland</u>
<u n="10" who="S0644"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0607"><vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0644">so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0607">so</u>
<u n="14" who="S0644">tell me about this potential trip you might be going on in Wales</u>
<u n="15" who="S0607">okay so there are two strands to the dilemma er it's all wonderful I just have to work it out because I can I just say it's a whole topic how</u>
<u n="16" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0607">sometimes I organise everything all wrong and it's all a stress and it's</u>
<u n="18" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0607">my own fault</u>
<u n="20" who="S0644">right</u>
<u n="21" who="S0607">you know when you're like why would I do that? like why did I organise to like go and babysit for two toddlers one day after we get back from America? you know that kind of thing er <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="22" who="S0644">I don't you don't really do you really do things like that? because it's</u>
<u n="23" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah in a rush</u>
<u n="24" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I I do think you sort of know</u>
<u n="25" who="S0607" trans="overlap">because of my own fault</u>
<u n="26" who="S0644">that you will not be up for things like that</u>
<u n="27" who="S0607">well that's kind of like a dumb example but I do end up in situations</u>
<u n="28" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I know what you're saying though</u>
<u n="29" who="S0607">where I'm like <trunc>ha</trunc> why did I not realise that wouldn't wanna do this?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="31" who="S0607">erm and now it's my own fault</u>
<u n="32" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0607" trans="overlap">and I can't not do it</u>
<u n="34" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0607">erm so there's two strands quite hard to remain in the normal like speech mode <unclear>after America</unclear></u>
<u n="36" who="S0644" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="37" who="S0607">erm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0644">it is hard</u>
<u n="39" who="S0607">it is hard cos it makes everything <unclear/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I see what you</u>
<u n="41" who="S0607">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0644">it does</u>
<u n="43" who="S0607">by the way this road is so fabulous</u>
<u n="44" who="S0644">it's good innit?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0607">erm so on the one hand <pause dur="short"/> there's three strands actually I know it's gonna get excruciatingly boring</u>
<u n="46" who="S0644">it's alright</u>
<u n="47" who="S0607">so the first thing is Denmark so wanna go to Denmark do the erm <pause dur="short"/> volunteering I was gonna go in July or August preferably August <pause dur="short"/> erm now the one the best one is now of course booked for July and August</u>
<u n="48" who="S0644">of course</u>
<u n="49" who="S0607">now I know it's complicated but so there's two things one is desperately wanna go for that one so I'm gonna have to go another month or find a different one that might not be as good people</u>
<u n="50" who="S0644">right</u>
<u n="51" who="S0607">and the others problem with that is that I know it's complicated and annoying but not sure I wanna do it in September because what if I do end up deciding to go and do that writing course in Cornwall? it starts in September and that's one of those things that you don't wanna do to yourself</u>
<u n="52" who="S0644">is it the masters?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0607">yeah which we don't know if I'm gonna do that that's a whole other topic like what will I do about writing?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0607" trans="overlap">whether I'll just write or do a smaller course all that that's the biggest course</u>
<u n="56" who="S0644">right right</u>
<u n="57" who="S0607">so if I wanted to do that I I would wanna be preparing for that because it would start like third week of September and I don't wanna be in Denmark then so I think September is out which leaves going in May or June to Denmark to the people who are still the <trunc>b</trunc> so the people who are the best people</u>
<u n="58" who="S0644">uhu</u>
<u n="59" who="S0607">can you believe that these are the only options left? erm or going to someone else</u>
<u n="60" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="61" who="S0607">and sticking with the month that I wanted now I do tend to get glued to to an idea and think that nothing else can be right</u>
<u n="62" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="63" who="S0607">so you know I wanted those people</u>
<u n="64" who="S0644" trans="overlap">and it could be an exercise in flexibility and adaptability</u>
<u n="65" who="S0607">yeah if I want to choose someone else I should possibly even though we're away and it's annoying like next time I'm laid in bed with wi-fi I should possibly check out the other people because they might also get booked up I think my favourite people <unclear>have got picked up</unclear> cos they sound so fabulous erm so maybe it is best with the with the Denmark thing because I don't really okay so there's June there's June right?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0607" trans="overlap">that's not too bad</u>
<u n="68" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="69" who="S0607">but just to explain the logic I kind of wanted to like fixate on the house-sitting until like maybe mid-July</u>
<u n="70" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="71" who="S0607">and then in the summer I wanted to be either by the sea a bit by the sea so either if there's a house in Cornwall or even like living at my mum and dad's because it's by the sea and hanging out</u>
<u n="72" who="S0644" trans="overlap">uhu mm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0607" trans="overlap">and like going to the beach and stuff</u>
<u n="74" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="75" who="S0607">or being hang on one nine seven</u>
<u n="76" who="S0644">er?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0607">oh is it just a junction? <unclear>one nine seven</unclear> erm I just wanted to do the house-sitting thing until like June Julyish and then have the summer like volunteering or beach stuff</u>
<u n="78" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="79" who="S0607">I didn't really want volunteering to start already at the beginning of June but maybe that's too rigid because what I could do is no you see I just feel like it's too <trunc>ear</trunc> cos I was thinking I was gonna maybe do a month in Denmark do two weeks at the café and two weeks on a farm</u>
<u n="80" who="S0644">right</u>
<u n="81" who="S0607">erm so</u>
<u n="82" who="S0644">would that</u>
<u n="83" who="S0607">it's</u>
<u n="84" who="S0644" trans="overlap">coincide?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0607">well you see if I wanted to do the <trunc>peo</trunc> if I was still fixated on the people that I wanted</u>
<u n="86" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="87" who="S0607">erm <pause dur="short"/> then I'd have to try and cos the it looks like in June they've got one place left so I'd have I'd have to like that's when the Wales thing comes into play so Wales is the twentieth till the twenty-ninth of June so I'd have to go to Denmark either only for three weeks like the first bit of June come back and go straight to Wales or set off to Denmark in May like the last week of May but then it's getting too soon and I know it sounds fussy but you know you've been saying like how you just know stuff?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0607">I feel like May is too soon I don't wanna already be going to Denmark in May <pause dur="short"/> it's just what I don't want I just wanna just want there to be several months stretching off into the distance so potentially house-sitting or you know being a floater</u>
<u n="90" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0607">erm so just floating around and like I'm not I'm trying not to say the word bum but you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="93" who="S0607">so I just don't wanna go</u>
<u n="94" who="S0644">dosser</u>
<u n="95" who="S0607">oh I'm gonna have to go May because there's Wales and then <vocal desc="misc"/> so maybe what I should do is maybe er I have talked myself into the answer which is</u>
<u n="96" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="97" who="S0607">do the Wales thing because I did wanna go to Wales and it's June so that and it's near the sea</u>
<u n="98" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0607">and then pick another Denmark er volunteering for July or August do you think?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0644" trans="overlap">or what oh yeah and you can't do September cos it might be they <trunc>g</trunc></u>
<u n="101" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="102" who="S0644">but the September <trunc>op</trunc> yeah you don't wanna mess them about I was gonna say could book <unclear/> and then if you change your mind about the course do that but er you don't wanna mess them about so yeah I would just do as little as possible really</u>
<u n="103" who="S0607">and also er sorry it's boring but</u>
<u n="104" who="S0644">no go on</u>
<u n="105" who="S0607" trans="overlap">also <pause dur="short"/> oh man oh man</u>
<u n="106" who="S0644">oh man <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0607">that was one of those where I wasn't really sure how near I was do you know did you feel near?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0644">erm that's the nearest I've felt to anything on this road cos</u>
<u n="109" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0644">it's so huge and like</u>
<u n="111" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and then the other thing is I've got this other disease going on which is like no it's not as strong as a disease but it's where things have been coming up for like July or August and I've been going yeah I just can't <trunc>con</trunc> I mean I just can't commit that far you know I just can't no no no no and it's because I've just got this feeling that I wanna be by the sea in July and August because and so for example a house-sit might come up in like there's been things coming up in like somewhere else</u>
<u n="112" who="S0644">mm mm</u>
<u n="113" who="S0607">and I've thought no no and it and I think it's partly because of the whole like don't wanna book myself up</u>
<u n="114" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0607">because by the summer I might wanna float around</u>
<u n="116" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="117" who="S0607">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0644" trans="overlap">now <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> this is what I was saying to you</u>
<u n="119" who="S0607" trans="overlap">but <unclear/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0644">erm let me just tell you what is your it's the habit you've got of being organised and booked and everything's organised and trying to fit everything in</u>
<u n="121" who="S0607">it's actually a <unclear>right</unclear> thing</u>
<u n="122" who="S0644" trans="overlap">it's a habit and you're it's but habits don't just die you have to work at it so you sort like are in limbo where you attempted to do all this booking and arranging and organising but really you know now that that don't work always for you</u>
<u n="123" who="S0607">oh I wanted to get down it didn't tell me I went down</u>
<u n="124" who="S0644">it did</u>
<u n="125" who="S0607" trans="overlap">anyway <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0644">didn't it? to forty-five? erm don't you love these trucks?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0644" trans="overlap">the <unclear>cab cars</unclear> so yeah I just think at least you're finally paying attention to yourself</u>
<u n="129" who="S0607">yes</u>
<u n="130" who="S0644">by saying actually I don't really wanna book everything four months five months six months in advance</u>
<u n="131" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0644">cos it might not work like that can I just give you an example? sorry to have to interject</u>
<u n="133" who="S0607">no it's brilliant</u>
<u n="134" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I mean then I'll let you get back so I dunno if you remember I used to be a lot more like that as in erm I've just gotta go here and I've just gotta do this and then I'm gonna do this and then I do this and then I go there and then I'm gonna do this</u>
<u n="135" who="S0607"><trunc>ye</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0644" trans="overlap">and I don't do that at all any more or</u>
<u n="137" who="S0607" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0644">yeah and it's</u>
<u n="139" who="S0607" trans="overlap"><trunc>becau</trunc></u>
<u n="140" who="S0644">it's really good</u>
<u n="141" who="S0607" trans="overlap">do you mean you don't plan it?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0644">no I mean even in the space of a weekend I'd I'd be talking to somebody and I'd go oh I'll pop in and see you on the way back and then I'd say well I'm just gonna go and see so and so as well on the way back cos I said no reason like I just said I'd I'd do all these things it was silly <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="143" who="S0607">go on dude go on go on <pause dur="short"/> and they don't go past when you're trying to get them to go past</u>
<u n="144" who="S0644">they can see what you're trying to do surely</u>
<u n="145" who="S0607">I didn't wanna go over that line either but we did okay anyway yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0644">just just for example erm say not so much last year but the year when I was going out with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so and I I'd got involved I used to not help <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a lot but one I there were times when she needed some help and I was trying to do what I could erm so I'd say yeah but I'll I'll give you a lift here or I'll do this and I'd be trying to see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I'd try and do aunt <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s at the weekend and I'd be at work and I'd wanna go and see my mum and I'd wanna go and see my dad and I'd wanna see whoever</u>
<u n="147" who="S0607">oh man it's so stressful</u>
<u n="148" who="S0644" trans="overlap">and then there was somehow I got involved and there was this this animal sanctuary it's a whole different topic and I got involved in helping them out a little bit</u>
<u n="149" who="S0607">you're helping too many people</u>
<u n="150" who="S0644">it <trunc>wa</trunc> in the end it was <unclear/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0607" trans="overlap">for you <unclear/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0644" trans="overlap">there <trunc>w</trunc> no spare time</u>
<u n="153" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0644">at all now I don't do anything</u>
<u n="155" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0644">because it slowly dropped er</u>
<u n="157" who="S0607">they can all just go and</u>
<u n="158" who="S0644" trans="overlap">it all just went</u>
<u n="159" who="S0607">they can all just go and like suffer and struggle alone</u>
<u n="160" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0607">no but it's true like you can't help so many many people</u>
<u n="162" who="S0644" trans="overlap">but it crept up it crept up</u>
<u n="163" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="164" who="S0644">but slowly slowly slowly things were dropping off and now I've realised I actually don't have anything to do a lot of the time and it's really good but whereas I would have filled it up before with stuff</u>
<u n="165" who="S0607" trans="overlap">but also you were totally obligated then cos you'd like arranged to help people</u>
<u n="166" who="S0644">well each of the things and they they still are each of the things were things that I could never really not do like my aunt <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s shopping and help with my aunt <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I have to do that erm the animal people I felt really bad about that cos if I wasn't doing it then who was <trunc>help</trunc>? that's a whole other topic I won't get into it erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> of course I wanted to help her where I could do like cos she couldn't drive the last</u>
<u n="167" who="S0607">ah</u>
<u n="168" who="S0644" trans="overlap">six months</u>
<u n="169" who="S0607">okay</u>
<u n="170" who="S0644">she wasn't allowed to drive cos she was she was ill so not that I did a lot by any stretch but I used to occasionally give her a lift and get</u>
<u n="171" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="172" who="S0644">get something for her or do whatever erm</u>
<u n="173" who="S0607">oh so</u>
<u n="174" who="S0644" trans="overlap">and it was constant though</u>
<u n="175" who="S0607" trans="overlap">so good</u>
<u n="176" who="S0644">it was but I'm not complaining obviously I'm just saying how if you've got this you're like a magnet right? and if you it just attracts some more so if you've already got this momentum going on this is the theory of everything if you've already got this momentum going on where you're looking for things to do helping people out trying to help here trying to do this trying to do this and your thing is organising innit and booking and trying to fit in as much and</u>
<u n="177" who="S0607" trans="overlap">and researching to the nth degree like</u>
<u n="178" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0607">any potential like anything check it</u>
<u n="180" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0607">you know how I said to you one day <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh I've just remembered there's no reception on this stretch of the highway <vocal desc="laugh"/> and you were like</u>
<u n="182" who="S0644">well I heard it but I couldn't believe I'd heard it</u>
<u n="183" who="S0607">oh my goodness is that a hotel? no</u>
<u n="184" who="S0644" trans="overlap">it's a museum</u>
<u n="185" who="S0607">it's a museum</u>
<u n="186" who="S0644">still pretty good innit?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0607">but is there a is there a hotel that's a <unclear>boat</unclear>?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0644">oh they're</u>
<u n="189" who="S0607" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="190" who="S0644">all <trunc>li</trunc> <trunc>ch</trunc> er chalets</u>
<u n="191" who="S0607">chalets oh by the way</u>
<u n="192" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0607" trans="overlap">if I bought a chalet I could buy one outright in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0644">yeah? really?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0607">yeah they're really cheap erm in fact</u>
<u n="196" who="S0644">and then you can rent out</u>
<u n="197" who="S0607" trans="overlap">which this one is like twenty-seven thousand it's like but I was thinking there must be something wrong with getting one like</u>
<u n="198" who="S0644" trans="overlap">you've gotta pay ground rent and you've gotta pay</u>
<u n="199" who="S0607">and it's probably not gonna go up in value like an actual property is it? it's not like</u>
<u n="200" who="S0644">I think they do a little bit</u>
<u n="201" who="S0607">but the other <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="202" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="203" who="S0607">and the other problem is that I then wouldn't be like gradually you know cos if I get a mortgage and get a proper one it's gradually paying itself off isn't it? and erm you're getting more of the money whereas if you just buy that one outright what are you doing with your money then?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0607"><unclear/> Brookings eight miles? Brookings is already here</u>
<u n="206" who="S0644">see everything's pretty close innit really?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0607">I can't can't believe it I mean I can't believe it</u>
<u n="208" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0607">sorry must be <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> so er yeah er organising and like preparing</u>
<u n="210" who="S0644">do you remember that film?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0607" trans="overlap">knowing everything</u>
<u n="212" who="S0644">Along Came Polly?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0607">yes oh god please don't talk to me about things like that</u>
<u n="214" who="S0644">what?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0607">because I'm not like her</u>
<u n="216" who="S0644">not her no you're more like the <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0607">now I'm <trunc>gon</trunc> now I'm gonna seriously kill you</u>
<u n="218" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you <trunc>r</trunc> you remember looked into everything?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0607">yes but the thing is I'm attracted to her character</u>
<u n="220" who="S0644">well he was as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0607" trans="overlap">you know I used to think I'm gonna be like her</u>
<u n="222" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0607">but okay this is actually a topic how far can you move from your natural? so I think there's a natural innate thing going on and then</u>
<u n="224" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="225" who="S0607">there's you making it worse so</u>
<u n="226" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0607">I think I think you can <trunc>t</trunc><trunc>t</trunc>teach yourself this is so fabulous to a certain extent</u>
<u n="228" who="S0644"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="229" who="S0607">I think you can</u>
<u n="230" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0607">teach yourself</u>
<u n="232" who="S0644">you completely can</u>
<u n="233" who="S0607">erm but you <trunc>ca</trunc> I don't think that you can go against your nature inherently so like for example when I was changing my career and I read that book do what you are</u>
<u n="234" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="235" who="S0607">and it's like I'm naturally good at this that and the other</u>
<u n="236" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0607">I can't suddenly be good at basically what we were doing in <anon type="place"/> couldn't do that and that was totally working</u>
<u n="238" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0607">against my natural</u>
<u n="240" who="S0644">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0607" trans="overlap">abilities and I think it is the same with your personality it's just that you can there are there's a scale that you're on</u>
<u n="242" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0607">and you can get er the worst end or the better end but I don't think you can become your scale you can't just change your whole nature completely</u>
<u n="244" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0607">so I could get to the other end of my scale towards Along Came Polly but I don't think I could end up exactly like her cos I'm not on her I'm not on the same scale as her do you see what I mean?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0644">I do <trunc>t</trunc> completely see what you mean but can I tell you the theory of everything?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0607">yes</u>
<u n="248" who="S0644">so</u>
<u n="249" who="S0607">by the way is it really called the theory of everything?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0644">no</u>
<u n="251" who="S0607">or was it you that call it that?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0644" trans="overlap">that's me that's calling it the theory of everything</u>
<u n="253" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0644">which is not really any I could right we'll call it vibrations theory</u>
<u n="255" who="S0607">yes</u>
<u n="256" who="S0644">so erm <pause dur="short"/> anything any time right so there's the you that's the physical you and then there's the you that's the non-physical you that's the</u>
<u n="257" who="S0607">the weirdo</u>
<u n="258" who="S0644">no no no the erm well yeah er in religious terms the it's a soul your soul</u>
<u n="259" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0644">erm and it's very complicated so I won't go into it too much but and then there's the <pause dur="short"/> so flat the horizon innit? so straight</u>
<u n="261" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="262" who="S0644">erm yeah and then there's the physical you like the actual tangible you</u>
<u n="263" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0644">but there's also the non-physical you right? now the non-physical you is always perfect and perfectly happy and ecstatic and everything's just ticking along nicely and what happens is</u>
<u n="265" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0644">when you have erm something wrong the physical you goes oh I don't like that but the non-physical you goes oh I prefer this and it becomes this do you see?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0607">no I don't</u>
<u n="268" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="269" who="S0607">you have to explain again</u>
<u n="270" who="S0644">it's really difficult to explain but basically</u>
<u n="271" who="S0607" trans="overlap">is there is there any is there an example?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0644">er</u>
<u n="273" who="S0607" trans="overlap">welcome to Oregon</u>
<u n="274" who="S0644">we in Oregon?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0607">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="276" who="S0644">that was quick</u>
<u n="277" who="S0607">it's a shame I couldn't stop and get you to take a picture</u>
<u n="278" who="S0644"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0607">did you see did it say State Line?</u>
<u n="280" who="S0644">er</u>
<u n="281" who="S0607">damn it</u>
<u n="282" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I didn't see a State Line</u>
<u n="283" who="S0607">in my imagination it's</u>
<u n="284" who="S0644" trans="overlap">State Line road</u>
<u n="285" who="S0607">oh man Oregon</u>
<u n="286" who="S0644" trans="overlap">State Line road</u>
<u n="287" who="S0607">I'm throw can you throw that California book out the window? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0644">shall I?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0607">I know you won't let me I've got to leave it in the motel</u>
<u n="290" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="291" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0644">we honour veterans that's good don't litter that's right</u>
<u n="293" who="S0607">actually one of the hotels throws desperately trying to research earlier and pick one but couldn't cos each one had good and bad things erm</u>
<u n="294" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="295" who="S0607">one of them a guy had said oh they gave me a veteran discount thanks for that</u>
<u n="296" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="297" who="S0607">thirty-four miles Gold Beach okay so we're either going to Gold Beach</u>
<u n="298" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="299" who="S0607">or we're going to Port Orford gut choice now erm so yeah anyway have you got an example?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0644">erm</u>
<u n="301" who="S0607">or or just try and explain it again otherwise</u>
<u n="302" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> right <pause dur="short"/> so there's this <pause dur="short"/> imagine you looking in the mirror right?</u>
<u n="303" who="S0607">that's bad</u>
<u n="304" who="S0644" trans="overlap">not that mirror this morning</u>
<u n="305" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> in the mirror is the real you like the perfect happy you</u>
<u n="307" who="S0607">that doesn't sound normal to me though <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="309" who="S0607">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0644">and you have in your er experience of going through life they'll call it contrast right? so the contrast choose gets you to decide what you do like so there's the something so for example erm Frankfurt very erm fast paced hardworking conformist and the experience of that has not made you go yes I'm gonna be hardworking driven conformist work as hard as I possibly can for as many hours as I possibly</u>
<u n="311" who="S0607" trans="overlap">I don't I don't want that</u>
<u n="312" who="S0644">it's gone I don't like this now if you had gone straightaway</u>
<u n="313" who="S0607" trans="overlap">that's the busy part of you</u>
<u n="314" who="S0644">yeah cos you're the one that's having the the experience now so as soon as you've gone I don't like this <pause dur="short"/> the non-physical you goes what I do like is to be more relaxed I like to be more</u>
<u n="315" who="S0607" trans="overlap">ah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="316" who="S0644" trans="overlap">erm enjoying everything not feeling so under pressure and it becomes that straightaway now if you decide to to do that as well then you you can do that</u>
<u n="317" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0644">but erm what often happens what we often do is instead of just going yeah I'm not gonna do that anymore I'm gonna do this we go concentrate on the I don't like it here it's really it's not me it's horrible here I'm not enjoying myself I'm not enjoying myself it's really awful I don't like it what am I gonna do? and then it's just gonna get worse and it's just gonna get worse and it's just gonna get worse</u>
<u n="319" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0644">now this sounds very simple doesn't it? and</u>
<u n="321" who="S0607" trans="overlap">and that which which you is that doing that?</u>
<u n="322" who="S0644">that's the physical you erm <pause dur="short"/> but occasionally and depending on what type of thoughts you what type of person or thought patterns you're used to having some people just go bollocks don't like this I'm off</u>
<u n="323" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0644">and and they'll not worry about it but then a different person not using you as an example but another type of person might go well I've got this fantastic job and I really ought to stay because that's what everyone else tells me I should do and everyone says that you've gotta the more money you're earning the better off you are and the the harder you're working the more money you're gonna earn and then it's it's just the way life is it's just how it is but another person might go well no er I'm gonna do what I like I can do whatever I want to it's my life and I can I can change it if I want to</u>
<u n="325" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0644">so basically that's the spectrum</u>
<u n="327" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="328" who="S0644">that you're talking about and there's the you and if you're a negative person then that person is always gonna veer upon the negative it's it's so interesting and it's so hugely massive I can't tell you all the examples in one go anyway if it's launched into a monologue so we're now gonna go back to your thing but I I get it what you're saying about the whole</u>
<u n="329" who="S0607" trans="overlap">what was my thing?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0644" trans="overlap">spectrum of of I can be a bit like this or I can be less like this</u>
<u n="331" who="S0607" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0644">but the the moral of the story of that was if you don't like something you can completely change it</u>
<u n="333" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="334" who="S0644">and the thing that says you can't that's your personality it's wrong it's not  your personality if it makes you not happy</u>
<u n="335" who="S0607">but do you think that it it's actually possible for me to become an Along Came Polly?</u>
<u n="336" who="S0644">yes it's neurological linguistic programming is the technical term <pause dur="short"/> you really could <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> if you had like a few weeks with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she could change your thinking</u>
<u n="337" who="S0607">I think it might take longer than two weeks</u>
<u n="338" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0607">but I do think that I can you know I keep reading that As You Think which I got because of you because you had a book that told you what book to get and erm it all makes total sense and then I don't do it I'm like</u>
<u n="340" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0607">right I'm gonna do it I'm gonna think differently why why on earth would I not be?</u>
<u n="342" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah yeah and then it goes back to normal that's cos it's a habit habits are not difficult they're not easy things to change that's why they're called habits innit? they're you have to work at it but eventually it does become</u>
<u n="343" who="S0607">maybe this house-sitting thing will be good because you're I'm forced to like be on my own and and work stuff out erm</u>
<u n="344" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I think it's completely what you need it's the opposite of erm what you've been doing</u>
<u n="345" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0644">innit? so it's it is what you need</u>
<u n="347" who="S0607">because erm for example when I was at that <unclear>camping thing</unclear> <vocal desc="yawn"/> erm and I was telling you how I <trunc>di</trunc> like was walking along the beach</u>
<u n="348" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0607">and fell over that thing and twisted my hip and I was like that's it the whole trip is ruined</u>
<u n="350" who="S0644"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="351" who="S0607">oh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm glad there are people in front of us cos otherwise I'd be like I</u>
<u n="352" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><trunc>s</trunc> go straight through the thing</u>
<u n="353" who="S0607">this happened to me on my driving test by the way where I had to like mount the pavement and all sorts of weird stuff and I kept</u>
<u n="354" who="S0644" trans="overlap">did you pass?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0607">and he was like it's okay it's it's an unfortunate like weird situation <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I did pass yeah I passed first time</u>
<u n="356" who="S0644">first?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0607">we nearly first time</u>
<u n="358" who="S0644" trans="overlap">brilliant <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="359" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah we did that I think not that I'm blowing my own trumpet or</u>
<u n="360" who="S0644" trans="overlap">that is brilliant</u>
<u n="361" who="S0607">erm</u>
<u n="362" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I'm only took seven</u>
<u n="363" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="365" who="S0607">I most people take about three</u>
<u n="366" who="S0644">yeah three's average I think that's really good <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0607">erm but so when I was there so it was like <vocal desc="yawn"/> trip over this thing twist the hip a bit</u>
<u n="368" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0607">oh my god America's ruined and then I went okay look <trunc>c</trunc> do you remember me telling you I had to say it out loud? I was like</u>
<u n="370" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0607">dude seriously you know I'm I am gonna stop this and I was like this is my the first day of my new life but it's almost like I have to be on my own to like do it I don't know how to explain it it's weird it's like if somebody's there they can help me and if there's</u>
<u n="372" who="S0644">yeah the</u>
<u n="373" who="S0607" trans="overlap">nobody there I have to help me</u>
<u n="374" who="S0644">oh yeah well cos</u>
<u n="375" who="S0607" trans="overlap">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0644" trans="overlap">the sometimes with your if you're around people that are used to you being like you then</u>
<u n="377" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0644" trans="overlap">it brings that out in you like not being funny if if your mum and dad for example like cos they know what you're like for worrying they'll do their best to like try and chill you out but that's actually inadvertently I'm not obviously doing their best but that's perpetuating the old behaviour like of we must we must try and calm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> down like that</u>
<u n="379" who="S0607">I think I need to do what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is doing in the book by not going on the Pacific Crest Trail but I've started to think about doing something similar that's really for me that's too extreme like I'm I'm not <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="380" who="S0644">you probably could do it though</u>
<u n="381" who="S0607" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="382" who="S0644">couldn't you?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0607">no the it's really bad <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you have like <pause dur="short"/> you have like three days' walking until the next walking source and stuff like that it's just too extreme really</u>
<u n="384" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah but I think in that context you you'll have to do it you'd have to do it and then once you've had to do it you know you can</u>
<u n="385" who="S0607">yeah but maybe you don't want to</u>
<u n="386" who="S0644">grill and chill</u>
<u n="387" who="S0607">but listen dude what about a similar thing that's not as <trunc>ex</trunc>? stop trying to make me do the <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> thing</u>
<u n="388" who="S0644">just do it</u>
<u n="389" who="S0607">now look</u>
<u n="390" who="S0644">see?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0607" trans="overlap">what about a similar thing</u>
<u n="392" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0607">that is erm not as extreme? for example</u>
<u n="394" who="S0644">Wales <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="395" who="S0607">walking across England no</u>
<u n="396" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="397" who="S0607">erm if I did it in summer I could even try the camping thing</u>
<u n="398" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0607">erm or some kind of crazy Scotland trail</u>
<u n="400" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="401" who="S0607">er because when I once had three months off work</u>
<u n="402" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="403" who="S0607">afterwards I was really annoyed cos I thought damn I want to walk across England and I didn't</u>
<u n="404" who="S0644">why didn't you do it again?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0607">I never thought of it</u>
<u n="406" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="407" who="S0607">I forgot that I wanted to do that</u>
<u n="408" who="S0644">do you ever watch Coast at home?</u>
<u n="409" who="S0607">no I haven't erm really seen anything yet</u>
<u n="410" who="S0644" trans="overlap">never?</u>
<u n="411" who="S0607">since I've been back</u>
<u n="412" who="S0644" trans="overlap">no this is an old programme it's years old</u>
<u n="413" who="S0607">oh</u>
<u n="414" who="S0644">Coast it's this really brilliant chap who just walks around the whole of England and then Ireland and then Wales the coast just does the coast and he he tells you the history and the oh it's just fantastic</u>
<u n="415" who="S0607">I did just read a book by the Guardian guy who did my writing course and he it was about him cycling the coast of of Great Britain that was cool erm but erm what was the point? the point is</u>
<u n="416" who="S0644" trans="overlap">so you might do that?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0607">that's sort of</u>
<u n="418" who="S0644" trans="overlap">you could do that</u>
<u n="419" who="S0607">like a bit more on my scale it's still pretty adventurous if all I'm doing is walking I could cycle gonna have to decide erm</u>
<u n="420" who="S0644">could drive and have a camp have a tent and then pitch up in places couldn't you?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0607">mm I could</u>
<u n="422" who="S0644" trans="overlap">and I'd rather walk</u>
<u n="423" who="S0607">well I suppose you could do a bit of both you could like drive to somewhere where there's a walk</u>
<u n="424" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="425" who="S0607">but I'd have to like choose one but then I get fussy so I could choose where I wanna walk from and to and it doesn't have to be something anybody else has done</u>
<u n="426" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="427" who="S0607">but of course there all these ones ah KFC erm I've had quite a lot of chicken now though</u>
<u n="428" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="429" who="S0607">there are all these ones that everyone else does like erm the across England one is it like the Pennine? no there's one where they go from coast to coast</u>
<u n="430" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="431" who="S0607">that's like a well-trodden path and that kind of gets on my nerves already though I bet it's wonderful</u>
<u n="432" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="433" who="S0607">it's like yeah <unclear>that's been done or whatever</unclear> erm <pause dur="short"/> so I don't think I should think about ones that other people have done also because to me coast to coast is sort of wrong cos I'd rather be on the coast all the time</u>
<u n="434" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0607">than like okay I have to walk for like eight hundred days</u>
<u n="436" who="S0644" trans="overlap">to the next bit of coast</u>
<u n="437" who="S0607" trans="overlap">to get the other coast so I could try and like erm work out my own one I'd have to decide do I really wanna do camping erm or do I wanna do like do I wanna do walking or do I wanna do cycling? maybe driving like you said and then like doing walking at different places</u>
<u n="438" who="S0644" trans="overlap">you now you now you can do rented cars and drop them</u>
<u n="439" who="S0607">yeah the thing is with driving is I've got my freedom more like I can just go do you know what? I'm going off to the other side of the country today</u>
<u n="440" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0607">I could just do a sort of like set off from <anon type="place"/> not not decide where I'm going</u>
<u n="442" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="443" who="S0607">and then just text you and go I'm in Shetland Island</u>
<u n="444" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="445" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I dunno what do you think? do you have a? there's <trunc>d</trunc> weird asking you what you think cos it's not you doing it but</u>
<u n="446" who="S0644">well I will I will for things like that that's gotta be fun innit? it's got it's it's if you need to do things like that now</u>
<u n="447" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0644">what I mean is I mean <vocal desc="cough"/> this trip what we're doing if you hadn't said let's do this and what a good idea it is and all the rest of it I would never have got around to it never ever because isn't that?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0607">oh</u>
<u n="450" who="S0644">I'm glad you did make me <pause dur="short"/> that's some avenue <vocal desc="sigh"/> beautiful</u>
<u n="451" who="S0607">oh I'm but yeah that's another reason not to book myself up with too many house-sits and things and Denmark and everything cos what if I decide I wanna walk across England? oh that brings us back to Wales</u>
<u n="452" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="453" who="S0607">earlier I felt like I'd decided that I would do Wales because it's by the sea in June <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0644">that's the craziest one I've ever seen</u>
<u n="455" who="S0607">Harris Beach State Park maybe we should have popped there erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah so like Wales I I should I was gonna do it and then do</u>
<u n="456" who="S0644" trans="overlap">how long is Wales?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0607">it's like nine days</u>
<u n="458" who="S0644">oh for nine days I'd do it</u>
<u n="459" who="S0607"><vocal desc="gasp"/> maybe it could be part of the erm <pause dur="short"/> walking across England but then it depends doesn't it how my <trunc>se</trunc> am I literally walking across England? am I really doing that or am I going in the car? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="460" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0607">oh I dunno now if I really wanna walk across England maybe Scotland</u>
<u n="462" who="S0644">or even just Devon to Cornwall or something like that or</u>
<u n="463" who="S0607">yeah cycling?</u>
<u n="464" who="S0644">er</u>
<u n="465" who="S0607">maybe cycling</u>
<u n="466" who="S0644" trans="overlap">around the Lake Districts? I'd do that along the tour of the Lake Districts</u>
<u n="467" who="S0607">yeah maybe cycling's better you know I've got a bike it's brand new</u>
<u n="468" who="S0644" trans="overlap">cycle</u>
<u n="469" who="S0607">I could do cycling you'd get you'd get further</u>
<u n="470" who="S0644">yeah but then haven't you got to</u>
<u n="471" who="S0607">carry everything on your back?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0644">yeah <pause dur="short"/> everything</u>
<u n="473" who="S0607">now that really will be a lesson in light packing I thought I had packed light</u>
<u n="474" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0607">until I saw you at the airport erm well I still think I did really well for a month don't you think someone else might have had a bigger case <pause dur="short"/> for a month?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0644">yeah well I dunno</u>
<u n="477" who="S0607">oh man</u>
<u n="478" who="S0644">I dunno man</u>
<u n="479" who="S0607">sometimes people just don't say what you want them to say</u>
<u n="480" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0607">you're like right right right?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0644" trans="overlap">thing is</u>
<u n="483" who="S0607">right?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0644">it doesn't matter</u>
<u n="485" who="S0607" trans="overlap">right? and you're like</u>
<u n="486" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0607">I can't can't betray myself dunno</u>
<u n="488" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="489" who="S0607">can't just say yes</u>
<u n="490" who="S0644">yeah they've definitely definitely <unclear/></u>
<u n="491" who="S0607" trans="overlap">no er</u>
<u n="492" who="S0644">it doesn't problem is with a with a case a massive case you've got more stuff but you need to carry it</u>
<u n="493" who="S0607"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0644">but you've got more stuff but you have to</u>
<u n="495" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0644">carry it but</u>
<u n="497" who="S0607">do you know what? this is a whole topic on its own when I saw you at the airport I was actually a bit like <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="498" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="499" who="S0607">cos <vocal desc="laugh"/> I had done so well and then now you you just waltzed in and went I packed yesterday and I only brought that</u>
<u n="500" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="501" who="S0607">and I was just like I already don't like you and it's only two minutes into the trip <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0644">erm</u>
<u n="503" who="S0607">I didn't know</u>
<u n="504" who="S0644">cheeky</u>
<u n="505" who="S0607" trans="overlap">cos your case it I think it was sneaky you never said by the way my case is a weekend case it was very like sneaky and and sort of like underhanded</u>
<u n="506" who="S0644">I think it's cos it doesn't interest me packing it it's it doesn't really it's not something I'd think to go into do you know what I mean? I'll think oh I'll take what I think I can what I can get away with if I thought too much about it it would <trunc>dr</trunc> it would annoy me packing like</u>
<u n="507" who="S0607">well yeah</u>
<u n="508" who="S0644" trans="overlap">if if I really run out of something I'll have to I'll have to find <trunc>s</trunc> there's always we're not really going to the proper outback are we? like if I have to buy some more knickers I can buy some more knickers</u>
<u n="509" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="510" who="S0644">and if I have to find somewhere to wash my clothes I'll wash my clothes it would annoy me having to take up too much time thinking about it</u>
<u n="511" who="S0607">well I took ages thinking about it but actually I didn't take as long as I make out because it erm what was different for me was that I know I've said this several times and that you think I'm exaggerating but I literally didn't have any casualwear only workwear</u>
<u n="512" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0607">so when I came home to England it was like me and mum went to get leggings casual trousers a couple of lumberjack shirts</u>
<u n="514" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh you've got your jogging bots on today I see</u>
<u n="515" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="516" who="S0644">they're nice</u>
<u n="517" who="S0607" trans="overlap">got those they were like fifteen pounds in M and S</u>
<u n="518" who="S0644">see? brilliant</u>
<u n="519" who="S0607">everything really cheap in England</u>
<u n="520" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0607">er this top was fifteen pounds I got I got five of these got four in black and this one</u>
<u n="522" who="S0644" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="523" who="S0607">I actually bought a red one but it was a funny red and we took it back</u>
<u n="524" who="S0644">okay</u>
<u n="525" who="S0607">erm but the idea was to just have one of these on every day and then of course cos it was supposed to be freezing I was gonna have like a <trunc>lum</trunc> my lumberjack shirt over the top and if necessary a jumper over that but I don't need any of that erm and so I didn't have any so it wasn't just for this trip it was actually</u>
<u n="526" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah had to go and get some clothes</u>
<u n="527" who="S0607">I'm not gonna be working this year what am I gonna wear?</u>
<u n="528" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0607">erm so the clothes thing at the beginning of the month was the main thing and actually that was fun cos there was still loads of time to go and we just gradually</u>
<u n="530" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0607">picked up</u>
<u n="532" who="S0644">bits</u>
<u n="533" who="S0607">erm literally two cardigans erm tracksuit bottoms leggings</u>
<u n="534" who="S0644">I think it was really good the reason it was so easy for me is cos it was not a going out</u>
<u n="535" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="536" who="S0644">holiday most days I've been able to have on I've looked a real state but it <trunc>d</trunc> hasn't mattered it's jogging bottoms and leggings and a T-shirt and then <unclear/></u>
<u n="537" who="S0607" trans="overlap">I think it's wonderful do you?</u>
<u n="538" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah I couldn't have been bothered with it</u>
<u n="539" who="S0607">no</u>
<u n="540" who="S0644">otherwise</u>
<u n="541" who="S0607">do you know what? you start to get back to like I looked at myself in the mirror in that erm car hire place and I thought do you know what? I like myself it's cos I'd washed my hair though</u>
<u n="542" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="543" who="S0607">as I said if it was like also the hair it would have been different but</u>
<u n="544" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="545" who="S0607">I just thought I like myself I'm getting used to myself</u>
<u n="546" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="547" who="S0607">oh the other hand I also prefer myself like no I don't</u>
<u n="548" who="S0644">when you've washed your hair <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="549" who="S0607">no when I've also got my lenses in erm and with <trunc>diff</trunc> I'm slightly different to when I've got my glasses on and all that stuff</u>
<u n="550" who="S0644">oh</u>
<u n="551" who="S0607">erm but I just this morning I just thought I'm not putting any makeup on I just maybe it'll be different when we get to the cities and then different again when we get to the San Juans but erm oh can we talk about stuff? is that definitely on by the way?</u>
<u n="552" who="S0644">I think it's on let me look</u>
<u n="553" who="S0607">by the way it doesn't you just have to like press the erm you do the <pause dur="short"/> but you you pressed the red button right?</u>
<u n="554" who="S0644">I did I did</u>
<u n="555" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah so it's still on just check I just suddenly thought what a good one this was and then I thought I bet it's not even on not not that you wouldn't be able to put it on but just one of those</u>
<u n="556" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="557" who="S0607">typical things isn't it?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="559" who="S0607">erm where nobody's talked about nobody's talked about er</u>
<u n="560" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="561" who="S0607">or <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm yeah can we talk about stuff?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0644">stuff as in</u>
<u n="563" who="S0607">like how you shouldn't oh so basically have you read about this erm woman?</u>
<u n="564" who="S0644">the magic of tidying up?</u>
<u n="565" who="S0607" trans="overlap">this this it's called Joy</u>
<u n="566" who="S0644">oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="567" who="S0607" trans="overlap">so my <trunc>frie</trunc> I when I was in Frankfurt I was</u>
<u n="568" who="S0644">she was on television the other day</u>
<u n="569" who="S0607">was she? the Japanese girl?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0644">no Joy</u>
<u n="571" who="S0607">oh no this is a Japanese girl whose book is called Joy</u>
<u n="572" who="S0644">oh sorry right</u>
<u n="573" who="S0607">erm so she so I was in like trying to pack my stuff for England and my main thing was I'm not packing I'm chucking away</u>
<u n="574" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="575" who="S0607">so the the first few months were spent trying to chuck stuff away</u>
<u n="576" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="577" who="S0607">and I actually felt like I chucked away a lot of stuff</u>
<u n="578" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0607">but I still had a lot of stuff so I said to my friend at work erm I can't I said to her I <trunc>tr</trunc> I tried to start on the clothes yesterday and I just couldn't do it like</u>
<u n="580" who="S0644" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="581" who="S0607">it just wouldn't happen I just kept looking at each item and just going I just can't do this today and she said well that's one of the things you do have to be in the right mood and it was true cos</u>
<u n="582" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="583" who="S0607">the next day I did it and suddenly I had two bin liners full</u>
<u n="584" who="S0644">mm mm mm mm</u>
<u n="585" who="S0607" trans="overlap">but she said to me she'd read this whole book</u>
<u n="586" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="587" who="S0607">and it was basically the upshot of having read the whole book was you pick up an item it doesn't have to be clothes</u>
<u n="588" who="S0644">uhu mm</u>
<u n="589" who="S0607">but we were doing clothes</u>
<u n="590" who="S0644">feel it</u>
<u n="591" who="S0607">and then does it bring you any joy?</u>
<u n="592" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="593" who="S0607">if not chuck it not I when was the last time I wore it?</u>
<u n="594" who="S0644" trans="overlap">I used this</u>
<u n="595" who="S0607">I might use it in the future it's <unclear>adjusting this item</unclear></u>
<u n="596" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="597" who="S0607">or blah blah blah does it bring you any joy? and it was amazing how it worked</u>
<u n="598" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="599" who="S0607">because I would pick something up it would actually bring me misery because I knew that I'd bought it wasted my money on it never worn it every time I look at it</u>
<u n="600" who="S0644" trans="overlap">never gonna</u>
<u n="601" who="S0607">it makes me feel stressed out cos I still have to try and make it work</u>
<u n="602" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="603" who="S0607">and so I just got really brutal</u>
<u n="604" who="S0644">brilliant brilliant brilliant</u>
<u n="605" who="S0607">and I chucked out you won't believe it cos I can't believe I had this much stuff I chucked out like five bin liners of clothes right?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0644">is this in Frankfurt or in England?</u>
<u n="607" who="S0607" trans="overlap">in Frankfurt</u>
<u n="608" who="S0644">oh good I'm glad you did it before</u>
<u n="609" who="S0607" trans="overlap">and I still had I still had a wardrobe full of winter clothes and a suitcase full of summer clothes</u>
<u n="610" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="611" who="S0607">and then when I came to actually pack it it turned out that there were <trunc>l</trunc> there were loads of extra items as well</u>
<u n="612" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="613" who="S0607">which I couldn't fit in so I had to have a last minute mega mega cull of like oh god I'm gonna get rid of that I can't believe it and I and I and I got another three bin liners out so and that's just clothes and I chucked away so much other stuff like all like for example a French and German dictionary giant dictionaries</u>
<u n="614" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="615" who="S0607">that I've had since I was eighteen</u>
<u n="616" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="617" who="S0607">they're completely out of date and you only use online ones now</u>
<u n="618" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="619" who="S0607" trans="overlap">so but I kept the Italian one cos it brings me joy</u>
<u n="620" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="621" who="S0607">so it was just anyway so I chucked out all this stuff right thought that</u>
<u n="622" who="S0644" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="623" who="S0607">I was amazing</u>
<u n="624" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="625" who="S0607">and I still had loads of stuff when it came down to it</u>
<u n="626" who="S0644">yeah but think how much better off you were</u>
<u n="627" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0644">than before</u>
<u n="629" who="S0607">but now I've got this fascination I'm gonna get rid of more stuff so</u>
<u n="630" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="631" who="S0607">the only thing is that some of the stuff that I've brought that's in my dad's attic it's for when you have an apartment</u>
<u n="632" who="S0644">right</u>
<u n="633" who="S0607">and I think it would be a mistake cos my mum said don't chuck away stuff that you're gonna have to buy again cos that's a waste of money</u>
<u n="634" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0607">so like a basket that you're gonna put things in in this fictional apartment or you know er loads of cables that do long</u>
<u n="636" who="S0644">attach to</u>
<u n="637" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="639" who="S0607">or you know there's all sorts of crap like that that</u>
<u n="640" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="641" who="S0607">that is but I think it's difficult to distinguish between those and the just in case items which will never get used and I tried to get rid of loads of just in case items</u>
<u n="642" who="S0644">oh look</u>
<u n="643" who="S0607">but what do you think? cos I'm thinking I'm gonna reduce my stuff and I've got I've I'm not gonna be working right? so I'm gonna go into the attic</u>
<u n="644" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="645" who="S0607">and I'm gonna start with the stuff that was already in the attic before I arrived</u>
<u n="646" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="647" who="S0607">and I'm gonna get rid of all and I want to get rid of eighty percent of it because do you know what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="649" who="S0607">I don't want loads of physical reminders of memories</u>
<u n="650" who="S0644">you don't need it either</u>
<u n="651" who="S0607">or sometimes they actually get you down even if they're good memories the actual item it's a bit funny feeling and I think the and <trunc>n</trunc> so anyway I've bought the book it's a bit over the top and it was like nine pounds but I just really wanna read it cos I just really want I went into the attic and looked at an item and I thought I need help from that woman</u>
<u n="652" who="S0644">in the theory of everything that's one of the methods that you can use for getting happy</u>
<u n="653" who="S0607">getting rid of stuff?</u>
<u n="654" who="S0644">yeah well tidying</u>
<u n="655" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="656" who="S0644">and getting which includes obviously getting rid of stuff putting things where they're supposed to be not holding onto things</u>
<u n="657" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0644">giving things away</u>
<u n="659" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="660" who="S0644">erm yeah</u>
<u n="661" who="S0607">she also tells you how to fold things and stuff like that goes down to</u>
<u n="662" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="663" who="S0607">that sort of level</u>
<u n="664" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="665" who="S0607">erm and there was a guy in The Guardian who did a taking the piss article about the about the book saying</u>
<u n="666" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="667" who="S0607">talk to your socks tell them oh yeah cos she does she talks to her things</u>
<u n="668" who="S0644">and she says don't <trunc>s</trunc> erm stick them together cos that means they never get a rest if you you know when you get socks? <vocal desc="sneeze"/></u>
<u n="669" who="S0607">bless you</u>
<u n="670" who="S0644">excuse me you know</u>
<u n="671" who="S0607" trans="overlap">bless you</u>
<u n="672" who="S0644">when you get socks now when I'm <vocal desc="sneeze"/></u>
<u n="673" who="S0607">bless you</u>
<u n="674" who="S0644">thank you when I'm very relaxed and I've got plenty of time I iron everything I iron knickers and socks and all that kind of thing</u>
<u n="675" who="S0607">really?</u>
<u n="676" who="S0644">yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to properly take the mick out of me knicker in knicker in irons ironing knickers</u>
<u n="677" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="678" who="S0644">erm but when I'm really relaxed I do that cos my nan always used to do it anyway the <trunc>diff</trunc> the that the <vocal desc="sigh"/> no time version is to get your socks and you just stick them in together like fold like squeeze the ends together do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="679" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="680" who="S0644">and fold them over</u>
<u n="681" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="682" who="S0644">so that you know you've got a pair but they're not ironed and they've not been and there is a definitely definitely a difference between picking out a pair of them to wear in the day and picking out a nice pair of ironed</u>
<u n="683" who="S0607">you know the ironed ones? do they also get stuck together?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0644">er what electrically you mean? electricity?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0607">no like do you fold them over each other</u>
<u n="686" who="S0644">no just lay them flat <pause dur="short"/> there's a tailback</u>
<u n="687" who="S0607">there is and I hadn't really noticed it's all that talking they've probably following us for five hundred miles</u>
<u n="688" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh there's only a few</u>
<u n="689" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="690" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> they've still not <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="691" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="692" who="S0644">that driver's wicked yeah in short it's fung shui innit?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0607">but she talks to the stuff she'll say lovely shirt thank you</u>
<u n="694" who="S0644">ah</u>
<u n="695" who="S0607">for bringing me such joy so that's why this bloke was a er</u>
<u n="696" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="697" who="S0607">even though I totally buying into this stuff cos I love this kind of stuff you know happiness project</u>
<u n="698" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="699" who="S0607">tidying book it's not about tidying it's about joy and and erm I love all that stuff so but even though I love all that stuff I was able to really have a good laugh at his book cos I do think it was <trunc>funn</trunc> er he <unclear/> it was funny</u>
<u n="700" who="S0644" trans="overlap">it's the sort of thing as much as you might like it yourself you can see how other people would take the piss</u>
<u n="701" who="S0607" trans="overlap">other people are like oh my god I love this woman right because this is another thing why can't me and you think of something? so she she's been a tidy freak since she was fourteen there was one day when she was fourteen when she was tidying up and she nearly collapsed under the whole pressure of it like how badly she wanted it all to be perfect</u>
<u n="702" who="S0644">really?</u>
<u n="703" who="S0607">and it was like a sort of like epiphany moment</u>
<u n="704" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="705" who="S0607">she's been really she's been I was gonna say really bad but no she's been like that for a long time so this led to her teaching other people how to do it</u>
<u n="706" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="707" who="S0607">which led to the book and now she's an international phenomenon and I'm like</u>
<u n="708" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="709" who="S0607">for crying out loud why can't? I wanna be like and then you don't have to work again anyway I just I just can't wait to read the book when I get back and I get rid of all that stuff because I want to be light I want to be light</u>
<u n="710" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="711" who="S0607">and if I'm gonna be house-sitting</u>
<u n="712" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="713" who="S0607">I wanna just have</u>
<u n="714" who="S0644">pick your bag of stuff</u>
<u n="715" who="S0607" trans="overlap">one suitcase of things and that's all I need</u>
<u n="716" who="S0644" trans="overlap">and and also know where everything is I mean the best thing ever like they got to a point when I was living in all different places I've probably said this to you a thousand times I've said it to everybody a thousand times but the losing of the keys and phone and the erm purse and <vocal desc="cough"/> phones and misplacing stuff all the time and it's cos I lived in all these different places and I had boxes of stuff here bags of stuff there and when I moved everything into oh wow look at that</u>
<u n="717" who="S0607">I think it's actually getting better</u>
<u n="718" who="S0644">it is getting better</u>
<u n="719" who="S0607">it's getting a bit it's getting different but in in my feelings but even better like I'm feeling even more calm yeah so anyway your keys and stuff</u>
<u n="720" who="S0644">so it took a a while but eventually I got everything from my mum's my dad's or anywhere other places that I'd left stuff and everything I now own more or less is in that four walled space and I know where everything is and I've got rid of so much stuff in the last in the few years since I've been there cos there ain't a lot of space there really</u>
<u n="721" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="722" who="S0644">I've had a a cull of books which is also like you've gotta be careful of books cos as much as they're things that you think you're gonna always use or refer back to or you wanna keep sometimes they can just take up too much space and they're no longer reflective of what you wanna</u>
<u n="723" who="S0607">mm</u>
<u n="724" who="S0644">look at or read about had a cull of books clothes it's just wonderful like every <trunc>s</trunc> you have to do it all the time constantly</u>
<u n="725" who="S0607" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="726" who="S0644">my sister said actually when my nan died and we had to clear out my nan's house she said it really taught her to constantly be on top of it she said because otherwise that's what happens</u>
<u n="727" who="S0607">yes and that's what I wanna do I don't want to like you know have to do a massive cull every so often</u>
<u n="728" who="S0644" trans="overlap">every three years yeah</u>
<u n="729" who="S0607">I want to keep doing it so you know how I gave you back that keyring?</u>
<u n="730" who="S0644">yes</u>
<u n="731" who="S0607">I thought I don't want that keyring and then if I if when I get home I don't throw it away straight away that and loads of other items are just gonna fester in a drawer</u>
<u n="732" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah it's the sort of thing you just keep out of habit you think oh I got that in in San Francisco I'll keep that why?</u>
<u n="733" who="S0607">you know with a keyring?</u>
<u n="734" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="735" who="S0607">I actually think so I had a keyring as a just in case item</u>
<u n="736" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="737" who="S0607">and I thought it's so inexpensive I'd rather just run out of keyrings</u>
<u n="738" who="S0644" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="739" who="S0607">and then have to get one</u>
<u n="740" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="741" who="S0607">and</u>
<u n="742" who="S0644">when you're inspired to get one</u>
<u n="743" who="S0607">yeah and I had this with flipping erm little compact mirror</u>
<u n="744" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="745" who="S0607">some somehow I'd ended up with like three so I had one that</u>
<u n="746" who="S0644" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="747" who="S0607">I was actually using I think it was a present probably from my sister</u>
<u n="748" who="S0644">mm just <unclear>so cool</unclear> <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> beautiful</u>
<u n="749" who="S0607">yeah I had two compact mirrors in reserve and did they get on my nerves? they were in the in reserve box and it felt like a waste</u>
<u n="750" who="S0644" trans="overlap">do you know what it is though? you get used to just seeing things you get used to just looking keeping things and in the end you've got this stuff and it's just there <pause dur="short"/> and you you'd get used to looking at it and don't even think about getting rid of it</u>
<u n="751" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="752" who="S0644">until <pause dur="short"/> I you do that with clothes I do it with clothes all the time clothes do have sentimental value</u>
<u n="753" who="S0607">yeah</u>
<u n="754" who="S0644">sometimes but eventually you have to get rid of them as well</u>
<u n="755" who="S0607">erm I've saw this guy on the house-sitting website not supposed to be using it to troll for guys and of course I'm not trolling for guys</u>
<u n="756" who="S0644" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="757" who="S0607">cos I don't I'm not interested in guys</u>
<u n="758" who="S0644">bet you were</u>
<u n="759" who="S0607">erm <pause dur="short"/> but I accidentally saw this guy who was a house-sitter like me I never see the house-sitters cos I'm always looking at the house-sits</u>
<u n="760" who="S0644">yeah of course you are</u>
<u n="761" who="S0607" trans="overlap">but erm he was this totally gorgeous bloke on a bike and he was like hi I'm so and so I basically have spent the last two years cycling around the world and now I'm writing a book about it I was like I hate you</u>
<u n="762" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="763" who="S0607">now I'm writing a book about it and basically I like to live very light like I hardly have any stuff and I just go from place to place and I'm writing and I was just like yeah alright you know we all know you're fantastic</u>
<u n="764" who="S0644" trans="overlap">enough about you when can I come and stay at your house for free?</u>
<u n="765" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="766" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="767" who="S0607">erm <pause dur="short"/> which brings us back to Wales</u>
<u n="768" who="S0644">right</u>
<u n="769" who="S0607" trans="overlap">now Wales is an exciting house-sit could it totally fuck up my erm freedom to do whatever the hell I want whenever I want? or</u>
<u n="770" who="S0644">not for nine days it can't no</u>
<u n="771" who="S0607">also because it'll get to June and I'll go I haven't got any house-sits I've got to live with my parents</u>
<u n="772" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="773" who="S0607">and you'll be like well there was that Wales one</u>
<u n="774" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="775" who="S0607">do you know what I mean? other thing is is it long enough to spend the petrol to go to Wales for nine days?</u>
<u n="776" who="S0644">you could erm get a train if you booked it in advance really cheap or a National Express</u>
<u n="777" who="S0607">well</u>
<u n="778" who="S0644" trans="overlap">don't you love the National Express?</u>
<u n="779" who="S0607">I do but it's one of those things where half of the thing of going would be I would stop and see people on the way in on the way back</u>
<u n="780" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="781" who="S0607">and it's one of those where she's said you need a car really</u>
<u n="782" who="S0644" trans="overlap">right fair enough fair enough</u>
<u n="783" who="S0607">but yeah otherwise I would</u>
<u n="784" who="S0644" trans="overlap">but it can't cost that much how much can it cost?</u>
<u n="785" who="S0607">well actually my dad said that I could get all the way up to the one that I'm doing in April he reckoned I could get all the way up there and still have some left over in the tank</u>
<u n="786" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="787" who="S0607">or did he say and the way back? no all the way up there</u>
<u n="788" who="S0644">mm</u>
<u n="789" who="S0607">cos that's the thing the Helmsley which is in the north I'm doing two weeks</u>
<u n="790" who="S0644">mm <pause dur="short"/> coast</u>
<u n="791" who="S0607">and I'll need two tanks of petrol but I'm actually going to Birmingham before then so that will be on the way so I'll probably only use two tanks of petrol for three weeks of house-sitting</u>
<u n="792" who="S0644" trans="overlap">are you going from Birmingham straight to Wales then?</u>
<u n="793" who="S0607">no to Helmsley which is the end of April</u>
<u n="794" who="S0644" trans="overlap">what's in Helmsley?</u>
<u n="795" who="S0607">it's the two weeks one with the golden retrievers</u>
<u n="796" who="S0644">oh so you've got loads booked up really haven't you?</u>
<u n="797" who="S0607">well now I'll have three if I say yes to the Wales oh no four because I've got four days in <anon type="place"/> near my mum and dad's in March</u>
<u n="798" who="S0644">so you'll be going consecutively from one place to the other if it works out more or less?</u>
<u n="799" who="S0607">well yeah I'm I wish it would work out like that but I've worked I've <trunc>tr</trunc> I don't know if it will but with the Birmingham and Helmsley one there's no point going back to <anon type="place"/> because you're halfway up the country already it means I'm gonna have to spend two nights in a B and B which is gonna cost me but so what I was trying to do is add up the petrol money add up the B and B money and hope that it's still a lot less than just renting a place yourself do you see what I mean? but I was thinking I would like to find a B and B somewhere really tiny really really really cheap like how cheap do you reckon you can get? this is amazing</u>
<u n="800" who="S0644">dead cheap</u>
<u n="801" who="S0607">thirty quid less?</u>
<u n="802" who="S0644">yes er <trunc>f</trunc> if it was a bed and breakfast</u>
<u n="803" who="S0607" trans="overlap">twenty-five?</u>
<u n="804" who="S0644">as in someone's house one of those oh I never got to tell you about erm bed and breakfast that's just reminded me I must tell you about this lady who really reminded me of you it was hilarious</u>
<u n="805" who="S0607">ah</u>
<u n="806" who="S0644" trans="overlap">oh look why isn't there a vista point?</u>
<u n="807" who="S0607" trans="overlap">do you think we should like stop and walk along it?</u>
<u n="808" who="S0644">yeah</u>
<u n="809" who="S0607">shall we? if we can?</u>
<u n="810" who="S0644">yeah there's there's a bit yeah yeah perfect <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> oh it's</u>
<u n="811" who="S0607" trans="overlap">we can just go on it right?</u>
<u n="812" who="S0644" trans="overlap">if we can</u>
<u n="813" who="S0607">let's see what this sign says do not go on the beach for the following eight dangers that's all that doesn't matter <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="814" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/> river</u>
<u n="815" who="S0607">mm general warning <pause dur="short"/> rip currents well we're not going in order to sneaker waves <trunc>th</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="816" who="S0644">sneaker waves</u>
<u n="817" who="S0607">use caution on rocks and jetties we obviously do beware of incoming tides we do stay off the logs we do well you don't <trunc>ev</trunc> don't do please don't do fireworks don't do this don't do that we're not doing any of that don't <unclear>kill</unclear> the wildlife don't disturb the marine animals collect your rubbish fantastic we're fine</u>
<u n="818" who="S0644">that's a relief</u>
<u n="819" who="S0607"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you just knew didn't you that we were gonna be driving oh going <vocal desc="laugh"/> too dangerous</u>
<u n="820" who="S0644"><vocal desc="laugh"/> too dangerous <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
