<text id="SQBK">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:12:15</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-06-21</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0653 S0654 S0655</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Kitchen, Comberton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Brownies and sexism, Twitter, The Boy in the Dress, gender confusion, food for tea</topics>
		<activity>Family talking about Brownies, gender confusion</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, complianing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T04</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0653">
				<exactage>39</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dartford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0654">
				<exactage>7</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>1_primary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0655">
				<exactage>9</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury St Edmunds</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>1_primary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0653">so we're gonna talk about Brownies today cos what was your erm earlier question <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0655">was it is Brownies</u>
<u n="3" who="S0653" trans="overlap">hang on a minute <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you want to start you're desperate to start the conversation go on?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0654">no I I was just reminding you that it's gonna be Brownies</u>
<u n="5" who="S0653">yes I know it's Brownies today but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what were you saying earlier?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0655">is Brownies illegal?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0653">illegal? now why do you why were you asking? what's your issue with it?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0655">erm because it's sexist and that's against the law</u>
<u n="9" who="S0653">and why is it sexist?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0655">cos they don't allow boys</u>
<u n="11" who="S0653">cos they don't allow boys so it is an interesting issue actually isn't it?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0653">cos if it was the other way around people would be possibly up in arms and saying this is real sexism and <trunc>girl</trunc>girls should be allowed to join Scouts and things and they are now allowed to do that but and it hasn't worked the other way around has it?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0655">no</u>
<u n="15" who="S0653">and the Brownies' website does promote it saying that girls prefer the fact that there are no boys but erm if you feel very strongly about it we could write a letter and make it public</u>
<u n="16" who="S0655" trans="overlap">right I'm going to ask some people erm who if they would prefer it if there were boys or not in Brownies?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0653">you're going to ask the Brownies themselves?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0655">yeah see if the Brownies</u>
<u n="19" who="S0653">but to be honest with you it's irrelevant if they that's not a legitimate thing cos you can't have you know people in a workplace saying well I don't really want girls in there they have to allow girls don't they and boys in society? so it is in fact very sexist that Brownies doesn't allow boys</u>
<u n="20" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0653">but I'm just saying if you wanna make an issue about it we could write an open letter and put it on Twitter or something to see what they might suggest I think in all I think perhaps most boys won't want to do Brownies but that's not the point if you wanted <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you're gonna spill garlic butter everywhere put that tray down</u>
<u n="22" who="S0655">there's barely any</u>
<u n="23" who="S0654" trans="overlap">no there's hardly any</u>
<u n="24" who="S0653" trans="overlap">but but if you want to join Brownies and do the activities that they do then perhaps you should be allowed</u>
<u n="25" who="S0655">I may not want to but</u>
<u n="26" who="S0653">yeah but I think you do don't you?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0655">yeah I do but</u>
<u n="28" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0655">I just wanted I just wanted so</u>
<u n="30" who="S0653" trans="overlap">you to be yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0655">yeah I just want boys to be allowed to join Brownies <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0653">I've yes but I think we could really only pursue it if you if you did actually personally want to do it because perhaps nobody wants to join Brownies perhaps no boy wants to join Brownies</u>
<u n="33" who="S0655">I'll ask some of my class</u>
<u n="34" who="S0653">or they've not really thought about it but I think if you made an issue about it then that other boys would start to think ooh actually yes I like the things that they do in Brownies stop doing that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know and I'd like to join in but you know I feel that if we manage to get the the rules changed or whatever and then you said well I don't want to do it I think it would be a bit of a shame if they'd had to sort of go through all the you know fuss about it do you see what I mean?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0653" trans="overlap">you shouldn't have to to do it or join it as justification for getting them to change the rules I mean if you like you can just make a statement saying that it is that you feel it's sexist in fact if you want I can film you saying this and I can put it on Youtube if you prefer?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0655">I think Twister would be better because</u>
<u n="38" who="S0653">you think Twister? Twitter?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0655" trans="overlap">Twitter might be better</u>
<u n="40" who="S0653">well I can also put Youtube stuff on Twitter but you'd prefer a letter?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0655">yeah <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0653">so what what are your thoughts do you want to to do that?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0655">if it really gets into my head and then I and then I probably will</u>
<u n="44" who="S0653">cos I know you've been quite upset about it on and off since <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> joined erm and understandably so and I think you'll probably be quite upset when we all do the Brownies ice cream parlour and have an amazing time but erm</u>
<u n="45" who="S0655">although there is one thing</u>
<u n="46" who="S0653" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="47" who="S0655">that's a problem</u>
<u n="48" who="S0653" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0655">will you be able to afford it?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0653">to do for you to do Brownies as well?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="52" who="S0653">I'd find a way of making it happen</u>
<u n="53" who="S0654">also <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you don't do drama you don't do diving</u>
<u n="54" who="S0653">you don't do diving any more</u>
<u n="55" who="S0654">what do you do?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0653">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="57" who="S0655">chess</u>
<u n="58" who="S0653">chess and football football</u>
<u n="59" who="S0655">mm but</u>
<u n="60" who="S0653">but chess doesn't cost me any money</u>
<u n="61" who="S0655" trans="overlap">like like out of school what do you do after school?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0653">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I do Brownies drama and ballet</u>
<u n="64" who="S0653">yes</u>
<u n="65" who="S0655">okay Brownies drama and ballet</u>
<u n="66" who="S0654">BGB</u>
<u n="67" who="S0653">oh yeah well you're not doing any drama lessons at the moment so but the question is do I mean we've talked about this before haven't we? in fact I saw something in a magazine and I took a photograph off today there's a senior army officer who joined the army as a man and then realised that she wants to become a woman</u>
<u n="68" who="S0655" trans="overlap">hey</u>
<u n="69" who="S0653">so she's now become a woman erm because there are people that feel that they're born in the wrong body or there are mainly men it doesn't really work the other way around that er don't want to change sex but they do want to wear ladies' clothes</u>
<u n="70" who="S0655">like David Walliams</u>
<u n="71" who="S0653">like David Walliams yeah or there's Grayson Perry</u>
<u n="72" who="S0654" trans="overlap">the <unclear/> erm the Grand Central boy did</u>
<u n="73" who="S0653">the Grand Central boy? the boy in the dress?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0653">yes that's right</u>
<u n="76" who="S0655">there's also a film called The Boy in the Dress</u>
<u n="77" who="S0653">ah erm yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0655">The Boy in the Dress is basically a life story about David Walliams</u>
<u n="79" who="S0653">well it sort of is and he he <trunc>c</trunc> he likes boys and girls as a in fact so I think what I'm asking you and we're not really sure is if you know do you want to be a Brownie because you'd like to be a girl or do you just want to join in and do what they do cos you like their activities?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0655">well apparently they're gonna go kayaking and it's just seems like a lot</u>
<u n="81" who="S0654">punting</u>
<u n="82" who="S0655">punting</u>
<u n="83" who="S0653">punting they're going to go punting</u>
<u n="84" who="S0655">but it just seems like so but Brownies just seems like so much more fun than er Scouts is it?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0654"><unclear/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0653">yes I think you definitely would prefer Brownies to Scouts</u>
<u n="87" who="S0655">yeah and to Beavers</u>
<u n="88" who="S0653">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but is that like is that just because of the activities themselves? <pause dur="short"/> do you want to become a <trunc>Br</trunc> do <trunc>y</trunc> or you do you just not know the reasons why?</u>
<u n="89" who="S0655">I do not know the reasons why</u>
<u n="90" who="S0653">yeah okay</u>
<u n="91" who="S0655">that's why it had such a big impact in my life</u>
<u n="92" who="S0653">well I don't want you to get upset about it this is just it's just a very complicated issue isn't it? there's absolutely no need to be worried if you're confused cos you're only nine and a half so er it's perfectly natural to not to not know how you feel isn't it? some some grown-ups don't quite know how they feel about these issues</u>
<u n="93" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0653">erm and we've we've sort of we have decided to be sisters together haven't we sometimes?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0654">sisters</u>
<u n="96" who="S0653">sisters together</u>
<u n="97" who="S0654"><unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="98" who="S0653">that we could all dress up in dresses and go out and stuff</u>
<u n="99" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0653">which would be lovely and you've got erm a dress well playsuit and you look lovely in it</u>
<u n="101" who="S0654" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and you can be my girlfriend <unclear>when</unclear> if you want to be a girl</u>
<u n="102" who="S0653">yeah I just want you</u>
<u n="103" who="S0655" trans="overlap">because</u>
<u n="104" who="S0653">to be happy and <trunc>h</trunc> feel comfortable in your own skin that's the most important thing</u>
<u n="105" who="S0655"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0653">so the whole kind of other sexual stuff is gonna come later but I still think we should make erm an issue about the Brownies thing</u>
<u n="107" who="S0655">really?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0653">because it is it is sexist and I think their argument on the website saying oh it's nice to have somewhere to go where there aren't any boys I've I personally find that quite offensive</u>
<u n="109" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0653">it's rude isn't it?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0655">I</u>
<u n="112" who="S0653" trans="overlap">because you'd never be able to say that of as a boy</u>
<u n="113" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0653">you know?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0655">yeah if it if there was a boy saying oh I love this place there's absolutely no girls there</u>
<u n="116" who="S0653">everyone would attack them wouldn't they? yeah</u>
<u n="117" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah everyone would be like oi that's against the law</u>
<u n="118" who="S0653">yeah they'd say well they'd say it would be very <trunc>se</trunc>sexist</u>
<u n="119" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="120" who="S0653">mm <pause dur="short"/> so I think</u>
<u n="121" who="S0655" trans="overlap">just</u>
<u n="122" who="S0653">I'll find out who the head of the Brownies is and I will write to them about it</u>
<u n="123" who="S0654" trans="overlap">do Brown Owl</u>
<u n="124" who="S0653">no no of the entire well of the whole country</u>
<u n="125" who="S0655">the queen?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0654">well <unclear/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0653" trans="overlap">the queen is not in charge of Brownies</u>
<u n="128" who="S0654">well the person did tell you</u>
<u n="129" who="S0653">the person did tell me? would you like to be a little bit more specific?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0653" trans="overlap">like the person told you that I was really good at Brownies remember? and she gave you a little phone call on the like a texty?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0653">what? a little phone call little do you mean?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0655">little phone</u>
<u n="134" who="S0654" trans="overlap">yes from Brownies</u>
<u n="135" who="S0653">there is somebody not <anon type="place"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the whole of the country there's someone in</u>
<u n="136" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I mean that she was the whole of the country</u>
<u n="137" who="S0653">well we haven't met her <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>which one are you talking about</unclear>?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0654">she texted you</u>
<u n="139" who="S0653">nobody's texted me to say that you were brilliant</u>
<u n="140" who="S0655">can we also complain to the people in the law so even so if Brownies doesn't do it then it might need to shut down because if it's sexist?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0653">well I think that would be a bit harsh but I think we will start with a campaign where we even where we contact the Brownies' head directly and then if we're not happy with what they say then we'll go public on Twitter</u>
<u n="142" who="S0655">yeah and if and then if we're still not happy loads of people are going oh no no no it's brilliant that there's loads of places there's finding a place where there's no boys and just girls then it then we might need to go to the head the people in the law</u>
<u n="143" who="S0653">well yes which well that would cost money so it would be a bit tricky but they might decide that you could be an honorary Brownie in <anon type="place"/> for example</u>
<u n="144" who="S0655">yeah er I'll ask my friends if they want if they wouldn't mind if they became a Brownie</u>
<u n="145" who="S0653">yeah that would be interesting take a poll</u>
<u n="146" who="S0655">because I'd like to have some friends there</u>
<u n="147" who="S0653">well you've got loads of friends you've got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="148" who="S0655">yeah I think quite a few people have a crush on me</u>
<u n="149" who="S0654">mm mm mm mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0655">it's possible</u>
<u n="151" who="S0653">and you've got your sister <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0655" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0653">is that what you wanted to say?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0654">mm</u>
<u n="155" who="S0653">yes <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0655">but I do want some like friends that are boys cos it would be a bit awkward if there was <unclear/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0653" trans="overlap">it wouldn't be awkward at all if you were the only boy</u>
<u n="158" who="S0655">I have to do my promise night</u>
<u n="159" who="S0653">well why would that be awkward? I could be there with you and hold your hand if you wanted?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0655">no I was just wondering cos I'd like to do the dancing dancing dancing</u>
<u n="161" who="S0654"><unclear/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0653" trans="overlap">can you just speak properly sorry?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0654">what's for dessert?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0653">I love that your <trunc>ex</trunc> high expectation erm well there's Frubes or strawberries cos you've eaten all the other stuff there's not jelly because there was a tiny bit and that's gone now in my tummy</u>
<u n="165" who="S0655" trans="overlap">I said</u>
<u n="166" who="S0653">erm</u>
<u n="167" who="S0655">I said <trunc>we</trunc>we've eaten all of the jelly</u>
<u n="168" who="S0653" trans="overlap">there's grapes and strawberries and if you have some of that erm I I think there's some ice cream still isn't there?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0654">Frubies</u>
<u n="170" who="S0653">what would you like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0654">well I'm looking as you've been bragging me about for a long time</u>
<u n="172" who="S0653">that I've been what whating you about? ragging you about?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0654">bragging</u>
<u n="174" who="S0653">bragging you about that doesn't work</u>
<u n="175" who="S0654">no like going <shift new="singing"/> de de de <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0653">begging you? well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it's driving me mad that there's an Easter Lindt little baby bunny and one marshmallow from all those weeks ago just sitting there uneaten</u>
<u n="177" who="S0654" trans="overlap">and I I've got <unclear/></u>
<u n="178" who="S0653">and you've got what?</u>
<u n="179" who="S0654">fine I'll eat it</u>
<u n="180" who="S0653">good eat the damn thing</u>
<u n="181" who="S0654">no I'm gonna eat the piece of chocolate not the bunny</u>
<u n="182" who="S0653">I'm not so interested about the <trunc>bu</trunc> the marshmallow I just I want the Lindt bunny I'm not joking if you've not eaten it by Friday then when you're at dad's this weekend I I'm going to eat it I don't I won't all my willpower will have run out no you can't hide it because you're not allowed to have food out of the kitchen come back cos we're doing a recording <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0654">no I don't</u>
<u n="184" who="S0655">eat that <unclear/> come back <unclear/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0653" trans="overlap">come back sit down <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0655"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0653" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sit down what are you going to eat for for your dessert as you so grandly call it?</u>
<event desc="sound of bang"/>
<u n="188" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="189" who="S0653"><unclear/> company</u>
<u n="190" who="S0654">there's ice cream</u>
<u n="191" who="S0653">you're not having chocolate ice cream you can have some fruit first</u>
<u n="192" who="S0654">can I have some crisps?</u>
<u n="193" who="S0653">no those are from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s lunch that he didn't eat all of them</u>
<u n="194" who="S0654">I didn't even have my crisps cos they were horrible</u>
<u n="195" who="S0653">can you sit down please?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0654">my crisps were horrible</u>
<u n="197" who="S0653">I'm just gonna pause this cos you're</u>
<u n="198" who="S0654" trans="overlap">I'm gonna have some strawberries</u>
<u n="199" who="S0653">you're just messing around now</u>
<u n="200" who="S0654">I'll have some strawberries mum</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
