<text id="SQWW">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:40:39</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-01-20</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0281 S0355</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speakers' home, Brighton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Scottish referendum, job interview, colleague, my daughter, present personal situation.</topics>
		<activity>Recent news, personal situation.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0281">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Brighton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>30</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0355">
				<exactage>64</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hove, Sussex</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Hove, Sussex</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>64 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>Business Owner</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>4</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0281">so how was your day?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0355">yeah good</u>
<u n="3" who="S0281">what did you do? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0355">I <pause dur="short"/> got up <pause dur="short"/> had a wash had my breakfast erm <pause dur="short"/> and I went into work</u>
<u n="5" who="S0281">what were you doing?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0355">erm we were putting the finishing touches to a <pause dur="short"/> to a erm</u>
<u n="7" who="S0281">a thing</u>
<u n="8" who="S0355">a thing <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> a steel band that goes around the handrail on a wooden balcony <pause dur="short"/> that so that if anyone fell against the wooden balcony</u>
<u n="9" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0355">and it broke it would you know its steel band would keep it all together</u>
<u n="11" who="S0281">oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0355">so we went and <pause dur="short"/> the steel band's got to be galvanised so</u>
<u n="13" who="S0281">galvanised being <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0355">galvanised it's got to be galvanised</u>
<u n="15" who="S0281">yeah <pause dur="short"/> galvanised is</u>
<u n="16" who="S0355" trans="overlap">that means that it's dipped in a molten bath of zinc</u>
<u n="17" who="S0281">oh yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0355">it's cleaned with acid and then dipped in a molten bath of zinc</u>
<u n="19" who="S0281">cos we often well sometimes use the word I was galvanised into action</u>
<u n="20" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="21" who="S0281">doesn't really <pause dur="short"/> well anyway <pause dur="short"/> I was dipped in a bowl of zinc which</u>
<u n="22" who="S0355" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah absolutely</u>
<u n="23" who="S0281">which made me move <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="24" who="S0355">make you run wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0355">well there's galvanic action <pause dur="long"/> galvanic action is not <pause dur="short"/> believe it or not <pause dur="short"/> the same as galvanising someone or something</u>
<u n="27" who="S0281">it's got a specific specific erm <pause dur="short"/> meaning in in metallurgy</u>
<u n="28" who="S0355">mm</u>
<u n="29" who="S0281">mm <pause dur="short"/> okay so you got that done <pause dur="short"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0355">mm <pause dur="short"/> got that done we dry fitted it you anything you make in a er that's got galvanised <pause dur="short"/> has got to be assembled you've got to be able to manufacture so that it can screw together <pause dur="short"/> into transportable and handleable pieces</u>
<u n="31" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0355">and then assembled with screws</u>
<u n="33" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="S0355">rather than something that <pause dur="short"/> can be fabricated by welding it all together <pause dur="short"/> and erm the reason for that is that if you <pause dur="short"/> weld something that's been galvanised you destroy the galvanised coating</u>
<u n="35" who="S0281">well I expect you would</u>
<u n="36" who="S0355">it burns off</u>
<u n="37" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="38" who="S0355">there you go</u>
<u n="39" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="40" who="S0355">so that's what we did we did a dry run we fitted it we found out <pause dur="short"/> erm where there could be pitfalls we overcame any pitfalls and then we marked positions in it to drill counter some clearance holes for screws which would <pause dur="short"/> have provide <pause dur="short"/> holes for the screws to fix it to the handrail</u>
<u n="41" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0355">so</u>
<u n="43" who="S0281">we being you and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0355">yes <pause dur="short"/> and then we erm <pause dur="short"/> part of the balcony was rotten the wood and I went and bought some wood hardener which is like a mixture of resins in a <pause dur="short"/> in a solvent and you paint the wood with that the the resins sink deep into the wood er pardon me the solvent vaporises and then the wood hardens the wood becomes waterproof and hard and when then you can we use just a plastic filler on top of that resin for the resin filler to fill in bits of</u>
<u n="45" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="46" who="S0355">wood to make it build it up</u>
<u n="47" who="S0281">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> you get your money off <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then? <pause dur="short"/> did you get your money off <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I did paid er for that he's put it in my bank four hundred quid he <trunc>pu</trunc> did that the other day</u>
<u n="49" who="S0281">that's good</u>
<u n="50" who="S0355">I was <trunc>thi</trunc> I think I'll text him because he wants me to do more work down there</u>
<u n="51" who="S0281">oh splendid</u>
<u n="52" who="S0355">tile the bathroom which will be a day or two days' work down there fiddling around <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="long"/> so that's good and and er the opportunity for me to earn a thousand quid came in</u>
<u n="53" who="S0281">oh wonderful</u>
<u n="54" who="S0355">so that will pay my <pause dur="short"/> national insurance contributions that I owe four hundred and thirty-one quid to <pause dur="short"/> hurrah <pause dur="short"/> and pay pay them er cos they were making noises <pause dur="short"/> the government has decided to change the ways in which er</u>
<u n="55" who="S0281" trans="overlap">we we'll be <unclear/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0355">which we are <pause dur="short"/> we pay our National Insurance contributions so <pause dur="short"/> I now have to <pause dur="short"/> well I don't have to I think pay it with your tax you pay it with the tax at the end of the year</u>
<u n="57" who="S0281">do you? what if you're self-employed?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0355">well that's what they're changing it to yes</u>
<u n="59" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0355">which is fine by me it's great good idea</u>
<u n="61" who="S0281">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes it is in a way erm good part about it is you you just have to muck about with it once</u>
<u n="62" who="S0355">yes exactly</u>
<u n="63" who="S0281">the the downside of course is that it's a large sum</u>
<u n="64" who="S0355">well they never were that er <pause dur="short"/> they never pursued you very <pause dur="short"/> greatly when you didn't pay it</u>
<u n="65" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="66" who="S0355">it wasn't something that they cared about much but <pause dur="short"/> erm what they did do erm <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> I know that I've got to pay one more year to qualify for my pension</u>
<u n="67" who="S0281">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0355">for a full pension</u>
<u n="69" who="S0281">oh good</u>
<u n="70" who="S0355">I've paid for</u>
<u n="71" who="S0281">how much is that a week?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0355" trans="overlap">nineteen years sorry?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0281">hundred and thirty-five is it a week?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0355">probably which is good to have you know</u>
<u n="75" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0355">that's alright <pause dur="short"/> better than nothing and erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it'll be brilliant to have that</u>
<u n="77" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well some people have to live on that don't they?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0355">sorry?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0281">some people have to live on it</u>
<u n="80" who="S0355">some people have to live on it I don't know how the hell they do I can't imagine how you one does</u>
<u n="81" who="S0281">you have to be very careful</u>
<u n="82" who="S0355">I would imagine you do bloody hell <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> but er <pause dur="long"/> yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0281">I had an unusual day</u>
<u n="84" who="S0355">oh what happened in your day?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0281">well first of all <pause dur="short"/> er I was thinking about phoning <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and then I tried on the on the Skype</u>
<u n="86" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="87" who="S0281" trans="overlap">to get through and</u>
<u n="88" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="89" who="S0281">immediately it said call failed I mean I tried call failed</u>
<u n="90" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="91" who="S0281">so I thought what on earth is that about? <pause dur="short"/> so I tried <pause dur="short"/> er contacting you</u>
<u n="92" who="S0355">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0281">and it went er and it was ringing so I thought okay it's well it's not my Skype that's er</u>
<u n="94" who="S0355" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="95" who="S0281">affected</u>
<u n="96" who="S0355">no</u>
<u n="97" who="S0281">it's it must be <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> so</u>
<u n="98" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh right yes</u>
<u n="99" who="S0281">so I used my phone to phone her and it said she was busy so I thought ah well that must be it but it</u>
<u n="100" who="S0355" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="101" who="S0281">because er she the phone's being used and I <trunc>mea</trunc> so anyway erm she must have er when she'd finished talking she must have seen that I'd been trying to contact her because she <trunc>ph</trunc> she contacted me on Skype so</u>
<u n="102" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="103" who="S0281">I managed to speak to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and erm er you know it's the same thing every time I I feel so <pause dur="short"/> oh you know a mixture of <pause dur="short"/> guilt for not being there with her and <pause dur="short"/> being lonely and <pause dur="short"/> not seeing her but it I mean it's good that I do see her</u>
<u n="104" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="105" who="S0281">and talk to her</u>
<u n="106" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="107" who="S0281">so anyway er when that was finished then I decided to go and get those wellingtons or at least check them out</u>
<u n="108" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="109" who="S0281">and I thought well before I do that I'll I'll go down to Vodafone because the contract I signed with them is two quid more than er it's two quid yeah it's two quid less than they've charged me for</u>
<u n="110" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="111" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well it's only two quid but you know two quid's two quid right? so I was going to go down to Vodafone to to find that out cos now I I I can check my account</u>
<u n="112" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0281">online and on my Ipad</u>
<u n="114" who="S0355">I'm with you</u>
<u n="115" who="S0281">and I can see how much I've used in minutes</u>
<u n="116" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="117" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and in er emails and although it's really very good how you how it's shown so anyway er that's what I'd planned to do and then do a bit of shopping</u>
<u n="118" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="119" who="S0281">and <pause dur="short"/> I thought right so off I went <pause dur="short"/> and found the shop well actually I didn't see the shop straight away I went down the street which strangely enough is called <anon type="place"/> street</u>
<u n="120" who="S0355">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0281">a street named after you also and <pause dur="short"/> as I was walking down right opposite where this er er spiral shop is <pause dur="short"/> was a very small</u>
<u n="122" who="S0355"><unclear/></u>
<u n="123" who="S0281"><trunc>n</trunc>no it's a small office and it said er English lessons or something like that so I thought well</u>
<u n="124" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="125" who="S0281">erm I'll pop in there anyway it doesn't look very big</u>
<u n="126" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0281">I'll pop in just to</u>
<u n="128" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0281">just to see and there was this old Arab guy sitting at the desk</u>
<u n="130" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="131" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and I said <foreign lang="ara">salaam</foreign> and he said <foreign lang="ara">salaam-Alaikum</foreign> you know erm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0355">yes as they do</u>
<u n="133" who="S0281">yes and er <pause dur="short"/> I'm saying I'm an English teacher looking for work and then he <trunc>sai</trunc> oh really yes he said well you know you know started chatting chatting and <pause dur="short"/> erm so after about five minutes of us both standing there <vocal desc="laugh"/> I said well shall we sit down? he said oh yes yes and so we sat down <pause dur="short"/> and <pause dur="short"/> very personable and <pause dur="short"/> we were chatting away and he was telling me about er his business</u>
<u n="134" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="135" who="S0281">and I <trunc>go</trunc> I started to get the feeling that he must he must be a bit lonely cos he he started telling me about <pause dur="short"/> erm what are you looking for?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0355">belt</u>
<u n="137" who="S0281">oh erm <pause dur="short"/> is that it?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0355">no that's not it</u>
<u n="139" who="S0281">well where's it gone?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0355">I dunno</u>
<u n="141" who="S0281">this is the new one I bought</u>
<u n="142" who="S0355">oh right I've got it right on then</u>
<u n="143" who="S0281">so he he's chatting the chatting</u>
<u n="144" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0281">and er <pause dur="short"/> he's he's turned into er <pause dur="short"/> telling me about his life story</u>
<u n="146" who="S0355">oh right</u>
<u n="147" who="S0281">and how that he comes from Jordan and over there if you <trunc>co</trunc> and he comes from the desert and when you're you're in the desert you it's not like being born in a hospital there's no record of your birth</u>
<u n="148" who="S0355">well that's handy</u>
<u n="149" who="S0281" trans="overlap">so honest he showed me his passport</u>
<u n="150" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="151" who="S0281">and there's no date of birth on there</u>
<u n="152" who="S0355">oh right</u>
<u n="153" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and</u>
<u n="154" who="S0355" trans="overlap">amazing</u>
<u n="155" who="S0281">yeah er he's telling me about his family he's got five daughters erm they've all put have gone to college got masters one's</u>
<u n="156" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="157" who="S0281">a solicitor and one works with him and all the rest of it</u>
<u n="158" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="159" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and it started it it <trunc>star</trunc> it he he was getting into it was like a life story you know and and then after I don't know about ten or fifteen minutes he said oh do you want a coffee or something? yeah thank you very much so I thought oh well I know it's a nice sunny day and I'm missing the sunshine but I've got nothing else to do so you know I'll chat with him <pause dur="short"/> and he was telling me about all what he used to do how he used to be a colonel in the army</u>
<u n="160" who="S0355">oh right</u>
<u n="161" who="S0281">in in Jordan</u>
<u n="162" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="163" who="S0281">and then was transferred to the air force</u>
<u n="164" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="165" who="S0281">and at one stage had thirty thousand thirty-two thousand men <trunc>un</trunc>under him</u>
<u n="166" who="S0355">good god</u>
<u n="167" who="S0281">yeah and how er he's er <pause dur="short"/> you now got in contact with er princes er cos there are thousands of princes over there</u>
<u n="168" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="169" who="S0281">and you know all the the <pause dur="short"/> all these important people that he knows and erm as as his life story <trunc>un</trunc>unfolded er</u>
<u n="170" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="171" who="S0281">he was telling me about er over here he's got three masters degrees and he went to</u>
<u n="172" who="S0355" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="173" who="S0281"><anon type="place"/> for one of them and he actually well at some stage took out his phone and showed me a lecture or a talk rather not a lecture</u>
<u n="174" who="S0355">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0281">there was a talk he was giving at Sussex University to a a group of people who have come er from all over the world or something</u>
<u n="176" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="177" who="S0281">so I know it wasn't bullshit you know he he's a straight up guy</u>
<u n="178" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="179" who="S0281">and while he's making the coffee I saw these framed certificates on the wall</u>
<u n="180" who="S0355">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0281" trans="overlap">er of how he's er an agent for all these different organisations</u>
<u n="182" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="183" who="S0281" trans="overlap">one of who is Kaplan you know you've heard me talk about them erm they're er a placement agency for lots of universities and things like that</u>
<u n="184" who="S0355">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="185" who="S0281">and er he had three or four of these on the wall er so I <trunc>sai</trunc> and and he was telling me about his life and er ah he's you know <pause dur="short"/> done a lot of things er met a lot of people erm <pause dur="short"/> er some very important er and er he showed me a letter that he'd recently written cos somebody was wanting to find out about his company and</u>
<u n="186" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0281">he showed me the letter I thought it was er to start with it was to check his English</u>
<u n="188" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0281">and I I started and I said well the <trunc>Eng</trunc>English is perfect he he said yes but he said well what about the content? I said oh oh sorry I was reading it primarily for checking your and I thought that's what you wanted me to me to do <vocal desc="laugh"/> but er he said I said yeah that's fine it's erm you know explained what about all <trunc>hi</trunc> about what his company does about how they <pause dur="short"/> find places at universities for students from abroad</u>
<u n="190" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0281">which is pretty much what the the woman used to do on erm who was my next door neighbour who gave me the office you know?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="193" who="S0281">and er <pause dur="short"/> and he said well yes he said er if I can he said er you know obviously it's a quiet time of the year but er if I can find you some work er you know I'll put you act as a middleman put your contacts said I don't want any money for it er I'll find you some work you know so I was I dunno I I told him a little bit about my background and we were chatting away there for over an hour</u>
<u n="194" who="S0355">brilliant</u>
<u n="195" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0355">yeah great great</u>
<u n="197" who="S0281">and <pause dur="short"/> nearly at the end of it my phone went and it was the <unclear>DOS</unclear> from that school that er I told you about wanted me to teach</u>
<u n="198" who="S0355">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0281">and she said oh can you do my <unclear>IOFS</unclear> lesson on Monday morning?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0355">oh great yeah</u>
<u n="201" who="S0281">I said yeah okay so</u>
<u n="202" who="S0355">do you need any books for that?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0281">well yes but they've got one she said er in the school there where I can get photocopies from <pause dur="short"/> so I said right I'll I'll be er she said come come round about four o'clock I said okay <pause dur="short"/> so I had time to er go over the road buy my wellies and the belts and come back here and change <pause dur="short"/> and er went off there <pause dur="short"/> and saw her I saw her boss first of all who's also an IOFS examiner and he was telling me that he goes up to London <pause dur="short"/> to examine</u>
<u n="204" who="S0355">oh right</u>
<u n="205" who="S0281">because there's not much in <anon type="place"/> you know they don't you know</u>
<u n="206" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0281">and I thought well that's <trunc>n</trunc> I don't really wanna go up to London and he said and he said well <pause dur="short"/> erm it's only er an hour on the train</u>
<u n="208" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="209" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and it's er right behind <anon type="place"/> station</u>
<u n="210" who="S0355">there you go</u>
<u n="211" who="S0281">so I said oh okay <pause dur="short"/> but it's er the they run it differently from <pause dur="short"/> china cos er here</u>
<u n="212" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0281">it's er you get paid I think eight pound fifty for one interview and eight pound for a writing script</u>
<u n="214" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="215" who="S0281">and what most of the examiners do they they do boo both speaking and writing but I never used to do writing</u>
<u n="216" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="217" who="S0281" trans="overlap">because you in China you have to be on BC premises that means you have to live in one of the four centres</u>
<u n="218" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="219" who="S0281">like in Shanghai you you have to go actually go there so that's why he works there so what examiners do is that you only get about <pause dur="short"/> a a dozen interviews <pause dur="short"/> er and then they do mark er mark the writing scripts</u>
<u n="220" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="221" who="S0281">and that's how they they make their money in a day</u>
<u n="222" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0281">erm but it it wouldn't be worth it for me cos I'd <trunc>onl</trunc> I'm only certified er for erm for the speaking and it just wouldn't be worth it you know <pause dur="short"/> especially erm the after if you haven't tested for three months er then you have to you <trunc>d</trunc>do six and they check to see if you're</u>
<u n="224" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="225" who="S0281">still</u>
<u n="226" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="227" who="S0281">marking accurately and then you can go for the full but in like in China you go for the weekend you stay in a five star hotel</u>
<u n="228" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0281">and er you do thirty interviews for the weekend and er you know get about four hundred quid</u>
<u n="230" who="S0355">fucking nora</u>
<u n="231" who="S0281">for the erm for the weekend</u>
<u n="232" who="S0355">that's amazing</u>
<u n="233" who="S0281">but here it's it just doesn't seem like it's worth it you know? if if it's in Brighton it would be worth it but not not going up to London <pause dur="short"/> anyway he gave me a phone number of a woman to contact <pause dur="short"/> so I was chatting with the director of studies about what she wanted me to do <pause dur="short"/> and it was only er an hour and a half class on Monday morning <pause dur="short"/> and the way she described it is er <pause dur="short"/> they don't seem to <pause dur="short"/> be all that good as a school really cos er she said the type of work I can offer you at the moment is er is <trunc>co</trunc> on cover <pause dur="short"/> you know if if somebody er</u>
<u n="234" who="S0355">if someone's sick</u>
<u n="235" who="S0281" trans="overlap">is calls in sick</u>
<u n="236" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0281">and they she'll call me up</u>
<u n="238" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0281">like half an hour's notice and say oh can you</u>
<u n="240" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="241" who="S0281">come in straight away and do it of course you <trunc>ca</trunc> haven't got any time for preparation right?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0355">god</u>
<u n="243" who="S0281">you've got to wing it <pause dur="short"/> er which of course I could do but <pause dur="short"/> you fixed it?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="245" who="S0281">oh you're brilliant</u>
<u n="246" who="S0355"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0281">what was wrong with it?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0355">well in there <pause dur="short"/> behind if you open it <pause dur="short"/> if you open it and withdraw the just open it click you little lever and open it</u>
<u n="249" who="S0281">mm <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="250" who="S0355">no open it <pause dur="short"/> that's it now if you see the little round button here</u>
<u n="251" who="S0281" trans="overlap">here?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0355">well that is hollow and in the back of there's a magnet</u>
<u n="253" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0355">and the magnet is not a fixed it's loose in there it's <trunc>w</trunc> er and when you click that up to it pulls it off the magnet well</u>
<u n="255" who="S0281" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0355">what happen is the magnet gets loose because it's loose it can jam up in there</u>
<u n="257" who="S0281">oh and that's what happened?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0355">and the magnet jammed up in there</u>
<u n="259" who="S0281">oh you clever chap thank you very much</u>
<u n="260" who="S0355">that's alright</u>
<u n="261" who="S0281">put it on my bill?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0355">yeah okay</u>
<u n="263" who="S0281">so erm anyway <pause dur="short"/> she at first first of all she started er saying oh er can you do reading exercises? and er so I said yeah alright <pause dur="short"/> and but in the end we decided that I was gonna do writing <pause dur="short"/> and er <pause dur="short"/> but the way</u>
<u n="264" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I thought you didn't do writing</u>
<u n="265" who="S0281">yeah but I can teach it <pause dur="short"/> I can't</u>
<u n="266" who="S0355" trans="overlap">examine it</u>
<u n="267" who="S0281">I can't be an examiner</u>
<u n="268" who="S0355">oh I see</u>
<u n="269" who="S0281">but <pause dur="short"/> anyway so we went through er what she wanted me to do and I I gave her my ideas and <pause dur="short"/> said right I'll need some photocopies of this and this she said yeah okay we'll get all that done for Monday morning <pause dur="short"/> er I said well <trunc>cou</trunc>could I come in on Sunday and they're closed at the weekends which for me is a very strange</u>
<u n="270" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="271" who="S0281">concept because er <pause dur="short"/> in China everybody works seven days a week you know <vocal desc="laugh"/> if you're the sort of language schools things and the weekends is the busiest time</u>
<u n="272" who="S0355">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="273" who="S0281" trans="overlap">but not here</u>
<u n="274" who="S0355">no</u>
<u n="275" who="S0281">anyway <pause dur="short"/> so Monday morning I've got my first lesson</u>
<u n="276" who="S0355">brilliant</u>
<u n="277" who="S0281">since</u>
<u n="278" who="S0355" trans="overlap">how much is that?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0281">oh it's not very much it's about fourteen and a half quid but it'll be even less than that</u>
<u n="280" who="S0355">what for an hour?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0355">fourteen and a half quid?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0355" trans="overlap">that's all you get for Monday morning?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0281">well for an hour for <trunc>hou</trunc> I'll be doing an hour and a half <pause dur="short"/> so it's not very much</u>
<u n="286" who="S0355">twenty-one quid</u>
<u n="287" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="288" who="S0355" trans="overlap">do you get travelling?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0281">no of course not no <pause dur="short"/> you can walk there</u>
<u n="290" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="291" who="S0281" trans="overlap">and erm</u>
<u n="292" who="S0355">where's this in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0281">no <anon type="place"/> road</u>
<u n="294" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="295" who="S0281">I can walk there in fifteen minutes</u>
<u n="296" who="S0355">oh that's just along the the the</u>
<u n="297" who="S0281">by the arcade</u>
<u n="298" who="S0355">by the arcade yeah gotcha</u>
<u n="299" who="S0281">so and it's a <trunc>st</trunc> first step you know</u>
<u n="300" who="S0355" trans="overlap">of course</u>
<u n="301" who="S0281">it's a first</u>
<u n="302" who="S0355" trans="overlap">oh absolutely</u>
<u n="303" who="S0281" trans="overlap">you know it's</u>
<u n="304" who="S0355">I'm I'm I'm fully behind you there</u>
<u n="305" who="S0281">so</u>
<u n="306" who="S0355">I'm not bemoaning the dosh I just think it's brilliant</u>
<u n="307" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="308" who="S0355">you know you've got er <pause dur="short"/> you know you will soon you're brilliant at this</u>
<u n="309" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh yeah I forgot I forgot to tell you when I was talking to this guy this Arab guy he's called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="311" who="S0281" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> not <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and er he said you know what if I er could get you a a job er in er like a head of studies or something like that?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0281">I said what would this be er in the Middle East? he said yes probably maybe a er <pause dur="short"/> saudi Arabia or Qatar</u>
<u n="314" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I said and I was sort of very thinking very quickly and I said well I've already <pause dur="short"/> erm seen adverts for jobs over there and I also one of my ex-colleagues er works in er Saudi Arabia and he lives on a compound and it sounds mm a bit isolated and all the rest of it and I said but but I said the reason I'm hesitating is that you know I've got a commitment in the summer to go and see my daughter er he said oh yes yeah of course of course er <pause dur="short"/> so so anyway in the end I just said er you know I'll send him my CV and <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="316" who="S0355">did he give you a an email address?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0281">well I've got his card</u>
<u n="318" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="319" who="S0281">where is it?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0355">well that's fantastic</u>
<u n="321" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="322" who="S0355">if he can get you something sorted out with er <pause dur="short"/> head of studies? blimey go for it <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> that might be the thing that is fantastic buys you a little flat and er keeps your daughter in <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="323" who="S0281">yeah well</u>
<u n="324" who="S0355" trans="overlap">whatever</u>
<u n="325" who="S0281" trans="overlap">it's erm <pause dur="short"/> I was telling him that the way I work as a teacher on one to ones</u>
<u n="326" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="327" who="S0281">and I said whenever I get a new student I cos they always think or hope that they can <pause dur="short"/> make tremendous strides in a short time</u>
<u n="328" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="329" who="S0281" trans="overlap">you know and I tell them straight away like it is you know it's it takes a lot of study</u>
<u n="330" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="331" who="S0281">to improve your standard of English you're not gonna do it it's not gonna be done quickly</u>
<u n="332" who="S0355">no</u>
<u n="333" who="S0281">er so that's the way I work I try and be honest and fair you know and tell them like it is from the start</u>
<u n="334" who="S0355">of course</u>
<u n="335" who="S0281">erm <pause dur="short"/> so er <pause dur="short"/> I erm <pause dur="short"/> I said that and he said well yeah that's er er that's good <pause dur="short"/> and so <pause dur="short"/> er I hope that well I'll I'll send him my CV tonight</u>
<u n="336" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="337" who="S0281">and er er in a week or two I'll pop in and just say hi and just do <trunc>c</trunc>cos <pause dur="short"/> he's obviously <pause dur="short"/> been an important man and is and is still</u>
<u n="338" who="S0355" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0281" trans="overlap">you know is if he's still giving talks at you know at <anon type="place"/> university to</u>
<u n="340" who="S0355" trans="overlap">on what?</u>
<u n="341" who="S0281">oh he's just telling welcoming everybody who come and er for the er talk and</u>
<u n="342" who="S0355">what's he talking on about?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0281">well it was just welcoming people to the reason what they're I don't know what the reason was everybody <pause dur="short"/> congregated there had been summoned but he he'd been asked to give a talk so well a welcoming speech or something like that</u>
<u n="344" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="345" who="S0281">and obviously I'm everything he told me I believed</u>
<u n="346" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="347" who="S0281">you know he's obviously been er some different stages in his life a very important man <pause dur="short"/> with a lot of contacts</u>
<u n="348" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0281">so I don't think it was bullshit <pause dur="short"/> so er anyway it's it's good to build up <pause dur="short"/> a relationship I'll just pop in and say hi you know <pause dur="short"/> so er all in all</u>
<u n="350" who="S0355" trans="overlap">that sounds wonderful</u>
<u n="351" who="S0281">it was right quite a positive day</u>
<u n="352" who="S0355">absolutely yeah <pause dur="short"/> sounds brilliant</u>
<u n="353" who="S0281">got a potential <pause dur="short"/> useful contact</u>
<u n="354" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="355" who="S0281">and got my first <pause dur="short"/> teaching er for my first lesson</u>
<u n="356" who="S0355">fantastic</u>
<u n="357" who="S0281">for months so</u>
<u n="358" who="S0355">that's brilliant</u>
<u n="359" who="S0281">can't complain really</u>
<u n="360" who="S0355">brilliant</u>
<u n="361" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="362" who="S0355">I would have thought though you could have commanded more money from than going in or on the chance of doing something for being called in for an emergency to cover is for fourteen quid an hour is seems to me</u>
<u n="363" who="S0281">it's it's</u>
<u n="364" who="S0355" trans="overlap">crazy</u>
<u n="365" who="S0281">it is <pause dur="short"/> but beggars can't be choosers you know I I'm doing it</u>
<u n="366" who="S0355">sure yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0281" trans="overlap">because I've got nothing else to do</u>
<u n="368" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0281">except write off for jobs and it's gonna get me out of the house it's gonna get me teaching again</u>
<u n="370" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="371" who="S0281" trans="overlap">thinking about teaching</u>
<u n="372" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="373" who="S0281">I'm gonna make contacts</u>
<u n="374" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="375" who="S0281">and <trunc>i</trunc>it's it's it's things like this one thing can lead to another you know</u>
<u n="376" who="S0355" trans="overlap">sure yeah no that's true that's true</u>
<u n="377" who="S0281" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="378" who="S0355" trans="overlap">for sure</u>
<u n="379" who="S0281">I know it's it's pitiful money</u>
<u n="380" who="S0355">it seems outrageous</u>
<u n="381" who="S0281">it is <pause dur="short"/> but that's that's the way it is for just casual work <pause dur="short"/> but <trunc>lo</trunc>look at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and how much trouble he's got finding any work I mean building labourer driver anything</u>
<u n="382" who="S0355">is it bad? did he say it was bad then?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0281">well he he told me that he'd he'd he's trying for all sorts of things writing off and he mentioned that er as far as driving jobs go he's <pause dur="short"/> he's er he's got convictions for <trunc>dri</trunc> you know and er he's</u>
<u n="384" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="385" who="S0281" trans="overlap">he he said well they'll just give me a chance and I'll even pay half the er increased cost of the insurance</u>
<u n="386" who="S0355">uhu</u>
<u n="387" who="S0281">yeah if they take him on and that kind of thing so I think he's pretty desperate to</u>
<u n="388" who="S0355">to work</u>
<u n="389" who="S0281" trans="overlap">to get work</u>
<u n="390" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah I'm sure he is</u>
<u n="391" who="S0281">and he</u>
<u n="392" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I'm sure he is yeah I just yeah <pause dur="short"/> I have a deeply suspicious nature and and a paranoia about people anyway because I've been fucked and stuffed and ripped off and done over too many times sometimes for thousands of pounds so</u>
<u n="393" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="394" who="S0355">you know</u>
<u n="395" who="S0281">well</u>
<u n="396" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I I</u>
<u n="397" who="S0281" trans="overlap">you know</u>
<u n="398" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I I I I've lived with people who just fucking lie <vocal desc="laugh"/> they lie and lie and lie</u>
<u n="399" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well I mean I don't know</u>
<u n="400" who="S0355" trans="overlap">and I just</u>
<u n="401" who="S0281" trans="overlap">maybe he is but I <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="402" who="S0355" trans="overlap">so no no no no I but I I'm I I I tend to go along with what you think about it but</u>
<u n="403" who="S0281">I think he is trying</u>
<u n="404" who="S0355">yeah I'm sure yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0281">but yesterday the positive thing he was er said er you know hello to him and said oh how are you? he said oh I'm find yeah so it's like he said yeah I feel a lot better I said oh that's good and I went yes yes er and erm not that anything particular happened I think he's just <pause dur="short"/> doing what I'm trying to do <pause dur="short"/> dig himself out of this <pause dur="short"/> dark hole of depression you know and he seems like he's succeeding he's a lot perkier and er</u>
<u n="406" who="S0355" trans="overlap">that's good</u>
<u n="407" who="S0281">I said er you know I said oh good you know well done erm I said you know some people look they look at a situation and they see a problem and other people they look at it and they see an opportunity so</u>
<u n="408" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0281">and he said yeah absolutely so it seems like he's got his motivation there you know like he he seemed like he was down the other day</u>
<u n="410" who="S0355">yeah</u>
<u n="411" who="S0281">he seems a lot better in that er aspect or respect</u>
<u n="412" who="S0355" trans="overlap">that's good</u>
<u n="413" who="S0281">and er</u>
<u n="414" who="S0355">well maybe it was partly the job getting him down</u>
<u n="415" who="S0281">I don't know I I didn't ask him about you know did he leave or was he pushed</u>
<u n="416" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="417" who="S0281">I thought well if he if he wants me to know he'll tell me you know <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm starting to do it you know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0355">what?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0281">you know</u>
<u n="420" who="S0355">do what?</u>
<u n="421" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you do it subconsciously or unconsciously don't you? you know cos you hear every</u>
<u n="422" who="S0355"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0281">everybody saying it <pause dur="short"/> in the street or on TV</u>
<u n="424" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="425" who="S0281">all levels of society right from</u>
<u n="426" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="427" who="S0281">those people on benefits that we were listening to in the <trunc>sh</trunc> listening to only yesterday</u>
<u n="428" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="429" who="S0281">right up to interviewers on national TV</u>
<u n="430" who="S0355">yes <pause dur="short"/> but er</u>
<u n="431" who="S0281" trans="overlap">you know what does it mean?</u>
<u n="432" who="S0355" trans="overlap">what do you prefer? do you prefer that or the American rising rising inflection?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0281">you know? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="434" who="S0355">rising <trunc>inflex</trunc></u>
<u n="435" who="S0281" trans="overlap">you know? erm</u>
<u n="436" who="S0355">what is it you</u>
<u n="437" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well it's not just American</u>
<u n="438" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="439" who="S0281" trans="overlap">it's er Australians speak like that as well</u>
<u n="440" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well there you go</u>
<u n="441" who="S0281" trans="overlap">as well?</u>
<u n="442" who="S0355" trans="overlap">both both fucking annoying people</u>
<u n="443" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well I'd prefer if nobody says it because I was from a a teaching point of view if er somebody asks me well what does it mean? <pause dur="short"/> and how I would explain it it it really doesn't serve much purpose it's actually called classified as what's called a discourse marker and <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>thi</trunc> I was trying to find another meaning you could substitute for it erm I suppose <pause dur="short"/> you could say it's short for er do you know what I mean? which is serves the same purpose er almost like a what we call a a tag question when tag questions are <trunc>n</trunc></u>
<u n="444" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I think it's it's searching for reassurance that the person who's being told the information or the story is following it and understanding it and I think I believe they're they're they're asking for</u>
<u n="445" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="446" who="S0355">confirmation</u>
<u n="447" who="S0281" trans="overlap">confirmation</u>
<u n="448" who="S0355" trans="overlap">of that</u>
<u n="449" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="450" who="S0355">so it may be the that erm and there's also a certain sense of something you know sharing about it</u>
<u n="451" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="452" who="S0355">when they say you know you know it's rather like</u>
<u n="453" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm yeah</u>
<u n="454" who="S0355" trans="overlap">having a fag together</u>
<u n="455" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="456" who="S0355" trans="overlap">or a beer it's you know you're you're joining in a story and</u>
<u n="457" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="458" who="S0355">you're becoming you're you're sort of bonding</u>
<u n="459" who="S0281" trans="overlap">it's to encourage</u>
<u n="460" who="S0355" trans="overlap">people's common experience</u>
<u n="461" who="S0281" trans="overlap">it's to encourage active listening <pause dur="short"/> isn't it? rather than passive listening where somebody's</u>
<u n="462" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0281" trans="overlap">just sitting there and</u>
<u n="464" who="S0355">yes</u>
<u n="465" who="S0281">active listening is when you're involved and you you do some <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>u</trunc>utter some kind of</u>
<u n="466" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0281">response oh yes you know or things like this you know</u>
<u n="468" who="S0355">unless</u>
<u n="469" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yes I agree or</u>
<u n="470" who="S0355" trans="overlap">unless the person talking is also addressing their their erm <pause dur="short"/> ego <vocal desc="laugh"/> or or talking to themselves perhaps <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0281">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="472" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> maybe we do maybe we do talk to ourselves <pause dur="short"/> maybe it's said <trunc>i</trunc> in <pause dur="short"/> in parenthesis in in in a way <pause dur="short"/> it's er <pause dur="short"/> to ourselves how about that?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="474" who="S0355">there's something to think about</u>
<u n="475" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="476" who="S0355" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="477" who="S0281">well I'm sure some academic has written some paper on it <pause dur="long"/> another thing I find very annoying in common parlance especially in young people is this overused word like <pause dur="short"/> like I was doing this like it's unreal like like and it it's well everything's like nothing is actually real it's it's <vocal desc="laugh"/> er like <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> so I said like erm</u>
<u n="478" who="S0355">what instead of saying comparable to? <pause dur="short"/> you could compare it to that sort of</u>
<u n="479" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well again it it's it's it doesn't serve much</u>
<u n="480" who="S0355"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0281">communicative purpose it's just a habit that people copy <pause dur="long"/> I suppose when we were young we had <pause dur="short"/> words that were everybody used in that generation like one springs to mind is cool <pause dur="short"/> every</u>
<u n="482" who="S0355" trans="overlap">is</u>
<u n="483" who="S0281" trans="overlap">all the <trunc>ki</trunc> cool oh that's cool</u>
<u n="484" who="S0355" trans="overlap">well that's what the kids say now</u>
<u n="485" who="S0281">do they still do it?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0355" trans="overlap">yes oh yes</u>
<u n="487" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yes oh okay <pause dur="short"/> or far out <pause dur="short"/> far out man</u>
<u n="488" who="S0355">no they don't say that</u>
<u n="489" who="S0281" trans="overlap">no they don't say it any more</u>
<u n="490" who="S0355" trans="overlap">that's old-fashioned</u>
<u n="491" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah so every generation's got its er</u>
<u n="492" who="S0355" trans="overlap">I say it to them because to my son and use as many obtuse words that I can remember from my youth because it makes him and his friends giggle <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="493" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0355">and he says people don't say that any more dad</u>
<u n="495" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="496" who="S0355">so I I</u>
<u n="497" who="S0281" trans="overlap">just old farts like you</u>
<u n="498" who="S0355" trans="overlap">it encourages it to <trunc>m</trunc> use it even more</u>
<u n="499" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="500" who="S0355"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh</u>
<u n="501" who="S0281">well I suppose I'd better get back to my emails <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0355">great good that's good well done <pause dur="short"/> well it's this arm is getting much better now</u>
<u n="503" who="S0281">good</u>
<u n="504" who="S0355">unbelievable just I think I knew it would I knew it fucking would I <unclear/> I knew it wouldn't <unclear/> cos it's quite a thing I have I have quite a lot of you've seen those drinks of spinach that I have?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="506" who="S0355">I mean that's but if you eat raw vegetables that's the best thing you can eat</u>
<u n="507" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="508" who="S0355">it gives you so much energy</u>
<u n="509" who="S0281">mm it's almost like your body's saying oh thank you at last</u>
<u n="510" who="S0355">it is yes</u>
<u n="511" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I've got some good things to nourish on</u>
<u n="512" who="S0355">it is yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's right isn't it?</u>
<u n="513" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="514" who="S0355">well I think I'm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0281" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="516" who="S0355">I'm going going to go and have a kip</u>
<u n="517" who="S0281">really? okay</u>
<u n="518" who="S0355" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="519" who="S0281">okay I've put some clothes that were dry from over there on your bed</u>
<u n="520" who="S0355">oh thanks <pause dur="short"/> thank you thank you indeed <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0281">okey-dokey then go and have your kip mate</u>
<u n="522" who="S0355">right</u>
<u n="523" who="S0281">you deserve it</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
