<text id="SR3P">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:20:00</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-02-23</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0653 S0654 S0655</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Home kitchen, Comberton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Balanceability, succeeding at something, assessments, homeschooling, a school friend’s new house being renovated, swimming pools, manmade waterfall, the dangers of diving into water, conversations at school, cats and National Cat Day in Japan, good food combinations, pizza</topics>
		<activity>Family talking about Balanceability and things at school</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0653">
				<exactage>39</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Dartford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0654">
				<exactage>7</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Norwich</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>1_primary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0655">
				<exactage>9</exactage>
				<age1994>0_14</age1994>
				<agerange>0_10</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Bury St Edmunds</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>UK</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>non (Southern?)</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Comberton</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>1_primary</edqual>
				<occupation>n/a</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0654">I'll break this one off</u>
<u n="2" who="S0653">so do you want to talk to tell us about the <pause dur="short"/> balance ability thing that you had to do?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0654">it was fun and a bit sad because at first it was quite fun we put on our helmets</u>
<u n="4" who="S0653">hang on don't talk really fast</u>
<u n="5" who="S0654">and then we went on some <pause dur="short"/> some cones</u>
<u n="6" who="S0653">around some cones</u>
<u n="7" who="S0654">we went on the cones</u>
<u n="8" who="S0653">you went on the cones oh</u>
<u n="9" who="S0654">yes we before we even went to the bikes</u>
<u n="10" who="S0653">why did you go on the cones?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0654">because we needed to warm up</u>
<u n="12" who="S0653">oh</u>
<u n="13" who="S0654">which was quite fun and then they said we could we needed to touch the bottom of on the on the blue cone and I thought which one there's two</u>
<u n="14" who="S0653">right</u>
<u n="15" who="S0654">but they said the first one <unclear/> aren't allowed</u>
<u n="16" who="S0653">they said the first one</u>
<u n="17" who="S0654">and they said the closest one</u>
<u n="18" who="S0653">to you</u>
<u n="19" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0653">uhu</u>
<u n="21" who="S0654">and I did that and then they said and then they said we can make it a bit harder by touching both by touching both sides on the cone</u>
<u n="22" who="S0653" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> with your hands or what I don't really?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0654">with our hands</u>
<u n="24" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="25" who="S0654">I thought that was quite cool</u>
<u n="26" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="27" who="S0654">can I have my rod please?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0653">can you have your what? yes</u>
<u n="29" who="S0654">and then after that we went on a bike we went to the bikes and what else?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0653" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> but they're balance bikes?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0654">yeah we erm we got to lift them up by bending our knees and grabbing the handlebars</u>
<u n="32" who="S0653">can you need to speak clearly dear</u>
<u n="33" who="S0654">we erm went to them and we didn't touch them until we were told and then we had to bend down on our knees grab them get them hold them upright and try to hold them steady then we had a go of walking them down I wasn't good at that my was wobbly</u>
<u n="34" who="S0653" trans="overlap">in a special way <pause dur="short"/> yours was wobbly well it is wobbly because it's you have to balance</u>
<u n="35" who="S0654">yeah and it was very heavy it was quite heavy for me</u>
<u n="36" who="S0653" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> was it a different colour to the other ones?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0654">no they were all the same colour</u>
<u n="38" who="S0653">what colour were they?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0654">black with green stripes</u>
<u n="40" who="S0653">right put your hand away from your mouth black with green stripes</u>
<u n="41" who="S0654">erm they were black with the grips with a green stripe saying something so was the helmets and so was erm and they had like this little sash on the on the handlebars and mum and then we did then we got to go on them these huge gigantic steps I was wobbling a bit I was left behind the front and the back I can't we were like</u>
<u n="42" who="S0653" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> steps? <pause dur="short"/> on the bike when you were on the bike?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0654">yeah we were like this</u>
<u n="44" who="S0653">no can you sit down come on</u>
<u n="45" who="S0654">and erm</u>
<u n="46" who="S0653">was that when you fell over?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0654">no</u>
<u n="48" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="49" who="S0654">that was on and</u>
<u n="50" who="S0653">but you did that okay?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0654">and then it was after that we did the tiny mouse steps it was and then we were trying to and then for a challenge we were trying to see how they they made us try to see how far we could go lifting our legs up erm that's and then I went downwards and I was quite good at that and there's a bit of a slope down the playground it goes like this and we still don't want to and then when we went upwards on the slope kind of bit I fell off</u>
<u n="52" who="S0653" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> good <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> oh dear</u>
<u n="53" who="S0654">and I didn't feel very proud of myself afterwards</u>
<u n="54" who="S0655"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the whole playground is sloped</u>
<u n="55" who="S0653">you must don't tap that there you must</u>
<u n="56" who="S0655">it goes like that</u>
<u n="57" who="S0653">listen people that are successful get successful because they've tried hard and they've failed at something and then they've carried on and worked hard and succeeded so that's what you are doing</u>
<u n="58" who="S0654">and when I fell over I just got on er they asked me if I was okay and I said I think so and I carried on</u>
<u n="59" who="S0653">oh baby <pause dur="short"/> brilliant</u>
<u n="60" who="S0654">but there wasn't a bit there was a bit more to go and then I and the people in the class they were just busy looking at us</u>
<u n="61" who="S0653">I know and that's not very nice is it</u>
<u n="62" who="S0654">yeah and they were like and it's really <unclear/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0653">mm is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> doing balance ability?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0654">she was she couldn't she can't ride this she can't ride a bike without stabilisers either</u>
<u n="65" who="S0653">mm goodness I'm wondering if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is going to have to take you both to school on Friday with your bikes eek mm</u>
<u n="66" who="S0655">I don't need to</u>
<u n="67" who="S0653">I know I'm talking about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="68" who="S0654">and some of the people I've seen everybody in my class did that</u>
<u n="69" who="S0653">everybody in the class did balance ability at some point did they? oh okay</u>
<u n="70" who="S0654">but some people could ride a bikes originally but I just did it</u>
<u n="71" who="S0653">I wonder if we can get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> dad to store the bikes on Thursday evening in his classroom that might be a bit easier I'll have a talk I do want to pop a little bit early to Brownies because I want to go to the village college and do some photocopying if I can <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0654">it's not Brownies yet is it?</u>
<u n="73" who="S0653">it's not Brownies yet no you've got a while yet so do you know did they tell you what you guys would be doing on Friday?</u>
<u n="74" who="S0655">no no clue</u>
<u n="75" who="S0653">but they were happy with your progress mm that's good <pause dur="long"/> <event desc="sound of eating"/> some of my students did an exam today</u>
<u n="76" who="S0655">did they all pass?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0653">I don't know because it's gonna be sent off to be marked but the questions were good</u>
<u n="78" who="S0655">what do you mean like hard?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0653">no they were ones that I knew that they they should be able to do if they've timed it properly and everything I felt that they were well prepared for those</u>
<u n="80" who="S0655">because of you?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0653">mm I guess so</u>
<u n="82" who="S0655">I would think so too</u>
<u n="83" who="S0653">mm <pause dur="short"/> there could have been other questions which would have been more of a challenge but all of these students are working in English as a second language so it is very difficult for them</u>
<u n="84" who="S0655">so they need to like <trunc>remem</trunc> so they actually need to know how to read the questions?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0653">sit down please well they it's not just reading the questions they need to understand them and be able to answer in in a lot of detail</u>
<u n="86" who="S0655">is it like adding and subtracting and times and dividing or?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0653">no it's an English thing</u>
<u n="88" who="S0655">oh</u>
<u n="89" who="S0653">I teach English don't I?</u>
<u n="90" who="S0655">mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0654">mama <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s not going to be at school any more she's going to home school</u>
<u n="92" who="S0653">what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is gonna have home school? are you serious? says <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what from when tomorrow?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0654">tomorrow and today</u>
<u n="94" who="S0653">was she not there today?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0654">she was here today and at the end of the week on Monday</u>
<u n="96" who="S0653">well why is she going to be homeschooled?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0654">I don't know</u>
<u n="98" who="S0653">does she want to be homeschooled?</u>
<u n="99" who="S0654">I don't know</u>
<u n="100" who="S0653">did you not ask her?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0654">no I don't know</u>
<u n="102" who="S0653">what did you just say oh?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0654">I don't know</u>
<u n="104" who="S0653">but how who told you?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0654"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="106" who="S0653">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0654" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0653">well why would <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> know?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0654">she told them</u>
<u n="110" who="S0653">but what did she say to you darling?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0654">she said I'm gonna I'm I'm gonna be I'm gonna have homeschool</u>
<u n="112" who="S0655">forever?</u>
<u n="113" who="S0654">yeah until we go to college</u>
<u n="114" who="S0653">I don't really understand why though <pause dur="short"/> is she not happy?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0654">I don't know</u>
<u n="116" who="S0653">well baby she's your friend</u>
<u n="117" who="S0654">I know</u>
<u n="118" who="S0653">are you not going to ask her?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0654">I'll ask her <trunc>to</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> tomorrow</u>
<u n="120" who="S0653" trans="overlap">because that would be <trunc>s</trunc> a sad thing wouldn't it? <pause dur="short"/> I mean you can still play together <pause dur="short"/> outside of school but it would just be a bit more difficult to arrange won't it? <pause dur="long"/> are you looking forward to doing your history <pause dur="short"/> experience on Saturday? <pause dur="short"/> the Ottoman Empire I don't know very much about the Ottoman Empire <pause dur="short"/> so you'll be able to tell me lots and lots <pause dur="short"/> erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum messaged me <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I well she initially said <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't mind coming to ours or you coming to his on Saturday but I said let the boys talk about it tomorrow</u>
<u n="121" who="S0655">I really really want to go to his house</u>
<u n="122" who="S0653">yeah but you are not going you are not going to go to his house because you haven't been invited because this is a <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thing but it may be <pause dur="short"/> I don't know their house is don't keep tapping their house is a bit of a building site they haven't got a roof at the moment you know <pause dur="short"/> they actually have no roof</u>
<u n="123" who="S0655">what if it rains?</u>
<u n="124" who="S0653">they've got a plastic sheet over it now</u>
<u n="125" who="S0654">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0655">what if it thunders? what if a lightning bolt strikes the roof?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0653">well I think we'd all be in trouble if that that happened but <pause dur="short"/> yeah amazing isn't it but they the lady that used to own the house was very old and so didn't really couldn't really look after the property for the last sort of ten years or so they need a new roof and a new lots of new things electricity kind of new wires and things like</u>
<u n="128" who="S0655">what are we doing?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0653">well for <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum because they were all I think it it was very cold when they went in there for a while and they were all sleeping in the same room for a bit it's just it's always this sort of thing that happens when it's not very nice weather like lots of people's boilers seem to need fixing and that kind of thing in winter it never happens in the summer because it wouldn't be too bad to have no roof in the summer would it but this is it is still winterish</u>
<u n="130" who="S0655">it wouldn't be bad at all</u>
<u n="131" who="S0653">well it depend if it was like a roasting hot day it would be okay wouldn't it but this is although it's spring it's still very icy outside</u>
<u n="132" who="S0655" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> mum</u>
<u n="133" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="134" who="S0655">in the summer I don't think I'm actually going to need a blanket</u>
<u n="135" who="S0653">no well that's why you still have your baby blanket so they're the lightest blanket you can have the thing is I don't ever sleep well in the summer because I like to have a quilt I like to be all snuggly and I find it very difficult to sleep without one even if it's really hot I still try and have a quilt</u>
<u n="136" who="S0655" trans="overlap">me to <pause dur="short"/> although I cannot sleep with a quilt in the summer</u>
<u n="137" who="S0653">no we've got like we've got an autumn quilt and a spring quilt which we put <trunc>toget</trunc> a summer quilt which we put together to make a winter one but even that is still but then we didn't really have a very hot summer last year did we? not really we had like a weekend when it was boiling and that was it</u>
<u n="138" who="S0654" trans="overlap">freezing <pause dur="short"/> you should have gone to Spain it was so hot</u>
<u n="139" who="S0653">well I yeah I <trunc>w</trunc> I mean it's alright being in a hot country if you are next to water isn't it?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0654">there was hardly any water</u>
<u n="141" who="S0653">no I mean swimming pool</u>
<u n="142" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0653">you can keep cool that way</u>
<u n="144" who="S0655">I was normally next to water</u>
<u n="145" who="S0653">sorry</u>
<u n="146" who="S0655">I was normally next to water and if not I'd probably be inside water</u>
<u n="147" who="S0653" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0654">er mama I saw this like thing on another house it was like a pool with a waterfall going into another bit and erm you could get out the other bit to the so if you like fell down that bit you couldn't get out yeah because the waterfall was going down</u>
<u n="149" who="S0653" trans="overlap">oh wow <pause dur="short"/> oh really <pause dur="short"/> into a swimming pool?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0654">into a pool</u>
<u n="151" who="S0653">into a pool that seems was it meant for people to go in there?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0654">I don't know</u>
<u n="153" who="S0653">that seems a bit of a silly design</u>
<u n="154" who="S0654">because I saw a house across</u>
<u n="155" who="S0653">how nice was it a man-made waterfall presumably someone built it?</u>
<u n="156" who="S0654">yeah it was basically like erm towers <unclear/> it was basically like a <trunc>wa</trunc> a waterfall like you've got at Legoland that you slide down</u>
<u n="157" who="S0653">like the one in Legoland ah</u>
<u n="158" who="S0654">it just goes down down down down down</u>
<u n="159" who="S0653">okay but in someone's house that's pretty cool</u>
<u n="160" who="S0654">outside</u>
<u n="161" who="S0653">well yes that would be less cool inside I think</u>
<u n="162" who="S0655">mum?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0653">yes</u>
<u n="164" who="S0654">you are allowed two <unclear/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0655">why do people die if they fall down a waterfall?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0653">well they don't necessarily die but it's a long way to fall so they tend to hit their head on something</u>
<u n="167" who="S0654">yeah and it has erm the and it has rapids you are basically like has really <unclear/></u>
<u n="168" who="S0655">no the rapids are before the waterfall</u>
<u n="169" who="S0653">the rapids are before the waterfall it <trunc>basic</trunc> it tends to have jaggedy rocks at the bottom so it's the fall I mean actually the force of water can break your arm on its own when it's very strong but it's that long drop and then for hitting something even the water because diving people when they go diving you can break an arm you know when you were doing five metre dives people do can easily break things sort of at the ten metre mark so it's hitting the force of the water badly</u>
<u n="170" who="S0655">I may have like erm I nearly broke my arm when I fell when I did a face plant into the water from the three metre</u>
<u n="171" who="S0653">well you didn't nearly break your arm but it does hurt doesn't it?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0655">yeah a huge amount</u>
<u n="173" who="S0653">it does hurt yes it's surprising how much getting landing in the water badly can really hurt</u>
<u n="174" who="S0655">yeah but if you point your feet and you land down straight as long as there's no jaggedy rocks at the bottom and it's quite and it's deep enough then you will survive</u>
<u n="175" who="S0653">but the problem with a waterfall is that that you know you are in water you are not leaping into water you are in water already and it's pushing you around and you probably don't know where you are going you can't see anything so you can't right yourself and get yourself into a position</u>
<u n="176" who="S0655"><unclear> I'm the same</unclear> I'd been like you might have actually missed the water and might be flying</u>
<u n="177" who="S0653">you might do but I just think it's very dangerous and they they can be very big drops can't they?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0653">very big but you know if you can you can be lucky <pause dur="short"/> <event desc="sound of eating"/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0655">in my It Can't be True in my It Can't be True book there's a gigantic waterfall that is like much taller than er which is taller than about five Leaning Tower of Pisa's</u>
<u n="181" who="S0653" trans="overlap">uhu <pause dur="short"/> wow really where's that then?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0655">I don't know shall I get it?</u>
<u n="183" who="S0653">not yet I wonder if it's in America like the Amazon or something</u>
<u n="184" who="S0654">or or Japan</u>
<u n="185" who="S0653">I think Japan have <trunc>water</trunc></u>
<u n="186" who="S0654">mum do you know what a boy called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in year one he told us <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> his dad was scratched by a lion</u>
<u n="187" who="S0653" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I doubt that's true</u>
<u n="188" who="S0654">yeah and he and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said oh was it in Japanee? Japanee <trunc>Jap</trunc> Jan Janpan which isn't a real country she's just made it up and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said yes</u>
<u n="189" who="S0653" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="190" who="S0655" trans="overlap">Janpan</u>
<u n="191" who="S0653">oh but he's only in year one</u>
<u n="192" who="S0654">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'm sorry to tell you that but it is not a real country</u>
<u n="193" who="S0653">and what did he say?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0654">he was like <pause dur="short"/> it is</u>
<u n="195" who="S0653">oh oh he was obviously trying to impress you with a tale</u>
<u n="196" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="197" who="S0653">oh that's very sweet isn't it</u>
<u n="198" who="S0654"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that was really funny</u>
<u n="199" who="S0653">that's very sweet</u>
<u n="200" who="S0654">and erm I and then the cat came and er people</u>
<u n="201" who="S0653">the school cat</u>
<u n="202" who="S0654">yeah and loads of people wanted to stroke it but I thought no you don't know where it's been and it might not like children because once it scratched <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0653">yes it did scratch <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yes</u>
<u n="204" who="S0655">well it doesn't it doesn't even belong to the school</u>
<u n="205" who="S0653">no it just kind of trots in do you know it was national cat day in Japan yesterday because they love cats so they were celebrating everything to do with cats yesterday</u>
<u n="206" who="S0654">do you know what mum?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0653">sorry</u>
<u n="208" who="S0654">do you know what mum?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0653">mm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0654">once in in year two the cat</u>
<u n="211" who="S0653">you are in year two</u>
<u n="212" who="S0654">once in year two at one time in year two the cat we were in the ICT suite and the cat as there</u>
<u n="213" who="S0653" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> right <pause dur="short"/> in the ICT suite that's very cheeky</u>
<u n="214" who="S0655">well the door was open</u>
<u n="215" who="S0653">yeah but it shouldn't be cocky enough to walk in should it because there's lots of cats around here but they don't come into our house and rightly so</u>
<u n="216" who="S0654">but you are scared to death <event desc="sound of ringing"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0653">I'm not scared of cats but I'm scared of birds so I don't ever want a a cat to come in</u>
<u n="218" who="S0655">with a dead bird</u>
<u n="219" who="S0653">with a dead bird <pause dur="short"/> because that would be horrid</u>
<u n="220" who="S0655">I think I will have a <trunc>des</trunc> instead a cake</u>
<u n="221" who="S0653">you will like to have a dessert</u>
<u n="222" who="S0655">yes</u>
<u n="223" who="S0653">I've got some</u>
<u n="224" who="S0655">oreos</u>
<u n="225" who="S0653">no I've got raspberries and blueberries and my Greek yogurt</u>
<u n="226" who="S0655">I'm gonna have some of your Greek yogurt with a a</u>
<u n="227" who="S0653">a bit of honey?</u>
<u n="228" who="S0655">yes</u>
<u n="229" who="S0653">yes</u>
<u n="230" who="S0655">if I get the er if I get the bowl and honey can you start putting</u>
<u n="231" who="S0653">I will</u>
<u n="232" who="S0655">erm I'll use this one erm <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0653">sit down</u>
<u n="234" who="S0655">it's amazing how nice Greek yogurt with honey tastes</u>
<u n="235" who="S0653">it is amazing</u>
<u n="236" who="S0655">because it was like sweet and kind of strong</u>
<u n="237" who="S0653">it's a classic combination</u>
<u n="238" who="S0655">I think cracker margarine and cheese should be a classic combination</u>
<u n="239" who="S0653">well cheese and crackers is pretty classic</u>
<u n="240" who="S0655">yeah and just the margarine</u>
<u n="241" who="S0653">I'm doing I'm cooking some rhubarb at the moment but it's got ginger in it so I can't imagine you would want</u>
<u n="242" who="S0655">rhubarb and ginger <vocal desc="laugh"/> is that a classic combination?</u>
<u n="243" who="S0653">it is</u>
<u n="244" who="S0655">wow</u>
<u n="245" who="S0653">I should have got some custard to go with it <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0655">I might need to get another spoon</u>
<u n="247" who="S0653">why?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0655">because I can't get any of this off</u>
<u n="249" who="S0653">there you are</u>
<u n="250" who="S0655">and it's a little big</u>
<u n="251" who="S0653">do you want any blueberries or raspberries in there?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0655">no thanks</u>
<u n="253" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="254" who="S0655">I think I will keep it like this <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0653">so what do you think you are going to do in forest school <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0655">mm I am going to pardon?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0653">what are you gonna do in <anon type="place"/> school?</u>
<u n="258" who="S0655">I've no idea</u>
<u n="259" who="S0653">did you do <anon type="place"/> school last year with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="260" who="S0655">yes</u>
<u n="261" who="S0653">okay so it's still with <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> did he do lots of toasting marshmallows like <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0655">we did one <trunc>tast</trunc> toasting marshmallows and popping popcorn</u>
<u n="263" who="S0653">oh cool</u>
<u n="264" who="S0655">pop the popcorn</u>
<u n="265" who="S0654">popping <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="266" who="S0653">how did you cook the popcorn?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0655">on the fire on a fire</u>
<u n="268" who="S0653">like in a saucepan?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0655">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0653">well that's cool do you know we haven't well I haven't been to <anon type="place"/> probably for like two years or something</u>
<u n="271" who="S0654">you really need to see where we do it</u>
<u n="272" who="S0653">well we yeah we did see we did go a long time when we saw it but it would be nice to go to <anon type="place"/> again</u>
<u n="273" who="S0654">erm mummy I think I will have those erm tomorrow for my lunch</u>
<u n="274" who="S0653">the rest of the pizza yes well yes because otherwise you will turn into a pizza</u>
<u n="275" who="S0654">no I won't erm I'm full</u>
<u n="276" who="S0655" trans="overlap"><unclear>if dog likes my body</unclear> <unclear/> pizza</u>
<u n="277" who="S0653">you are full</u>
<u n="278" who="S0654">mm my little legs my little legs are saying to me no more</u>
<u n="279" who="S0653">well that's fine that's fine now do you yes you like to bring your water beaker don't you to Brownies</u>
<u n="280" who="S0654">my water what?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0653">you like to take a beaker to Brownies yes?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0654">mm</u>
<u n="283" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="284" who="S0654">how long is it to Brownies?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0653">it is thirty-five minutes but we will be going early so do you want to go and get ready?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0654">yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0653">okay</u>
<u n="288" who="S0654">my hair won't matter because it'll be dry by the time I'm at Brownies</u>
<u n="289" who="S0653">I will dry your hair don't worry</u>
<u n="290" who="S0654">no it will be dry by the time I go to Brownies</u>
<u n="291" who="S0653">well I doubt it</u>
<u n="292" who="S0654">well</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
