<text id="SR8N">
<header>
		<rec_length>1:00:01</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2012-03-01</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2012</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2012_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0037 S0115</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON and ANON’s home, Cambridge</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Family, plants, cookery</topics>
		<activity>Talking while making tea</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Original</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0037">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sunderland, Tyne and Wear</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>North East</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>northeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Research Manager</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0115">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years, 2 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>PhD student</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- Advanced; German -- Advanced</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
<body>
<u n="1" who="S0037">sorry about that</u>
<u n="2" who="S0115"><unclear/> um so what did they say then?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was just ringing to tell us <pause dur="short"/> well I text him and last week and he didn't reply so then</u>
<u n="4" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah he sort of ignored didn't he?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0037">I text him saying Not speaking like? And then he said so then he text us back and then he just said Oh I thought I'd ring you <pause dur="short"/> Um he was just telling us about what he'd been doing and about the baby and stuff <pause dur="short"/> so they've had their</u>
<u n="6" who="S0115" trans="overlap">what's he been doing then? He he described himself as a busy bee?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0037">he said he'd been very busy <pause dur="short"/> so he's got TE loads of different things on the go like <pause dur="short"/> as usual <pause dur="short"/> ooh what you making?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0115">it's supposed to be mayonnaise but I don't know how to make it <pause dur="short"/> I'm just <vocal desc="laugh"/> I just put like the egg yolks <pause dur="short"/> it is egg white and yolk uh</u>
<u n="9" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't know actually <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> you've gotta put quite a lot of oil in I think but</u>
<u n="10" who="S0115">first or?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0037">no no I think you you whisk the egg yolks for a long time and then you sort of</u>
<u n="12" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah that's what I was doing</u>
<u n="13" who="S0037">and then you sort of drip the oil in</u>
<u n="14" who="S0115">I've got six in there like uh</u>
<u n="15" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I can find I can <trunc>Goo</trunc></u>
<u n="16" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I've got six or d'you think there's not gonna be enough?</u>
<u n="17" who="S0037">no no that sounds like a lot <pause dur="short"/> tE do you want me to Google it? I'll just get my thing</u>
<u n="18" who="S0115">uh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0037">anyway yes so then <pause dur="short"/> so then he um <pause dur="short"/> so then he was saying that he</u>
<u n="20" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0037">he was telling me what he'd been doing <pause dur="short"/> so he was saying that once the baby's born</u>
<u n="22" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0037">the plan is that <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'ll go back to work actually but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gonna try and fit his work around looking after the baby</u>
<u n="24" who="S0115">why? I mean he he what about like and presumably TE you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and them lot are gonna do that like</u>
<u n="25" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gonna be the <pause dur="short"/> well yeah and everyone else so <pause dur="short"/> so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s gonna look after it on a Thursday and someone else is gonna look after her on <trunc>S</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> like her sister's gonna look after it on a some sort of day and</u>
<u n="26" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> any way so</u>
<u n="28" who="S0115" trans="overlap">right well that sounds very reasonable doesn't it?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but he's gonna be the one like he's gonna be the main carer I think</u>
<u n="30" who="S0115">um yeah fair enough <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="31" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but he likes kids doesn't he I mean?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> gonna? Does he reckon <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s got a better chance of getting a better job then?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0037" trans="overlap">getting a job <pause dur="short"/> well she has</u>
<u n="34" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="35" who="S0037">she's like an administrator and he's like a general purpose dogsbody</u>
<u n="36" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well <pause dur="short"/> he does a  he does a  variety of things doesn't he um?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0037">does he?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0115">well he has done <pause dur="short"/> yeah a barman</u>
<u n="39" who="S0037">yeah but</u>
<u n="40" who="S0115">that's his main qualification isn't it?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but <trunc>n</trunc> no like skilled work <pause dur="short"/> at least Sarah's like a financial administrator</u>
<u n="42" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well he does have that qualification TE you know he's he's only got the qualification as a barman yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0037">yeah he's a barman he's worked in a factory he's worked in a</u>
<u n="44" who="S0115" trans="overlap">he has experience as a bingo called</u>
<u n="45" who="S0037">his work <pause dur="short"/> he's a bingo <vocal desc="laugh"/> caller he's a furniture salesman he's a</u>
<u n="46" who="S0115">A club um worked in a club as a barman</u>
<u n="47" who="S0037">tE do you know what I mean he's just like <pause dur="short"/> he's</u>
<u n="48" who="S0115">furniture salesman yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0037">but he's more <pause dur="short"/> what he was saying is he's got like the type of <pause dur="short"/> like working in a pub for example that's always on an evening so</u>
<u n="50" who="S0115">yeah that that does allow you to sort of fit in uh I guess bring up a child around that</u>
<u n="51" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I suppose like my worry there is though that he would like if Sarah goes to work all day and he's looks after the baby all day then he goes to work all night like that's not gonna be very good for them two</u>
<u n="52" who="S0115">oh yeah I think they they gonna have to work really hard and like um</u>
<u n="53" who="S0037">no but I mean like their relationship</u>
<u n="54" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I don't</u>
<u n="55" who="S0037">tE you know</u>
<u n="56" who="S0115">uh well I mean <trunc>th</trunc> they're already um they already spend a lot of time apart don't they uh I think I mean I no I don't know to be honest but like</u>
<u n="57" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Cos he was like Oh we can't afford childcare <pause dur="short"/> Time apart yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0115">they're certainly don't don't they TE you know both have like spend part of their time with their own families don't they?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0037">I think so <pause dur="short"/> well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doing all his various tasks and</u>
<u n="60" who="S0115" trans="overlap">just uh</u>
<u n="61" who="S0037">he's also been like doing odd jobs and he's been <pause dur="short"/> he's selling those you know those <trunc>import</trunc> and those T-shirts I was telling you</u>
<u n="62" who="S0115">is he still doing?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0037">he said that's doing really well <pause dur="short"/> he said he earnt like a hundred and twenty pounds last month doing that so</u>
<u n="64" who="S0115">oh right well it seems like he he's making quite a lot of money then?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0037">well he always is but just never <trunc>e</trunc> sort of never enough</u>
<u n="66" who="S0115">tE do you think that he gets it and <pause dur="short"/> you think he earns quite a lot but spends quite a lot</u>
<u n="67" who="S0037">he does <pause dur="short"/> definitely does</u>
<u n="68" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I'm assuming the child I mean how much time how much does it cost to raise a child like as cheap as</u>
<u n="69" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well <trunc>I'd</trunc> I don't know I've got absolutely no <pause dur="short"/> I've got absolutely no like nothing to go on but anyway so then I was saying Ah have you had your scan SE? and he said oh I've got a picture for you <pause dur="short"/> um I'll send you it in the post <pause dur="short"/> I don't wanna put it Facebook I think it's a bit obscene <pause dur="short"/> which it is <pause dur="short"/> he was like  he was like  Here's a picture of my child in inside my girlfriend LOL <pause dur="short"/> Like he doesn't really think that's a</u>
<u n="70" who="S0115" trans="overlap">like why? Is it? Do people not do that?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0037">well yes people do do that but</u>
<u n="72" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no I don't think it's disgusting to put a  to put a  scan</u>
<u n="73" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but I don't dunno if I would wanna do it like <pause dur="short"/> here's a picture of my insides like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="74" who="S0115">well that's rather a negative view I would've thought</u>
<u n="75" who="S0037">I dunno I didn't really like the idea either</u>
<u n="76" who="S0115">really?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0037">I sort of understood</u>
<u n="78" who="S0115">really? I think it's very interesting</u>
<u n="79" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you you don't even like Facebook at the best of times you wouldn't wanna <trunc>pict</trunc> put a picture of like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0115">um? No I know I mean like you you could put that <pause dur="short"/> well putting a scan I don't see why  I don't see why  you wouldn't wanna put  wouldn't wanna put  a scan</u>
<u n="81" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I can't seem to find like the the the instructions</u>
<u n="82" who="S0115">for mayonnaise?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0037">anyway</u>
<u n="84" who="S0115">have you not googled How to make mayonnaise?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0037">yeah I've got I'm on the BBC Food one that I normally like</u>
<u n="86" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><unclear/> uh rather obvious</u>
<u n="87" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="88" who="S0115">is that my one actually</u>
<u n="89" who="S0037">that's mine I've just opened that <pause dur="short"/> tE do you want? Yours is here</u>
<u n="90" who="S0115"><unclear/></u>
<u n="91" who="S0037">anyway so <pause dur="short"/> so then he was saying um <pause dur="short"/> then I said Have you thought about any? <trunc>Th</trunc> then they said he they decided not to find out if it's a girl or a boy</u>
<u n="92" who="S0115">decided not to?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and he said and I said Oh I mean understand like it's a good surprise <pause dur="short"/> I said Oh is there any reason? And he said well Apparently <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> TE  mam had loadsa miscarriages and so did her nana and her aunties and they're just worried like <pause dur="short"/> suppose they're just being a bit cautious he said like if he <pause dur="short"/> if they sort of started thinking about it like as a boy or a girl <pause dur="short"/> and then anything happened <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0115">make it worse?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0037">so okay here's Delia's recipe <pause dur="short"/> two egg yolks <pause dur="short"/> put the egg yolks in a basin <pause dur="short"/> add the salt and pepper</u>
<u n="96" who="S0115">okay <pause dur="short"/> I'll just get some salt</u>
<u n="97" who="S0037">then holding your electric whisk in one hand</u>
<u n="98" who="S0115">right</u>
<u n="99" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/> uh add a drop of oil to the mixture and whisk in</u>
<u n="100" who="S0115">right it's just sort of whisked in</u>
<u n="101" who="S0037">then it says However stupid this may sound the key to successful mayonnaise is make sure each drop of oil is thoroughly whisked in before adding the next drop <pause dur="short"/> it won't take all day because after a few minutes the mixture will go thick and very stiff and lumpy <pause dur="short"/> when you get to this stage add a teaspoon of vinegar <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0115">so could use uh</u>
<u n="103" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so you pour it you you pour it a drop at a time</u>
<u n="104" who="S0115">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0037">and then</u>
<u n="106" who="S0115">could use um <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> our um blender thing</u>
<u n="107" who="S0037">yeah? It <trunc>prob</trunc> that would probably be better</u>
<u n="108" who="S0115">but uh wasn't sure like if that would like rip it up and?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0037">no I it'll be fine <pause dur="short"/> that'll be quicker</u>
<u n="110" who="S0115">and um <pause dur="short"/> so any other news from Tom?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh and then I said erm have you thought of any? Are you staying with the same names? And they said he said Oh if it's a boy I'm still going to call him <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0115">fair enough</u>
<u n="113" who="S0037">if it's a girl they're had a new idea and they're thinking of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="115" who="S0037">but calling her <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> which I quite like <pause dur="short"/> definitely better than <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> which isn't even a real name anyway</u>
<u n="116" who="S0115">yeah I mean well I would have said you like there is a slight risk with with uh with rarer names</u>
<u n="117" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> sounds quite nice</u>
<u n="118" who="S0115">I think the rarer name can be a bit like be a bit of a stigma sometimes</u>
<u n="119" who="S0037">but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s quite nice?</u>
<u n="120" who="S0115">yeah I think that's that's that's alright yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0037">I was like Yeah <pause dur="short"/> do that one <pause dur="short"/> do that one  <pause dur="short"/> never mind <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0115">that's pretty um</u>
<u n="123" who="S0037">so</u>
<u n="124" who="S0115">that's that sounds good yeah <pause dur="short"/> I like it</u>
<u n="125" who="S0037" trans="overlap">that's where that is <pause dur="short"/> and then he was saying</u>
<u n="126" who="S0115">getting kind of thicker now</u>
<u n="127" who="S0037">have you put any oil in?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0115">yeah I have</u>
<u n="129" who="S0037">but just do a drop <pause dur="short"/> like literally a drop at a time Delia said</u>
<u n="130" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I know <pause dur="short"/> that's the second drop <pause dur="short"/> yeah second drop's gone in yeah</u>
<u n="131" who="S0037">um</u>
<u n="132" who="S0115">you've got to uh yeah like I guess you've got to uh yeah like I guess you've got to like whisk whip it for ages so that it um</u>
<u n="133" who="S0037">do you want me to do some? Is your hand getting tired?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0115">uh yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> whisk it to make sure all the oil is um distributed <pause dur="short"/> uh so that'll be fine</u>
<u n="135" who="S0037">and then?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0115">so yeah <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s a better name isn't it uh than <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="137" who="S0037">that's much better</u>
<u n="138" who="S0115">I think it would <pause dur="short"/> it might be a bit of a stigma if you gave</u>
<u n="139" who="S0037">I know</u>
<u n="140" who="S0115">if you had a name like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then uh anything else?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> what was he saying? He was saying they're thinking about like maybe moving to a different place cos obviously they're in like a one-bedroom flat <pause dur="short"/> at the moment</u>
<u n="142" who="S0115">yeah yeah it's hard to raise a child if you've only got one bedroom</u>
<u n="143" who="S0037">but he said he'll obviously have to just save up because they need to get</u>
<u n="144" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well he seems to be making quite a bit of money doesn't he?</u>
<u n="145" who="S0037">well they need to get the new deposit before they get the old deposit back <pause dur="short"/> you know same as us here</u>
<u n="146" who="S0115">you need to?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0037">like we've got a <trunc>de</trunc> like we've got like fifteen hundred pounds of deposit held with our letting agent</u>
<u n="148" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0037">but if we wanted to move we'd have to find a new fifteen hundred pounds before we got the old one back</u>
<u n="150" who="S0115">I see right <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> some house deposits are very high aren't they?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0037">oh if you wanted to buy yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0037">no I don't think he's in quite that state yet <pause dur="short"/> anyway and then um <pause dur="short"/> what else what he saying? Oh I said I was telling him about  <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and he was like Oh we should go there on like me you and Matt <pause dur="short"/> we should go <pause dur="short"/> and I was thinking um baby?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think um</u>
<u n="155" who="S0037">then I was saying we were thinking of going to Sunderland like in September <pause dur="short"/> the start of September</u>
<u n="156" who="S0115">yeah around that sort of time yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he said <trunc>w</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> once</u>
<u n="158" who="S0115">I <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah um</u>
<u n="159" who="S0037">once the baby had had chance to stop like being weird</u>
<u n="160" who="S0115" trans="overlap">if I can <pause dur="short"/> hopefully I'll be able to get</u>
<u n="161" who="S0037">do you want to put some?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0115">um integrate that um <pause dur="short"/> another drop?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0037">do you think?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0115">I mean cos if you look at it obviously it's <pause dur="short"/> you can't really easily see much much oil can you?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="166" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> I guess it's kind of partly up to the discretion of the uh TE you know how much oil you put is is up to TE you know personal taste innit? I think they make a lot of like you know those light mayonnaise and like light light mayonnaise where it's like really</u>
<u n="167" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> extra super super <pause dur="short"/> but we saw that programme didn't we they put in like</u>
<u n="168" who="S0115" trans="overlap">just wonder how are they making the mayonnaise runny?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="170" who="S0115">put them up</u>
<u n="171" who="S0037">where we put in like gum Arabic was it?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0115">ah you mean was that like uh How It How It's Made?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0037">they put in <pause dur="short"/> no it was like um like Jimmy's Food Factory or whatever it was? TE do you remember and he made like industrial scale?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah</u>
<u n="175" who="S0037">yeah um <pause dur="short"/> yeah and then I spoke to me mam briefly</u>
<u n="176" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0037">she was asking about  <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> and then I was saying like cos I said I went in C and A <pause dur="short"/> cos I used to really like C and A and me mam <pause dur="short"/> I knew me mam used to love it like the shop <pause dur="short"/> c and A</u>
<u n="178" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="179" who="S0037">and she was like <pause dur="short"/> then she was saying Ooh I got this <pause dur="short"/> I remember once me dad bought us this  swing jacket from C and A and I was like Ooh  swing jackets are back in now and she said oh</u>
<u n="180" who="S0115" trans="overlap">shall I do it? What are they?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0037">like <trunc>y</trunc> those coats that sort of go like that? They're kind of looser and sort well they sort of swing out like sort of</u>
<u n="182" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0037">not like a tight sort of fitting coat like more like a</u>
<u n="184" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0037">anyway <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="186" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0037">and then she said she's gonna ring tomorrow for a proper chat I was like yay</u>
<u n="188" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Yeah so I'm gonna invite my parents write an email and</u>
<u n="189" who="S0037">do you wanna email? I can help you</u>
<u n="190" who="S0115">that's right</u>
<u n="191" who="S0037">if you wanna</u>
<u n="192" who="S0115">actually should have put a bit of garlic in there <pause dur="short"/> it's uh too late  too late  for that now <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0037">mm <pause dur="short"/> do you want some of this chilli some?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0115" trans="overlap">just uh slipped a little bit there like</u>
<u n="195" who="S0037" trans="overlap">huh? Whoops</u>
<u n="196" who="S0115">no it's  <trunc>al</trunc> no it's alright <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> yeah and when they come they'll probably bring some plants and it'll be</u>
<u n="197" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> what were we on about before with uh we were on about um oh yeah <trunc>b</trunc> the taxation actually we were on about which was uh</u>
<u n="199" who="S0037">ooh quite boring</u>
<u n="200" who="S0115">uh like and you were</u>
<u n="201" who="S0037">do you want some of this?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0115">you were <trunc>say</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> uh no I think it's a bit uh</u>
<u n="203" who="S0037">bit what?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0115">it's a bit strong</u>
<u n="205" who="S0037">oh I like it</u>
<u n="206" who="S0115">not really in the mood for uh</u>
<u n="207" who="S0037">mm it's nice <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="208" who="S0115">so I don't really know when to stop with this I'm just gonna keep on uh</u>
<u n="209" who="S0037">until it looks like mayonnaise it's still a bit runny isn't it?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the main thing is that it isn't white it's yellow so yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no but the that's alright</u>
<u n="212" who="S0115">that's like the probably the main uh observation that I would make</u>
<u n="213" who="S0037">but real mayonnaise is yellow like</u>
<u n="214" who="S0115">yeah I could put a bit of mustard in maybe</u>
<u n="215" who="S0037">hmm?</u>
<u n="216" who="S0115">bit of mustard like might go nicely</u>
<u n="217" who="S0037">oh yeah that'd be nice <pause dur="short"/> have we got any of that ones with the specs in?</u>
<u n="218" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="219" who="S0037">whole grain</u>
<u n="220" who="S0115">think so</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="221" who="S0037">and I said like something like um Is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> gonna be alright with the pregnancy I know she's can be a bit like sort of TE you know?</u>
<u n="222" who="S0115">she she can be a a tad um uh well she seems to have quite a few health well she seems to get quite a few health problems like</u>
<u n="223" who="S0037">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said Well she'll have to be <pause dur="short"/> it's in there <pause dur="short"/> it's gotta come out <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="224" who="S0115">well yeah like you do <pause dur="short"/> you have to sort of like</u>
<u n="225" who="S0037" trans="overlap">can I do it for a bit?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0115">I've only just started <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="227" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh sorry <pause dur="short"/> I thought felt like it'd been a while <pause dur="short"/> so he said something like Well it's in there <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna have to come out <pause dur="short"/> And then I said</u>
<u n="228" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah yeah you have to be uh <trunc>manu</trunc> matter of fact about it</u>
<u n="229" who="S0037">and then I said Ah have you seen pictures of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s baby cos you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just had a baby yesterday?</u>
<u n="230" who="S0115">oh did he yeah <pause dur="short"/> right</u>
<u n="231" who="S0037" trans="overlap">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said Ah he's he he text us saying like Ooh I've just got the call I'm going to the hospital <pause dur="short"/> she's three centimetres dilated and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like you really didn't need to put that other bit on the end <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="232" who="S0115">he's getting  he's getting  very like like uh like <trunc>medic</trunc> like he doesn't like um</u>
<u n="233" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no that's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> saying that</u>
<u n="234" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like getting all like quite anti-medical like he doesn't</u>
<u n="235" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well I just thought like</u>
<u n="236" who="S0115">he doesn't like listening to details or seeing scans</u>
<u n="237" who="S0037">but remember those two have been friends since they were like little boys and he's like I really don't wanna know how how much dilated your girlfriend's girlfriend is really <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="238" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh I'm more  I'm more  like interested in in the sort of um medical aspect of it I suppose</u>
<u n="239" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0115">I'm sort cos I'm I'm quite I quite like science TE you know so</u>
<u n="241" who="S0037">aha <pause dur="short"/> but I suppose if it's like</u>
<u n="242" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I'm not  I'm not  <trunc>s</trunc> I'm not like I don't wanna be squeamish although I am a bit squeamish with blood but I wouldn't wanna be too squeamish I <trunc>w</trunc> I'd be like I'd wanna be more like</u>
<u n="243" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0115">trying to help like I suppose if TE you know if you were having a child and uh something something had gone wrong or something I'd like to know a bit of the medical side so</u>
<u n="245" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="246" who="S0115">so I might be able to help or something like that</u>
<u n="247" who="S0037">well anyway <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="248" who="S0115">um but yeah um <pause dur="short"/> some people like that some people don't</u>
<u n="249" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he said Me nana's been me nana <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s been like knitting like it's going out of fashion <pause dur="short"/> he was like You should see some of the things that she's knitting <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh that's really good and uh</u>
<u n="251" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I was like Ah no I can't compete <pause dur="short"/> no competition <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="252" who="S0115">oh yeah so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s like your number two knitter and then  and then  uh Auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is your uh number one?</u>
<u n="253" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well they're both of them <pause dur="short"/> but me nana I think me nana'll <trunc>h</trunc> has got more sort of well it's her first great grandchild isn't it she's obviously like</u>
<u n="254" who="S0115">oh yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0037">she's obviously totally excited</u>
<u n="256" who="S0115">alright <pause dur="short"/> I've <unclear/> need a break</u>
<u n="257" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I've seen I saw in the um in the shop that I cycle past like that they do these um <pause dur="short"/> when I these</u>
<u n="258" who="S0115" trans="overlap">guess I could whip whip that up and have a raita or whatever</u>
<u n="259" who="S0037">ooh yeah <pause dur="short"/> saw these things that said like when I</u>
<u n="260" who="S0115" trans="overlap">mousse chocolate mousse</u>
<u n="261" who="S0037">yeah maybe</u>
<u n="262" who="S0115">which if I'd been a bit <trunc>s</trunc> if I'd thought ahead I could've got some plain chocolate and TE you know</u>
<u n="263" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no it's alright <pause dur="short"/> can probably keep it anyway in the fridge</u>
<u n="264" who="S0115">like got some of this this is hazelnut chocolate I can you know melt that down and mix it to make a mousse</u>
<u n="265" who="S0037">the um <pause dur="short"/> I saw these in the shop these things that said like When I grow up I'm gonna go to <anon type="place"/> University</u>
<u n="266" who="S0115">in a shop?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0037">with like the logo on</u>
<u n="268" who="S0115">you <pause dur="short"/> sorry you did? Where where was that?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0037">in the shop on <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0115">where's that?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> like just near <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0115">oh right yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0037">I might get one</u>
<u n="274" who="S0115">oh little baby things yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> so yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="275" who="S0037" trans="overlap">as like an ironic gesture <pause dur="short"/> when I grow up I'm gonna go to <anon type="place"/> University?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no well you don't know  you don't know  Baby <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> could uh</u>
<u n="277" who="S0037">have its brains from well not <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="278" who="S0115">mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> No it it is he's he's not  he's not  uh he's not that bad is he?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0037">no he not but he wouldn't have gone to <anon type="place"/> University</u>
<u n="280" who="S0115">I dunno partly it's partly cultural isn't it TE you know um I think the sort of</u>
<u n="281" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> what?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0037">yeah but I mean he wouldn't have</u>
<u n="284" who="S0115" trans="overlap">sorry I didn't? What did you?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0037">no nothing</u>
<u n="286" who="S0115">are you gonna close that?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0037">no no no <pause dur="short"/> it's fine <pause dur="short"/> shall I put some more oil in this?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> I dunno I mean like</u>
<u n="289" who="S0037">does taste quite nice</u>
<u n="290" who="S0115">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> like we probably don't wanna put loads of oil in</u>
<u n="291" who="S0037">it <trunc>do</trunc> it <trunc>do</trunc> <trunc>ha</trunc> it is supposed to have quite a lot of oil in though I think</u>
<u n="292" who="S0115">well it's as I said it it sort of um</u>
<u n="293" who="S0037" trans="overlap">it's very white peppery maybe don't put any more white pepper in for me</u>
<u n="294" who="S0115">oh no I mean uh I uh</u>
<u n="295" who="S0037">mm?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0115">I didn't <trunc>mea</trunc> I didn't intend to put that in like</u>
<u n="297" who="S0037">it does taste like really white peppery</u>
<u n="298" who="S0115">fair enough <pause dur="short"/> have have I screwed it up?</u>
<u n="299" who="S0037">no you haven't screwed it up</u>
<u n="300" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh well never mind <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0037">no you haven't <pause dur="short"/> you haven't</u>
<u n="302" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh it's alright well you don't have it on its own do you so I mean if you wanna put like uh put some mustard in if you wanna balance that out a bit <pause dur="short"/> balance those flavours</u>
<u n="303" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> have a taste <pause dur="short"/> what do you think?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0115">it's alright</u>
<u n="305" who="S0037">what motivated you to put six six eggs in like? Was it just?</u>
<u n="306" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you could <trunc>perha</trunc> you could perhaps do  you could perhaps do  um</u>
<u n="307" who="S0037">why six eggs like?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0115">well <pause dur="short"/> cos I was thinking of making like quite a lot  you know like to last for like more than one meal  you know</u>
<u n="309" who="S0037">I see yeah yeah no it's a good idea</u>
<u n="310" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well cos two cos like two <trunc>s</trunc> two eggs if you scramble two eggs it's it doesn't come out with very much does it?</u>
<u n="311" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="312" who="S0115">two scrambled eggs isn't isn't loads like I don't think <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> so yeah well we had a lot of eggs as well uh so I thought well we haven't got many so I thought I'd uh use it up</u>
<u n="313" who="S0037" trans="overlap">we we need a beater though this is a bit</u>
<u n="314" who="S0115">we um if you wanna just use the  use the  electric one we could do that</u>
<u n="315" who="S0037">shall I give it a try?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0115">yeah if if you  if you</u>
<u n="317" who="S0037">need it out for me soup anyway <pause dur="short"/> might spurt everywhere though I'm I'm a bit clumsy</u>
<u n="318" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> I'll have it I'll do it</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="319" who="S0037">I can  I can  do it I don't mind</u>
<u n="320" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> hold on uh <pause dur="short"/> just get that</u>
<u n="321" who="S0037">I always worry like about using this like cos usually it's <pause dur="short"/> oh what's in ah it's just the thing</u>
<u n="322" who="S0115">I'll I'll do that it's uh if you  if you  think  you know</u>
<u n="323" who="S0037">no and let's just try it</u>
<u n="324" who="S0115">uh <pause dur="short"/> oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> it works then</u>
<event desc="sound of blender"/>
<u n="325" who="S0037">is that doing it?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think yeah <pause dur="short"/> slowly yeah</u>
<u n="327" who="S0037">that looks more mayonnaisey already doesn't it?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> It is a bit faster than I thought</u>
<u n="329" who="S0037">slightly slightly faster than the uh</u>
<u n="330" who="S0115">it's done the uh well it's done in like one second what like took us like fifteen minutes to do <pause dur="short"/> it's going a lot whiter innit?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0037">huh?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0115">it's going a lot <trunc>whit</trunc> it's going a lot whiter isn't it?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="333" who="S0037">is it alright? What  do you think?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0115">uh looks okay</u>
<event desc="sound of splatting"/>
<u n="335" who="S0037">ugh</u>
<u n="336" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0037">it splatted on us</u>
<u n="338" who="S0115">shall I have a go? Whoops <pause dur="short"/> yeah just don't like do any sort of sudden sudden movements with it</u>
<u n="339" who="S0037">is it okay?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0037" trans="overlap">ooh <pause dur="short"/> sorry</u>
<u n="342" who="S0115">little bit of a <pause dur="short"/> shall I have a go?</u>
<u n="343" who="S0037">ooh tastes more like mayonnaise</u>
<u n="344" who="S0115">it's getting  it's getting  better but it's we've just gotta get it um  you know like salad</u>
<u n="345" who="S0037" trans="overlap">needs some vinegar in it's like too sort of thick</u>
<u n="346" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh yeah lemon yeah with uh <pause dur="short"/> grab uh</u>
<u n="347" who="S0037">it's too sort of thick and peppery</u>
<u n="348" who="S0115">sorry about that pepper uh</u>
<u n="349" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you put too much white pepper in I think</u>
<u n="350" who="S0115">I think you've you've said that a couple of times already</u>
<u n="351" who="S0037">sorry <pause dur="short"/> I just don't really like white pepper that much I like a tiny bit</u>
<u n="352" who="S0115">really? I'd assumed you <unclear/></u>
<u n="353" who="S0037" trans="overlap">just a small bit like I find it just</u>
<u n="354" who="S0115">you you never bought any black pepper</u>
<u n="355" who="S0037">no no I keep forgetting</u>
<u n="356" who="S0115">with uh your hatred of white pepper</u>
<u n="357" who="S0037">no it's not a hatred it's more like um</u>
<u n="358" who="S0115">I dunno actually for a mayonnaise like I would've thought white pepper would go better</u>
<u n="359" who="S0037">no maybe it you might even be right yeah maybe it does <pause dur="short"/> I just think</u>
<u n="360" who="S0115">no I think there's a lack of aroma in there <pause dur="short"/> there's a  there's a  lack of aroma like um</u>
<u n="361" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0115">like mustard or garlic or something like  you know</u>
<u n="363" who="S0037">maybe mustard would be better actually</u>
<u n="364" who="S0115" trans="overlap">we we don't have um we don't enough aroma in there <pause dur="short"/> that's that's why you know the only the white pepper's coming out so</u>
<u n="365" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="366" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> uh <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> maybe the I think the mayonnaise'll be nice</u>
<u n="368" who="S0115">mm</u>
<u n="369" who="S0037">were you gonna make a sandwich? Was that why you started making the mayonnaise while I was on the phone?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's tuna <trunc>s</trunc> it's to go with a tuna sandwich yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh that'd be really <trunc>ni</trunc> <vocal desc="cough"/> that'd be really nice <pause dur="short"/> I dunno what's wrong with my throat maybe I was snoring <pause dur="short"/> ooh <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> Like it how you tried to catch that drip</u>
<u n="372" who="S0115"><unclear/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0037">just press it like just let it go <pause dur="short"/> woo</u>
<u n="374" who="S0115">anything else from uh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> then?</u>
<u n="375" who="S0037">no I only talked to her for a minute she was um</u>
<u n="376" who="S0115">or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0037">no like she was</u>
<u n="378" who="S0115">did you speak to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0037"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wasn't there</u>
<u n="380" who="S0115">oh right so they were in um in the pub aren't they?</u>
<u n="381" who="S0037">but she was coming down because apparently they were going to watch some wrestling thing like <pause dur="short"/> like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> from being a little boy's always liked those like is it Wrestlemania?  do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0115">were they are they gonna watch the wrestling in the pub or?</u>
<u n="383" who="S0037">no at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s</u>
<u n="384" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="385" who="S0037">she's got like some stupid Sky thing or whatever <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> that was the plan</u>
<u n="386" who="S0115">I guess there isn't as much wrestling on um terrestrial TV is there?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0037">well I think it was big like in the sort of um like fifties and stuff wasn't it but then <pause dur="short"/> it wasn't then like</u>
<u n="388" who="S0115">uh I never really I never followed it much but I know a lot of like kids did in my school and stuff</u>
<u n="389" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/>  No <pause dur="short"/> in the fifties?</u>
<u n="390" who="S0115">no no no I I mean I never really liked it that much like during my  during my  lifetime</u>
<u n="391" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you mean like like Hulk Hogan times? Yeah</u>
<u n="392" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> but that's sort of</u>
<u n="393" who="S0037">me brother used to really like it he had like  he had like</u>
<event desc="sound of blender"/>
<u n="394" who="S0115">just let it go</u>
<u n="395" who="S0037">I suppose we can't really talk over that</u>
<u n="396" who="S0115">yeah he um <pause dur="short"/> he's always uh he's always liked that hasn't he? So I think he he's <trunc>prob</trunc> he'll probably get he'll probably do weight training eventually</u>
<u n="397" who="S0037" trans="overlap">do you think so? No he's never been that health conscious to be honest like</u>
<u n="398" who="S0115">think he could uh <pause dur="short"/> likes he'd like to have  you know some big muscles wouldn't he?</u>
<u n="399" who="S0037">I think he'd like to but also he also just likes pies and</u>
<u n="400" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I think he just it's just inevitable to uh</u>
<u n="401" who="S0037">na</u>
<u n="402" who="S0115">like um <pause dur="short"/> gonna get <trunc>s</trunc> like loads of spitting from this</u>
<u n="403" who="S0037">na I think like it wasn't really spitting that much I think if you lift it up too much it spits <pause dur="short"/>  do you want me to have a go?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0115">um no I'll just hold it down and  do it</u>
<u n="405" who="S0037"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0115">whoa and then it does some <vocal desc="laugh"/> I think you're just  you're just  inevitably gonna get like spitting coming out</u>
<u n="407" who="S0037">just do it in little bits <pause dur="short"/> just redecorating  you know A nice mayonnaise coloured speckle <pause dur="short"/> this is gonna be so annoying to transcribe <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="408" who="S0115">oh no no no it's probably not that much</u>
<u n="409" who="S0037">with a like <event desc="sound of roaring"/> blender</u>
<u n="410" who="S0115">well <pause dur="short"/> you don't have to transcribe the blender though do you so</u>
<u n="411" who="S0037">you could write blender in like square brackets <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="412" who="S0115">no you don't you wouldn't have to write blender every time</u>
<u n="413" who="S0037">no I know</u>
<u n="414" who="S0115">do you wanna move it further away then you wanna put it over there or something?</u>
<u n="415" who="S0037">yeah but then <pause dur="short"/> but then uh</u>
<u n="416" who="S0115">right well well put it <pause dur="short"/> you're holding it for some reason during uh</u>
<u n="417" who="S0037">I thought it was gonna get uh mayonnaise splattered on its face</u>
<u n="418" who="S0115">oh no <pause dur="short"/> they're quite  espensive little things aren't they?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0037">these? Yeah very <pause dur="short"/> and I just chuck it in my handbag like</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="420" who="S0037">hey <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like those plant holders are like glowing in the dark <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="421" who="S0115">those what?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0037">those knitted plant holders that I've made <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="423" who="S0115">yeah they're pretty bright aren't they?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0037">well they'll attract the um <trunc>be</trunc> bumble  bees</u>
<u n="425" who="S0115">yeah well I mean I guess they will but I don't know for certain <pause dur="short"/>  But because they're bright you're just guessing that they'll be more attractive to</u>
<u n="426" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/>  you know like have you ever done it where you've worn like a bright shirt?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0115">you've got like what?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0037">where you've worn like a bright shirt and then you've been like bothered by wasps</u>
<u n="429" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh like wasps and that?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0037">na</u>
<u n="431" who="S0115">uh <trunc>y</trunc> sometimes yeah but</u>
<u n="432" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I suppose maybe you don't wear bright shirts</u>
<u n="433" who="S0115">no but like sometimes you you you think that yeah that there's something like if you have like hair gel on it's attracting like</u>
<u n="434" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="435" who="S0115">it's got like sugar in and it's attracting like wasps and that</u>
<u n="436" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah and like an <trunc>l</trunc> an ice cream or something?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah and um no one likes wasps <pause dur="short"/> we we're alright over here in this house where we don't really have any I've never seen any wasps around here <pause dur="short"/>  do you  do you wanna do that?</u>
<u n="438" who="S0037">do you think we need some more oil in</u>
<u n="439" who="S0115">I guess so</u>
<u n="440" who="S0037">shall I have a try?</u>
<u n="441" who="S0115">I mean I'm just getting a bit getting really bored of of uh <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="442" who="S0037">doing it?</u>
<u n="443" who="S0115">whipping it</u>
<u n="444" who="S0037">here you are then</u>
<u n="445" who="S0115">I'll put this over here</u>
<u n="446" who="S0037">ugh</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="447" who="S0037">feel like I'm just covered in speckles <pause dur="short"/> where's that? Oh</u>
<u n="448" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> how many plants  do you reckon you think we'll be growing like? How many <trunc>t</trunc> how many tomatoes  do you think we're gonna uh are we gonna grow?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Woah <pause dur="short"/> think I might just have sprayed me <pause dur="short"/> um I don't know <pause dur="short"/> what  do you think?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0115">could go back to hand whipping it <pause dur="short"/> doesn't seem to be  doesn't seem to be  doing it</u>
<u n="451" who="S0037">it did do a lot better though for a while</u>
<u n="452" who="S0115">it looked like it was much better but then it sort of <pause dur="short"/> I don't know if that's <unclear/> actually cos that's actually chopping it you know what I mean? I think we might've um think think we might've <pause dur="short"/> can I help <pause dur="short"/> I think we might've made a mistake because like that's the wrong type of instrument I think like</u>
<u n="453" who="S0037">yeah but we haven't got anything else</u>
<u n="454" who="S0115" trans="overlap">we we we weren't we want to whisk it not chop it  you know what I mean? That's a chopper</u>
<u n="455" who="S0037">yeah but we haven't got anything else like</u>
<u n="456" who="S0115">you know what I mean? I was thinking that the  that the  knife action from it might actually break apart the the yolk  you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0037">maybe it was too much lemon</u>
<u n="458" who="S0115" trans="overlap">in a way that  in a way that  didn't want <pause dur="short"/>  You know what I mean?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no because once it's mixed in <pause dur="short"/> you're supposed to do it with a hand blender I mean</u>
<u n="460" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no no you're supposed to do it with an electric whisk <pause dur="short"/> it's not the same</u>
<u n="461" who="S0037">I mean that's what I meant sorry</u>
<u n="462" who="S0115">not not quite the same as um a chopper cos uh because because it's like a different shape um  you know the bit is a different shape isn't it so? I guess it will taste a bit nicer than than it did but uh</u>
<u n="463" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="464" who="S0115">but it's just worth like we had a lot of eggs so I just thought we might as well try it I mean</u>
<u n="465" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well maybe we should just leave it there like</u>
<u n="466" who="S0115">you think it's uh I'll probably could give it a few more hand whips and then uh</u>
<u n="467" who="S0037">I'm just getting sick of <trunc>ty</trunc> like whisking it I suppose</u>
<u n="468" who="S0115">well you don't have to I'll just I'll do it then it doesn't matter it was just like an experiment you know</u>
<u n="469" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0115">yeah it's got a decent</u>
<u n="471" who="S0037">it'd be nice though anyway like as a little sauce</u>
<u n="472" who="S0115">yeah yeah like one of them German yellow sauces innit?</u>
<u n="473" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0115">um  do you wanna put that back where it was?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0037">um sorry</u>
<u n="476" who="S0115">actually we'll we'll go through shall we cos uh you've got anything</u>
<u n="477" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/>  do you wanna make a sandwich now then or?</u>
<u n="478" who="S0115" trans="overlap">have you got anything more to do? I don't mind <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="479" who="S0037">I'm a bit hungry</u>
<u n="480" who="S0115">okay well shall we do that then?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0037">suppose so yeah</u>
<u n="482" who="S0115">something like</u>
<u n="483" who="S0037">what shall we have? Um how about like a</u>
<u n="484" who="S0115" trans="overlap">just tuna mayo innit?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0037">well what about like a tuna cheese melt like we could toast some bread and some</u>
<u n="486" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right yeah okay I I quite like that idea</u>
<u n="487" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so if we toast some bread and then make some tuna and then put some cheese and that on the top and melt it a bit and then <pause dur="short"/> I think I've got a bit of salad and that we could put in</u>
<u n="488" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0037">that might be quite nice <pause dur="short"/> okay I'll put the oven on <pause dur="short"/> excuse me?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0115">I'll leave that there for later cos um</u>
<u n="491" who="S0037">I know yeah <pause dur="short"/> so we should try and remember to blend the soup tonight and that and like not in the morning cos I'm always aware that I'm like <event desc="sound of blender"/> and it's the <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="492" who="S0115">oh well well yeah yeah we'll do it tonight yeah no problem</u>
<u n="493" who="S0037">oh is this the last of the bread?</u>
<u n="494" who="S0115">oh where did that go <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="495" who="S0037">I don't know <pause dur="short"/> actually it was me on Friday when I came back from the pub like making cheese on toast and egg bread and stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="496" who="S0115">oh possibly yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0037">that was part of it anyway <pause dur="short"/> it is naughty</u>
<u n="498" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> through <pause dur="short"/> is it still going?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="500" who="S0115">grab this and then</u>
<u n="501" who="S0037">oh yeah</u>
<u n="502" who="S0115">uh right <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/>  do you want are you gonna <unclear/> say like uh how many tomatoes we're getting and how many like?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0037" trans="overlap">we might <trunc>s</trunc> you might need to move some stuff off the table <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no I'll just  I'll just  um</u>
<u n="505" who="S0037">oh right <pause dur="short"/> I'll close this <pause dur="short"/> the fridge light's come back on did I tell you?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0115">it's on and off innit?</u>
<u n="507" who="S0037">I wonder what's doing that like? It's so annoying <pause dur="short"/> oh I forgot we'd bought <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know we had this Branston pickle</u>
<u n="508" who="S0115">oh yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0037">I know <pause dur="short"/> I keep forgetting</u>
<u n="510" who="S0115">so like have we decided how many  how many  <unclear/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh that really needs eating wonder if we should've put that in the soup?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0115">no we'll cook it tomorrow or something</u>
<u n="513" who="S0037">okay</u>
<u n="514" who="S0115">have we decided how many um how many plants were growing now?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0037">um well no so so I wrote down like the <trunc>bo</trunc></u>
<u n="516" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah so I thought <unclear/> wanted to talk about</u>
<u n="517" who="S0037">I wrote down like the boxes that we have um at the moment</u>
<u n="518" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="519" who="S0037">and we've got like um five of those sort of trough ones</u>
<u n="520" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="521" who="S0037">we've got two of those kind of big tomato tubs <pause dur="short"/> round ones <pause dur="short"/> um that have got like the dead ones from last year in there I need to throw away</u>
<u n="522" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0037">and then we've got um <pause dur="short"/> we've got like what else have we got hang on a minute <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah we've got like a big green like a big green planter</u>
<u n="524" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0037">and also like a big um <trunc>s</trunc> one that I bought last year but I didn't use in the end <pause dur="short"/> like <trunc>ar</trunc> um like a bit sort of what's it called? I think it was for strawberries or something <pause dur="short"/> it's like a big um thing that's got like holes in the side</u>
<u n="526" who="S0115">uh right</u>
<u n="527" who="S0037">so it's like it's collapsible <pause dur="short"/>  do you remember when I bought it I bought it from Aldi</u>
<u n="528" who="S0115">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="529" who="S0037">it's collapsible so <pause dur="short"/> but it's got like holes in the side where things poke out of</u>
<u n="530" who="S0115">right yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I think I remember that yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0037">so you could put in like herbs or <trunc>i</trunc> like um strawbs or something <pause dur="short"/> but so I think tomorrow I might  I might  buy that or <trunc>la</trunc> later tonight even I might buy that um greenhouse thing that I saw  you know those little like collapsible temporary ones?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0115">um yeah</u>
<u n="533" who="S0037">because I was looking at I was reading some um articles on um like this gardening thing <pause dur="short"/> and they were saying about like the like aubergines are kinda hard to grow here but not impossible <pause dur="short"/> and I think certainly given our</u>
<u n="534" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> because it's just too damn cold then is it?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0037">well it's a bit cold but they say they grow well in like a sheltered spot or in like a little greenhouse thing so if we got a little greenhouse and put its little lid down then I imagine it would grow <pause dur="short"/> but there's certain types that are really good like ones that grow smaller and</u>
<u n="536" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> shall I just grab a chair?</u>
<u n="537" who="S0037">um yeah <pause dur="short"/> ones that grow  ones that grow  <trunc>sma</trunc> oh we can go through actually while we're waiting</u>
<u n="538" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> right yeah <pause dur="short"/> whatever's easier</u>
<u n="539" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh no actually I'll</u>
<u n="540" who="S0115">Cos you've got that bread on there</u>
<u n="541" who="S0037">I know yeah <pause dur="short"/> I <trunc>w</trunc> I'll just do the rest of this <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> you can get like ones that are like um smaller <pause dur="short"/> the plants grow smaller and they grow like like more more sort of fruits on the</u>
<u n="542" who="S0115">I see</u>
<u n="543" who="S0037">plants than the other ones <pause dur="short"/> and if you  if you   google it if you have a look here you go if you have a look for like aubergine seeds I didn't realize how many there were <pause dur="short"/> you can get white ones you can get white and purple zebra like stripy ones <pause dur="short"/> you can get really long thin ones</u>
<u n="544" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah I think that that's the case with a lot of plants isn't it like uh <pause dur="short"/> they have you can generally get loads and loads of varieties of plants can't you?</u>
<u n="545" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> like in the supermarket you only see  you only see  you only see those wel like those ones in there those kind of like sort of fattish like oval black ones but purple black ones but you can get all like crazy kinds so</u>
<u n="546" who="S0115" trans="overlap">black black ones <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="547" who="S0037">but this article that I read said that this one called fairy tail this variety called fairy tail was good <pause dur="short"/> it they grew in kind of into like a sort of shrubby sort of <trunc>bru</trunc> uh bush</u>
<u n="548" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="549" who="S0037">and um like produced a lot of uh fruit  you know given the crop given the size of the plant so that might be worth having a look at</u>
<u n="550" who="S0115">right</u>
<u n="551" who="S0037">but the things that I liked the most last year like in fact the year before <pause dur="short"/> we did have things the year before didn't we cos we had cucumbers didn't we? Just get a tomato</u>
<u n="552" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="553" who="S0037">like tomatoes were really good and chillies <pause dur="short"/> you could never have too many tomatoes and chillies <pause dur="short"/> or cucumbers even <pause dur="short"/> so I'd definitely like to grow those again</u>
<u n="554" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0037">but earlier today I put in peas carrots which I've never done before <pause dur="short"/> I did we did peas last year</u>
<u n="556" who="S0115" trans="overlap">um <pause dur="short"/> yeah carrots are new yeah</u>
<u n="557" who="S0037">carrots and spring onions which could be really nice</u>
<u n="558" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right that that'll be uh that'll be good</u>
<u n="559" who="S0037">so they're in now and like we have to sow them every two weeks <pause dur="short"/> dunno how quite how we're gonna</u>
<u n="560" who="S0115">no they are in they are the <trunc>solen</trunc> solenoids</u>
<u n="561" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I know same as potatoes yeah I was surprised</u>
<u n="562" who="S0115">that was a sort of a guess that I guessed at first but then I like wasn't sure</u>
<u n="563" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="564" who="S0115">but in fact um they are the um <trunc>solen</trunc> like they that that's their name solanum uh melangina</u>
<u n="565" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh they're like the <trunc>n</trunc> the name the</u>
<u n="566" who="S0115">they're they're the type</u>
<u n="567" who="S0037">the county palatine</u>
<u n="568" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="569" who="S0037">you know what I mean</u>
<u n="570" who="S0115">the type of uh species or the uh <pause dur="short"/> yeah the I've I've I dunno what the word is but  you know they're the type the um</u>
<u n="571" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I don't  I don't  know either <pause dur="short"/> no vocabulary <pause dur="short"/> anyway so so I'd really like to try some aubergines just cos I like the taste of them so much and then uh courgettes were good last <pause dur="short"/> was it courgettes we had?</u>
<u n="572" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="573" who="S0037">things that grow quite fast <pause dur="short"/> courgettes grow quite fast <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="574" who="S0115">ah a lot  of these are poisonous actually</u>
<u n="575" who="S0037">I know poison ivy and stuff in that group yeah I read</u>
<u n="576" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><unclear/> So like yeah so what were you saying uh find um different varieties or?</u>
<u n="577" who="S0037">so oh yeah so if you type go on Amazon and then type in like uh aubergine seeds</u>
<u n="578" who="S0115">those like little round ones from uh?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0037">you can get like baby ones um</u>
<u n="580" who="S0115">oh you want me to search for how many seeds are available?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0037">well just like that's a <pause dur="short"/> I was just wanting to show you what I saw before like where so I typed in aubergine seeds and then there was like so many different and I don't just mean like different people selling them I meant like different types  you know like they all looked kinda different <pause dur="short"/> which I thought was good</u>
<u n="582" who="S0115">oh right so you can eat some of them can't you?</u>
<u n="583" who="S0037">sorry?</u>
<u n="584" who="S0115">you can eat aubergine seeds can't you?</u>
<u n="585" who="S0037">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="586" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0037">you mean like pumpkin seeds?</u>
<u n="588" who="S0115">uh yeah</u>
<u n="589" who="S0037">I suppose you can <pause dur="short"/> I never really thought about it</u>
<u n="590" who="S0115">no it was just Google suggest uh I put in aubergine seeds and it produced that</u>
<u n="591" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh you mean like yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0115">like it suggested it yeah <pause dur="short"/> it suggested edible</u>
<u n="593" who="S0037">huh <pause dur="short"/> but um anyway so <pause dur="short"/> this has firmed up a bit actually</u>
<u n="594" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="595" who="S0037">anyway so yeah there there's so many different varieties</u>
<u n="596" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="597" who="S0037">just thought like we should get some different ones so I quite fancy doing that I mean how about you what do you  what do you  fancy growing?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0115">ah I was interested in um like uh um <trunc>or</trunc> like <trunc>y</trunc> yeah like citrus and like stuff you make in a greenhouse that you make in a greenhouse</u>
<u n="599" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="600" who="S0115">uh but I think pretty much the same as you I mean we've got a lot of things going so</u>
<u n="601" who="S0037">no well I haven't got</u>
<u n="602" who="S0115">I mean pretty much the same as you but perhaps to try and get quite a lot large quantity and then plan ahead so we try and save some money  you know use it to to um to have like a bit of a strategy and like plan to save money</u>
<u n="603" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> the things that we would normally buy <pause dur="short"/> well I think we've got I think the one thing this year I'm more aware of like the space that we've got <pause dur="short"/> last year I've just been like putting like um sort of things round the edge of the little bit of patio <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm more ruthless this year I think I'll be like well I've already started like hanging stuff up and</u>
<u n="604" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I mean we do have  you know gotta make use of the space you've got and we have got  we have got  space  you know</u>
<u n="605" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="606" who="S0115">well a fair amount of space so <pause dur="short"/> uh so what you wanted me to search for like um the availability of them?</u>
<u n="607" who="S0037" trans="overlap">uh no I don't I suppose I just wanted you to see like the <trunc>varie</trunc></u>
<u n="608" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so I've got uh Real Seeds Dot Co Dot UK</u>
<u n="609" who="S0037">no just go to like <trunc>Amaz</trunc> Amazon or something or <pause dur="short"/> well go wherever you want obviously</u>
<u n="610" who="S0115">well this is like just Google results <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> they grow a bit slower than tomatoes and peppers their relatives uh</u>
<u n="611" who="S0037">but that's funny because for us the tomatoes grew really fast and the <trunc>toma</trunc> and the peppers grew really slow last year so</u>
<u n="612" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="613" who="S0037">maybe it's a temperature thing</u>
<u n="614" who="S0115">start them off with some heat and then either transplant out um or grow in a greenhouse <unclear/></u>
<u n="615" who="S0037" trans="overlap">um where's the cheese? Is it still in my bag?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0115">probably</u>
<u n="617" who="S0037"></u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="618" who="S0037">yes it was</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="619" who="S0115">well they got one called uh de Barbentane</u>
<u n="620" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0115">a medium sized cylindrical black aubergine from France <pause dur="short"/> they've got  Ronde de Valence which is a a new one they're trying out this year</u>
<u n="622" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="623" who="S0115">uh round black fruit like a tennis ball size</u>
<u n="624" who="S0037">hm <pause dur="short"/> so yeah I think</u>
<u n="625" who="S0115" trans="overlap">you can save them yourself from the plant while they're inside it inside the uh inside the fruit <unclear/></u>
<u n="626" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah but sometimes the ones that you grow from like  you know they've been treated or they're not like the best variety</u>
<u n="627" who="S0115">uh well yeah but it's still worth trying isn't it? And these ones seem to say like you you could save it yourself but um</u>
<u n="628" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh of course</u>
<u n="629" who="S0115">if you cut the seed out of the middle of it</u>
<u n="630" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="631" who="S0115">with a bowl of water or something yeah</u>
<u n="632" who="S0037">okay</u>
<u n="633" who="S0115">A very ripe fruit</u>
<u n="634" who="S0037">well that one is very ripe we could maybe try that one</u>
<u n="635" who="S0115">rinse it through a sieve to get the seed</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="636" who="S0037">mm this cheese is a bit disappointing</u>
<u n="637" who="S0115" trans="overlap">uh this is actually selling seeds and it will sell you twenty-five for two pounds</u>
<u n="638" who="S0037">yeah I saw them on uh</u>
<u n="639" who="S0115">from um these these ones <pause dur="short"/> uh bought seeds</u>
<u n="640" who="S0037">I saw them on Amazon and stuff so <pause dur="short"/> I might try well I might try that variety that was mentioned because like if it's a recommended  you know Uh it's in the BBC Gardening magazine thing</u>
<u n="641" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="642" who="S0115">is there any news?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="643" who="S0115">Amazon search</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="644" who="S0115">I'm just in Amazon <pause dur="short"/> if I go to</u>
<u n="645" who="S0037">yeah there's some good ones</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="646" who="S0037">okay</u>
<u n="647" who="S0115">Amazon <unclear/></u>
<u n="648" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> sorry?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0115">enter</u>
<u n="650" who="S0037">I've got some of that left?  do you want some?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0115" trans="overlap">just searching Amazon <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> what for?</u>
<u n="652" who="S0037">couldn't balance it on <pause dur="short"/> it's just the tuna I couldn't balance it all on the bread</u>
<u n="653" who="S0115" trans="overlap">oh right <pause dur="short"/> did you save any mayonnaise or did you put it all in?</u>
<u n="654" who="S0037">no no no of course there's loads</u>
<u n="655" who="S0115">oh right yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah I was  I was  kind of thinking that like I would make like a whole jar  you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="656" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="657" who="S0115">but I reckon you'd probably need about twenty eggs for that <pause dur="short"/> um which we haven't got</u>
<u n="658" who="S0037">no I don't know there's like that's quite a lot there</u>
<u n="659" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> viserba <pause dur="short"/> something called Viserba aubergine</u>
<u n="660" who="S0037">let me look</u>
<u n="661" who="S0115">it's on Amazon</u>
<u n="662" who="S0037">uh if you open the Amazon like um it's got like an Amazon app</u>
<u n="663" who="S0115">oh yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah I mean okay I'll have a look on this</u>
<u n="664" who="S0037">it's um it's not on the net <pause dur="short"/> it's on</u>
<u n="665" who="S0115">it's not on the main desktop</u>
<u n="666" who="S0037">no it's in um it's just here on the left</u>
<u n="667" who="S0115">Will you uh see if is he uh is our recorder going okay?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0037">ay? Uh yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's fine</u>
<u n="669" who="S0115">so would you like to be a farmer then?</u>
<u n="670" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> I don't know</u>
<u n="671" who="S0115" trans="overlap">of of um like oranges and?</u>
<u n="672" who="S0037">I sort of like the outdoor thing but I think I might get sick of it <pause dur="short"/> like it's nice like in the summer like it's nice for us to be like ooh look it's a lovely day I'll potter round in the garden <pause dur="short"/> Ah no it's raining never mind I'll do it next week let's go to the pub <pause dur="short"/> Like</u>
<u n="673" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="674" who="S0037">if you're a farmer it's</u>
<u n="675" who="S0115">ah yeah I mean it's like it sounds nice on paper doesn't it?</u>
<u n="676" who="S0037" trans="overlap">you don't get that choice <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="677" who="S0115">maybe it sounds nice but in reality it's not quite as idyllic as it sometimes</u>
<u n="678" who="S0037" trans="overlap">na <pause dur="short"/> I think  I think  I'd like a beer garden</u>
<u n="679" who="S0115" trans="overlap">and <trunc>look</trunc> looking like at grapes  you know like grapes or or hops or something</u>
<u n="680" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="681" who="S0115">I I I thought that I would really like to be brewer</u>
<u n="682" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="683" who="S0115">um of some sort</u>
<u n="684" who="S0037">but being a brewer and being a hop grower isn't the same is it I mean?</u>
<u n="685" who="S0115">I guess not although</u>
<u n="686" who="S0037">I mean obviously they go hand in hand</u>
<u n="687" who="S0115" trans="overlap">no they they they yeah I mean</u>
<u n="688" who="S0037">wine fine fine growing</u>
<u n="689" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah <trunc>some</trunc> but if I was <pause dur="short"/> yeah it sounds nice  sounds nice  like to get out and go south of France or something get a house and like grow loads of like grapes and stuff but uh</u>
<u n="690" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but it's the same as anything like <pause dur="short"/> I think I'm realistic like any job  any job  it no matter how fantastic it sounds there's always like crap bits isn't there like? And I think</u>
<u n="691" who="S0115">well I mean you got some some jobs are just some jobs are definitely better than others well  you know I suppose</u>
<u n="692" who="S0037" trans="overlap">like if if my job was like knitting things all day I would I'm sure I would get totally pissed off with it like <pause dur="short"/> but because it's not and it's just something I like doing then I like doing it <pause dur="short"/> like I was just saying there like the gardening I'd like a bigger garden with like <trunc>mo</trunc> I'd like a greenhouse I'd like more space</u>
<u n="693" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="694" who="S0037">I'd like some chickens really but I wouldn't want a farm where I had to get up at five in the morning and like <vocal desc="laugh"/> every day and without fail  you know?</u>
<u n="695" who="S0115">yeah I mean well there's a big big difference <trunc>betwe</trunc> <pause dur="short"/> but you can employ I suppose you can  you can  sort of employ people can't you?</u>
<u n="696" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well same with anything though you can of course you can you can employ someone to do your garden</u>
<u n="697" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> so I guess I meant like that you would employ</u>
<u n="698" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but I don't really see the point in like people who have  you know like gardens that've got like flowers and that in <pause dur="short"/> I like flowers and I think they're very beautiful <pause dur="short"/> but I sort of don't really like <pause dur="short"/> I think it's a waste when I see these gardens that've just got like <trunc>bu</trunc> like bushes and that in</u>
<u n="699" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so you wouldn't like to live in in Spain and have a big massive load of orange trees and uh</u>
<u n="700" who="S0037">yeah it might be really nice but</u>
<u n="701" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but it might be a bit of a pain</u>
<u n="702" who="S0037" trans="overlap">if you're the person who's in charge and responsible for those orange trees</u>
<u n="703" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="704" who="S0037">then that might take the shine off</u>
<u n="705" who="S0115">the problem with farming is that they suffer from  you know like um</u>
<u n="706" who="S0037" trans="overlap">crops and  pestilence yeah</u>
<u n="707" who="S0115">it it there's a <trunc>ga</trunc> there's an element of gambling isn't there because you could get a very bad bad you know lack of sun and you could lose loads of money if you don't the sun right</u>
<u n="708" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think it would be nice to like for example go to stay in an orange grove and for a while <vocal desc="laugh"/> think it would</u>
<u n="709" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well like I kind of like I <trunc>k</trunc> I like the idea of being more more self-sufficient  you know</u>
<u n="710" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh it's nearly done <pause dur="short"/> I'd like it if my parents had one and then I could just go over when I pleased loll around do whatever I fancied</u>
<u n="711" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="712" who="S0037">not really one that I was responsible for and was down to me sort of thing <pause dur="short"/> ah I've eaten all the nuts</u>
<u n="713" who="S0115">yeah um that is  that is  something that I'm guilty of</u>
<u n="714" who="S0037">it's alright though <pause dur="short"/> they were yours</u>
<u n="715" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Amazon's got two hundred seeds for ninety-nine P <pause dur="short"/> oh but a pound for shipping <pause dur="short"/> so we're back on two pounds again <pause dur="short"/> plus <pause dur="short"/> uh but these ones have more seeds</u>
<u n="716" who="S0037" trans="overlap">do you want the crust or  do you want me to have the crust?</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="717" who="S0115">probably I dunno about Amazon <trunc>pro</trunc> probably be better off going to a specialized specialized seed maker</u>
<u n="718" who="S0037" trans="overlap">Sutton Seeds or something? No but I just meant like</u>
<u n="719" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I mean that last website looked good <pause dur="short"/> but I but I'd also like to</u>
<u n="720" who="S0037" trans="overlap">actually no you have this one</u>
<u n="721" who="S0115">I'm not actually hungry so I can put if you put mine on the side somewhere <pause dur="short"/> so are we gonna move through?</u>
<u n="722" who="S0037">uh yeah</u>
<u n="723" who="S0115">to</u>
<u n="724" who="S0037">oh are you not hungry?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0115">not right now but I I might be like</u>
<u n="726" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I'm sorry I shouldn't have made it if you weren't hungry</u>
<u n="727" who="S0115">no cos you were hungry so</u>
<u n="728" who="S0037">well that doesn't mean anything</u>
<u n="729" who="S0115">it doesn't</u>
<u n="730" who="S0037">kinda always hungry a bit</u>
<u n="731" who="S0115">uh I'll have it later yeah</u>
<u n="732" who="S0037">what have you been nibbling things in there?</u>
<u n="733" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but the you've got the suggestions for uh Amazon like</u>
<u n="734" who="S0037">oh have I?</u>
<u n="735" who="S0115">customers who liked this also liked would like tomatoes</u>
<u n="736" who="S0037" trans="overlap">also like <pause dur="short"/> ah</u>
<u n="737" who="S0115">tomatoes money maker it says</u>
<u n="738" who="S0037">what's that?</u>
<u n="739" who="S0115">fifty seeds</u>
<u n="740" who="S0037">I suppose it does make you money cos you you know like you spend a pound on like</u>
<u n="741" who="S0115">I think tomatoes and but we also use a lot of lemons like there's a sort of advantage of that</u>
<u n="742" who="S0037">ah but those tomatoes last year the smell of them like <pause dur="short"/> and they were so tasty weren't they? They were just like so nice in your mouth</u>
<u n="743" who="S0115">yeah yeah them them cherry ones like really sort of tangy and sweet yeah</u>
<u n="744" who="S0037">your parents brought those like maybe they'll bring some more <pause dur="short"/> maybe your mam'll bring some more</u>
<u n="745" who="S0115">yeah I'm gonna uh see if they don't mind bringing some stuff</u>
<u n="746" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I wouldn't mind if she did <pause dur="short"/> shall I eat this one with the crust then?</u>
<u n="747" who="S0115">uh yeah <pause dur="short"/> I'll um pour me some bring bring that through <pause dur="short"/> uh</u>
<u n="748" who="S0037">that is that mine? Oh I can't handle everything <pause dur="short"/> I mean I can't carry everything</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="749" who="S0037">ah thank you</u>
<u n="750" who="S0115"><unclear/></u>
<u n="751" who="S0037">ah you left the lid off</u>
<u n="752" who="S0115">ah well yeah I couldn't fit it on but it's</u>
<u n="753" who="S0037">oh right</u>
<u n="754" who="S0115">it should be alright in the short term</u>
<u n="755" who="S0037">no it's fine</u>
<u n="756" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Um are we gonna get some silly videos on and um</u>
<u n="757" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> uh maybe we should get one of those have you heard of those like um TVs that you sort of link up to the internet?</u>
<u n="758" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="759" who="S0037">like a internet TV?</u>
<u n="760" who="S0115">oh right</u>
<u n="761" who="S0037">oh <trunc>ha</trunc> hairy bobber <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="762" who="S0115">excuse me?</u>
<u n="763" who="S0037">it's Harry Potter <pause dur="short"/> I was just doing it in my Mary Poppins voice imagining that Dick Van Dyke was in it</u>
<u n="764" who="S0115">do you think that Dick Van Dyke should be in it?</u>
<u n="765" who="S0037" trans="overlap">hairy Bobber <pause dur="short"/> have you seen this one? Did we watch this one at Christmas?</u>
<u n="766" who="S0115">I haven't seen any of them apart from like</u>
<u n="767" who="S0037">no you have because we watched some at Christmas</u>
<u n="768" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="769" who="S0037">didn't we? Although we did both <trunc>f</trunc> fall asleep and it was Christmas so we were at various points between sobriety and hangover</u>
<u n="770" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I just yeah you think yeah I mean I just um I don't really know that much about Harry Potter <pause dur="short"/> okay <pause dur="short"/> probably something better on <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="771" who="S0037">the Voice <pause dur="short"/> the Voice UK <pause dur="short"/> oh it's ending</u>
<u n="772" who="S0115">that's Russell Howard there <pause dur="short"/> the Man Who Discovered Egypt uh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="773" who="S0037">oh it sounds a bit stupid</u>
<u n="774" who="S0115">like if <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="775" who="S0037">um <pause dur="short"/> I could just put the radio on</u>
<u n="776" who="S0115">but still like I like  you know for Sunday like it's good to have a bit of uh a bit of documentary isn't it?</u>
<u n="777" who="S0037">I do like it but I'm gonna if we're doing this I dunno if I can <pause dur="short"/> could watch Britain's Got Talent</u>
<u n="778" who="S0115">uh not not a massive fan of Britain's Got Talent uh <pause dur="short"/> put put some silly uh</u>
<u n="779" who="S0037">series A <pause dur="short"/> oh no <pause dur="short"/> maybe we should get ESPN</u>
<u n="780" who="S0115" trans="overlap">locked out</u>
<u n="781" who="S0037">maybe we should get it <pause dur="short"/> oh Silent Witness is nearly on and I quite like that</u>
<u n="782" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="783" who="S0037">ah she's <trunc>an</trunc> even more annoying than Julia Bradbury</u>
<u n="784" who="S0115">who's like  who's like  your most annoying presenter of all time?</u>
<u n="785" who="S0037"> Um <pause dur="short"/> kay Burley <pause dur="short"/> by miles</u>
<u n="786" who="S0115">oh yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> she's really awful <pause dur="short"/> uh did you see that thing with uh</u>
<u n="787" who="S0037">yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> ron Burgundy</u>
<u n="788" who="S0115">with the quote quotes from Ron Burgundy um?</u>
<u n="789" who="S0037">did you get them?</u>
<u n="790" who="S0115">no so I don't  I don't  know Ron Burgundy that well <pause dur="short"/> like you you'd have to seen  you know Anchor Man  you know a couple of times to know all the lines like</u>
<u n="791" who="S0037">that <trunc>maze</trunc> mayonnaise is really nice</u>
<u n="792" who="S0115">excellent <pause dur="short"/> not not too bad with the pepper then but uh you you getting a bit like uh getting a bit annoyed by the pepper earlier it was getting  it was getting  on your nerves wasn't it?</u>
<u n="793" who="S0037">I don't like <trunc>i</trunc> the taste if it on its own very much but I like it in things</u>
<u n="794" who="S0115" trans="overlap">it's uh you're not supposed to have it on its own and that's that's the point isn't it like?</u>
<u n="795" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> it's almost got like a um <pause dur="short"/> like a sort of smoky taste but I don't know wheat that's from</u>
<u n="796" who="S0115">ah</u>
<u n="797" who="S0037">have a bit</u>
<u n="798" who="S0115">uh no I'm okay for now <pause dur="short"/>  Is it the rocket?</u>
<u n="799" who="S0037">maybe it's the cheese</u>
<u n="800" who="S0115">the rocket that's doing that?</u>
<u n="801" who="S0037">uh <pause dur="short"/> maybe</u>
<u n="802" who="S0115">so what what job would you do like ideally then cos like</u>
<u n="803" who="S0037">I do quite like my job really I mean <pause dur="short"/> maybe I'd just like to work part time <vocal desc="laugh"/> That'd be quite nice</u>
<u n="804" who="S0115">you're saying just just no job then?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0037">mm <pause dur="short"/> I don't know I like</u>
<u n="806" who="S0115" trans="overlap">gotta do  gotta do  a bit <pause dur="short"/> gotta have a bit of something to do</u>
<u n="807" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I like my job in that like it's quite varied and it does use the skills that I've got <pause dur="short"/> um if I didn't need any money <pause dur="short"/> oh I don't know actually I've never really</u>
<u n="808" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but you <trunc>s</trunc> I think you said you would <trunc>g</trunc> you would get like um maybe get more qualifications then wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="809" who="S0037">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I would</u>
<u n="810" who="S0115">if you  if you  didn't need money</u>
<u n="811" who="S0037">but I think I'd also like to indulge my creative side</u>
<u n="812" who="S0115">yeah?</u>
<u n="813" who="S0037">do more knitting and</u>
<u n="814" who="S0115"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="815" who="S0037">that kind of thing but <pause dur="short"/> I don't know really <pause dur="short"/> and for job though uh I'm not sure <pause dur="short"/> I'd have to give it some thought</u>
<u n="816" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> um <pause dur="short"/> well it's <pause dur="short"/> no I think I'd I'd like to be sort of a  you know researcher doing what I do now and</u>
<u n="817" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="818" who="S0115">but with with more like if I had a bit more money then I I'd be able to get like better equipment and stuff</u>
<u n="819" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="820" who="S0115">um</u>
<u n="821" who="S0037">I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I suppose I do quite like my job I mean there's there's good things and bad things about all jobs <pause dur="short"/> I think it's really easy to be like <pause dur="short"/>  you know sort of thinking that something else is really great <pause dur="short"/> things always look really great when you're not doing it like <pause dur="short"/>  you know grass is greener and all</u>
<u n="822" who="S0115">oh um yeah</u>
<u n="823" who="S0037">I mean I think it's it'd be fabulous to do this but</u>
<u n="824" who="S0115">you mean like well talking of Britain's Got Talent I mean  you know like a being a star</u>
<u n="825" who="S0037">well <pause dur="short"/> it's never ever been anything I've even been remotely interested in</u>
<u n="826" who="S0115">right <vocal desc="laugh"/> No I wouldn't I'm I'm not really a</u>
<u n="827" who="S0037">I don't understand why people wanna do it</u>
<u n="828" who="S0115">although <pause dur="short"/> I mean but when I was  you know learning guitar I think I would've liked to have been in a band and but</u>
<u n="829" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="830" who="S0115">but</u>
<u n="831" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but that's for the that's for being in a band not cos you wanna be like pop star</u>
<u n="832" who="S0115" trans="overlap">but I think um I wouldn't wanna be  I wouldn't wanna be  like yeah I wouldn't wanna be like a one of those types of pop stars</u>
<u n="833" who="S0037">no</u>
<u n="834" who="S0115">nor would people want to uh to listen to me <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="835" who="S0037">no don't be silly <pause dur="short"/> no I just think like <pause dur="short"/> it's not really my sort of thing</u>
<u n="836" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="837" who="S0115">who is this?</u>
<u n="838" who="S0037">might like to have like a little coffee shop or something that you could just potter about in</u>
<u n="839" who="S0115">right yeah yeah yeah like a something casual</u>
<u n="840" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="841" who="S0115">maybe like growing stuff and like brewing maybe</u>
<u n="842" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="843" who="S0115">if you're just doing it uh sort of casually <pause dur="short"/> doing it more for yourself like <trunc>sel</trunc> self sufficiency uh rather than like um</u>
<u n="844" who="S0037">yeah be nice</u>
<u n="845" who="S0115">as a as for a living <pause dur="short"/> um</u>
<u n="846" who="S0037">Good sandwich <pause dur="short"/> if I do say so myself</u>
<u n="847" who="S0115">yeah well uh you put quite a lot of effort into  you know with</u>
<u n="848" who="S0037">not really</u>
<u n="849" who="S0115">well making the mayonnaise and everything</u>
<u n="850" who="S0037">well yeah <pause dur="short"/> sorry I was on the phone so long</u>
<u n="851" who="S0115">oh no it's no problem well you you gotta stay in touch with your family haven't you?</u>
<u n="852" who="S0037">you do</u>
<u n="853" who="S0115">um <pause dur="short"/> ah so has <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got uh a <trunc>jo</trunc> a new job you were saying uh?</u>
<u n="854" who="S0037">mm <pause dur="short"/> he's like one of those like <pause dur="short"/> you know when you're in the street?</u>
<u n="855" who="S0115">I  overheard  I overheard  some stuff</u>
<u n="856" who="S0037" trans="overlap">when you see someone with a clipboard?</u>
<u n="857" who="S0115">I overheard the word clipboard</u>
<u n="858" who="S0037">like me dad said he's a professional  beggar yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's true</u>
<u n="859" who="S0115">so he's he stands with a clipboard and um</u>
<u n="860" who="S0037">tries to <pause dur="short"/> no I think he's going from door to door or something <pause dur="short"/> it's not the first time he's done that sort of rubbish</u>
<u n="861" who="S0115" trans="overlap">who does he work for?</u>
<u n="862" who="S0037">he used to sell TalkTalk um  Broadband door to door</u>
<u n="863" who="S0115">that was the sort of thing that that the jobs kind of jobs that were going around like when I was at finishing school um like my friend sort of like tried to do that sort of job</u>
<u n="864" who="S0037" trans="overlap">but now he's going door to door <pause dur="short"/> he's going door to door um asking for <trunc>donation</trunc> donations for a local hospice or something</u>
<u n="865" who="S0115">uh okay fair enough I mean</u>
<u n="866" who="S0037">well not fair enough</u>
<u n="867" who="S0115">I I don't personally</u>
<u n="868" who="S0037" trans="overlap">they're just annoying</u>
<u n="869" who="S0115">yeah I I don't like  I don't like  it when someone <pause dur="short"/> I don't like anything door to door to be honest</u>
<u n="870" who="S0037">me neither <pause dur="short"/> it's just an <trunc>in</trunc> invasion of your like home isn't it?</u>
<u n="871" who="S0115">it's I mean if it was here like I think we're  benefiting from the fact that we're in a flat and therefore like you <trunc>s</trunc> you feel slightly safer like cos you you're not the only one so like <pause dur="short"/> but I generally don't answer the door or the phone unless I know who it is um</u>
<u n="872" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no I don't <pause dur="short"/> I've got no reason to if like</u>
<u n="873" who="S0115">no it's</u>
<u n="874" who="S0037">I think if someone was like</u>
<u n="875" who="S0115" trans="overlap">Cos we don't <trunc>w</trunc> we don't  we don't  get much knocking round here I think</u>
<u n="876" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I think if someone was really urgently like <trunc>ra</trunc> ringing the doorbell and banging on the door I would go and look and see what it is but if someone just rings the doorbell I just think I'm not expecting a parcel  <pause dur="short"/> I'm not expecting anyone <pause dur="short"/> I'm not gonna answer <pause dur="short"/> it's obviously just gonna be people bothering you</u>
<u n="877" who="S0115">yeah I know  it is  it is um there is something that's sort of</u>
<u n="878" who="S0037" trans="overlap">I hate all that stuff <pause dur="short"/> I really do</u>
<u n="879" who="S0115">I mean the thing with a charity is that you you have to beg otherwise you you won't get anything will you unless you can somehow secure government funding from somewhere or unless you you</u>
<u n="880" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I know <pause dur="short"/> but the reason he's taking is because it's like sixteen hours a week but you can do them whenever you want</u>
<u n="881" who="S0115">yeah so he must be <pause dur="short"/> well as as usual he he's presumably working like sixty hours a week or or more than that like</u>
<u n="882" who="S0037" trans="overlap">oh obviously yeah</u>
<u n="883" who="S0115">he he's always works many hours doesn't he? Um that's just  that's just  what he likes isn't it?</u>
<u n="884" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well he's working twenty-four hours at the pub and sixteen hours at this thing and then</u>
<u n="885" who="S0115">I suppose importing <pause dur="short"/> and that seemed like a really quite um quite a a quite a positive actually this importing but is he just doing that I mean how is he?</u>
<u n="886" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah but never getting anywhere</u>
<u n="887" who="S0115">is he buying how's he buying it cos he's buying stuff from China isn't he?</u>
<u n="888" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he's um <pause dur="short"/> mhm</u>
<u n="889" who="S0115">and who's he <trunc>buy</trunc> where's he <trunc>get</trunc>?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he's buying them from China <pause dur="short"/> these so it's a wrestling thing <pause dur="short"/> so apparently um</u>
<u n="891" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="892" who="S0037">certain wrestlers like I don't really follow the wrestling</u>
<u n="893" who="S0115">no I don't don't following wrestling no but</u>
<u n="894" who="S0037">all these different wrestlers or whatever <pause dur="short"/> um and well it came about cos he wanted to himself to buy like a a T-shirt with like let's just make up a name like Steaming <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or something</u>
<u n="895" who="S0115" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Tent Tent Peg</u>
<u n="896" who="S0037" trans="overlap">right so he wanted to buy <trunc>s</trunc> a Steaming Steaming <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> Tent Peg</u>
<u n="897" who="S0115">tent Peg and his arch enemy Stone or Mister Pebbles or whatever like</u>
<u n="898" who="S0037" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Steaming <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> Tent Peg he wanted to buy his um <pause dur="short"/> wanted to buy a shirt  a shirt  with his face on or I don't know some sort of <pause dur="short"/> anyway he wanted to buy some shirt some wrestling shirt</u>
<u n="899" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="900" who="S0037">and he realized he could only get it from the US or from China <pause dur="short"/> and it was really expensive it was</u>
<u n="901" who="S0115">yeah <pause dur="short"/> so he chose China because it's cheaper?</u>
<u n="902" who="S0037">well no <pause dur="short"/> I mean to buy one for himself and it was like pardon me it was really expensive so then</u>
<u n="903" who="S0115" trans="overlap">yeah so bought like a <unclear/> like like he's like bit like Del Boy he's a bit of that in him</u>
<u n="904" who="S0037">he <trunc>i</trunc> he is definitely like Del Boy <pause dur="short"/> so then he worked so then he looked into how much he would cost to buy <pause dur="short"/> cos he had some mates who wanted one as well or something</u>
<u n="905" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="906" who="S0037">and so then he worked how much it would cost to buy ten and how much it would cost to buy a hundred or whatever <pause dur="short"/> so then he got in touch with some <trunc>h</trunc> whoever and bought like however many</u>
<u n="907" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="908" who="S0037">then started selling them online <pause dur="short"/> so he's been doing that and then I think now I'm not sure if he's rented a a rail in like a alternative shop in the Galleries <pause dur="short"/> alternative I mean like</u>
<u n="909" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="910" who="S0037">goth punk rock <pause dur="short"/>  you know</u>
<u n="911" who="S0115" trans="overlap">so he's rented rented a rail yeah <pause dur="short"/> that sounds like like a promising thing although like like</u>
<u n="912" who="S0037" trans="overlap">well he said it's doing some <pause dur="short"/> it's paying some bills</u>
<u n="913" who="S0115">it it did sound promising um</u>
<u n="914" who="S0037" trans="overlap">so <pause dur="short"/> and he's like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s he's doing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s nana's garden and he's washing someone else's car and</u>
<u n="915" who="S0115" trans="overlap">well he's he's really coming out with  you know masses of ideas masses of like plans and that</u>
<u n="916" who="S0037" trans="overlap">he has to <pause dur="short"/> I think he's just scared cos like obviously</u>
<u n="917" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I think I would've though that <pause dur="short"/> is it still okay? I'd thought though that like while he's in he he's putting in a lot of time but I think it's also important to try and <pause dur="short"/> are you uh changing it or?</u>
<u n="918" who="S0037">no no it's fine</u>
<u n="919" who="S0115">well keep it  keep it  going or or?</u>
<u n="920" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah I know</u>
<u n="921" who="S0115">I think he he would try and maybe get something with a higher rate of pay so that if if if possible</u>
<u n="922" who="S0037" trans="overlap">yeah he really should <pause dur="short"/> I dunno <pause dur="short"/> I'm hoping that he'll just scrabble around and eventually like find something that'll come good but in the meantime he's just like doing odds and sods</u>
<u n="923" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I think <trunc>pr</trunc> I I'd say probably most likely that he would make more out of importing and selling I think</u>
<u n="924" who="S0037">well I don't know <pause dur="short"/> it's hard to tell</u>
<u n="925" who="S0115" trans="overlap">I think that that is  that is  more it's the most promising sort of thing</u>
<u n="926" who="S0037" trans="overlap">depends like how much the demand is for like these <trunc>w</trunc> weird wrestling shirts</u>
<u n="927" who="S0115">well yeah I mean I suppose you make connections and <pause dur="short"/> you make demand connections and make supply connections and in theory</u>
<u n="928" who="S0037">yeah</u>
<u n="929" who="S0115">um you could use those connections to sort of</u>
<u n="930" who="S0037">well yeah I mean or it might lead on to different things you just don't know</u>
<u n="931" who="S0115" trans="overlap">although <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="932" who="S0037">but he'll be fine like <pause dur="short"/> he always <pause dur="short"/> he always like</u>
<u n="933" who="S0115">really?</u>
<u n="934" who="S0037">comes out of it okay</u>
<u n="935" who="S0115" trans="overlap">would you say he  would you say he  always comes out okay like?</u>
<u n="936" who="S0037">no because he he makes it okay like he just he'd work  he'd work  a hundred hours a week if needed to like</u>
<u n="937" who="S0115">yeah</u>
<u n="938" who="S0037">he's not one of these people who's like I've got nothing to do and I've got loads of bills <pause dur="short"/> He'd just go out and</u>
<u n="939" who="S0115">yeah I mean he's he's the <trunc>s</trunc> he's the sort of person that who you would tell um  you know uh like someone who's who's on benefits or something</u>
<u n="940" who="S0037">yeah I know</u>
<u n="941" who="S0115">you tell them what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> does and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got like ten different jobs like you <trunc>c</trunc> it's never true that there's  that there's no  that there's no like</u>
<u n="942" who="S0037" trans="overlap">no that's what I get  that's what I get  annoyed about like</u>
<u n="943" who="S0115" trans="overlap">the the only</u>
</body>
</text>
