<text id="SR8V">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:32:27</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-10</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0428 S0610 S0612</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON's home, East London</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>BNC recordings, Linked In, Social Media, living abroad, visiting London, travelling, being scared of flying, Maldives, Whales, Spain, Pugs</topics>
		<activity>Sunday morning chat with friends</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, Inquiring, complaining, advising, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0428">
				<exactage>27</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Aylesbury, Buckinghamshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Eastern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language Research Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified; Italian -- level unspecified; French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0610">
				<exactage>28</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Abergavenny</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Wales</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Wales/ England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>V. Slight Welsh Accent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>4 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>wales</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>wales</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>wales</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Editor</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2>French</l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- Good working level; Italian -- Degree level</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0612">
				<exactage></exactage>
				<age1994>Unknown</age1994>
				<agerange>Unknown</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat></nat>
				<birthplace></birthplace>
				<birthcountry></birthcountry>
				<l1></l1>
				<lingorig></lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None indicated</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country></hab_country>
				<hab_dur></hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>9_unknown</edqual>
				<occupation></occupation>
				<socgrade>unknown</socgrade>
				<nssec>unknown</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0610">what tell me how you get the recordings on an email</u>
<u n="2" who="S0428">erm well from your phone you just kinda like erm <vocal desc="misc"/> you've just got to like upload them to like Dropbox or to your I dunno <trunc>h</trunc> I don't know how <trunc>y</trunc>your phone would do it</u>
<u n="3" who="S0612">I'm so rubbish with all these technologies</u>
<u n="4" who="S0610" trans="overlap">how are you gonna <trunc>s</trunc> get us to sign anything?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0428">pardon?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0610">how are you gonna get us to sign anything?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0428">I'll send it to you in the post I've already sent stuff <vocal desc="laugh"/> to you in the post</u>
<u n="8" who="S0610">I know I still don't know what happened to that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got an hour on his phone</u>
<u n="9" who="S0428">really?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0428">just <trunc>chu</trunc>chuck it over</u>
<u n="12" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0612">what so if I get one at home I can send it to you?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0428">yeah and you just have to sign the <trunc>for</trunc> I'll send you the forms to sign</u>
<u n="15" who="S0612">okay I have conversations from time to time at home</u>
<u n="16" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="17" who="S0428">they can't be with yourself or imaginary people</u>
<u n="18" who="S0612"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you'll just sort of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like with loads of different voices <vocal desc="laugh"/> and all these consent forms of like written in your left hand <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0612"><unclear>funny</unclear></u>
<u n="21" who="S0610" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0612">do you guys have Linkedin?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0610">I do but it hasn't been updated for about four years</u>
<u n="24" who="S0428">I do but I never use it</u>
<u n="25" who="S0610">why? but</u>
<u n="26" who="S0612" trans="overlap">cos I forwarded my CV on to this person who was like really high up in HR and she's emailed me back and she was like de la la so your CV's blah erm you just need to you need to do a few things like join up to Linkedin</u>
<u n="27" who="S0610">yeah I think it's really important</u>
<u n="28" who="S0612">but what if I don't have anybody to like I don't know how it works but don't</u>
<u n="29" who="S0610" trans="overlap"><trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="30" who="S0612">you need people to endorse your skills?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0610">yeah and you will find that loads of people that you know are on it and it'll automatically tell you cos it's like links up to Facebook or <trunc>kn</trunc> it just fucking knows it's scary I'll show you if you like on what mine looks like</u>
<u n="32" who="S0428">yeah I need to update mine as well</u>
<u n="33" who="S0610" trans="overlap">cos as soon as I start looking for a job properly a job search er that'll be the first thing I'll update definitely</u>
<u n="34" who="S0612">what? Linkedin?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0610">yeah and especially if you're in HR I bet lots of HR people use it</u>
<u n="36" who="S0612" trans="overlap">oh that's so <trunc>annoyi</trunc> why can't people just like your read CVs nowadays?</u>
<u n="37" who="S0610" trans="overlap">I know but</u>
<u n="38" who="S0428" trans="overlap">erm</u>
<u n="39" who="S0610">it's just a case really of getting whatever's on your CV on there and then getting a a <trunc>prof</trunc>a profile picture of yourself and then really all it is is it'll just automatically say oh do you know this person? link up with them do you know this person? <unclear>and go</unclear> and then so everyone you know you can just link up with and then you might think oh who have I worked with in the past? <trunc>l</trunc><trunc>l</trunc>look them up <trunc>mayb</trunc> you know and they might be on there <pause dur="short"/> it's easier than you think</u>
<u n="40" who="S0428">and actually like I have a really bad profile like I don't even have a picture don't have anything on it and erm I've been headhunted a couple of times through it like</u>
<u n="41" who="S0612">oh wow</u>
<u n="42" who="S0428">yeah people have said oh er erm have you thought about applying for this job?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0610">yeah so that's a really good way of using it</u>
<u n="44" who="S0428">and I I haven't I haven't put myself honestly I've not put myself out there at all so</u>
<u n="45" who="S0612">but cos the girls were talking about it at work and they were like endorse mm the fact that I'm good with customers so people click on something</u>
<u n="46" who="S0610">yeah so there are these skills so it says</u>
<u n="47" who="S0612" trans="overlap">but nobody's gonna like my skills now</u>
<u n="48" who="S0610">yeah they will cos er I even like people who say your friends at work or your er</u>
<u n="49" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh you took my tea away</u>
<u n="50" who="S0610">no</u>
<u n="51" who="S0428">my green tea</u>
<u n="52" who="S0610">no</u>
<u n="53" who="S0428"><unclear>just hiding it from me</unclear></u>
<u n="54" who="S0610">erm</u>
<u n="55" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0612">you took my tea</u>
<u n="57" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="58" who="S0610">erm <pause dur="short"/> if they're on it then they can endorse you you know? and do you have what who's your manager at work? or <trunc>h</trunc> who er do you know someone above you at work?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0612">uhu</u>
<u n="60" who="S0610">would they be on Linkedin?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0612">I dunno</u>
<u n="62" who="S0610">well you might be surprised <pause dur="short"/> or if they are and they've just got a dormant profile maybe you could always just like message them and say hey do you mind just logging in to Linkedin and? <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="63" who="S0612">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0428">the thing is it's quite cringey but then it's the way things are done now</u>
<u n="65" who="S0610">yeah what I don't like is that you just type in <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or whatever on Google and it's like the third thing on there and then people just see everything <trunc>ab</trunc> you know?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah I don't like it at all and also the endorsing skills my dad endorsed me how shit does that look? like <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0612">does it say does it show you who endorses who?</u>
<u n="69" who="S0610">yeah you can click on it</u>
<u n="70" who="S0428"><unclear>but er</unclear></u>
<u n="71" who="S0610" trans="overlap">the worst thing I think is that you can see when someone's seen your profile?</u>
<u n="72" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0610">so like you'll go onto people who you're interested in and they know that you've <trunc>see</trunc> like you've been looking at their profile which I think's a bit weird</u>
<u n="74" who="S0428" trans="overlap">so I never look at anyone</u>
<u n="75" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0428">I never go on it to be honest</u>
<u n="77" who="S0610">erm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0612">it's just annoys me that you have to have Twitter Facebook</u>
<u n="79" who="S0428">but I don't think you do</u>
<u n="80" who="S0612">blah blah blah blah di blah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0428">I just I also think in a <trunc>wa</trunc>in a way like that you can do that and you also can not? like I no like erm <vocal desc="misc"/> when when I started my master's they were like right you'll have a Twitter account in a week and I was like I probably won't because I don't want that and er obviously</u>
<u n="82" who="S0612" trans="overlap"><unclear>right</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0428">there is that whole part of the industry where everyone's like <trunc>ma</trunc> there are loads of jobs that are on there and blah blah blah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0610">yeah it's true</u>
<u n="85" who="S0428" trans="overlap">but also they're not <trunc>j</trunc> they don't just put them on Twitter they put them er other places as well</u>
<u n="86" who="S0612">do you guys have Twitter?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0428">no</u>
<u n="88" who="S0610">I do although I haven't ever used it really and er oh it's embarrassing cos actually that's like the second thing down and there's a shitty picture of like oh anyway but actually a lot of journalists say but maybe it's different for HR cos journalism er you have to have a Twitter account but I don't use it</u>
<u n="89" who="S0428">but then that's what Twitter's was was set up for journalism wasn't it? I guess</u>
<u n="90" who="S0610">but don't worry about that but Linkedin if you're looking for a job first thing you should do I think cos it is like taking your CV</u>
<u n="91" who="S0612" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0610">to just online and that can only be a good thing</u>
<u n="93" who="S0612">yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0610">and once you've set it up and put your CV on there and stuff you don't necessarily have to use it again it's just a good way of maybe of just having <trunc>yours</trunc>yourself out there</u>
<u n="95" who="S0612">yeah</u>
<u n="96" who="S0610">it is scary though when you look up your name and then see like everything you've done in the past is on there and I hate it cos I thought god if I ever if I ever get famous</u>
<u n="97" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0612">well with your articles coming out left right and centre</u>
<u n="99" who="S0428" trans="overlap"><unclear>I'm sure</unclear></u>
<u n="100" who="S0610"><unclear/> no but if you ever became like a reputable journalist or whatever then people will look you up won't they? that's the first thing they might do if they like</u>
<u n="101" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="102" who="S0610">trying to commission you whatever and then you've got like your blog from when you were fucking fifteen on there or like</u>
<u n="103" who="S0612">I think Facebook's difficult for us <trunc>b</trunc> well</u>
<u n="104" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0612">er it depends what you've done but</u>
<u n="106" who="S0610">we've been on it for <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="107" who="S0612" trans="overlap"><trunc>pho</trunc>photos</u>
<u n="108" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0612">back when you're like drunk</u>
<u n="110" who="S0610">eighteen</u>
<u n="111" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yep</u>
<u n="112" who="S0428">and you don't wanna delete them</u>
<u n="113" who="S0610">no</u>
<u n="114" who="S0428">but also you don't want anyone to see them</u>
<u n="115" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">no</u>
<u n="116" who="S0610">no <pause dur="short"/> if you've put on a load of private I er I haven't got I don't even know my privacy controls</u>
<u n="117" who="S0428">oh I had to because when I was teaching</u>
<u n="118" who="S0612">oh</u>
<u n="119" who="S0428">like one like my students would come and be like we saw your Facebook I'd be like that's really spooky</u>
<u n="120" who="S0612" whoConfidence="low">yeah it's not ideal</u>
<u n="121" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0610" whoConfidence="low">did erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> have a good time?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> she did she sent me a message saying thank you so much for inviting me I had a <trunc>l</trunc> such a lovely time and</u>
<u n="124" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh bless her</u>
<u n="125" who="S0428">yeah it must be so hard</u>
<u n="126" who="S0612">ouch</u>
<u n="127" who="S0428">are you alright?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0612">I just cricked my neck oh oh I'm just breaking</u>
<u n="129" who="S0610"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0428">I'm sure she'll settle in though</u>
<u n="131" who="S0610">it's just so</u>
<u n="132" who="S0612" trans="overlap">well it's not long until ah</u>
<u n="133" who="S0428">her brother gets back</u>
<u n="134" who="S0612">mm yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0610">but it's just so lonely</u>
<u n="136" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="137" who="S0610" trans="overlap">remember when it was just me and you in Spain? and we had each other at least</u>
<u n="138" who="S0428">oh thank god <unclear/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0610" trans="overlap">but it was just I had those moments of like pure loneliness and that wasn't even that bad a situation compared to her</u>
<u n="140" who="S0428">no it was and we no that <trunc>tho</trunc>those first like six months well no cos when we when we made friends it was fine but when they all left I remember going back that <trunc>s</trunc> that like in that September</u>
<u n="141" who="S0610">I did as well I felt so lonely</u>
<u n="142" who="S0428" trans="overlap">and feeling so lonely and low and</u>
<u n="143" who="S0610">I just <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0428">yeah it's really hard and it makes it's I like it's really hard to to make a good group of friends who you feel really comfortable with</u>
<u n="145" who="S0610">exactly it takes a long time</u>
<u n="146" who="S0428">and she's</u>
<u n="147" who="S0610" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="148" who="S0428">miles away as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0610">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's mad I've got this erm I've luckily so I know someone at work who does freelance writing and she's invited me to this erm Facebook group called the <anon type="place"/> or something</u>
<u n="150" who="S0428">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> after the?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0610">what is it after?</u>
<u n="152" who="S0428">you know the book the number one detective agency?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0610">oh that's it and erm it's really good cos there's all journalists on there and some people are like er <pause dur="short"/> and like loads of like call-outs like does anyone wanna do this? does anybody wanna do this? does anyone know about erm does anyone know what it's like to go through menopause? I <trunc>wan</trunc> I'm <trunc>wri</trunc>I'm writing I'm writing an article about it does anyone wanna do this? it's really good</u>
<u n="154" who="S0428">oh <pause dur="short"/> just fame when it comes comes fast</u>
<u n="155" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0612"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0610">erm</u>
<u n="158" who="S0612"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0610">I'm on the hunt for a volunteer whose brows are in need of a bit of a boost to try a nano-needle eyebrow treatment so they're obviously gonna write up about it weird <pause dur="short"/> anyway</u>
<u n="160" who="S0612">have I got a <unclear>hair bobble</unclear>? yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0428">I've enjoyed this green tea</u>
<u n="162" who="S0610">it's caffeinated isn't it?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0428">mm they're all from the same plant like green tea red tea white tea</u>
<u n="164" who="S0612">are they?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0612">white tea is supposed to be really good for you</u>
<u n="167" who="S0610">but then is camomile and all that stuff just other herbs and stuff? that</u>
<u n="168" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0610">isn't the same? oh</u>
<u n="170" who="S0612">why is green tea good for you?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0610">I don't really know</u>
<u n="172" who="S0428">good for your bones no I've no idea</u>
<u n="173" who="S0612">good for your bone?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0428">no I don't think it is that's just completely made up</u>
<u n="175" who="S0612"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh</u>
<u n="176" who="S0428">I don't know but my grandad always says oh green tea's really good for you I think for your digestion</u>
<u n="177" who="S0612">mm</u>
<u n="178" who="S0428">maybe that's other tea I have no idea</u>
<u n="179" who="S0612">peppermint tea's good for tummies <pause dur="short"/> I know that</u>
<u n="180" who="S0610">it is yeah you're right <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0428">I don't really like white tea</u>
<u n="182" who="S0612">don't think I've had it</u>
<u n="183" who="S0610">I don't mind it <pause dur="short"/> you know?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0428">kind of just like normal</u>
<u n="185" who="S0612">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="186" who="S0610">it is quieter in here the trains don't you think?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0428">what? than in your room?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0612">yeah</u>
<u n="190" who="S0428">have you got double glazing?</u>
<u n="191" who="S0610">no not right here</u>
<u n="192" who="S0428">that'll be it in Finland they have triple glazing it's mental</u>
<u n="193" who="S0612">it's cos it gets so fucking cold</u>
<u n="194" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="195" who="S0610">yeah and I guess they need the</u>
<u n="196" who="S0428" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said minus thirty</u>
<u n="197" who="S0612">oh I've been well I've been to we went to Helsinki and it wasn't <pause dur="short"/> I don't think I'd go back</u>
<u n="198" who="S0610">er I mm yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0428">that's what I I feel like when I went cos I went to visit my brother when he was living there</u>
<u n="200" who="S0610" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0428">and erm yeah it was just a bit like it was really nice it was so cold</u>
<u n="202" who="S0612">yeah and expensive</u>
<u n="203" who="S0428"><trunc>expensi</trunc></u>
<u n="204" who="S0612" trans="overlap">it's rare that you go somewhere that's more expensive than England</u>
<u n="205" who="S0610">mm yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0428">yeah and not that like compared to Norway I if I was to go back I know Finland's not Scandinavia but I just I'd go to Sweden or Norway cos I think they're</u>
<u n="207" who="S0612">I've never been to either of those but er <trunc>Finl</trunc> I just felt it was so</u>
<u n="208" who="S0610">it was just the big big buildings it felt like you were in Russia</u>
<u n="209" who="S0612">Baltic and</u>
<u n="210" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0612">cold and</u>
<u n="212" who="S0428">and the countryside</u>
<u n="213" who="S0610" trans="overlap">I was so cold wasn't it? <vocal desc="laugh"/> and it was May</u>
<u n="214" who="S0428" trans="overlap">it was so cold</u>
<u n="215" who="S0610">it was May</u>
<u n="216" who="S0612">was it May?</u>
<u n="217" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0428">I remember I got on a flight from Spain from Barcelona to this town called Turku and I was like I just didn't have any suitable clothes cos I was living in Spain <trunc>s</trunc> but I took like my warmest jacket or what I thought was warm</u>
<u n="219" who="S0612">oh</u>
<u n="220" who="S0428">landed and I just wanted to cry</u>
<u n="221" who="S0612">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0428" trans="overlap">it was so cold</u>
<u n="223" who="S0610">I dunno how people live there it's just the darkness I think I don't know who will cope with the darkness</u>
<u n="224" who="S0428" trans="overlap">no <unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="225" who="S0610">I mean it's bad enough here when the in the winter but</u>
<u n="226" who="S0612">oh it'll start er getting lighter now</u>
<u n="227" who="S0428">yeah we're over the hump</u>
<u n="228" who="S0612">yay hump day Wednesday hump day</u>
<u n="229" who="S0428">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0610">what is?</u>
<u n="231" who="S0428">I love the sound of Finnish though it sounds so <unclear>happy</unclear> what does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do out there?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0610">he's a chemical engineer isn't he?</u>
<u n="233" who="S0612"><unclear>well he's in</unclear> mining</u>
<u n="234" who="S0610">yeah cos he's mining <pause dur="short"/> and he erm goes to South America and stuff and mines</u>
<u n="235" who="S0428">is that how he met?</u>
<u n="236" who="S0610">yeah that's how he met mm what's her name? <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="237" who="S0612" trans="overlap">is she pretty? we were saying yesterday though I think it's gonna be such a massive culture shock for her</u>
<u n="238" who="S0428">like she <unclear/></u>
<u n="239" who="S0612" trans="overlap">to go from living from South America where it's very</u>
<u n="240" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="241" who="S0612" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/> and like</u>
<u n="242" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0612" trans="overlap">warm and</u>
<u n="244" who="S0610">and they're in their summer now as well</u>
<u n="245" who="S0612">happy and de de to kind of</u>
<u n="246" who="S0610">Finland</u>
<u n="247" who="S0428" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">cold</u>
<u n="248" who="S0610">well she was saying she's visited <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a few times there and she's like well the Finnish are really just like they have they it's just really hard cos er I've noticed they just like er they're not very friendly or they put well they if they are they put up a front you know like it's not like</u>
<u n="249" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah you have</u>
<u n="250" who="S0610" trans="overlap">Peru where you</u>
<u n="251" who="S0428">you have to get to know them and <unclear>then</unclear> they're really friendly but like</u>
<u n="252" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah of course but I guess</u>
<u n="253" who="S0612">isn't that funny how like nationalities have different kind of like?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0610" trans="overlap">it yeah</u>
<u n="255" who="S0612">it's like it makes me laugh when erm Family Guy in erm they I mean there you can't really base anything on Family Guy cos it's quite awful really but when they do stereotypical <trunc>c</trunc> nationalities and when they do the British we've all got horrible teeth and</u>
<u n="256" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0612">and really like oh talk like this which nobody does <unclear>er hardly any more</unclear></u>
<u n="259" who="S0610" trans="overlap"><unclear>I know</unclear> it's bad that we have the bad teeth reputation</u>
<u n="260" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0612">I don't know why we have that</u>
<u n="262" who="S0610">well in comparison to the States we do</u>
<u n="263" who="S0612">yeah but</u>
<u n="264" who="S0428">yeah but they're probably all plastic</u>
<u n="265" who="S0612">they're all fake</u>
<u n="266" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0612">they're not all fake but</u>
<u n="268" who="S0610" trans="overlap">well they they're nice and <trunc>whi</trunc>white but they do have white and straight teeth</u>
<u n="269" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0610">whereas</u>
<u n="271" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I hate teeth</u>
<u n="272" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="273" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I hate my teeth <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0428" whoConfidence="low">I love your teeth</u>
<u n="275" who="S0612"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh I'm filming something</u>
<u n="276" who="S0610">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> do you remember the <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> guys?</u>
<u n="277" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="278" who="S0612">how could we <trunc>for</trunc></u>
<u n="279" who="S0610" trans="overlap">he had a baby</u>
<u n="280" who="S0612">really?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0428" trans="overlap">has he?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0612" trans="overlap">oh my god everyone's having babies</u>
<u n="283" who="S0428" trans="overlap">where's he living?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0610">and my ex-boyfriend <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had a baby <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="285" who="S0612">what?</u>
<u n="286" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I think you told me he was pregnant well not him</u>
<u n="287" who="S0610" trans="overlap">no I didn't know</u>
<u n="288" who="S0612" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0428">I thought</u>
<u n="290" who="S0612">that's weird</u>
<u n="291" who="S0610">but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> probably told you so yeah it'll be</u>
<u n="292" who="S0428" trans="overlap">maybe</u>
<u n="293" who="S0612">oh</u>
<u n="294" who="S0610">cos I was gonna go to <trunc>Amster</trunc> or whatever I dunno we or maybe we just messaged on each other's birthdays</u>
<u n="295" who="S0428">is he living in Amsterdam?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0610">yeah he's been living there for a few years and he met his French girlfriend there so he must be about thirty-eight now I guess or thirty yeah <trunc>thir</trunc> late thirties and erm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0428">you were in love with him</u>
<u n="298" who="S0610">I liked him so much but then I realised it was just an illusion anyway erm yeah and like er and he was just like yeah I'm having a little kid blah blah blah and then I saw on Facebook</u>
<u n="299" who="S0612" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0610">it was like our little <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and it's <trunc>c</trunc> yeah so it's like a really French name</u>
<u n="301" who="S0612"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0610"><anon type="name" nameType="n"/> and they live in Amsterdam and it's so nice</u>
<u n="303" who="S0428" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0610">and they bought a house together and</u>
<u n="305" who="S0428">wow</u>
<u n="306" who="S0610">and then</u>
<u n="307" who="S0428" trans="overlap">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is it with the same girl?</u>
<u n="308" who="S0610">yeah with this girl he's been with for a couple of <trunc>yea</trunc> four years I think and I was out on Christmas Eve and I was like usually the it's <trunc>l</trunc> my usually the boys come out not many of the girls come out any more and I was like so where's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> then? they're like oh he's had a kid <unclear>I was like</unclear></u>
<u n="309" who="S0612"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0610">what? they're like yeah it was a surprise earlier this year and then erm yeah born about a month ago little <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I was like fuck <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="311" who="S0612">what?</u>
<u n="312" who="S0610">usually you find out about this stuff on Facebook</u>
<u n="313" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0610">but he doesn't really use it and erm yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0428">oh so you don't ever see him?</u>
<u n="316" who="S0610">no and then I <trunc>messa</trunc> er I it was nice cos I text him it's just mad how like I was like how does that even happen?</u>
<u n="317" who="S0428">yeah <trunc>s</trunc>sad isn't it?</u>
<u n="318" who="S0610">yeah but I did text him and I just said</u>
<u n="319" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0610">like congratulations and whatever and he text back and he was just like he was really nice so I think a lot of people I know someone at work as well like <trunc>l</trunc> people for the first time people I know are having children</u>
<u n="321" who="S0428" trans="overlap">are having babies</u>
<u n="322" who="S0610">and they're all they've all given birth like er the end of <trunc>Ja</trunc> December beginning of January it's really weird</u>
<u n="323" who="S0428">what happened nine months ago?</u>
<u n="324" who="S0610">what happened nine months ago exactly March spring ain't it?</u>
<u n="325" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0428">uprisings</u>
<u n="327" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0612">now</u>
<u n="329" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm?</u>
<u n="330" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">can I ah I need to sit up can I be a pain? erm can you go and grab that towel</u>
<u n="331" who="S0610">oh yeah of course</u>
<u n="332" who="S0612">for me? cos I might have a shower whilst it's quiet</u>
<u n="333" who="S0610">which colour is it?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0612">blue</u>
<u n="335" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0610">is it in my room?</u>
<u n="337" who="S0612">mm I'd go but obviously <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like</u>
<u n="338" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0612">naked on <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="340" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> standing by the window</u>
<u n="341" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="342" who="S0610"><unclear/></u>
<u n="343" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0428" whoConfidence="low">he's standing by the window</u>
<u n="345" who="S0612">ah</u>
<u n="346" who="S0610">what? with his leg up <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0612">okay that's really painful why am I so <unclear>retard lame</unclear>? okay they're both not good words to use erm</u>
<u n="348" who="S0428">but but you've oh sweet</u>
<u n="349" who="S0612"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> oh oh <pause dur="short"/> I might go erm if I put it under a hot shower</u>
<u n="350" who="S0428">it'll be fine</u>
<u n="351" who="S0612">will that? no I can't really turn my I can do that oh <vocal desc="misc"/> I'm just breaking ah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0428" trans="overlap">how are you getting home? coach?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0612">yeah so it's great cos the train is what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I have usually done when we've I've er I've er come up and she's come down and that's gone up to like sixty quid return thank you so much</u>
<u n="354" who="S0610">what's that for?</u>
<u n="355" who="S0612">it's the train</u>
<u n="356" who="S0610">oh yeah</u>
<u n="357" who="S0612">but now the <anon type="place"/> coach it's like this <anon type="place"/> service and erm er from the village that we've moved to erm erm it goes through it on the way</u>
<u n="358" who="S0610">oh wow</u>
<u n="359" who="S0612">so I literally walk to the bus stop</u>
<u n="360" who="S0610">that's so good</u>
<u n="361" who="S0612">and then I was in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0610">that's so good</u>
<u n="363" who="S0612" trans="overlap">like of all the places that</u>
<u n="364" who="S0610" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <unclear>amazing</unclear> I'm totally doing that next time</u>
<u n="365" who="S0612">yeah it's <trunc>th</trunc> and it's thirty pound return</u>
<u n="366" who="S0428" whoConfidence="low">that's so good</u>
<u n="367" who="S0612">so it's erm and all it's just as <trunc>effi</trunc> the only thing is is there's only two services in the morning but you can get you can either go at eight say eight thirty and then that's normally busy with like the day trippers cos they get here early do the day trip go back erm and there's only two at night so like four and then eight</u>
<u n="368" who="S0428">do you have to book on a special one?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0612">yeah yeah yeah you er you all book before</u>
<u n="370" who="S0610" trans="overlap"><unclear/> you have to book <unclear/> with National Express it's National Express I imagine is it?</u>
<u n="371" who="S0612">no it's erm <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="373" who="S0612">it's a West <anon type="place"/> company</u>
<u n="374" who="S0610">oh right oh that's why I've never okay by the way all my <trunc>s</trunc>shower stuff is on the on the left side of the bath as in like nearest the sink and</u>
<u n="375" who="S0612">yeah thank you</u>
<u n="376" who="S0610">you've put a right crick in your neck haven't you?</u>
<u n="377" who="S0428">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="378" who="S0612">yeah I can't look that way <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="379" who="S0610"><unclear/> do you need a massage? <unclear/></u>
<u n="380" who="S0612">no that's very kind</u>
<u n="381" who="S0610">are you sure?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0612" trans="overlap">I will be fine I need to man up really essentially</u>
<u n="383" who="S0610">it's a bit weird</u>
<u n="384" who="S0428">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0610">mm I'm tired</u>
<u n="386" who="S0612">when does <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> go to <trunc>f</trunc> erm New Zealand?</u>
<u n="387" who="S0610">I think February isn't it?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0428">is that their honeymoon?</u>
<u n="389" who="S0612">yeah</u>
<u n="390" who="S0610" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="391" who="S0428">oh how long are they going for?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0612">a month I think</u>
<u n="393" who="S0610" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sigh"/> oh</u>
<u n="394" who="S0428">how nice</u>
<u n="395" who="S0612">oh I'm hoping to go to New Zealand this year</u>
<u n="396" who="S0428">oh what a beautiful place</u>
<u n="397" who="S0612">it's like my big thing before <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I even consider having children <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="398" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="399" who="S0610">yeah you're gonna have to at least but you don't have to worry for a while <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0428">does he want children now?</u>
<u n="401" who="S0612">no no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's like he's thirty-five so he should be of an age where he might consider them but he's like trapped in a young like this young mind</u>
<u n="402" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="403" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">of wanting to race cars that's all he wants to do so he's <trunc>f</trunc> sold his house on Wednesday and er he's already bought a brand new race car pretty much how to build a brand new race car he's probably spent like ten grand and it's just it's dead money because he doesn't you don't win anything apart from a trophy</u>
<u n="404" who="S0610"><unclear>I guess</unclear> he just loves it</u>
<u n="405" who="S0428" whoConfidence="low">and the glory</u>
<u n="406" who="S0610">and the glory <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0612">yeah I know</u>
<u n="408" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0612">but hey-ho he wants to do</u>
<u n="410" who="S0610">at least he's got a passion I need er something as a hobby probably not an expensive one like that though <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0428">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> just imagine if</u>
<u n="412" who="S0612">I'd love it if you did</u>
<u n="413" who="S0428">next time we come you're in <vocal desc="laugh"/> you come in your motorcar <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0612">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="415" who="S0610">got a new hobby guys</u>
<u n="416" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0610">I've used up all my savings</u>
<u n="418" who="S0428">you've got like your erm <vocal desc="laugh"/> glasses on and like a</u>
<u n="419" who="S0612"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="420" who="S0428">I can so see that would go with your personality as well</u>
<u n="421" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0428">that's just <unclear/></u>
<u n="423" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="424" who="S0612">bright orange</u>
<u n="425" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0612" trans="overlap">race race car</u>
<u n="427" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="428" who="S0612">right I'm gonna go and is it hot water or cold water that's good for your muscles?</u>
<u n="429" who="S0610">cold apparently</u>
<u n="430" who="S0428">maybe a bit of both? like go from hot <trunc>an</trunc> to cold</u>
<u n="431" who="S0612">well it's like that thing I was trying <unclear/></u>
<u n="432" who="S0428" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0612">but I kind of forgot oh weather update showers today</u>
<u n="434" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="435" who="S0612">I don't <unclear>even want</unclear> I don't need that</u>
<u n="436" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="437" who="S0612">I need to go looking for ah <vocal desc="laugh"/> just <unclear>clicked</unclear></u>
<u n="438" who="S0610">er <trunc>y</trunc> if you want a massage after let me know even just a little squeeze</u>
<u n="439" who="S0612">maybe it's from games night <unclear/></u>
<u n="440" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="441" who="S0612">I'll come back <unclear/> I'll be yeah okay I can't walk I'm like this</u>
<u n="442" who="S0610">I know</u>
<u n="443" who="S0612"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0610"><unclear>it's great</unclear></u>
<u n="445" who="S0428">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> shut the door</u>
<u n="446" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="447" who="S0610">oh mm</u>
<u n="448" who="S0428">you alright?</u>
<u n="449" who="S0610">sleepy <unclear>I must not've slept very well</unclear></u>
<u n="450" who="S0428">I slept better last night than</u>
<u n="451" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="452" who="S0428" trans="overlap">the night before</u>
<u n="453" who="S0610">it is cooler in here like like I think it was really hot last night</u>
<u n="454" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> with the extreme weather <unclear>bob</unclear></u>
<u n="455" who="S0610"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm god imagine <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> with a kid</u>
<u n="456" who="S0428">everyone's growing up <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="457" who="S0610">it's so scary</u>
<u n="458" who="S0428">what shall we do?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0610">er not do that</u>
<u n="460" who="S0428">just run away?</u>
<u n="461" who="S0610">yeah <pause dur="short"/> at least <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't want a kid so</u>
<u n="462" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="463" who="S0610">that's good</u>
<u n="464" who="S0428">it's freaky though isn't it? like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="465" who="S0610">I still think thank god compared to the last generation twenty-eight is still</u>
<u n="466" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="467" who="S0610">pretty young like er the very vast <trunc>m</trunc> the minority of friends have had kids and like that's just <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> at our age and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> whereas er you know like <pause dur="short"/> yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s like thirty-eight or whatever but</u>
<u n="468" who="S0428">yeah no I do I think it is but it's still like</u>
<u n="469" who="S0610">but it's still like really scary <pause dur="long"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> cos it's gonna be at least I mean I can't even envisage it er in five years <trunc>li</trunc> er let alone <trunc>li</trunc>like seven I I just <vocal desc="sigh"/> I mean life changes I guess but I just can't even imagine wanting I do want one but being ready for one</u>
<u n="470" who="S0428">yeah it's a really</u>
<u n="471" who="S0610">I've got so much life to live yet</u>
<u n="472" who="S0428">I know you can live a life when you have a baby</u>
<u n="473" who="S0610">yeah but I mean like</u>
<u n="474" who="S0428" trans="overlap">well I dunno I've not had one so <vocal desc="laugh"/> talking rubbish</u>
<u n="475" who="S0610">but you can't just like make off and do what you want can you?</u>
<u n="476" who="S0428">no I think though there are definitely like people who make it completely their world and people who have a child and a life</u>
<u n="477" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="478" who="S0428" trans="overlap">well I'm not saying like put the child in nursery like I'd hate that like</u>
<u n="479" who="S0610">that's the thing though</u>
<u n="480" who="S0428" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="481" who="S0610">the pressures</u>
<u n="482" who="S0428"><vocal desc="sigh"/> it's pressure to make sure that you're <trunc>growi</trunc> you're making something lovely as well</u>
<u n="483" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="484" who="S0428">like this whole life is in your hands</u>
<u n="485" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="486" who="S0428">I couldn't <trunc>d</trunc>I couldn't do it</u>
<u n="487" who="S0610">but like the <trunc>press</trunc> yeah and like the the worry all the <trunc>ti</trunc> I just I think I'd be such a worried mum <pause dur="short"/> I'd be constantly worrying about them</u>
<u n="488" who="S0428">but maybe like maybe you wouldn't like you know erm like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? she was just so unmotherly and like</u>
<u n="489" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="490" who="S0428">and she had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and now she's just like the best mum in the world she's so good with him</u>
<u n="491" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="492" who="S0428">and er I guess you just learn like you have to</u>
<u n="493" who="S0610">I guess you surprise yourself</u>
<u n="494" who="S0428">I think</u>
<u n="495" who="S0610" trans="overlap">you either are good or not yeah</u>
<u n="496" who="S0428">and maybe like you wouldn't worry so much yourself cos you're more like concerned about like making sure they've got a good life and <pause dur="short"/> I dunno it's a <trunc>rea</trunc> it's a really weird one I can't imagine a day that like we meet up and we've both got a child</u>
<u n="497" who="S0610">yeah I <unclear>fear</unclear> that it probably won't ever happen and that's a fear it's a fear I'm as scared of that as erm it actually happening you know? like <trunc>bo</trunc> er I just</u>
<u n="498" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="499" who="S0610">the other day we started talking about what I'm dreading is cos I'm so bored of wedding chat I'm just dreading the moment when</u>
<u n="500" who="S0428">you <unclear/> chat</u>
<u n="501" who="S0610" trans="overlap">I'm certainly I'm certainly a big step behind a majority not all thank god but a majority of friends mainly like</u>
<u n="502" who="S0428">but do you think you'll ever be like them?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0610"><vocal desc="misc"/> I mean not as a <trunc>m</trunc> wedding stuff but</u>
<u n="504" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I would absolutely love it if we got married</u>
<u n="505" who="S0610">and I think</u>
<u n="506" who="S0428" trans="overlap">and we just turned into like absolute <unclear/></u>
<u n="507" who="S0610" trans="overlap">that's all we talked about</u>
<u n="508" who="S0428" trans="overlap">after all after all the chat</u>
<u n="509" who="S0610" trans="overlap">all that chat</u>
<u n="510" who="S0428">that we were like <vocal desc="laugh"/> it wouldn't surprise me of us either it's a kind of</u>
<u n="511" who="S0610" trans="overlap">it wouldn't surprise me cos we're knobs</u>
<u n="512" who="S0428">yeah it's the kind of thing we do</u>
<u n="513" who="S0610">but erm <pause dur="short"/> erm but because there's such such a big step behind anybody else that's already boring me to tears so when it starts baby chat as well it's just gonna be like I can't relate to anything you ever say to me</u>
<u n="514" who="S0428">but then like for example with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's got two babies and I don't find her chat ever boring like she doesn't do that she's just got these two things</u>
<u n="515" who="S0610" trans="overlap">no but but what's worse is er that's fine but it's when everyone's er you know like</u>
<u n="516" who="S0428">together?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0610">when er people are together and they've all experienced something and then this is like like everyone talking about oh yeah well for my wedding for my wedding for my wedding</u>
<u n="518" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh god but</u>
<u n="519" who="S0610">honestly and I've had been in situations like that not that often often</u>
<u n="520" who="S0428" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="521" who="S0610">with like the uni girls</u>
<u n="522" who="S0428">that's the hard thing and you <trunc>kn</trunc> and you you don't wanna like <vocal desc="misc"/> take yourself away from them and like be like that person that's all aloof but then</u>
<u n="523" who="S0610">but er sometimes it's just boring as fuck</u>
<u n="524" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0610">cos you can't simply you just can't relate you know? but then I'm like am I just being like really cynical? but it's not that I just cannot relate to what they're saying</u>
<u n="526" who="S0428">no I couldn't really couldn't</u>
<u n="527" who="S0610">but anyway maybe it'll be different with babies I mean I think I'm getting more into babies</u>
<u n="528" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="529" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">not like having them myself but like I'm beginning to understand why people have them but <pause dur="short"/> jesus can't even conceive of it</u>
<u n="530" who="S0428">no I mean I love children and I can't even imagine it</u>
<u n="531" who="S0610"><vocal desc="sigh"/> I think the twenties was supposed to be difficult decade the thirties is gonna be fucking difficult</u>
<u n="532" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> at least we'll know who we are by then</u>
<u n="533" who="S0610"><vocal desc="laugh"/> will we?</u>
<u n="534" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0428"><unclear/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0610">mm <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="537" who="S0428">oh mate we should go on holiday</u>
<u n="538" who="S0610">yeah we should <unclear/></u>
<u n="539" who="S0428">yeah no but like</u>
<u n="540" who="S0610" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0428" trans="overlap">do you know what I mean? like I'd like to just go on holiday with you and like <trunc>d</trunc> not invite anyone else <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="542" who="S0610">I know and just go and chat shit with people</u>
<u n="543" who="S0428">and not yeah cos I like Ibiza was lovely but</u>
<u n="544" who="S0610" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="545" who="S0428">we it it wasn't the same</u>
<u n="546" who="S0610">no it wasn't</u>
<u n="547" who="S0428">have you got anywhere that you'd love to like <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="548" who="S0610" trans="overlap">god yeah so many but obviously this travelling thing</u>
<u n="549" who="S0428">mate are you going round Europe? or?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0610">yeah I <trunc>h</trunc> thing is mate I'm not very adventurous I've realised because</u>
<u n="551" who="S0428"><unclear/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0610">I'm too scared to go outside of Europe</u>
<u n="553" who="S0428">I just love Europe as well</u>
<u n="554" who="S0610">I do love Europe and er and I <unclear/></u>
<u n="555" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I'm such a knob</u>
<u n="556" who="S0610">should I not be like going anywhere else?</u>
<u n="557" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="558" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">there's a big world out there</u>
<u n="559" who="S0428">I know</u>
<u n="560" who="S0610">Europe's tiny</u>
<u n="561" who="S0428">but it's so amazing</u>
<u n="562" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0428" trans="overlap">like I just love it so much I'd like to go to South America but</u>
<u n="564" who="S0610">it's weird <unclear/></u>
<u n="565" who="S0428">because maybe on your travels we could meet up for a week</u>
<u n="566" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah for sure cos I imagine <pause dur="short"/> yeah absolutely a hundred percent just need to <trunc>fi</trunc>figure myself out that's why I'm not making any plans this year where would you like to go?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0428">erm I really want to go to the Azores islands</u>
<u n="568" who="S0610">oh yeah we were talking about that weren't we?</u>
<u n="569" who="S0428">yeah I have a thing about islands I love em erm and I'd like to go to like Croatia Albania down there</u>
<u n="570" who="S0610" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="571" who="S0428">I've never been there <unclear/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0610" trans="overlap">er that's probably the area I might be going to</u>
<u n="573" who="S0428">yeah and I'd love just I'd love to go to erm France as well cos I <trunc>ha</trunc></u>
<u n="574" who="S0610" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="575" who="S0428">it's just I had such a good time this summer in Montpellier</u>
<u n="576" who="S0610">oh yeah</u>
<u n="577" who="S0428">such a good time and cos my problem is I love Spain so much that it's like my default go-to place</u>
<u n="578" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0428">I I don't even particularly feel abroad there I love I love speaking Spanish like it it just <unclear/></u>
<u n="580" who="S0610" trans="overlap">but it's not a holiday necessarily?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0428">but I just er I love it equally so it's always it's always a difficult one cos it's always a draw</u>
<u n="582" who="S0610">erm I get but like</u>
<u n="583" who="S0428">Albania</u>
<u n="584" who="S0610">yeah that <trunc>w</trunc>that way</u>
<u n="585" who="S0428">we could go and see <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="586" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="587" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="588" who="S0610">cos in my mind what I'd like to do but this is just what I've I'd like to start in Italy cos I've seen a few Workaways that I like there and I really wanna go to the Dolomites and around the Verona that like top top top</u>
<u n="589" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="590" who="S0610">right corner</u>
<u n="591" who="S0428">yeah it's amazing</u>
<u n="592" who="S0610">so I'd like to go around there <unclear>so like okay</unclear> maybe I should start there and then go <trunc>d</trunc> across and then down into Croatia and then across to like Hungary Romania and then into Turkey or go</u>
<u n="593" who="S0428">up</u>
<u n="594" who="S0610">Austria Czech <trunc>Repu</trunc> you know that way</u>
<u n="595" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="596" who="S0610">but then always go down to Turkey</u>
<u n="597" who="S0428">you wanna go to Turkey? yeah <trunc>y</trunc> speak to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="598" who="S0610">I well I went <trunc>t</trunc> well anyway obviously I only went to Istanbul and then south erm southern but I loved it</u>
<u n="599" who="S0428">yeah it's amazing isn't it?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0610">people keep telling I don't think you should go there at this time</u>
<u n="601" who="S0428">I think also erm it's worth going to like northern Cyprus and</u>
<u n="602" who="S0610">oh yeah</u>
<u n="603" who="S0428" trans="overlap">like not obviously Faliraki in Cyprus but other parts of Cyprus are incredible like</u>
<u n="604" who="S0610">Ayia Napa you mean?</u>
<u n="605" who="S0428">yeah where's Faliraki?</u>
<u n="606" who="S0610">I think it's Rhodes</u>
<u n="607" who="S0428">oh</u>
<u n="608" who="S0610">well anyway</u>
<u n="609" who="S0428">haven't been to any of them but anyway oh did I show you my erm my grandad wrote this article and it's like The Road to Ayia Napa and it's like the donkeys on the road</u>
<u n="610" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="611" who="S0428" trans="overlap">to Ayia Napa and it's and my grandma's drawn a picture of like nothing so when they were there there was nothing in Ayia Napa</u>
<u n="612" who="S0610">wow</u>
<u n="613" who="S0428">and yeah he's written all these like the dusty track to Ayia Napa</u>
<u n="614" who="S0610">and now it's erm a superhighway well it's not but</u>
<u n="615" who="S0428">yeah erm</u>
<u n="616" who="S0610">it's fucking <unclear>rank man</unclear></u>
<u n="617" who="S0428">I'd like to go to Sicily as well</u>
<u n="618" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="619" who="S0428">a bit more</u>
<u n="620" who="S0610">oh I love Sicily yeah</u>
<u n="621" who="S0428">and erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah and all that yeah just all of those er Amsterdam I'd love to go to I've never been</u>
<u n="622" who="S0610">mm yeah Amsterdam is way up there maybe we should go to Amsterdam</u>
<u n="623" who="S0428">have you been?</u>
<u n="624" who="S0610">no</u>
<u n="625" who="S0428">I just don't wanna go on the plane no one gets it I wanna go there like on the boat or</u>
<u n="626" who="S0610" trans="overlap">on land</u>
<u n="627" who="S0428">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh mate I've got so scared of flying</u>
<u n="628" who="S0610">oh have you?</u>
<u n="629" who="S0428">yeah like and oh when</u>
<u n="630" who="S0610" trans="overlap">why?</u>
<u n="631" who="S0428"><vocal desc="sigh"/> I don't know like <vocal desc="sigh"/> so honestly in in Berlin actually Berlin Italy and Ireland I freaked out on all those planes</u>
<u n="632" who="S0610">what made you freak out? turbulence?</u>
<u n="633" who="S0428">well the Irish one we landed in like Storm Frank so it was like <vocal desc="misc"/> and it was like really bumpy so that's why I was freaking out erm the Berlin flight we landed and he</u>
<u n="634" who="S0610" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="635" who="S0428">put the brakes on and we skidded across the runway like <trunc>n</trunc> the plane nearly left the runway and it was like you know normally you're like you land and you're like phew?</u>
<u n="636" who="S0610">yeah yeah yeah <unclear>awesome</unclear></u>
<u n="637" who="S0428" trans="overlap">and then there was like <vocal desc="misc"/> it was just the worse it was so awful</u>
<u n="638" who="S0610">oh god</u>
<u n="639" who="S0428">and then erm <unclear>it's just Italy just</unclear> <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="640" who="S0610">you need to nip this in the bud</u>
<u n="641" who="S0428">I know no I know and I I</u>
<u n="642" who="S0610" trans="overlap">I don't know how though but</u>
<u n="643" who="S0428">I've erm been on loads of flights so I can't you know it's really horrible like when you feel you're getting a fear</u>
<u n="644" who="S0610">I know</u>
<u n="645" who="S0428" trans="overlap">but you can't stop it so erm I also like I I was in a tower in Verona and I started to feel a bit like weird about heights and I've never felt weird about heights</u>
<u n="646" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="647" who="S0428">and I was like <vocal desc="sigh"/> don't I don't want this to be a thing</u>
<u n="648" who="S0610">no</u>
<u n="649" who="S0428">I don't want this fear but you can feel <trunc>yoursel</trunc> it's really strange</u>
<u n="650" who="S0610">it's funny how you develop them as well well with flying</u>
<u n="651" who="S0428">yeah what are you tricks?</u>
<u n="652" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="653" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="654" who="S0610">I don't have any I'm shit at it <pause dur="short"/> what is the <trunc>w</trunc> I mean I guess the more you fly the better it'll be but</u>
<u n="655" who="S0428">I'm not sure I've done like ten flights in the last month so but I dunno</u>
<u n="656" who="S0610">you need a couple of smooth flights and it might make you feel better again</u>
<u n="657" who="S0428">got to say we we to Italy er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I flew British Airways and we landed and I didn't even feel the plane touch the runway so you know</u>
<u n="658" who="S0610" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="659" who="S0428">you know like Ryanair it was like <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="660" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="661" who="S0428">it is like that is a really big difference</u>
<u n="662" who="S0610">wow really?</u>
<u n="663" who="S0428">yeah I cos I was freaking out and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like we've landed <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="664" who="S0610">wow that says something doesn't it?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0428"><unclear>yeah</unclear> and I was like oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="666" who="S0610">well we shouldn't sit together on this next Ryanair flight should we?</u>
<u n="667" who="S0428">but I always think that when you're with someone who's scared like I was quite good do you remember when we went when we last flew? and like and you were like <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="668" who="S0610">I was</u>
<u n="669" who="S0428" trans="overlap">and I was just chatting to you and I wasn't scared because like I knew you were more scared</u>
<u n="670" who="S0610">but is it cos you just weren't scared?</u>
<u n="671" who="S0428">no I was I've been scared for about a year and a half two years</u>
<u n="672" who="S0610" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="673" who="S0428">or longer but and it's just getting <unclear>worse</unclear></u>
<u n="674" who="S0610" trans="overlap">I dunno if we just wind each other up are you a scared flyer? you're a</u>
<u n="675" who="S0612" trans="overlap">erm mm no</u>
<u n="676" who="S0610" trans="overlap">you're okay</u>
<u n="677" who="S0612">well that's only cos I've had as I <trunc>s</trunc>as I said you need to speak to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="678" who="S0610">yeah he's so chilled</u>
<u n="679" who="S0428">is he in the RAF?</u>
<u n="680" who="S0612">er navy but he flies</u>
<u n="681" who="S0428" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="682" who="S0612">helicopters so</u>
<u n="683" who="S0428" trans="overlap">does he?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0612">yeah erm so when we were coming back from the Maldives we had quite bad turbulence and that was at the stage when they thought that turbulence had brought the Malaysian airplane down and like</u>
<u n="685" who="S0610">and who? who brought the Malaysian airplane?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0612">before they found out that it was erm actually er a technical error that the staff just switched off</u>
<u n="687" who="S0610">oh is that really what the thing is now?</u>
<u n="688" who="S0612" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="689" who="S0610">in the flight</u>
<u n="690" who="S0612">yeah they <trunc>fou</trunc> they've they've they've they've gave erm an investigation so there was something wrong with it but the staff kept resetting the system so</u>
<u n="691" who="S0610">oh my god</u>
<u n="692" who="S0428" trans="overlap">what the the one that landed?</u>
<u n="693" who="S0612">the one that went missing</u>
<u n="694" who="S0610"><unclear>the other one</unclear></u>
<u n="695" who="S0428">how do they know that?</u>
<u n="696" who="S0610">how do they know that?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0612">from the er but I dunno but they published it so</u>
<u n="698" who="S0428" whoConfidence="low">I didn't know that</u>
<u n="699" who="S0610" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">maybe it's just a theory</u>
<u n="700" who="S0612"><trunc>s</trunc> but so we were flying back but cos they only released that I think just before Christmas or over Christmas how it went down or <trunc>w</trunc>why it went down and I asked <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I was like is there any any circumstances a turbulence can bring a plane down? and he was like no <pause dur="short"/> pretty much there isn't no planes are designed to cope with it so yeah you might get it really bad but turbulence can't take a plane out of the sky</u>
<u n="701" who="S0610"><trunc>i</trunc>it always feels so weird</u>
<u n="702" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="703" who="S0610" trans="overlap">it's like so against our <trunc>bei</trunc> <trunc>thi</trunc>thinking isn't it?</u>
<u n="704" who="S0428">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> always said to me like she was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> if a plane crashes it doesn't just like a plane doesn't just fall out of the sky it would do this</u>
<u n="705" who="S0612">yeah</u>
<u n="706" who="S0428">and that made me feel a bit better cos I just imagined it going like</u>
<u n="707" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="708" who="S0612"><vocal desc="misc"/> <unclear/> <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="709" who="S0610">yeah yeah so I guess er the thing but still they go really fucking <trunc>fa</trunc> well anyway let's not talk about it</u>
<u n="710" who="S0428" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="711" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="712" who="S0428">how long is the flight to the Maldives?</u>
<u n="713" who="S0612">it's six hours to Dubai and then from Dubai well Abu Abu Dhabi no that's it Abu Dhabi erm</u>
<u n="714" who="S0610">do you want a massage? do you want me to like just go like that?</u>
<u n="715" who="S0612">well does it help?</u>
<u n="716" who="S0610">I dunno try it</u>
<u n="717" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> <unclear>gonna</unclear> <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear>try and attempt a</unclear> massage and then</u>
<u n="718" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">and then from Abu Dhabi it was four hours to Mali which is the capital of the</u>
<u n="719" who="S0610">where was it hurting?</u>
<u n="720" who="S0612">er there</u>
<u n="721" who="S0610"><unclear>if it gets it worse then</unclear></u>
<u n="722" who="S0428" trans="overlap">were you on like your own island?</u>
<u n="723" who="S0612">yeah</u>
<u n="724" who="S0610">really?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0612">oh it was the most luxurious thing I've ever done in my life we had our own hut in the sea</u>
<u n="726" who="S0610"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="727" who="S0428">in the sea?</u>
<u n="728" who="S0610" trans="overlap"><unclear/> madness</u>
<u n="729" who="S0612">and we had a <trunc>p</trunc> like an infinity pool off the back of it</u>
<u n="730" who="S0610">what like like er stalks out like what's it called when you have <trunc>st</trunc>?</u>
<u n="731" who="S0612" trans="overlap">I'll show you I'll show you er</u>
<u n="732" who="S0428">what? it was?</u>
<u n="733" who="S0610" trans="overlap">what you mean the the hut was like pillars out of the sea?</u>
<u n="734" who="S0612" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah I'll show you a video because erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I were playing sea animals where we had to guess what we were doing and</u>
<u n="735" who="S0610">is that <trunc>h</trunc> where is your crick?</u>
<u n="736" who="S0612">er there</u>
<u n="737" who="S0610">okay</u>
<u n="738" who="S0612">like around there videos <pause dur="short"/> so this is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I playing sea <trunc>anim</trunc> okay well I'll show you this video first this is our</u>
<u n="739" who="S0428">let's have a look <pause dur="short"/> oh wow</u>
<u n="740" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh my fucking Christ</u>
<u n="741" who="S0428"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="742" who="S0610">how much do you wanna dive into that pool? into that</u>
<u n="743" who="S0428">oh my god that's like heaven</u>
<u n="744" who="S0612" trans="overlap">how come there were tiles oh no that's the corner of it okay</u>
<u n="745" who="S0610">oh my</u>
<u n="746" who="S0428" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="747" who="S0610">god</u>
<u n="748" who="S0428">so everyone had their own pool?</u>
<u n="749" who="S0612">not everybody er</u>
<u n="750" who="S0428">how long were you there?</u>
<u n="751" who="S0612">erm seven days</u>
<u n="752" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh my <unclear>god</unclear></u>
<u n="753" who="S0612"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="754" who="S0610" trans="overlap">fucking christ oh my god look at that water</u>
<u n="755" who="S0428">oh my</u>
<event desc="sound of video"/>
<u n="756" who="S0612"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="757" who="S0428">when you're ready? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="758" who="S0612" trans="overlap">guess what guess what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s trying to be</u>
<u n="759" who="S0610">is that an infinity pool?</u>
<u n="760" who="S0612">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of video"/>
<u n="761" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="762" who="S0428">that's amazing</u>
<u n="763" who="S0612"><unclear>excuse</unclear> my weird baby voice</u>
<event desc="sound of video"/>
<u n="764" who="S0612">see like he gets into it he like er swims around gets into his little world <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<event desc="sound of video"/>
<u n="765" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="766" who="S0428">that is funny</u>
<u n="767" who="S0612">oh</u>
<u n="768" who="S0610">anyway what's er a dolphin? no</u>
<u n="769" who="S0612">killer whale that was this I was <unclear/></u>
<u n="770" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I've never seen a killer whale oh</u>
<u n="771" who="S0428">oh</u>
<u n="772" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="773" who="S0612">there's a fish we saw turtles there</u>
<u n="774" who="S0610">wow</u>
<u n="775" who="S0612">two turtles in the middle of this er we went snorkelling all the way up there</u>
<u n="776" who="S0428">oh my god it is stunning</u>
<u n="777" who="S0612">erm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="778" who="S0428">how did you choose the Maldives?</u>
<u n="779" who="S0612">oh I've always wanted to go</u>
<u n="780" who="S0428">really?</u>
<u n="781" who="S0610">wow</u>
<u n="782" who="S0612">that was like the view from the breakfast bar</u>
<u n="783" who="S0610">fuck off <vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="784" who="S0428">it is like heaven isn't it? I'd just love to be somewhere like that and just to completely switch off like</u>
<u n="785" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="786" who="S0428">forget what day it is and er I just wanna</u>
<u n="787" who="S0610" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="788" who="S0428">like leave everything and some</u>
<u n="789" who="S0610" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="790" who="S0428">say someone's gonna come for me when it's time to finish</u>
<u n="791" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="792" who="S0428">and time to go home</u>
<u n="793" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="794" who="S0428">just taps you on the shoulder and says off you trot</u>
<u n="795" who="S0610">and then maybe you leave your phone at the desk and be like if there's an emergency I'll tell like tell your family what number to call</u>
<u n="796" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="797" who="S0610" trans="overlap">at the hotel don't look at your phone</u>
<u n="798" who="S0428">like back in the day when we used to go on holiday as a family and like my mum would just give like my grandparents the name of like the <trunc>h</trunc> like</u>
<u n="799" who="S0610" trans="overlap">the hotel yeah</u>
<u n="800" who="S0428" trans="overlap">not even the hotel like the campsite or whatever</u>
<u n="801" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0428">and like so that if there was a problem but now you'd always have your like</u>
<u n="803" who="S0612">oh yeah er we turned I was like we're turning our phones off as soon as we got there it was like I don't want to be known</u>
<u n="804" who="S0610">so did you have your phone on at all?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0612">erm <trunc>o</trunc>only to like listen to music and stuff but we turned erm like</u>
<u n="806" who="S0610"><unclear>turn wi-fi off</unclear></u>
<u n="807" who="S0428" trans="overlap"><trunc>wi</trunc> and er like just like aeroplane mode</u>
<u n="808" who="S0610" trans="overlap">that's such a good idea</u>
<u n="809" who="S0428">couldn't you?</u>
<u n="810" who="S0612">it's funny how much you do rely on it though like you feel uncomfortable after a while you're like well what happens if something's happened to my dad? and it's like well you know that used to like you say it used to happen where if anything was major you'd hear</u>
<u n="811" who="S0610">you would hear somehow yeah like they would just find out but people would just find out the hotel you're at like like</u>
<u n="812" who="S0428">yeah they would though</u>
<u n="813" who="S0610" trans="overlap">er people are more resourceful than you think</u>
<u n="814" who="S0428">yeah and so what erm what so you were there for seven days?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0612">yeah</u>
<u n="816" who="S0428">were you just there on that island?</u>
<u n="817" who="S0612">yeah yeah literally there's <vocal desc="laugh"/> no you couldn't really go for more than like two weeks I don't think and even then two weeks is a bit of a long <trunc>tr</trunc></u>
<u n="818" who="S0610" trans="overlap">even then I think you'd get a bit bored</u>
<u n="819" who="S0612">yeah</u>
<u n="820" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah could you walk round the island? are there like things to do?</u>
<u n="821" who="S0612" trans="overlap">yeah we had bikes they gave us bikes</u>
<u n="822" who="S0428">oh</u>
<u n="823" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">erm</u>
<u n="824" who="S0612" trans="overlap">so you cycled round the island</u>
<u n="825" who="S0610"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is erm her honeymoon they're still planning it but <trunc>th</trunc> she was like I think I'll be too bored spending even a week on the Maldives even though she really <trunc>wa</trunc> er she's like er it it'd be nice on honeymoon they're gonna go to South <trunc>Amer</trunc> er South Africa</u>
<u n="826" who="S0612">wow</u>
<u n="827" who="S0610">and then erm and then go via the Maldives or something spend like four days in the Maldives</u>
<u n="828" who="S0428">where is the Maldives?</u>
<u n="829" who="S0610">it's by Africa isn't it?</u>
<u n="830" who="S0612" trans="overlap">Indian Ocean</u>
<u n="831" who="S0610">has that helped at all?</u>
<u n="832" who="S0612">yeah</u>
<u n="833" who="S0610">has it?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0612" trans="overlap">it's amazing thank you ever so much</u>
<u n="835" who="S0610">has it actually though?</u>
<u n="836" who="S0612">yeah</u>
<u n="837" who="S0610">mm mm</u>
<u n="838" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="839" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> as you say</u>
<u n="840" who="S0612">I feel like when I do this I look very inquisitive like</u>
<u n="841" who="S0610"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="842" who="S0612">mm</u>
<u n="843" who="S0610">I think it's like there's Africa er like correct me if I'm wrong there's Africa and it's here</u>
<u n="844" who="S0428">really?</u>
<u n="845" who="S0610">is it?</u>
<u n="846" who="S0428">like near Madagascar <trunc>Madagas</trunc> <trunc>Mada</trunc> <trunc>Mada</trunc></u>
<u n="847" who="S0612" trans="overlap">it's like there they are</u>
<u n="848" who="S0610">ah</u>
<u n="849" who="S0428">oh well done</u>
<u n="850" who="S0612">that's India Maldives</u>
<u n="851" who="S0428">oh okay so not</u>
<u n="852" who="S0612" trans="overlap">and I was really to be honest I was scared about flying over like we had to fly over Iraq and everywhere and I was like that's when I freaked out because they did bring a plane down</u>
<u n="853" who="S0610">it must be near the Seychelles then cos the Seychelles is around here I think</u>
<u n="854" who="S0612" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="855" who="S0610">cos that's where my uncle's from</u>
<u n="856" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">wow</u>
<u n="857" who="S0428">so how many erm?</u>
<u n="858" who="S0610">it's not actually near South Africa at all</u>
<u n="859" who="S0428">no or <trunc>M</trunc>or Madagascar</u>
<u n="860" who="S0612">no</u>
<u n="861" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's like miles away</u>
<u n="862" who="S0612">I reckon from South Africa to the Maldives is like nearly the same</u>
<u n="863" who="S0610">yeah that's that's <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="864" who="S0610"><unclear/> I might open these curtains</u>
<u n="865" who="S0428">so is er the Maldives is it just millions of islands? or is there?</u>
<u n="866" who="S0612" trans="overlap">millions</u>
<u n="867" who="S0428"><unclear/></u>
<u n="868" who="S0612">yeah they they did count them and <trunc>w</trunc> ours was like really south like we <trunc>ha</trunc> as soon as we arrived in Mali we had to get another plane but like a smaller one and that was like an hour's flight just to get to our island but the island</u>
<u n="869" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh my god an hour's flight?</u>
<u n="870" who="S0612">there's so many islands and honestly just looking out the <pause dur="short"/> looking out the aeroplane it was so beautiful it's everything that you think the Maldives are and I do recommend it because it's pure we I don't think we'll be able to go again unless we win a competition erm</u>
<u n="871" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="872" who="S0612">cos it's just you can't justify spending that much money</u>
<u n="873" who="S0610">yeah I know</u>
<u n="874" who="S0612">and the <trunc>peo</trunc> I mean er <vocal desc="sigh"/> the <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>peo</trunc> like the people there are so lovely as well but you you don't know whether that's just because the hotel had told them to be nice to the guests</u>
<u n="875" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="876" who="S0612">cos everybody from like the <trunc>peo</trunc> they had people that brush stones off the beach to make it like look this and brush the pathways after the storms so it looks</u>
<u n="877" who="S0610" trans="overlap">see that's weird man and erm like</u>
<u n="878" who="S0612">and you kind of yeah but they were all ever so friendly</u>
<u n="879" who="S0610">I wonder what their lives are like I bet they live in quite poverty poor conditions</u>
<u n="880" who="S0428">are there like yeah like poorer islands that aren't touristy or?</u>
<u n="881" who="S0610">there must be places where people live</u>
<u n="882" who="S0612" trans="overlap">there must be yeah I think Mali is like I think it's the most er densely populated city</u>
<u n="883" who="S0428">really?</u>
<u n="884" who="S0612">in all the second or third something city cos it's like compacted I think that's got quite erm</u>
<u n="885" who="S0610">you can't imagine great conditions there can you?</u>
<u n="886" who="S0428">cos sometimes you see pictures I think it's more of the Seychelles or it might be the Maldives of like just <trunc>rubbi</trunc> like islands full of rubbish</u>
<u n="887" who="S0610">yeah I guess it collects all up yeah gross</u>
<u n="888" who="S0612">they're very probably very clever about hiding it cos you couldn't even see that from the air</u>
<u n="889" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="890" who="S0612">my biggest ambition is to find or on my bucket list is to see a whale from the sky cos I reckon you would be able to</u>
<u n="891" who="S0610" trans="overlap"><unclear/> wow <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="892" who="S0612">so I spent the whole hour's flight <trunc>lo</trunc> like</u>
<u n="893" who="S0428">why from the sky?</u>
<u n="894" who="S0612">just because I'd love to see a whale and I'd be too scared to be on the sea to see a whale</u>
<u n="895" who="S0428">I've seen a whale</u>
<u n="896" who="S0612"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="897" who="S0610">how?</u>
<u n="898" who="S0612">wow</u>
<u n="899" who="S0428" trans="overlap">well my</u>
<u n="900" who="S0612"><unclear>but I meant</unclear></u>
<u n="901" who="S0428" trans="overlap">when I went when I went</u>
<u n="902" who="S0612">go on</u>
<u n="903" who="S0428">to Australia with my aunt</u>
<u n="904" who="S0612">oh you</u>
<u n="905" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I was working on a boat that was tracking the whales up in the Indian Ocean</u>
<u n="906" who="S0612">oh my</u>
<u n="907" who="S0428" trans="overlap">and we went out we saw like three hundred whales like they were like</u>
<u n="908" who="S0610" trans="overlap">like big ones? or how big?</u>
<u n="909" who="S0428">massive ones yeah</u>
<u n="910" who="S0610">wow</u>
<u n="911" who="S0428" trans="overlap">they don't look that big in the sea like when you're on a boat so what they what they were doing was they were like counting them to see if the if they put an like if an oil refinery <trunc>ha</trunc> was like changing like the natural course of the whales</u>
<u n="912" who="S0612" trans="overlap">yeah wow</u>
<u n="913" who="S0428">erm</u>
<u n="914" who="S0612">cos they say fishing harbours do now don't they?</u>
<u n="915" who="S0610">what?</u>
<u n="916" who="S0428">yeah it's</u>
<u n="917" who="S0612">that like fishing harbours change cos er that was on that David Attenborough Hunt documentary which was amazing</u>
<u n="918" who="S0610">oh I didn't see that I wanna see that</u>
<u n="919" who="S0612" trans="overlap">oh it was amazing you no that I'm sure is on BBC Iplayer but they had</u>
<u n="920" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="921" who="S0612">a whole mm erm blue whale? cos that's the largest one isn't it?</u>
<u n="922" who="S0610">is it?</u>
<u n="923" who="S0612">and they're just</u>
<u n="924" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I think ours were humpbacks that we were tracking</u>
<u n="925" who="S0612">they're just incredible creatures</u>
<u n="926" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="927" who="S0612">I'm</u>
<u n="928" who="S0428">in awe of them</u>
<u n="929" who="S0612" trans="overlap">weirdly <trunc>ob</trunc>obsessed with them</u>
<u n="930" who="S0610">wow</u>
<u n="931" who="S0612" trans="overlap">just to see one from at least er</u>
<u n="932" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="933" who="S0612">if like if you're that <trunc>l</trunc> er obviously you can't when you're like up there but if you're like there and you just see the silhouette of</u>
<u n="934" who="S0610" trans="overlap">of this huge mammal</u>
<u n="935" who="S0612" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="936" who="S0610">just in this ocean</u>
<u n="937" who="S0428" trans="overlap">but they they don't cos the sea is so big they don't look that big it's really weird</u>
<u n="938" who="S0612" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="939" who="S0428">and like even when you're just in Australia and you stand er cos like my aunt's obviously like worked with them a lot she we'll just</u>
<u n="940" who="S0610" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="941" who="S0428">you we'll just be standing on the coast she'll be like there's a whale</u>
<u n="942" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">wow</u>
<u n="943" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">and I would just see it as the sea and then you can see them like doing all their like</u>
<u n="944" who="S0612">tail</u>
<u n="945" who="S0428" trans="overlap">their tail flips and like</u>
<u n="946" who="S0612" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="947" who="S0428" trans="overlap">puffing water out</u>
<u n="948" who="S0612">wow</u>
<u n="949" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah the thing which was amazing is that obviously like you know this about whales but like they're just this the on the documentary you're just swimming along and suddenly it wanted to eat all the plankton or whatever it it eats</u>
<u n="950" who="S0610"><unclear>its food</unclear></u>
<u n="951" who="S0612">and then its thing just goes <vocal desc="misc"/> like its chin almost just it's huge</u>
<u n="952" who="S0610">are they they don't eat meat?</u>
<u n="953" who="S0428">they don't like salt no it's a joke <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="954" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="955" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="956" who="S0612">I believed you then I was like wow</u>
<u n="957" who="S0610">yeah how do they filter it out?</u>
<u n="958" who="S0428" trans="overlap"><unclear/> but how do they get so big without eating meat? or maybe they do eat meat</u>
<u n="959" who="S0610">do they eat meat?</u>
<u n="960" who="S0428">I dunno because <unclear/></u>
<u n="961" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="962" who="S0612">they can't er they basically if they open their mouth then it's pot luck what's in there isn't it?</u>
<u n="963" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="964" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="965" who="S0612">no you er you could they could eat human</u>
<u n="966" who="S0610" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="967" who="S0612">and I don't think they'd mean to</u>
<u n="968" who="S0610">ah</u>
<u n="969" who="S0612" trans="overlap">cos that would scare me like the amount that they open their whale er mouth</u>
<u n="970" who="S0428">Jonah and the Whale ain't it?</u>
<u n="971" who="S0612">yeah you'd just go right in there and then er I don't want to think</u>
<u n="972" who="S0428">oh god you can't even imagine</u>
<u n="973" who="S0612" trans="overlap">mind you can swim in a a whale's vein or something it's that big</u>
<u n="974" who="S0610">how big are they like in <trunc>c</trunc>in comparison to this room?</u>
<u n="975" who="S0428" trans="overlap">they're just ginormous</u>
<u n="976" who="S0612" trans="overlap">they're it's crazy</u>
<u n="977" who="S0610" trans="overlap">like could it fill this room?</u>
<u n="978" who="S0428">no bigger way bigger than this room</u>
<u n="979" who="S0612">it's like</u>
<u n="980" who="S0610">imagine that</u>
<u n="981" who="S0612">almost like one of the <trunc>G</trunc> like a Gherkin but not that big</u>
<u n="982" who="S0428">no that's big</u>
<u n="983" who="S0428">they're just erm</u>
<u n="984" who="S0610">compared to that shipping container what about a shipping container?</u>
<u n="985" who="S0428" trans="overlap">they're probably about the size of a shipping container</u>
<u n="986" who="S0612">yeah the blue whale would be like</u>
<u n="987" who="S0428" trans="overlap">or bigger</u>
<u n="988" who="S0612">the size of five of them</u>
<u n="989" who="S0610">no</u>
<u n="990" who="S0612">they're huge wait a minute</u>
<u n="991" who="S0610">let me have a look let me have a look</u>
<u n="992" who="S0428">and er it's <trunc>j</trunc> honestly it's just incredible when you just look across the ocean cos erm we saw this one boat and there was a whale swimming in the background then there was a group of dolphins like jumping and then a shark swam at the dolphins and they all stopped and they all like got together and they like protected each other this and then er we saw the shark swim off and then the dolphins started playing again then this <trunc>wha</trunc>whale's just drifting on in the background</u>
<u n="993" who="S0612">wow what?</u>
<u n="994" who="S0428" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="995" who="S0612">so sharks eat dolphins?</u>
<u n="996" who="S0428">they will attack them yeah</u>
<u n="997" who="S0612">bastards no one like sharks</u>
<u n="998" who="S0428">but the dolphins like all like</u>
<u n="999" who="S0612">good</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0428"><trunc>prote</trunc> like they protect <trunc>themse</trunc> like like</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0612" trans="overlap">get into a little club</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0612">good</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0610" trans="overlap">ah</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0428">the dolphin club</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0612">and whales I mean there's no point in trying to take that one out</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0428">no</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0612">mind you I don't see how a whale could defend itself</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0610">so twenty-five metres</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0428">so about</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0612">is that a large blue <trunc>w</trunc> the the great blue whale?</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0610">the blue whale</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0428">so this room is probably like six metres</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0610">oh my fucking Christ</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0612">yeah</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0610" trans="overlap">you're right a shipping container is probably only like</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0428">ten? we'll look it up maybe</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0612">so can you get a scale?</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0428">yeah and they have like</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0610" trans="overlap">okay yeah</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0428">a human's toenail next to a</u>
<u n="1022" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1023" who="S0428">like a a human's mouth next to a whale's mouth</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0612">but yeah I've for some reason whales have always fascinated me so</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0428">but I just think and they're</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0610" trans="overlap">you should go on like a whale watch somewhere</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0612">I would but then I get scared that</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0610">oh my god</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0612">like you <trunc>h</trunc> they they had that one in Canada which capsized didn't it? and then people</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0612">drowned <unclear>on it</unclear></u>
<u n="1032" who="S0610">look at that so hang on how do I get all the other shit off the screen? so blue whale comparison to say an elephant</u>
<u n="1033" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1034" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">that's a fucking elephant in comparison and there's us that's us in comparison to that blue whale</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0428" trans="overlap">er we're not like we wouldn't even like <trunc>m</trunc> we're not even as tall as their <trunc>f</trunc>fin</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0610">oh my god I didn't realise they were that big</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0612">that's why it's they're so cool</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0428" trans="overlap">but you honestly the the sea</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0612" trans="overlap">they're like the last</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0428" trans="overlap">the sea is so big you don't even realise they're big like they look small</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0612" trans="overlap">you need to if you're yeah watch if you watch any episode of The Hunt watch the sea one because they show do the whale</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0612">and they they also have the section about like these jellyfish that look like they're raving underwater</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0610">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0428" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0612" trans="overlap">it's</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0610">is it cos they light up or something?</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0612" trans="overlap">there's so there's so many different <trunc>w</trunc> like you <trunc>hone</trunc> like when you see something like that I can't <trunc>h</trunc>help thinking there is some sort of god</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0610">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I know</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0612">because it just doesn't <trunc>happe</trunc> like</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0428">who would put raving jellyfish in the sea?</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0612">yeah they are incredible and like they're all these crazy shapes that you would just think <unclear>are</unclear> in your dreams</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0428">er I remember we went onto this one beach and like you can't swim cos they're completely poisonous but all these jellyfish had washed up on the beach</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0428">er and we were just walking in shoes and it's like they're it's like bubble-wrap and they've got like like a bubble and you just and it's like it's horrible it's like pop pop pop pop and it's like they're completely <trunc>dea</trunc> like deadly if you cos there's so many of them and the whole beach is just like bubble-wrap they've got a name</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0612" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0428">I can't remember what they're called</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0610">cor this is so sad so yeah like you say er they their diet is almost <trunc>c</trunc> exclusively of small crustaceans</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0612">oh <unclear>okay</unclear></u>
<u n="1061" who="S0610">erm but</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0612" trans="overlap">which we found out about last night <unclear/></u>
<u n="1063" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0428">we need we need <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to come and tell us about that</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0612"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1066" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1067" who="S0610">blue whales were abundant in nearly all the oceans on earth until the beginning of the twentieth century</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0612">and then humans <unclear>messed</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="1069" who="S0610" trans="overlap">for over a century they were hunted almost to extinction by whalers until protected by the international community in nineteen sixty-six a two thousand and two report estimated there were five thousand to two <trunc>thou</trunc> so between five thousand and twelve thousand blue whales worldwide in at least five groups that's not a lot is it?</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0428">no</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0610">twelve thousand</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0612">we <trunc>s</trunc> we ruined so much</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0610">that's why it's so important people I just don't understand how people can't respect nature and like how</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0428" trans="overlap">and we and it's it's getting worse that's what upsets me it's like we've we know this we know we're like we know we should protect them protect everything</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0610">I just don't understand</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0612">no</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0610">so before whaling there were about two hundred and thirty-nine thousand sorry this is really depressing let's just look at how nice they are</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0612">mm well no it's <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1079" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">but I mean</u>
<u n="1080" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">I guess at least they are protected now cos hopefully they can just mate a bit more and make a few more</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0610">hang on <unclear>though</unclear> what number's that?</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0612" trans="overlap">there are two groups</u>
<u n="1083" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0610">hang on <unclear>as of</unclear> twenty-fourteen the Californian blue whale has rebounded to nearly its pre-hunting population</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0612">oh</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0610" trans="overlap"><unclear/> this is completely <trunc>re</trunc></u>
<u n="1087" who="S0612">that's good</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0610">oh so hang on sorry</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0612">this journalist obviously doesn't write as er</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0610" trans="overlap">there remain only</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0612">properly as you do</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1093" who="S0612">and all</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0428" trans="overlap"><unclear>and they</unclear> won't be famous</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0610"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah I don't really understand what they're talking about there hunting yeah well it's just erm fucking mad</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0428" trans="overlap">well I saw three hundred so there are at least three hundred whales in the world</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0612">that's <trunc>incre</trunc> that's so cool</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0428">it's quite <unclear>it's just</unclear> mental</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0610" trans="overlap"><unclear>this is blue whales erm <trunc>s</trunc>specifically</unclear></u>
<u n="1100" who="S0612" trans="overlap">but humpback whales so what do they look like?</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0610">they're just really big</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0428">and we saw a hammerhead shark as well that just swam past the boat and it freaked me out</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0612">that would freak me out when erm we went in the Maldives <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I are not big fans of the sea because in the sea I'm <trunc>t</trunc>terrified of jellyfish sharks I know I mean</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0428">are there Maldives in the <trunc>sh</trunc> are there <vocal desc="laugh"/> sharks in</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0612" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> are there <trunc>Maldi</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1106" who="S0428">are there sharks in the Maldives?</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0612">yeah and but the the funny thing is when we got there like I loved the fact also their health and safety is not as anal as we are here</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0428">yeah <unclear>it makes a difference</unclear></u>
<u n="1109" who="S0612" trans="overlap">cos we had we didn't get any sort of briefings about what's in the sea they just said if you're going snorkelling don't go out when the current's doing you can't go to the side of the island because you'll get washed away in a current so they they were just like just go to the end of the reef and then you'll be fine</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0610" trans="overlap">that's quite scary <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1111" who="S0612">yeah erm and but they didn't give you er kind of there's this in the sea there's this in the sea and so on in the sea I'm petrified of jellyfish and on land I'm petrified of cockroaches I hate the fuckers so</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0428">oh they're disgusting</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0612">yeah and erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I met this other couple there and er the man in this couple they'd just got married too and he was an avid snorkeler and he'd been out every day twice a day for a couple of hours and he was just telling us everything that he'd seen and ever since I went to Cape Verde and we saw a turtle on the beach I've just been obsessed with trying to see one in the it's like swimming around like happy unaffected by humans because we were on a beach and it was trying to lay eggs and all these stupid tourists and we all <unclear/></u>
<u n="1114" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0612">yeah erm even though we were good we were respecting the tortoise but then <trunc>s</trunc> and they just said you can watch them and don't make any <trunc>mov</trunc> like you had to be really quiet</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0428">you should go to where <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s just been</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0612">and they were like you just can't take any flash photography and then this dickhead took a flash <trunc>photog</trunc> and then the turtle freaked out and ran back in where's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just been?</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0428">I dunno somewhere in <unclear/></u>
<u n="1119" who="S0612" trans="overlap">oh yeah cos you you showed us a video of <unclear>him</unclear></u>
<u n="1120" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0610">wow so amazing facts about blue whales their tongues alone can weigh as much as an elephant</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> woah</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0610">their hearts as much as a car <pause dur="short"/> amazingly though this giant of the ocean feeds on some of the smallest marine life</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0428">ah</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0610">tiny shrimp-like animals called krill</u>
<u n="1126" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="1127" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">a single adult blue can consume three <pause dur="short"/> thirty-six thousand kilo</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0612" trans="overlap">I mean isn't that just also incredible that it's not it's this huge thing and it doesn't need to eat huge things it just survives on the most tiny thing</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0610" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0612">in the ocean?</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0428">yeah and it doesn't it's not aggressive like it's it's big but it's not like I'm the</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0610"><unclear>like a</unclear> shark</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0428" trans="overlap">king of the ocean and I'm gonna kill everything</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0612" trans="overlap">is that in your way?</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0428">no no not at all there's someone in the toilet</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0612">do you wanna share the sixty-six million pound jackpot?</u>
<u n="1138" who="S0428">I can just share that out between sixty-six like everyone <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1139" who="S0610">they are thought to form close attachments then there's wow it's so crazy though we can't hear them blue whales</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0428">well don't don't worry it's fine <unclear>sweetie</unclear></u>
<u n="1141" who="S0612" trans="overlap">no cos you can't be comfortable <unclear/></u>
<u n="1142" who="S0610">though we can't hear them blue whales are one of the loudest animals on the planet communicating</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0428" trans="overlap">they're having a party down there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1144" who="S0610">communicating with each other using a series of low frequency pulses groans and moans</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0612" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1146" who="S0610">it is thought that in er good conditions blue whales can hear over distances of up to one thousand six hundred kilometres</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0612">cor</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0428" trans="overlap">no way that's mental</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0612" trans="overlap">that's mental</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0610">it is thought that whales feel emotions</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0428">I don't know the door's still shut it's always open isn't it?</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0610">yeah someone's probably in it</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0612"><unclear/> <unclear>hear someone come out of there</unclear></u>
<u n="1154" who="S0428">I know</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0610">oh give it a <trunc>g</trunc>give it a go then they could've been <unclear/> <unclear>girlfriend</unclear> <pause dur="long"/> blue whales have few predators but are known to fall victim</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0428" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1157" who="S0610">to attacks my sharks and killer whales but many and many are injured or die each year from impacts with large ships</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0612">oh that's er er <trunc>m</trunc> actually <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said that his cos they're er he's on he's in navy ships and the they crashed into a whale and you just felt it like <trunc>ver</trunc> reverberate around the</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0610">wow</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0612" trans="overlap">the whole ship why can't they avoid them?</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0610">I guess it's quite hard if I dunno</u>
<u n="1162" who="S0428">but they'd come on their tracking system wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="1163" who="S0610">but maybe they wouldn't be able to I don't know</u>
<u n="1164" who="S0612">they probably don't give a shit</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0610">god I'd give a shit imagine that? it's like <pause dur="short"/> that whale is more valuable than one human life <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1166" who="S0612">mm</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0428">well it's worth how many?</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0428">it's just so big isn't it?</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0610">are you guys hungry?</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0612">mm</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0610">are you hungry?</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0612" trans="overlap">strangely enough</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0428">erm</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0610">trying to think what to make for breakfast today <pause dur="short"/> what would you like? I've got some really nice bread obviously erm half a bottle of red wine</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1177" who="S0610">half a bottle of red wine I could</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0612"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1179" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh this is nice</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0612">I'm actually really not hungry which is strange</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0610">but in an hour you might be</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0612">oh okay</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0610">you're probably hungry now aren't you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0428">I I need a wee so I can't think about food until I have a wee</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0610">I could</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0428" trans="overlap">one thing at a time <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1187" who="S0610">it'd be nice to eat that nice bread wouldn't it with something?</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0610">I've got some</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I'm gonna go home quite soon actually</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0610">do you wanna have the breakfast?</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0428">yeah cos I won't make it</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0428">home without brek</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0610">er</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0612">you'll get hallway there and just <unclear/></u>
<u n="1197" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1198" who="S0610">well you could have some toast and I could make us a fry up</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0612">no no no no no no</u>
<u n="1200" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah I could</u>
<u n="1201" who="S0612" trans="overlap">no no no no no</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0610"><vocal desc="laugh"/> in like an hour I've got some bacon left over in the freezer <unclear>could</unclear> go and get some beans</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0612">baked beans</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0610">I've got mushrooms what do you reckon? or we could go out but it's cheaper this way isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> what are you saying <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0612" trans="overlap">see shall we see how <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> feels when he's up and about?</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0428">do you have</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0612" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1208" who="S0428">do you have another toilet?</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0610">yeah first floor</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0428">where is it?</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0610">just er where the cloakroom is there's a door next to it</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0428">the cloakroom?</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0610">the the hallway</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0428" trans="overlap">the ground floor</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0612">so you go down the stairs and it's on your left</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0428">really? on the like the one that you come in on? there's so many floors in this <unclear>house</unclear></u>
<u n="1217" who="S0612" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="1218" who="S0610">ground floor <unclear/></u>
<u n="1219" who="S0612" trans="overlap">it's like the Crystal Maze</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0610">well</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0428">okay</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0610">when you go through erm cos there's two you'll see do two doors and one is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s room so it's the one you go through the door and it's just straight there on your left</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0428">hang on you go through</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0610">so you come down the stairs</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0610">on the ground floor on your left is a door that comes off the <trunc>hallwa</trunc> you'll see it and then it's the first door on your left</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0428">first door on your left when you come</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0610">down and then first door on your left again left left it's not that complicated</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0428">it'll be really embarrassing if I like go into <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s <trunc>r</trunc> is it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0610">don't worry about it <pause dur="short"/> I'm thirsty</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0612">mm</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0610">we should go for a walk in erm <anon type="place"/> park <unclear>and look at</unclear> the ducks it's my favourite thing to do</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0612"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="1234" who="S0610">do you have any requirements for your stay?</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0612">not at all</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0610">anything you want to do?</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0612">erm <pause dur="long"/> er I don't believe there is</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0610">no? we'll have a chilled morning so we could have some nice breakfast</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0612">mm</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0610">and then we could go for a <trunc>w</trunc> stroll around <anon type="place"/> park you know <anon type="place"/> park don't you?</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0612">yeah I think we met <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> there for the first time <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="1242" who="S0610">yeah and then I <trunc>l</trunc> er just there are so many ducks and stuff and birds so <unclear/></u>
<u n="1243" who="S0612" trans="overlap">we could take some bread</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0610">yeah go round there and we could stop somewhere for coffee and then we could stroll back here watch a bit of telly read a bit of books</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0612">mm</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0610">relax</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0612">erm I need to find out cos they on the <anon type="place"/> apparently they're doing some servicing stuff</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0612">I need to find out <pause dur="long"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear>probably</unclear> take about an hour</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0612">but it says <vocal desc="sigh"/> part closure no service <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> due to</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0610" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1253" who="S0612">engineering work</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0612">good service on the rest of the line</u>
<u n="1256" who="S0610">fine you're fine</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0612">but it says customers should use the <anon type="place"/> services between <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1258" who="S0610">no you're fine erm like go <anon type="place"/> and do your journey and see if it says what see what it says <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1259" who="S0612">when I got on from when I got when I went to <anon type="place"/> did you find it okay?</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0428">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was like really worried there's no lights it's so dark</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0612">oh</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0428">so I had to like find the light switch by the door</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0610"><vocal desc="cough"/> was it a good wee?</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0428">I can't believe I've never been in that bathroom before</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0612">I never have either</u>
<u n="1267" who="S0610" trans="overlap">I never I never really go</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0428">quite a good bathroom</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0612" trans="overlap">is it clean? as in like cos that must be just be his bathroom really</u>
<u n="1270" who="S0610">it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they use it</u>
<u n="1271" who="S0428">it's really clean</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0612">that's good <unclear/></u>
<u n="1273" who="S0610" trans="overlap">do you have a cleaner?</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0612">I like a clean toilet clean toilet <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> yeah <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> part closure <unclear/></u>
<u n="1275" who="S0428">where have you got to get to?</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0610"><anon type="place"/> I think you're fine</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0612">can I check it's you?</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="1279" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1280" who="S0610"><unclear/> back to results alright <anon type="place"/> to <anon type="place"/> god that's quite good</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0612">it's really good</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0610">view details</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0612" trans="overlap">and <anon type="place"/> I know where that station is now it's just down the way</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0610">yeah cos you always get a bus from <anon type="place"/> don't you?</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0612">yeah which I do also enjoy because you go past all the sights of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1286" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah it's nice</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0612">and it's number <trunc>twe</trunc>twenty-six which is my lucky number <pause dur="short"/> I yeah when we were in the Maldives so we managed to <trunc>g</trunc>get the courage to go out snorkelling</u>
<u n="1288" who="S0610">oh</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0612">erm and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's funny cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s normally like really er he if he wants to do it he'll do it and he doesn't really care but he was really like panicking and he was like I don't wanna do this I don't wanna do this but we did it so we went out</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0610"><unclear>why</unclear> was he scared about?</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0612">cos he's just scared of like not being able to control the situation in the sea</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0612">like you're in their habitat</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0612">and we saw lots of sea cucumbers which er constantly made me giggle cos they're</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0610">what?</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0612">sea cucumbers they're hilarious <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1298" who="S0610" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0612">really little <trunc>s</trunc> cucumbers under the sea</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0428">oh really?</u>
<u n="1301" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="1302" who="S0612">and they're just like worms aren't they? but but they just</u>
<u n="1303" who="S0610" trans="overlap">I've never seen that</u>
<u n="1304" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I've never seen one</u>
<u n="1305" who="S0612">they're so funny oh I was giggling the whole way erm</u>
<u n="1306" who="S0428" trans="overlap">it's really hard when you giggle in a snorkel</u>
<u n="1307" who="S0612">yeah mm erm</u>
<u n="1308" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> a problem I often have</u>
<u n="1309" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1310" who="S0612">and then we got to the edge of the reef and we were just like oh trying to gear ourselves up to go over and then er we just saw this <trunc>obj</trunc> like this large thing like swimming around and you looked at it and it was a shark</u>
<u n="1311" who="S0610">what?</u>
<u n="1312" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1313" who="S0612">but it was it was a reef shark so they're about that long</u>
<u n="1314" who="S0610">and they're not?</u>
<u n="1315" who="S0612">and they look like and they're <trunc>bl</trunc> they're called blacktip <trunc>r</trunc>blacktip reef sharks and we looked at it and it didn't do anything cos it obviously saw us and we were like fuck and I was like mm no I'm not swimming towards them because</u>
<u n="1316" who="S0610">no</u>
<u n="1317" who="S0612" trans="overlap">you just don't know like we didn't know if it was a vegetarian shark or</u>
<u n="1318" who="S0610"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1319" who="S0612">anything like that so we</u>
<u n="1320" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1321" who="S0612">but as soon as we like</u>
<u n="1322" who="S0428" trans="overlap">or a vegan</u>
<u n="1323" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1324" who="S0612">tried we tried like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> tried swimming <trunc>m</trunc> like swimming away which kind of pushed me closer to the sharks and I was like no erm but we had flippers on so you can swim quite fast and then so we were trying to get away like you just saw like four or five of them come out and they just started circling this entrance to the reef</u>
<u n="1325" who="S0610"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1326" who="S0612">and we were like oh my god so we couldn't have been er like where that sofa is that's how close we were to these sharks</u>
<u n="1327" who="S0610">oh my god</u>
<u n="1328" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh fuck <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1329" who="S0612">yeah I know and we were like oh and then we started to swim erm back and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I was like oh <vocal desc="sigh"/> I don't wanna go in cos I haven't seen a turtle and this guy at the bar had been like there's loads of them and I was like I need to see one and like up until like we literally there's we hadn't been that far off the seabed and I I thought that was it like that was snorkelling</u>
<u n="1330" who="S0428" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1331" who="S0612">then we went down a bit and then went through this other gap and then suddenly the bed just gave way to this kind of well there was nothing like you couldn't see the sea it was amazing but really scary</u>
<u n="1332" who="S0610" trans="overlap">what? with life you mean? or?</u>
<u n="1333" who="S0612">huh?</u>
<u n="1334" who="S0610">like with sea life?</u>
<u n="1335" who="S0612">well that yeah oh the fish are beautiful like again they're just all the colours under the sun they're gorgeous but it was just the way that <unclear><trunc>s</trunc> you were like</unclear> by the seabed and then suddenly</u>
<u n="1336" who="S0610" trans="overlap">and then suddenly it dropped off?</u>
<u n="1337" who="S0612">and like it's er the <trunc>t</trunc> length of the house is where the seabed is and you're just like flying it was incredible and then</u>
<u n="1338" who="S0428">would you've done diving?</u>
<u n="1339" who="S0612">no no I couldn't do that I <trunc>c</trunc>I couldn't do it because I'm scared that I'd kill myself as in I er accidentally burp or something and then something would happen</u>
<u n="1340" who="S0610" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1341" who="S0428">what? if you burp?</u>
<u n="1342" who="S0610">no</u>
<u n="1343" who="S0612">I dunno but cos you're in control of that aren't you? and also there's all those things that if you swim up too fast you can</u>
<u n="1344" who="S0610" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1345" who="S0612">blow your brains out or something I dunno no that's too hectic for me but</u>
<u n="1346" who="S0428">you can get you can see so much just snorkelling that's crazy though just seeing the sea drop away</u>
<u n="1347" who="S0612">yeah er I've never seen</u>
<u n="1348" who="S0428" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="1349" who="S0612">I've never been very like been out that far ever in anywhere and it was just so beautiful because it was just so</u>
<u n="1350" who="S0610" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="1351" who="S0612">it was like Disney <trunc>B</trunc>Bedknobs and Broomsticks and then and then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like there's a turtle and I was like what? a turtle and I didn't and he was pointing and I couldn't see what he was pointing at and he was desperate to leave by this point so he was like look at the fucking turtle</u>
<u n="1352" who="S0610"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1353" who="S0612">and then there was one just</u>
<u n="1354" who="S0610">ah</u>
<u n="1355" who="S0612" trans="overlap">like</u>
<u n="1356" who="S0428">oh and you saw him?</u>
<u n="1357" who="S0612">I <trunc>s</trunc> yeah I saw him and he kind of came a bit close to us and then went away but it was just so nice to see him in his habitat just like like</u>
<u n="1358" who="S0610">ah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1359" who="S0612" trans="overlap">and he was like that big like he was good decent sized one and then we saw another one</u>
<u n="1360" who="S0428">oh I'm so pleased you saw one</u>
<u n="1361" who="S0612">oh I I know otherwise I would've had to keep going back out I mean it was literally the most amazing thing I've ever seen a one-off and then we went back and er as soon as we got out of our back onto our thing you just saw this reef shark swim up to and they don't come that close because it's quite shallow and it was just funny the way that he just swam up to our</u>
<u n="1362" who="S0610">thing yeah</u>
<u n="1363" who="S0612" trans="overlap">thing went under it and then away and it was almost like stay out of our habitat</u>
<u n="1364" who="S0610">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1365" who="S0612">or</u>
<u n="1366" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh keep out yeah</u>
<u n="1367" who="S0612" trans="overlap">we let you live this time</u>
<u n="1368" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1369" who="S0612">but not next time</u>
<u n="1370" who="S0610"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1371" who="S0612">so after that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was googled reef blacktip reef sharks and they're not like scary ones but it's I mean it's just like the thing that they have been known to bite somebody</u>
<u n="1372" who="S0610">okay but I guess</u>
<u n="1373" who="S0612" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="1374" who="S0610">that's when they feel</u>
<u n="1375" who="S0612">yeah</u>
<u n="1376" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="1377" who="S0612">threatened so</u>
<u n="1378" who="S0428">god sharks swimming around</u>
<u n="1379" who="S0610" trans="overlap">so did you then avoid the sea? cos I guess was that the only time you went in the sea? or?</u>
<u n="1380" who="S0612">yeah the rest of the time we were</u>
<u n="1381" who="S0428">in the pool</u>
<u n="1382" who="S0612">in the pool and they had a pool and a beach bar which was really nice with the beds in the water so we <unclear/></u>
<u n="1383" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I just the love the sea like</u>
<u n="1384" who="S0610">yeah I know</u>
<u n="1385" who="S0428" trans="overlap">that's why I like to be in like the Med cos I feel safe in the Med like you get <trunc>jellyf</trunc> like</u>
<u n="1386" who="S0610" trans="overlap">that's the thing I'm a like I'm a right pussy so if I was to go to the Indian Ocean I'd feel really scared to be in the sea when there was probably a stupid thing to be scared of I don't know</u>
<u n="1387" who="S0612">I wouldn't say it's I I think it's just you have to be sensible and the thing is there is nothing <trunc>th</trunc> like there are no nets around the island to protect <trunc>y</trunc> like if for example a great white</u>
<u n="1388" who="S0428" trans="overlap">in Singapore there are nets</u>
<u n="1389" who="S0612" trans="overlap">had gone off course</u>
<u n="1390" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="1391" who="S0612">and was in er like we wouldn't've known we could've been out there we would've</u>
<u n="1392" who="S0428">mm like in <trunc>S</trunc>in Singapore they have nets on the beaches to stop the sharks coming in</u>
<u n="1393" who="S0612" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1394" who="S0428">but there was a shark in Valencia who got lost</u>
<u n="1395" who="S0610">oh really?</u>
<u n="1396" who="S0428" trans="overlap">and erm</u>
<u n="1397" who="S0612">yeah that's the thing er there's always that one time when</u>
<u n="1398" who="S0428" trans="overlap">but they can trap them in the Med cos they come in through the gap between Gibraltar</u>
<u n="1399" who="S0610">of course</u>
<u n="1400" who="S0428">and they can see them coming in</u>
<u n="1401" who="S0612">can they?</u>
<u n="1402" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="1403" who="S0612">so what do they do? they don't kill them?</u>
<u n="1404" who="S0428">no I think they just say there's an <trunc>al</trunc> they put alerts out</u>
<u n="1405" who="S0612">mm</u>
<u n="1406" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1407" who="S0428">and <unclear>respect</unclear> it</u>
<u n="1408" who="S0612">er do they guide the shark erm</u>
<u n="1409" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1410" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1411" who="S0428">the <trunc>sh</trunc> get some they get some sheep dog</u>
<u n="1412" who="S0610">yeah once it's in the Med it'd be pretty hard for the shark to get out again</u>
<u n="1413" who="S0428">yeah it doesn't like it there I don't think</u>
<u n="1414" who="S0610">no it's too warm isn't it?</u>
<u n="1415" who="S0428" trans="overlap">claustrophobic</u>
<u n="1416" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="1417" who="S0428">it's so scary though</u>
<u n="1418" who="S0610">the sea does scare me I'm such a fucking <unclear>pansy</unclear></u>
<u n="1419" who="S0428">I think it's quite good cos when I was when I was in Australia with my aunt cos she's like she's obviously done so much with like the whales and like the sea and she's like lived on boats for months on end</u>
<u n="1420" who="S0612">that's so cool</u>
<u n="1421" who="S0428" trans="overlap">she knows kind of what to do and so I <trunc>f</trunc> totally feel safe being with her and like so</u>
<u n="1422" who="S0612" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1423" who="S0428">when we went snorkelling I've only ever been snorkelling once in my life</u>
<u n="1424" who="S0612">cos that would be scary cos it's cos I don't know if I'd be able to snorkel there because they are</u>
<u n="1425" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="1426" who="S0612">great whites about</u>
<u n="1427" who="S0428">but we were on like we were in this place called</u>
<u n="1428" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh scary</u>
<u n="1429" who="S0428" trans="overlap">Coral Bay and it's got a big soft coral reef so the sharks don't really go into the coral reef erm so we kayaked out attached our boats and then erm and then we were like snorkelling but yeah they're like don't wee in the sea because the shark can smell it from like miles and miles and miles away and they know there's something there</u>
<u n="1430" who="S0612">it's crazy</u>
<u n="1431" who="S0428">I was really scared cos I</u>
<u n="1432" who="S0612" trans="overlap">but what an interesting job</u>
<u n="1433" who="S0428">I cut myself on erm coral and I was like bleeding and I was like oh no the sharks are gonna come <vocal desc="laugh"/> but like they don't like I think</u>
<u n="1434" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1435" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">it's very unlikely they they they kind of do follow very similar patterns like and you shouldn't go in at dusk I think that's when they get a lot at the surface</u>
<u n="1436" who="S0612">it's like a feeding time isn't it?</u>
<u n="1437" who="S0428">yeah so I think there are like certain precautions you can take</u>
<u n="1438" who="S0612">have you seen that video when er that guy's doing like surfing and he gets attacked but he like punches it</u>
<u n="1439" who="S0428">in the <trunc>m</trunc> like <trunc>m</trunc> you <trunc>g</trunc></u>
<u n="1440" who="S0612" trans="overlap">he does something and gets away</u>
<u n="1441" who="S0428" trans="overlap">that's what you're supposed to do punch it in the nose</u>
<u n="1442" who="S0610">what? did you see it? it's a video?</u>
<u n="1443" who="S0612">yeah you see like he's <trunc>sur</trunc> like on this huge wave it's on Youtube because it was quite like it was in the news and everything because he like fends off this great white which is trying to eat him whilst he's <trunc>surfi</trunc></u>
<u n="1444" who="S0610" trans="overlap">what? he punches him in the face?</u>
<u n="1445" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="1446" who="S0612">he does something or <trunc>sta</trunc> yeah he does something</u>
<u n="1447" who="S0610">get him in the eyes</u>
<u n="1448" who="S0612">easier said than done I mean</u>
<u n="1449" who="S0610" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1450" who="S0612">it's a split second isn't it? when you're like you're either gonna just go like that cos you're scared or</u>
<u n="1451" who="S0610">that's what I would do</u>
<u n="1452" who="S0428">you never know</u>
<u n="1453" who="S0610">I'd be like</u>
<u n="1454" who="S0428">no no</u>
<u n="1455" who="S0610" trans="overlap">okay just take me quick</u>
<u n="1456" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="1457" who="S0612">oh it'd be horrible</u>
<u n="1458" who="S0428">especially if it like takes a bite and <unclear>just like cos</unclear> they don't like the taste of humans and then just spits you out and you're left there like</u>
<u n="1459" who="S0610"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1460" who="S0612" trans="overlap">don't they like the taste of humans?</u>
<u n="1461" who="S0428">no</u>
<u n="1462" who="S0612">cheeky fuckers</u>
<u n="1463" who="S0428">no they think we're seals</u>
<u n="1464" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1465" who="S0612">cheers sharks oh seals they're so cute as well</u>
<u n="1466" who="S0428">oh they're so cute</u>
<u n="1467" who="S0612">I love seals</u>
<u n="1468" who="S0428">we saw a seal in Ireland</u>
<u n="1469" who="S0610">little heads</u>
<u n="1470" who="S0612">yeah <unclear/> in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1471" who="S0610" trans="overlap"><unclear>bald heads</unclear></u>
<u n="1472" who="S0428">if you go out in <anon type="place"/> you see like hundreds they're amazing</u>
<u n="1473" who="S0612">that's good cos I think seals have got a lot of enemies</u>
<u n="1474" who="S0428">oh I love em and otters</u>
<u n="1475" who="S0612">polar bears eat them too er</u>
<u n="1476" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="1477" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">and orcas those black and white killer whale things</u>
<u n="1478" who="S0610">yeah I was just <trunc>l</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="1479" who="S0612">they eat they literally eat the on you watch this Hunt it's erm beautiful and I love David Attenborough but they like come up to the seashore to try and get seals and they kind of launch into this pre-planned attack of like getting the pups as they're like</u>
<u n="1480" who="S0610" trans="overlap">they're very intelligent aren't they?</u>
<u n="1481" who="S0612">but then they can beach themselves and then it's like well that's your own fault but then</u>
<u n="1482" who="S0610"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1483" who="S0428">they</u>
<u n="1484" who="S0612">it's not really</u>
<u n="1485" who="S0428" trans="overlap">recently they've stopped like cos they used to keep killer whales in captivity didn't they? and I watched a documentary did you see that?</u>
<u n="1486" who="S0612">no but is that where Seaworld in America?</u>
<u n="1487" who="S0428"><unclear>fuck</unclear> yeah it was just I <trunc>rea</trunc></u>
<u n="1488" who="S0610">oh no</u>
<u n="1489" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I was crying</u>
<u n="1490" who="S0610">I have not</u>
<u n="1491" who="S0428">I was crying</u>
<u n="1492" who="S0610">I can't take that</u>
<u n="1493" who="S0428">but I think now they've stopped</u>
<u n="1494" who="S0612" trans="overlap">it's like Free Willy</u>
<u n="1495" who="S0428">they've stopped a lot of the killer whales in captivity after that documentary</u>
<u n="1496" who="S0610" trans="overlap">after the documentary I'm so glad jesus</u>
<u n="1497" who="S0428">oh</u>
<u n="1498" who="S0612">I don't see it's it's sad isn't it that <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> that's for entertainment</u>
<u n="1499" who="S0428">mm</u>
<u n="1500" who="S0612">but fortunately my parents never and I'm glad they didn't because you kind of go from what your parents like if they're gonna take you to Sea Life centre or something you're gonna go</u>
<u n="1501" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="1502" who="S0612">but I'm so glad that they never took us to anything like circuses or</u>
<u n="1503" who="S0428">no</u>
<u n="1504" who="S0612">any er thing like in America where they do those shows</u>
<u n="1505" who="S0610">it's awful yeah</u>
<u n="1506" who="S0428">I felt really bad in the Oceanogrfic in Valencia I didn't like it when I saw er seeing those dolphins and</u>
<u n="1507" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah when you see like I remember like seeing quite like a not a huge whale but a whale</u>
<u n="1508" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah in a smallest space it was so sad but then it's nice to see them I dunno it's</u>
<u n="1509" who="S0610">but it's it's nice to for us to see them but</u>
<u n="1510" who="S0428"><vocal desc="sigh"/> not for them to be there</u>
<u n="1511" who="S0610">yeah it's got nothing to do with us why they exist <pause dur="short"/> humans beings are fucking knobs</u>
<u n="1512" who="S0428">imagine if they</u>
<u n="1513" who="S0612" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1514" who="S0428">collected us and put us in cages <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1515" who="S0610">I know</u>
<u n="1516" who="S0428">we'd be mental</u>
<u n="1517" who="S0610">the problem is with human beings and I</u>
<u n="1518" who="S0612" trans="overlap">we'd turn on each other</u>
<u n="1519" who="S0610" trans="overlap">I do I must say the Bible does er not the Bible religion also like makes you think that as well that men own the earth but really the earth is not it doesn't own us but the er the earth is <trunc>w</trunc>we're living on the earth basically what am I gonna try and say? <pause dur="short"/> we're not the king of the earth and we don't own it we just happen to be living on this earth and its <trunc>inhab</trunc> it's allowing us to inhabit it like it's</u>
<u n="1520" who="S0428" trans="overlap">and we're like quite high up the chain</u>
<u n="1521" who="S0610">it's giving us the conditions to be able to live on earth but we don't own it we don't own Mother Earth do we? it's not and er we don't own it more than a whale does or a seal or whatever</u>
<u n="1522" who="S0612">mm no</u>
<u n="1523" who="S0610" trans="overlap">like we're all equal animals on this earth</u>
<u n="1524" who="S0612"><unclear>this er the <trunc>p</trunc> but er</unclear> the funny thing is that humans only do because of cowardice because guns guns control populations really but it's a cowardly weapon humans actually wouldn't be able to survive a lot of them wouldn't be able to survive in the wilderness</u>
<u n="1525" who="S0428">no of course not no</u>
<u n="1526" who="S0612">we wouldn't we're actually not that great at survival now because we've got lazy so actually if they took all the weapons away we'd be screwed</u>
<u n="1527" who="S0610">yeah I know but we think we have this like</u>
<u n="1528" who="S0612">and they can bomb</u>
<u n="1529" who="S0610" trans="overlap">mortal right</u>
<u n="1530" who="S0612">bomb each other from thousands of miles away what's the kind of that's cowardly</u>
<u n="1531" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="1532" who="S0610">but we think we have this mortal right that we own this earth and we do not own it and that's what's sad because we then we think we think we have the right over all animals and think we can kill them and there's no comeuppance and we think we can do whatever we like it's disgusting</u>
<u n="1533" who="S0612">I think the world is <trunc>cha</trunc> I think more and more people are <trunc>bec</trunc> like going more towards animal rights they are</u>
<u n="1534" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="1535" who="S0612">like things like Facebook I think help <unclear>but</unclear> when you see these different erm it's like that shooting of the lion and er</u>
<u n="1536" who="S0610" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1537" who="S0612">and like er that happens everywhere like</u>
<u n="1538" who="S0610">I know</u>
<u n="1539" who="S0612">hunting happens in this country but the more <trunc>visu</trunc> like I think more and more people are kind of against animal cruelty</u>
<u n="1540" who="S0610">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="1541" who="S0428" trans="overlap">then you think there are so many like countries that are so massive that you know don't respect it and</u>
<u n="1542" who="S0612">mm</u>
<u n="1543" who="S0428">I mean like whaling happens in Norway and they're like so civilised</u>
<u n="1544" who="S0612">yeah</u>
<u n="1545" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="1546" who="S0612">and they have that yeah</u>
<u n="1547" who="S0428">like they're so that's like the the country on this planet that's so broad thinking</u>
<u n="1548" who="S0610">I read this interview with the head of new head of Greenpeace oh no well the head of Greenpeace is stepping down and he's being replaced oh yeah yeah so it's the new head of Greenpeace and he's like Greenpeace environmental erm our campaigns the worst mistake ever to have been made is that it's about saving the planet it's not about saving the planet when we get extinct when we become extinct the planet's gonna live on it's just gonna <trunc>re</trunc><trunc>re</trunc><trunc>re</trunc>resuscitate and revive and</u>
<u n="1549" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="1550" who="S0610">it'll live on cos it's a powerful thing but it's about not about saving the planet it's about helping people live in harmony with the earth for for as long as possible without basically making it an <trunc>in</trunc><trunc>in</trunc>inhabitable place and that was interesting because lots of people when you see environment oh shut up like we don't give a shit about the animals or whatever but it's not about that it's about making it habitable for us for as long as possible</u>
<u n="1551" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1552" who="S0610">and I don't think people realise that you have to work with the environment rather than think you can rape it for all its worth dunno</u>
<u n="1553" who="S0612">that's why I like it when grass grows through tarmac</u>
<u n="1554" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="1555" who="S0612" trans="overlap">that's a very good example of <trunc>n</trunc>nature being more powerful than man</u>
<u n="1556" who="S0610">that's true</u>
<u n="1557" who="S0612" trans="overlap">and also it just needs to make a tornado and it's wiped out nearly a population or a volcano or some tsunami they <trunc>g</trunc> it's</u>
<u n="1558" who="S0428" trans="overlap">weather bomb</u>
<u n="1559" who="S0612">weather bomb</u>
<u n="1560" who="S0610" trans="overlap">I think it'll be a virus that wipes as out</u>
<u n="1561" who="S0612">there's too many human beings</u>
<u n="1562" who="S0610">there are really kind of scary <pause dur="short"/> anyway doomsday</u>
<u n="1563" who="S0428">yeah let's not talk about that</u>
<u n="1564" who="S0612">so do you think my journey's okay then without?</u>
<u n="1565" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah there's no erm</u>
<u n="1566" who="S0612">can you chuck me my telephone please?</u>
<u n="1567" who="S0428">your mobolio?</u>
<u n="1568" who="S0612">thank you for my mobolio</u>
<u n="1569" who="S0610" trans="overlap">no if you want some toast serve yourself</u>
<u n="1570" who="S0428">yeah I'm gonna gonna get some I think <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="1571" who="S0610">or porridge</u>
<u n="1572" who="S0428">I'm not a big fan of porridge these days</u>
<u n="1573" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="1574" who="S0428">I'm not I'm just not hungry I might have some in about in about quarter of an hour <unclear>at the moment I'm alright</unclear></u>
<u n="1575" who="S0610">make sure you take a lime with you</u>
<u n="1576" who="S0612"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1577" who="S0610">I'm getting upset with these limes going off</u>
<u n="1578" who="S0428">where did you get them from?</u>
<u n="1579" who="S0610">they just were brought over on New Year's Eve and weren't used so they're a little bit old now</u>
<u n="1580" who="S0428">that's alright I've got some from before Christmas</u>
<u n="1581" who="S0610">they're just going all brown</u>
<u n="1582" who="S0428">oh nice thanks</u>
<u n="1583" who="S0610">we never had my gin did we?</u>
<u n="1584" who="S0428">save it for next time</u>
<u n="1585" who="S0610"><unclear>no</unclear> so I looked up flights to Valencia</u>
<u n="1586" who="S0612">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="1587" who="S0610" trans="overlap">just saying</u>
<u n="1588" who="S0612">when did you do that?</u>
<u n="1589" who="S0610">this morning</u>
<u n="1590" who="S0612">oh clever</u>
<u n="1591" who="S0610">sixty pounds</u>
<u n="1592" who="S0612">return? obviously</u>
<u n="1593" who="S0610" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1594" who="S0612">yeah yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1595" who="S0610">from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1596" who="S0612">okay I need to speak to my dad and see if he can give me a lift to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> I'm not sure</u>
<u n="1597" who="S0610" trans="overlap">will he do that? that's quite far</u>
<u n="1598" who="S0612">he <trunc>di</trunc> yeah he did it <trunc>f</trunc>for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s wedding <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1599" who="S0610">what?</u>
<u n="1600" who="S0612">he took me to <anon type="place"/> airport like</u>
<u n="1601" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh my god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1602" who="S0612" trans="overlap">five A M in the morning he always does it</u>
<u n="1603" who="S0428" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="1604" who="S0612" trans="overlap">but I take advantage I shouldn't</u>
<u n="1605" who="S0428">if you if you the other thing you can do is you can just get the train to <anon type="place"/> or the bus and then you can just</u>
<u n="1606" who="S0610" trans="overlap">the night before</u>
<u n="1607" who="S0428">and get one of those</u>
<u n="1608" who="S0612" trans="overlap">I've never been to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1609" who="S0610">we're staying at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s the night before</u>
<u n="1610" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah and you're so welcome to stay and then we can all go you can have a look round <anon type="place"/> and then</u>
<u n="1611" who="S0612" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1612" who="S0428">we can all go</u>
<u n="1613" who="S0612">okay what date is this again please?</u>
<u n="1614" who="S0610">so the flight is the fifth but it's at seven AM so we're going to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s on the fourth of Feb</u>
<u n="1615" who="S0612" trans="overlap">fourth of February</u>
<u n="1616" who="S0610">yeah so we'll go up in the night after work but</u>
<u n="1617" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1618" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> in the middle of the night <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1619" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="1620" who="S0612">it's the only the only acceptable time to get up early</u>
<u n="1621" who="S0610">is there enough room for all of us by the way in your dad's?</u>
<u n="1622" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's fine</u>
<u n="1623" who="S0612">erm</u>
<u n="1624" who="S0428">but you <trunc>c</trunc> if you fancy coming up I finish work at half three so</u>
<u n="1625" who="S0612">cool</u>
<u n="1626" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><shift new="singing"/> Valencia <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1627" who="S0610">and then we're coming back it's like eleven AM on Monday morning</u>
<u n="1628" who="S0428">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="1629" who="S0612" trans="overlap">and also it's quite easy Valencia so if for <trunc>examp</trunc></u>
<u n="1630" who="S0610">yeah it's so easy isn't it?</u>
<u n="1631" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="1632" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">cos when you get there it's like twenty minutes</u>
<u n="1633" who="S0612">cos if my dad's a bit like nah then I could I could well I could get the train to <anon type="place"/> blah or I could go to <anon type="place"/> if I've got and meet you there</u>
<u n="1634" who="S0610">oh yeah well I dunno how much the flights are then</u>
<u n="1635" who="S0612">no</u>
<u n="1636" who="S0428">I don't think there are flights to <anon type="place"/> this time of year to Valencia</u>
<u n="1637" who="S0612">are there not?</u>
<u n="1638" who="S0428">no</u>
<u n="1639" who="S0610">there could be you never know</u>
<u n="1640" who="S0612"><anon type="place"/>'s rubbish</u>
<u n="1641" who="S0610">you never know</u>
<u n="1642" who="S0428">but yeah</u>
<u n="1643" who="S0612">but I know I can remember you literally get into Valencia and then you're on a tube</u>
<u n="1644" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="1645" who="S0612">all the way into wherever you're going</u>
<u n="1646" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="1647" who="S0428" trans="overlap">or like we could all like it there's so many of us it'd be cheaper to get a taxi we could get a big taxi</u>
<u n="1648" who="S0610">oh you mean on this side? or on the other side?</u>
<u n="1649" who="S0428">on the other side it's so expensive</u>
<u n="1650" who="S0610" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="1651" who="S0612"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1652" who="S0428">the</u>
<u n="1653" who="S0612"><shift new="singing"/> on the other side <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="1654" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1655" who="S0610">the taxi driver was laughing at us when we were doing that</u>
<u n="1656" who="S0428">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1657" who="S0612">yeah er taxi drivers must be a really fun job really like</u>
<u n="1658" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1659" who="S0612">just er I mean sometimes not so much if somebody's being horrible but erm</u>
<u n="1660" who="S0610" trans="overlap">they <trunc>mu</trunc>they must listen to some trashy conversations though</u>
<u n="1661" who="S0612" trans="overlap">some funny conversations</u>
<u n="1662" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1663" who="S0610">erm</u>
<u n="1664" who="S0428">I always want to make it into a TV show but I think it's already been done apparently</u>
<u n="1665" who="S0610">right you should totally do it</u>
<u n="1666" who="S0612" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <unclear>really good chats</unclear></u>
<u n="1667" who="S0428"><unclear>oh go on come</unclear> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1668" who="S0612"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1669" who="S0610">it's cheaper with <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="1670" who="S0612">I know but it's just</u>
<u n="1671" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1672" who="S0612">oh I know</u>
<u n="1673" who="S0610" trans="overlap">I know I know I know yeah but</u>
<u n="1674" who="S0428" trans="overlap">it would be so amazing to have you there</u>
<u n="1675" who="S0610">I wonder if we could like</u>
<u n="1676" who="S0428">we can cook</u>
<u n="1677" who="S0610">I wonder if we can get a</u>
<u n="1678" who="S0612" trans="overlap">I don't want to be the unemployed annoying person that can't</u>
<u n="1679" who="S0610">no</u>
<u n="1680" who="S0612" trans="overlap">you can't do what you want because there's me</u>
<u n="1681" who="S0610">no cos it's</u>
<u n="1682" who="S0428" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="1683" who="S0610">cheap anyway it's not like we're gonna be doing anything</u>
<u n="1684" who="S0428">it <trunc>w</trunc> like what we love doing in Valencia is is just free it's just being <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1685" who="S0612">what's that drink out there that er?</u>
<u n="1686" who="S0428">Agua de Valencia</u>
<u n="1687" who="S0610">yeah that's it</u>
<u n="1688" who="S0612" trans="overlap">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1689" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="1690" who="S0612">I forgot about that</u>
<u n="1691" who="S0428" trans="overlap">we can we can make it at home</u>
<u n="1692" who="S0610">but even when you buy it it's like you know cheap as <unclear>sangria</unclear></u>
<u n="1693" who="S0612" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1694" who="S0428" trans="overlap">er honestly the other day I went out and there were like four people and I bought everyone tapas with drink and it came to ten euro and they were like shall we give you money? I was like it's fine that's like</u>
<u n="1695" who="S0612" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="1696" who="S0428">eight quid</u>
<u n="1697" who="S0612">that is amazing and it's proper <trunc>t</trunc> Spanish oh</u>
<u n="1698" who="S0610">we need to book our Airbnb mind you</u>
<u n="1699" who="S0428" trans="overlap">it's obviously yeah it's so cheap <pause dur="short"/> if you wanna invite anyone else</u>
<u n="1700" who="S0610" trans="overlap">and the and the Airbnbs are cheap as hell like I've been looking at them like</u>
<u n="1701" who="S0428">yeah they're gonna be like ten euros ten pounds a night</u>
<u n="1702" who="S0612">yeah we did Airbnb in Cape Verde</u>
<u n="1703" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="1704" who="S0612">and er</u>
<u n="1705" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I'd love to go there</u>
<u n="1706" who="S0612">it was like for two weeks it was like two hundred pound the accommodation it was just the flights which were pricey</u>
<u n="1707" who="S0610" trans="overlap">that's so good</u>
<u n="1708" who="S0612">even though there were so many cockroaches I nearly had a nervous breakdown</u>
<u n="1709" who="S0610">oh bless you</u>
<u n="1710" who="S0612">poor <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> literally this holiday cos this lovely and I pretty much ruined it by cos I couldn't go out at night time</u>
<u n="1711" who="S0610">oh bless you</u>
<u n="1712" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>oh no</unclear></u>
<u n="1713" who="S0612">it's really <trunc>pathe</trunc> it's so pathetic it's and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> also if there was one on me she would just pick it up she's so unafraid of bugs well actually no she probably is but it's just she doesn't want them</u>
<u n="1714" who="S0428" trans="overlap">they climb on you?</u>
<u n="1715" who="S0612">I er er er they were everywhere so the reason is is because when I was about my first year just before we were supposed to go to Venice</u>
<u n="1716" who="S0610">oh <trunc>Mala</trunc> erm</u>
<u n="1717" who="S0612">my</u>
<u n="1718" who="S0610">Magaluf</u>
<u n="1719" who="S0612">yeah ex went to work in Magaluf for the summer so I was like well I don't really wanna be stuck here by myself type thing so <trunc>bef</trunc> and also I needed to earn a lot of money to go to Venice with so I flew out there and then er <trunc>wi</trunc>within a week I'd found a job just working in <anon type="place"/> beach bar so I did like the ice creams and the takeaways and</u>
<u n="1720" who="S0610" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="1721" who="S0612">got to work there which was cool cos they were all Spanish and it was quite fun like</u>
<u n="1722" who="S0428" trans="overlap">is that er is that is that Majorca?</u>
<u n="1723" who="S0612">yeah no <trunc>Mag</trunc> yeah yeah Magaluf</u>
<u n="1724" who="S0610">Majorca yeah</u>
<u n="1725" who="S0612">erm and it was great but at night time it wasn't actually that great in the end in fact it was shit and I er should've come home erm mind you I was so cross because my erm <vocal desc="misc"/> er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had a different work shift so I'd work like from nine till five and then every day and then have like the evening off but my erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> worked like shifts so one week he'd be working</u>
<u n="1726" who="S0428">what was he doing?</u>
<u n="1727" who="S0612">he was a chef in a the <trunc>re</trunc> er</u>
<u n="1728" who="S0428" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="1729" who="S0612">yeah I mean not a great one like a Wetherspoons microwave place but erm so he'd like one week he'd be there at night time and then the next he'd be working till like midnight or one o'clock in the morning so I'd be sat in this like apartment building and it was quite nice we weren't in like the hotel bit we had a an apartment up here with a pool and then the night would come and</u>
<u n="1730" who="S0610" trans="overlap">then the cockroaches would come out</u>
<u n="1731" who="S0612" trans="overlap">and then <unclear>you'd just see it</unclear></u>
<u n="1732" who="S0610">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1733" who="S0612">and I was like what the fuck is that? and then I just saw this and they were big ones</u>
<u n="1734" who="S0610">yeah</u>
<u n="1735" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah they have <unclear/> ones</u>
<u n="1736" who="S0612" trans="overlap">they were like that big and they just kept <trunc>w</trunc> there were so many of them so</u>
<u n="1737" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1738" who="S0612">er and I saw one jump off here one was there</u>
<u n="1739" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's horrible</u>
<u n="1740" who="S0612" trans="overlap">they were just running round and outside like</u>
<u n="1741" who="S0610" trans="overlap">that is horrible I can</u>
<u n="1742" who="S0612" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1743" who="S0610" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1744" who="S0612" trans="overlap">and so I just had to collect them in these glasses cos I didn't know what else to do with them but then I was literally I couldn't sleep because I was worried I it got to a stage where I became so scared of them that I was duct-taping every doorway in this house so they couldn't come in under the door</u>
<u n="1745" who="S0610">oh</u>
<u n="1746" who="S0612">and then I was duct-taping myself in in my bedroom every night and then one night <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> brought one in and he was like we were just like there and then he suddenly like er jumped up and was like and I was like what the fuck? and then you just saw this big black beetle on him and I was like ah so I run into the next person's room cos I <trunc>w</trunc> you have to go through this other person's room to get to our room it was horrible and I <trunc>ra</trunc> and he was saying what the fuck? with his girlfriend <vocal desc="misc"/> and <unclear>I was just</unclear> oh they were everywhere and then if you</u>
<u n="1747" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh my god <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="1748" who="S0612" trans="overlap">cleaned there was just dead cockroaches everywhere under all the furniture</u>
<u n="1749" who="S0610" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="1750" who="S0612">cos it was a boy's place and they don't clean</u>
<u n="1751" who="S0428">oh</u>
<u n="1752" who="S0610">that is literally the worst story ever</u>
<u n="1753" who="S0612">I hated it and ever since I've just</u>
<u n="1754" who="S0428">yeah awful</u>
<u n="1755" who="S0612">but then I did find cockroach killer</u>
<u n="1756" who="S0610">I've killed one like that and it just <trunc>l</trunc> oh it wasn't pleasant <unclear/></u>
<u n="1757" who="S0428">did erm do you ever hear from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like?</u>
<u n="1758" who="S0612">no ever no</u>
<u n="1759" who="S0428">really? like do you know like you don't know what he's doing? or?</u>
<u n="1760" who="S0612">I know he's move he lived in <anon type="place"/> for a while but he moved back to <anon type="place"/> which is quite <trunc>weir</trunc></u>
<u n="1761" who="S0428" trans="overlap">is that where you grew up?</u>
<u n="1762" who="S0612">yeah and it's also like where my <trunc>p</trunc> family kind of live now and I'm just always like paranoid I mean it doesn't matter cos it was like six seven</u>
<u n="1763" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1764" who="S0612">eight years ago but just <unclear>like I</unclear> could bump into him and then it'd just be really awkward</u>
<u n="1765" who="S0610">especially if you were with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oh I'm just gonna go and see if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s awake I heard some movement just then</u>
<u n="1766" who="S0612">I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> must've got wasted last night because I haven't heard from him yet and it's eleven o'clock</u>
<u n="1767" who="S0610"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1768" who="S0428">is it eleven? <vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="1769" who="S0612">yeah</u>
<u n="1770" who="S0428">oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1771" who="S0610">I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s taken the newspapers upstairs and he's reading them all upstairs</u>
<u n="1772" who="S0428">really? <vocal desc="laugh"/> cheeky</u>
<u n="1773" who="S0610" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1774" who="S0612">one of my friends has gone on honeymoon to Mauritius</u>
<u n="1775" who="S0428">oh that's another nice place <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> went there</u>
<u n="1776" who="S0612">wow</u>
<u n="1777" who="S0428">with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s parents <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="1778" who="S0612">look at that little face</u>
<u n="1779" who="S0428">oh a pug</u>
<u n="1780" who="S0612">so cute I can't wait to get one</u>
<u n="1781" who="S0428">when are you gonna get one?</u>
<u n="1782" who="S0612"><vocal desc="sigh"/> well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s being a pain and like trying to hold back erm which is really annoying</u>
<u n="1783" who="S0428">what's the reason for holding back?</u>
<u n="1784" who="S0612">he just gets like he thinks that we haven't <trunc>r</trunc> like properly had time to chill since we got married and <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> he wants to just chill but by the time that we like er he wants to get one we'll be racing and that means we go away every month to go racing</u>
<u n="1785" who="S0428">what's what's er what kind of racing?</u>
<u n="1786" who="S0612">er</u>
<u n="1787" who="S0428" trans="overlap">in the car?</u>
<u n="1788" who="S0612">erm <vocal desc="misc"/> circuit racing so just like MR two? Toyota MR two?</u>
<u n="1789" who="S0428">I don't know what that means</u>
<u n="1790" who="S0612">it's er it's just a type of car but it's just good fun <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s obsessed with racing</u>
<u n="1791" who="S0428">yeah you said that he loves his cars</u>
<u n="1792" who="S0612">so</u>
<u n="1793" who="S0428">but could you take the dog?</u>
<u n="1794" who="S0612">no cos it's too loud so many engines</u>
<u n="1795" who="S0428">could you like so you'd go do you go every month?</u>
<u n="1796" who="S0612">yeah once a month over the summer it starts in March and runs till erm</u>
<u n="1797" who="S0428">could you not go a couple of months while you had the dog to like look after it?</u>
<u n="1798" who="S0612">yeah I think that's what I'll have to do I'd rather stay and look after little Ralph he's gonna be a puppy he'll be like that big</u>
<u n="1799" who="S0428">how much are pugs?</u>
<u n="1800" who="S0612">er they're quite expensive I think they're like eight hundred to a thousand pound</u>
<u n="1801" who="S0428">really?</u>
<u n="1802" who="S0612">but you can get the bitches which are twelve hundred pounds</u>
<u n="1803" who="S0428">wow it's so much money isn't it for a dog?</u>
<u n="1804" who="S0612">I know for a <trunc>s</trunc> it's they're also really small so oh I just oh I saw one yesterday at the market and I nearly freaked out they're just so cute but they're not to everybody which is funny</u>
<u n="1805" who="S0428">I just always worry that they're like overbred</u>
<u n="1806" who="S0612">yeah which I think they are so they're not very good genetically any more</u>
<u n="1807" who="S0610">do you guys have any painkillers?</u>
<u n="1808" who="S0428">no</u>
<u n="1809" who="S0610">do you have any?</u>
<u n="1810" who="S0612">no sorry I've got allergy tablets</u>
<u n="1811" who="S0610"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1812" who="S0428">are you why? are you?</u>
<u n="1813" who="S0612" trans="overlap">is he not very well?</u>
<u n="1814" who="S0610">no he feels really sick and he's got a really bad headache</u>
<u n="1815" who="S0428">he didn't drink that much</u>
<u n="1816" who="S0610">no <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> happened he thinks he's getting <unclear/></u>
<u n="1817" who="S0612">oh bless</u>
<u n="1818" who="S0610">mm <unclear/></u>
<u n="1819" who="S0428">pardon?</u>
<u n="1820" who="S0610">oh <unclear>what's this</unclear>? allergy tablets <unclear>oh look at that</unclear> those aren't yours are they?</u>
<u n="1821" who="S0612">nope <pause dur="short"/> no I think my I think it's my <trunc>per</trunc> er cos I had to like take them all the time for some reason at the moment I reckon it's cos they're drowsy as well which is why I fall asleep everywhere</u>
<u n="1822" who="S0610">yeah but they probably are</u>
<u n="1823" who="S0428">some of them are some allergy <trunc>tab</trunc>allergy tablets</u>
<u n="1824" who="S0610">mm</u>
<u n="1825" who="S0428">oh poor <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1826" who="S0610">don't know what to do about that <pause dur="short"/> er where will we have some?</u>
<u n="1827" who="S0612">could oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1828" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh hi there</u>
<u n="1829" who="S0610">you don't have any painkillers do you?</u>
<u n="1830" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">er <trunc>s</trunc>some paracetamol?</u>
<u n="1831" who="S0610">yeah do you?</u>
<u n="1832" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">you know what? I think I do</u>
<u n="1833" who="S0610">oh er amazing <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1834" who="S0428" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
	
	</body>
</text>
