<text id="SR96">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:27:24</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-02-26</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0167 S0378</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>A pub in London</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Relationships, food, work, studying, family, future plans, domestic issues, birthdays</topics>
		<activity>Catching up over tea</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T06</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0167">
				<exactage>24</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Ashford, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>South East/Kent</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Romney Marsh, Kent</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>southeast</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Copywriter</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0378">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Oxford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>none</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Streathan, London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>unspecified</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>unspecified</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Student/ part time survey programmer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0167">It's just a diary erm so I thought I'd use this for the year and then I've still got my Filofax at home and find some inserts for the year and start using that again so yeah I do like it and I've got a picture of <unclear/></u>
<u n="2" who="S0378">oh look at you guys</u>
<u n="3" who="S0167">that's a <anon type="place"/> beach</u>
<u n="4" who="S0378">oh yeah thank you <pause dur="short"/> three pounds forty for two pancakes</u>
<u n="5" who="S0167">you can have some cheesy chips if you want</u>
<u n="6" who="S0378">oh my god</u>
<u n="7" who="S0167">feel free to all my cheesy chips I've got loads of food in my bag so don't feel like I'm going to go hungry okay definitely won't</u>
<u n="8" who="S0378">that is so lovely</u>
<u n="9" who="S0167">yeah that's when he came to visit me in June cos I was only back in June between coming back from Germany and going to Peru so that me in that time</u>
<u n="10" who="S0378">ah</u>
<u n="11" who="S0167">and stuff</u>
<u n="12" who="S0378">but yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0167">this job interview for there's a festival in Yorkshire called the Deer Shed festival and it's they wanted a press and marketing intern paid for the four months running up to the festival the festival's in July</u>
<u n="14" who="S0378">mm</u>
<u n="15" who="S0167">and</u>
<u n="16" who="S0378">that's amazing four months</u>
<u n="17" who="S0167">and I got selected for the interview and I was like oh my god I wasn't expecting that in Yorkshire</u>
<u n="18" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="19" who="S0167">anyway so I went anyway just to see what is was like so I went up to Yorkshire in the morning and came back in the afternoon</u>
<u n="20" who="S0378">oh my god</u>
<u n="21" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so like three and a half hours each way</u>
<u n="22" who="S0378">really?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0167">which wasn't as much as I thought it was going to be I thought it was going to be six hours each way but it was really good actually erm so yeah I was I was in Yorkshire yesterday the interview went quite well I think actually but I'm not sure if I want to relocate to Yorkshire for four months and then come back and be at square one be back at square one with no job it would be the pay is only national minimum wage and I'd have to you know have to pay for somewhere to stay while I'm up there</u>
<u n="24" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="25" who="S0167">and so I don't know if I'd come back with any more money although it would be like a really cool experience like working on a festival but if it was down here I'd do it but seeing as it's up there I don't</u>
<u n="26" who="S0378">do you have anyone you could stay with?</u>
<u n="27" who="S0167">no I don't know anyone up there it's also like do I really want to be away in Yorkshire for so long?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0167">away from home</u>
<u n="30" who="S0378">is it full time?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0167">yeah it's full time for the whole four months and I'm working up to you're on up to the festival and the festival itself and the job itself sounds like amazing</u>
<u n="32" who="S0378">I'm going to have to take them back</u>
<u n="33" who="S0167">are they horrible?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0378">mm and that's golden syrup it's not maple syrup</u>
<u n="35" who="S0167">yeah that's definitely something about that's shit</u>
<u n="36" who="S0378">I'm really sorry I hope this isn't embarrassing</u>
<u n="37" who="S0167">no</u>
<u n="38" who="S0378">it's like really clumpy it's like really chewy as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="39" who="S0167">look like honey</u>
<u n="40" who="S0378">yeah I don't know sorry</u>
<u n="41" who="S0167">that's okay</u>
<u n="42" who="S0378">gonna have to do it <event desc="sound of restaurant"/> <pause dur="long"/> sorry</u>
<u n="43" who="S0167">are you getting a refund?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0378">yeah they're really nice</u>
<u n="45" who="S0167">getting something else? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0378">they're really nice they were like oh what's that? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0167">I told you I brought food with me thought we'd have a picnic with our tea</u>
<u n="48" who="S0378">amazing erm yeah pancakes so</u>
<u n="49" who="S0167">so are you not going to like order something else then?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0378">maybe I should</u>
<u n="51" who="S0167">I mean obviously feel free to my cheesy chips have as many as you want</u>
<u n="52" who="S0378">don't worry I was mm I don't know cos I'm I'm not like hungry hungry do you have an oyster card?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0378">oh don't do that chewing gum inside it</u>
<u n="55" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> sorry I was like too much chewing gum in there</u>
<u n="56" who="S0378">no this was from <anon type="place"/> cos my mum lives in <anon type="place"/> and I went to go see her at the weekend</u>
<u n="57" who="S0167">how are her studies going?</u>
<u n="58" who="S0378">oh my god she's almost dying from it</u>
<u n="59" who="S0167">ah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0378">she is so</u>
<u n="61" who="S0167">it will be so worth it though at the end imagine does she want to be a lawyer?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0378">she's actually coming up for an interview</u>
<u n="63" who="S0167">oh wow so she's at the end of her third year</u>
<u n="64" who="S0378">mm she's at the end of her third year second term so she's just got so much work</u>
<u n="65" who="S0167">dissertation</u>
<u n="66" who="S0378">mm no she's got like three twenty page research projects though and like a bunch of essays as well so it's really super hardcore</u>
<u n="67" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="68" who="S0378">like writing erm but yeah she's coming up for an interview in a temple do you know it? in a temple</u>
<u n="69" who="S0167">no</u>
<u n="70" who="S0378">it's this <anon type="place"/> in London and it's this really really old like centuries old kind of law school type establishment</u>
<u n="71" who="S0167">okay</u>
<u n="72" who="S0378">for lawyers to go and train to go to the bar to become barristers yes please</u>
<u n="73" who="S0167">thank you oh okay cheesy chips</u>
<u n="74" who="S0378">no I'm good honestly</u>
<u n="75" who="S0167">have some cheesy chips</u>
<u n="76" who="S0378">erm so yeah she's doing that really exciting but I still want to know about this stuff in what are you doing in Peru? were you with a family? where did you meet <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? is it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0167"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0378"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="79" who="S0167">he's German I met him in Germany</u>
<u n="80" who="S0378">mm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0167">cos when I was out there working as a language teacher</u>
<u n="82" who="S0378">mm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0167">yeah so I was out there working as a language assistant and I got a kind of weekend job as well cos I wanted a bit of extra money I was being paid quite well to be a language assistant but I just wanted more money erm and I got a job as a waitress in this hotel restaurant in town and his parents owned the restaurant and he was a chef there and so one day one day cos I hadn't thought of him in this way until then he was just like my manager</u>
<u n="84" who="S0378">he was your manager</u>
<u n="85" who="S0167">he kind of runs it with his parents like his parents</u>
<u n="86" who="S0378">does he own it?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0167">yeah erm and so yeah so anyway one day he took me by surprise and he asked me out and I was like erm oh okay so anyway we went on a couple of dates and that was really fun erm now we decided to stay together even after I'd left Germany and erm so yeah we're still together now and we've been together since beginning of May last year and he came out to visit me in Peru</u>
<u n="88" who="S0378">mm</u>
<u n="89" who="S0167">and we climbed the Machu Picchu together</u>
<u n="90" who="S0378">oh yeah</u>
<u n="91" who="S0167">to see the pictures?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0378">yeah I did yeah so nice</u>
<u n="93" who="S0167">and that was really cool and he was with me for ten days in Peru and erm then I just went to visit him we talk on Skype every day and like Whatsapp and stuff it's quite easy now with like Whatsapp and that</u>
<u n="94" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0167">we can just talk for free</u>
<u n="96" who="S0378">are you like planning to move or live together or to be in the same country?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0167">the problem is he wants to stay in this town called <anon type="place"/> which is a really lovely town but kind of in the middle of nowhere and there's not really much going on it's a lovely historical medieval town with cobbled streets but it's like you know</u>
<u n="98" who="S0378">sounds pretty logical but it's not</u>
<u n="99" who="S0167">yeah it's lovely to visit you know lovely for a local but not somewhere I'd want to go and live like I I couldn't go out there there's no opportunities for me unless I want to be a waitress or something to work in <anon type="place"/> erm so the problem is he's just bought the brewery cos they brew their own beer</u>
<u n="100" who="S0378">wow</u>
<u n="101" who="S0167">he's just bought the brewery from his dad and he's expanding it and he's got his own side business on their hotel and he's bought this building and he's going to extend it by three times the size and put all his big machines in there and brew all the beer and sell it like across the country at the moment they just sell it at the hotel</u>
<u n="102" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="103" who="S0167">but he wants to market it across the country so he's got his own little business he's setting up</u>
<u n="104" who="S0378">he wants you to work in it?</u>
<u n="105" who="S0167">well no he hasn't said that but he's got no like plans to cos ideally I'd like him to come to London and live with me</u>
<u n="106" who="S0378">so why can't he just own the business and get someone else to do all the grafting?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0167">I don't know that hasn't crossed his mind I don't know whether he wants to be</u>
<u n="108" who="S0378">and then he can be franchise involved or</u>
<u n="109" who="S0167">yeah I mean that would be an idea</u>
<u n="110" who="S0378">have one in London as well</u>
<u n="111" who="S0167">problem is he still lives with like he doesn't live with his parents but he kind of does it's a weird set up like he's lived in <anon type="place"/> all his life in that same house all his life his parents own</u>
<u n="112" who="S0378">and you were like the</u>
<u n="113" who="S0167">restaurant all his life</u>
<u n="114" who="S0378">interesting like quasi exciting woman that walked into his</u>
<u n="115" who="S0167">did go away for a few years to train in France as a chef and then he came back and worked in the restaurant actually his last girlfriend was Hungarian she still works in the restaurant</u>
<u n="116" who="S0378">she still works in the restaurant oh my god</u>
<u n="117" who="S0167">she's really nice actually</u>
<u n="118" who="S0378">is that weird?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0167">mm well I kind of dished with her before I even started seeing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so we already kind of knew each other anyway and erm they'd only just broken up like a month before</u>
<u n="120" who="S0378">mm</u>
<u n="121" who="S0167">but erm yeah so she's she's really nice but they their friendship group they're still friends cos they are still in the same friendship group so they still see each other all the time</u>
<u n="122" who="S0378">how long was it like a long one or was it?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0167">two years</u>
<u n="124" who="S0378">three years two years?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0167">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0378">that's not too bad</u>
<u n="127" who="S0167">they met they met at a party he said she lived in Hungary and he lived in Germany and they did to and fro a few times and she eventually came to visit and came to live with him and got a job in his restaurant and she's been working there ever since so and then he broke up with her so she had to find a <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0378">not a life that's not what you want really and you're capable of just a lot more than waitressing been there and done there as well and it's not something I would want to go back to that would make it a bit weird</u>
<u n="129" who="S0167">so yeah I'm not really sure what we're going to do at the moment we just keep visiting each other and talking on Skype and</u>
<u n="130" who="S0378">let things happen that's the best thing to do actually let things happen organically</u>
<u n="131" who="S0167">yeah well we're going on we're going on holiday to Paris with his friends</u>
<u n="132" who="S0378">oh ah I've been thinking about Paris so much lately</u>
<u n="133" who="S0167">yeah?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0378">yeah to the extent where when I was visiting mum we sat in bed one day we were looking up all of these different Parisian houses and</u>
<u n="135" who="S0167">oh yeah</u>
<u n="136" who="S0378">French châteaus</u>
<u n="137" who="S0167">want to live in Paris?</u>
<u n="138" who="S0378">yeah I will do one day I think next year</u>
<u n="139" who="S0167">next year?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0378">oh my god</u>
<u n="141" who="S0167">I guess you can speak French can't you?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0378">that's the reason I want to go other than loving it and also feeling like maybe I need a bit of a new</u>
<u n="143" who="S0167">start</u>
<u n="144" who="S0378"><anon type="place"/> and a new start and stuff um yeah my French is so rusty now and I never use it so if I go out there and I immerse myself I'll have more of a chance of learning it and it will be handy for medicine so I've gone to the</u>
<u n="145" who="S0167">yeah definitely</u>
<u n="146" who="S0378">and also I'd want to go and work for them and my uncle has given me the offer of a lifetime</u>
<u n="147" who="S0167">what is it?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0378">I cried when he said this you know my uncle that's not an uncle but totally</u>
<u n="149" who="S0167">oh uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0378">yeah he took me under his wing</u>
<u n="151" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0378">he said he sat me down one day cos he came to visit for like an hour or two in London so we met him in London and he sat me down and he said I haven't contributed towards your education he's like put his kids through like private school and everything and he feels like I'm a child I think</u>
<u n="153" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="154" who="S0378">and so he I think he felt like he wanted to do something like that to so he said</u>
<u n="155" who="S0167">that's lovely</u>
<u n="156" who="S0378">haven't contributed towards your education but what I want to do is offer you the travel expenses and subsidise your accommodation for six months if you find a <anon type="place"/> if you find a <anon type="place"/> or an internship with Médecins Sans Frontières abroad</u>
<u n="157" who="S0167">oh that's so nice</u>
<u n="158" who="S0378">so but it has to be by January 2016 cos if I haven't found it but January 2016 then it's not the offer's not there any more</u>
<u n="159" who="S0167">why does if he have a blanket loan or something?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0378">no it's to like make me do it so so</u>
<u n="161" who="S0167">but you've got plenty of time to look haven't you?</u>
<u n="162" who="S0378">no I'm just ah just seeing all of your photos and all of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s photos</u>
<u n="163" who="S0167">travels</u>
<u n="164" who="S0378">yeah I want to travel I haven't travelled before really got I've got itchy feet now yeah and I don't just want to I want to live for a period of time somewhere</u>
<u n="165" who="S0167">I keep thinking if I get a job in Berlin that would be a good compromise cos he's only two hours south of Berlin</u>
<u n="166" who="S0378">that's a really good</u>
<u n="167" who="S0167">there's lot of opportunities in Berlin and also carry on improving my German and stuff</u>
<u n="168" who="S0378">yeah are you actually fluent now though right?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0167">yeah I'm a lot better now and I speak it every day now obviously cos I speak with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0378">in German</u>
<u n="171" who="S0167">in German not in English ever</u>
<u n="172" who="S0378">does he not speak English?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0167">he does but the only time we speak English is like when he came to visit and we were with my parents so we didn't speak any German in front of them but we do speak German together yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0378">oh I'm so happy for you it's so bless his heart what's he like what kind of person is he?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0167">he's quite like when I first met him he's got a very gentle voice and he's quite quiet and quite reserved he's not really like in your face which is why I didn't really notice him before</u>
<u n="176" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="177" who="S0167">and erm it's only once he asked me and out and I was like oh alright so I go why not? and then it turned out I had a really good time so I was yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0378">that's so cute so cute</u>
<u n="179" who="S0167">erm yeah he's I don't know he's really nice he's really gentle he's really thoughtful he's really romantic</u>
<u n="180" who="S0378">is he?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0167">I was in the office one day in Peru I just got this erm someone came over to me and said oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> there's someone at the door for you and I was like okay so he didn't fly all the way over I was like who's this? bit weird so I opened the door and it was a man with a big bunch of flowers</u>
<u n="182" who="S0378">oh</u>
<u n="183" who="S0167">and he'd ordered a big bunch of flowers to be delivered to my office from this really cute romantic note like I love you so much</u>
<u n="184" who="S0378">oh my god</u>
<u n="185" who="S0167">the most wonderful girl in the world and it's like I walked into the office and everyone was like they were absolutely humungous</u>
<u n="186" who="S0378">oh my god that's so lovely though isn't it?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0167">it wasn't for a reason he just did it</u>
<u n="188" who="S0378">bless him</u>
<u n="189" who="S0167">and for my birthday</u>
<u n="190" who="S0378">nice guy</u>
<u n="191" who="S0167">he stayed he left the week before my before cos obviously my birthday I was in Peru and then we said to cos his birthday was also while I was in Peru so I said we'll do birthday presents when I come and visit you in Germany and we won't bother doing it before so I wasn't expecting anything so anyway on my birthday I go downstairs cos we lived in a block of flats where there was a doorman and he let us in and out and I was walking to work one day and just as I was going out the door the doorman said oh I've got something for you and it was a birthday card with a rose in a plastic pouch and it was like a real rose and it was freeze dried so it will never die</u>
<u n="192" who="S0378">oh my god</u>
<u n="193" who="S0167">and it said erm erm hi <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I just didn't want to leave you with nothing on your birthday have a really good day at work and I thought oh that's cute thought that was it</u>
<u n="194" who="S0378">what?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0167">so we also had a maid that used to come in and clean every day</u>
<u n="196" who="S0378">no way</u>
<u n="197" who="S0167">so I got home and there was a present and a card on my bed</u>
<u n="198" who="S0378">on my bed?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0167">which he'd given to the maid and said on her birthday can you put that on her bed</u>
<u n="200" who="S0378">on your bed particularly on your bed?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0167">yeah from him so I was like oh my god I've got another present</u>
<u n="202" who="S0378">that must have been so weird</u>
<u n="203" who="S0167">it was</u>
<u n="204" who="S0378">to find something that you hadn't left</u>
<u n="205" who="S0167">well I knew the maid there so it must have been something he'd given to the maid to put on my bed so I opened it and mm I opened the present and the card said erm go onto your computer and open this document it's a it's a password protected document you've got to find the password yourself I'll give you a clue it's related to the last love letter I sent you we were sending each other letters while I was in Peru</u>
<u n="206" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="207" who="S0167">and then anyway a long story short I found the password was and it was something like I love you one two three four</u>
<u n="208" who="S0378">right</u>
<u n="209" who="S0167">I opened this password protected document on my computer and it said now if you go to somewhere close to where your other present was you'll find another little surprise so I was like well must be under my bed then I'm guessing and there was a present under my bed that he'd put there while I was there</u>
<u n="210" who="S0378">oh my god no way</u>
<u n="211" who="S0167">with a card</u>
<u n="212" who="S0378">he put there?</u>
<u n="213" who="S0167">yeah he actually put there</u>
<u n="214" who="S0378">another card</u>
<u n="215" who="S0167">three cards got so many cards this card said well done for finding this present up to now you might want a break so I recommend that you go to this particular bar and order this particular drink and I was like oh my god</u>
<u n="216" who="S0378">oh my god</u>
<u n="217" who="S0167">so <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> my house mate and I we we cos there was three of house living in a house so the company put us up in a flat together so there were three of us two American girls and me</u>
<u n="218" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="219" who="S0167"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I went to this bar</u>
<u n="220" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0167">that was just down the road</u>
<u n="222" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="223" who="S0167">well unfortunately it had been closed down the day before for two weeks by the health and safety people and so I was like oh okay I hope that was the last one and I you know I don't have to go to somewhere else so anyway we just went out somewhere else and the next day I said you know I went to the bar I don't know what was there but erm you know I couldn't pay for my drink</u>
<u n="224" who="S0378">oh</u>
<u n="225" who="S0167">he'd already pre paid for my drink as well he paid for my drink so he'd arranged with the people behind the bar that he would he'd paid for this drink that I was going to order and then that was the signal for them to give me my present my main birthday present anyway</u>
<u n="226" who="S0378">no oh my god</u>
<u n="227" who="S0167">so I sent them I wrote them a little note cos I said I thought you know the boss must be going in and out at some point like someone will be so I wrote a note saying my boyfriend came in a week ago and gave you a present to give to me I was just wondering if you could email me and I can come and collect it or something anyway someone called me up and said yeah come down so I went and collected it and it was this picture of us that he'd ordered and it was in a block of plastic so it was in the back so it</u>
<u n="228" who="S0378">oh yeah</u>
<u n="229" who="S0167">was like a block of plastic and our picture at the back</u>
<u n="230" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0167">it's all nicely wrapped and everything</u>
<u n="232" who="S0378">and what so it's stand free standing</u>
<u n="233" who="S0167">so it stands up yeah so I mean it was a really romantic idea it just didn't quite work out the way he'd planned</u>
<u n="234" who="S0378">oh bless him he must have been so annoyed</u>
<u n="235" who="S0167">and it opened a week after that opened back again</u>
<u n="236" who="S0378">oh my god so much effort went into that and it's really shit that they didn't like</u>
<u n="237" who="S0167">well they didn't know</u>
<u n="238" who="S0378">they didn't know how to contact him?</u>
<u n="239" who="S0167">yeah they didn't know how to contact him cos he thought you know oh that's my job done</u>
<u n="240" who="S0378">you would never think oh this place is going to be shut down the day before as well</u>
<u n="241" who="S0167">yeah cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I had Spanish lessons and we walked past it every day and we walked past it the day before and there were people in there so it was literally that night that they closed down the day before my birthday like the worst timing ever</u>
<u n="242" who="S0378">oh bless him</u>
<u n="243" who="S0167">but at least I did get the present in the end like that wasn't a complete waste</u>
<u n="244" who="S0378">is it that photo?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0167">it's that photo yeah it's the most romantic birthday surprise I've ever had in my life so well planned</u>
<u n="246" who="S0378" trans="overlap">oh my god it's so lovely that's so lovely you deserve it so much there were no good men in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0167">oh they were all shit weren't they?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0378">they are all shit <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> lost her bloke I say lost purposefully lost him</u>
<u n="249" who="S0167">how was how was that what happened with that?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0378">she's fine</u>
<u n="251" who="S0167">cos all I know is what she wrote on Facebook</u>
<u n="252" who="S0378">oh yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0167">I'm going to get another cup of tea</u>
<u n="254" who="S0378">oh yeah me too</u>
<u n="255" who="S0167">I can grab you one if you want</u>
<u n="256" who="S0378">oh yeah please <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0167">I'm afraid I don't have any more hobnobs</u>
<u n="258" who="S0378">ah we will survive <pause dur="long"/> <event desc="sound of restaurant"/></u>
<u n="259" who="S0167">spoons there no spoons left <pause dur="long"/> <event desc="sound of restaurant"/> that's your original cup I promise</u>
<u n="260" who="S0378">don't want your cooties <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="261" who="S0167"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I never told you what I was writing about in Peru guess what my topic area was?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0378">sex?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0167">no</u>
<u n="264" who="S0378">nits?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0167">no</u>
<u n="266" who="S0378">verrucas?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0167">no it's something that I would never have any experience with</u>
<u n="268" who="S0378" trans="overlap">breast milk</u>
<u n="269" who="S0167">until I'm a lot older</u>
<u n="270" who="S0378">dementia?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0167">no not that old</u>
<u n="272" who="S0378">erm incompetence?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0167">no menopause</u>
<u n="274" who="S0378">oh no</u>
<u n="275" who="S0167">I was writing this company that has websites for older women about how to deal with menopause</u>
<u n="276" who="S0378">why would you why would you commission someone like a twenty-three year old woman?</u>
<u n="277" who="S0167">cos it's aimed at UK US audiences they every six months they get three new interns in because they want it to be you know grammatically correct and all of that and just make sure that it's written kind of in the style that an English speaker would understand</u>
<u n="278" who="S0378" trans="overlap">oh my god oh my god so what did you have to write? so now are you an expert?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0167">I'm an absolute expert I know exactly which herbs to take cos it was like</u>
<u n="280" who="S0378" trans="overlap">herbs? herbal?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0167">it was like which exercises to do yeah okay cos the business sells herbal supplements for menopause symptoms and they have a load of websites to kind of for informational websites for women to go onto and be like how do I deal with headaches during menopause how do I deal with a hot flush?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="283" who="S0167">why do hot flushes happen and stuff? and erm so I had to write these articles and I had to research them and write them</u>
<u n="284" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="285" who="S0167">and erm so I'd get like three articles a day three articles in the morning I'd have to write about how to deal with like all these menopause symptoms and then in the afternoon I'd have to write erm they had this other website called herbases which was just about herbal remedies and herbal living for <trunc>gen</trunc> just a general website</u>
<u n="286" who="S0378">mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0167">and like I'd write an encyclopaedic article about it a potato like history of a potato the scientific information about a potato</u>
<u n="288" who="S0378" trans="overlap">a potato <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="289" who="S0167">how to cook a potato <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0378">no way</u>
<u n="291" who="S0167">it was hilarious</u>
<u n="292" who="S0378">oh my god have you still got them? have you got like a portfolio?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0167">no cos none of our work was I actually got that from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> for my last birthday my twenty-third</u>
<u n="294" who="S0378">oh my god that is so pretty</u>
<u n="295" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="296" who="S0378">that is so beautiful</u>
<u n="297" who="S0167">yeah I really like that</u>
<u n="298" who="S0378">yeah I think it must be silver</u>
<u n="299" who="S0167" trans="overlap">did you have a good birthday by the way? did you get my card?</u>
<u n="300" who="S0378">I did I got it a bit late</u>
<u n="301" who="S0167">I'm glad you got it</u>
<u n="302" who="S0378">because we've got this weird post box system</u>
<u n="303" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="304" who="S0378">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> refused to let me have the post key for a while cos she was like it'll get lost so she had it on her thing all the time so I couldn't get into the post box</u>
<u n="305" who="S0167">oh no</u>
<u n="306" who="S0378">but I did get it</u>
<u n="307" who="S0167">so you got your birthday card late</u>
<u n="308" who="S0378">yeah I did but I got it actually yeah yeah no I did get it it was lovely thank you  thank you</u>
<u n="309" who="S0167">oh good I'm glad it came so what did you do for your birthday?</u>
<u n="310" who="S0378">actually I was with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on my birthday</u>
<u n="311" who="S0167">yeah cos I guess you were like really close weren't you? so</u>
<u n="312" who="S0378">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0167">celebrate together</u>
<u n="314" who="S0378">yeah and she'd been given tickets to Paolo Nutini for her birthday so two tickets and so she and it was on my birthday so</u>
<u n="315" who="S0167">oh okay</u>
<u n="316" who="S0378">it was on the twelfth so she gave one to me as my birthday present and we went and I bought us dinner beforehand cos it was at the 02</u>
<u n="317" who="S0167" trans="overlap">oh that's so nice</u>
<u n="318" who="S0378">so we went to <anon type="place"/> do you know <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0167">no</u>
<u n="320" who="S0378">if you like steak</u>
<u n="321" who="S0167">oh I do like a good steak I love a steak</u>
<u n="322" who="S0378">it is an incredible steak restaurant so we went there and I bought her dinner and then she we went to this gig it was really really cool it was such a nice birthday actually</u>
<u n="323" who="S0167">ah</u>
<u n="324" who="S0378">what did I do in the day? ah I got shat on by a bird <vocal desc="laugh"/> on my birthday</u>
<u n="325" who="S0167" trans="overlap">that's lucky I was with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when she got shat on by a bird in in erm was it <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="326" who="S0378">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0167">and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0378">that photo <vocal desc="laugh"/> just before it happened</u>
<u n="329" who="S0167">I loved that</u>
<u n="330" who="S0378">oh too funny</u>
<u n="331" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="332" who="S0378">so that's what I did really</u>
<u n="333" who="S0167">ah nice birthday</u>
<u n="334" who="S0378">erm yeah it was good I saw <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I've seen <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a couple of times too</u>
<u n="335" who="S0167">yeah she mentioned she mentioned that cos I saw I met up with her and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> actually a few weeks ago</u>
<u n="336" who="S0378">oh my god <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s engaged</u>
<u n="337" who="S0167">I know isn't that crazy?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0378">how weird is that?</u>
<u n="339" who="S0167">well I guess they live together so I guess</u>
<u n="340" who="S0378">everything's so like quick though</u>
<u n="341" who="S0167">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0378">I guess that was the same with erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0167">that's true</u>
<u n="344" who="S0378">all of these marriages have been very quick apart from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="345" who="S0167">ah they're engaged too</u>
<u n="346" who="S0378"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I want to go to his wedding but I don't think I'm going to be invited</u>
<u n="347" who="S0167">no me neither</u>
<u n="348" who="S0378">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0167">never mind we'll have our own weddings</u>
<u n="350" who="S0378">yes do you know what's really funny? is that I've got a Pinterest do you know Pinterest?</u>
<u n="351" who="S0167">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0378">well I've got a board on Pinterest</u>
<u n="353" who="S0167">for weddings</u>
<u n="354" who="S0378">for weddings I suppose loads of women must do mustn't they? I've never done that before and it's never been something that's interested me ever but now for some reason I think I just did it out of like curiosity one day</u>
<u n="355" who="S0167">yeah I love looking at wedding venues I do it all the time</u>
<u n="356" who="S0378" trans="overlap">I know me me too I love it and dresses</u>
<u n="357" who="S0167">I was looking at the other day like how to have an eco wedding and I was like I'm going to buy my wedding dress from a charity shop and I'm going to do this like eco venue</u>
<u n="358" who="S0378">oh are you?</u>
<u n="359" who="S0167">and the card's going to be like an eco like card with seeds in that you can plant and like we're going to have like recycled chairs</u>
<u n="360" who="S0378">that's so nice</u>
<u n="361" who="S0167">it's like and we're going to try and make it like a eco wedding</u>
<u n="362" who="S0378">that's a good idea</u>
<u n="363" who="S0167" trans="overlap">I was looking up ideas</u>
<u n="364" who="S0378">are you every eco now?</u>
<u n="365" who="S0167">I try and be <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0378">is this still recording?</u>
<u n="367" who="S0167">I can turn it off</u>
<u n="368" who="S0378">is this still recording? cos I</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
