<text id="SRCA">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:16:25</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-02-19</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0275 S0276</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>University canteen</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Friday evening, Valentine’s Day, cinema, movies, food, restaurants, problems, shopping, accents</topics>
		<activity>Friends reflecting on Valentine’s Day and their weekend</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, complaining, advising, anecdote telling, telling jokes</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0275">
				<exactage>20</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>West London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0276">
				<exactage>19</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Phillipines</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Lincolnshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>e_midlands</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0275">what do you mean no? he released a mix tape</u>
<u n="2" who="S0276">okay</u>
<u n="3" who="S0275" trans="overlap">randomly and it's called erm If You Are Reading This Then It's Too Late</u>
<u n="4" who="S0276">okay</u>
<u n="5" who="S0275" trans="overlap">and look <vocal desc="laugh"/> but look at this <vocal desc="laugh"/> look at this picture my sister put up it is so funny <vocal desc="laugh"/> it is too late if you read this <vocal desc="laugh"/> and there's no more tissue <vocal desc="laugh"/> isn't that funny?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0276">yeah that's funny</u>
<u n="7" who="S0275">it's funny you joker anywhos you went to the cinema?</u>
<u n="8" who="S0276">mm</u>
<u n="9" who="S0275">on Valentine's?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0276">no</u>
<u n="11" who="S0275">oh on Friday</u>
<u n="12" who="S0276"><unclear/> Friday</u>
<u n="13" who="S0275"><unclear/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0276">yeah Fifty Shades of Grey</u>
<u n="15" who="S0275">how was it then?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0276">no just no</u>
<u n="17" who="S0275">I nearly lost my hot chocolate what do you mean no? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0276">I was so pissed that I wasted nine quid on that shit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0275">what do you mean <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0276">I get I read the</u>
<u n="21" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh you read the book</u>
<u n="22" who="S0276">I read the book so</u>
<u n="23" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah that's the problem first of all</u>
<u n="24" who="S0276">like <pause dur="short"/> I don't like the actress she bugs the shit out of me she can't act there was no chemistry between them her voice pisses the hell out of me</u>
<u n="25" who="S0275"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="26" who="S0276">I don't find her sexy</u>
<u n="27" who="S0275">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0276">Jamie Dornan a gorgeous guy but his eyes are just <unclear> cold</unclear> eyes</u>
<u n="29" who="S0275">it is a bit scary sometimes <unclear/></u>
<u n="30" who="S0276" trans="overlap">and oh my gosh like it was full arse naked</u>
<u n="31" who="S0275">oh so what's it there wasn't enough nakedness?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0276">yeah you didn't see those bits but you saw once you didn't saw that but you saw like pubic hair on both of them</u>
<u n="33" who="S0275">oh no</u>
<u n="34" who="S0276">so you <trunc>s</trunc> near it was practically</u>
<u n="35" who="S0275">oh no</u>
<u n="36" who="S0276">but do you know what? it was funny there were actually scenes of <pause dur="short"/> there were actual bits where it was funny cos it wasn't supposed to be</u>
<u n="37" who="S0275">yeah as long as it's funny</u>
<u n="38" who="S0276">it is okay at the end are you going to see it?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0275">no</u>
<u n="40" who="S0276">okay please don't please don't</u>
<u n="41" who="S0275"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0276" trans="overlap">but at the end and so I remember this from the book and it's where he's like whipping her with his belt like telling her this is how he wants to punish her</u>
<u n="43" who="S0275">oh my god</u>
<u n="44" who="S0276" trans="overlap">and it is like this is how the the and at the end it really like a heartbreaking scene because like she's in pain and like she leaves and she ends it me of course</u>
<u n="45" who="S0275">of course</u>
<u n="46" who="S0276">I just like <pause dur="short"/> my mind is like it is supposed to be emotionally emotional and like it is supposed to like this isn't good this is bad</u>
<u n="47" who="S0275">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0276" trans="overlap">blah de blah de blah what song comes in my head? Smack That</u>
<u n="49" who="S0275"><vocal desc="gasp"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="50" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and then just then I like <unclear/> do you know what's in my head? Smack That</u>
<u n="51" who="S0275">no are you serious?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0276" trans="overlap">and then when she there just stick in it twice now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="53" who="S0275" trans="overlap">are you serious?</u>
<u n="54" who="S0276">it was like I felt so bad because obviously that was a really like</u>
<u n="55" who="S0275">she's there crying?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0276">yeah and then there's just us mumbling to ourselves <shift new="singing"/> smack that hard <shift new="normal"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="57" who="S0275">oh my god <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you don't rate her she's there crying and she's heartbroken and you are singing <pause dur="short"/> a song</u>
<u n="58" who="S0276">mm mm</u>
<u n="59" who="S0275">poor girl <pause dur="short"/> she's a waste man anyways I don't want to watch that movie</u>
<u n="60" who="S0276">don't</u>
<u n="61" who="S0275">I am not interested in it at all</u>
<u n="62" who="S0276">don't</u>
<u n="63" who="S0275">Nando's food poisoning</u>
<u n="64" who="S0276">really?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0275">yeah how did I get it? there's some Nando's by my <trunc>hou</trunc> well it's not by my house it is the different area right but I've never been to that one and we were going to <anon type="place"/> Nando's me and my sister and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but we was like obviously <anon type="place"/> is going to be packed they're couples <unclear/></u>
<u n="66" who="S0276" trans="overlap">when when was it?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0275">Valentine's Day</u>
<u n="68" who="S0276">ah right</u>
<u n="69" who="S0275">yeah erm and we was going to the one by my sister's house but that was so tiny because it is always full because it is that small so there was no point going there the one in <anon type="place"/> is a bit too crusty <pause dur="short"/> erm and I forgot where the other one is oh the one in <anon type="place"/> would have been too full  of <unclear/> because it is a big one she said let's go to one we haven't been to where there's gonna be no people <pause dur="short"/> the one in <anon type="place"/> because the one in <anon type="place"/> has got on like er er <pause dur="short"/> it's basically in the middle of nowhere like no one is there</u>
<u n="70" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0275">oh but I don't know why they put a Nando's there really I mean there's nothing there except for Tesco and then there was like a couple of shops anywhos we went there it was er like it was full but there were seats</u>
<u n="72" who="S0276">yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0275" trans="overlap">they didn't want to seat us <pause dur="short"/> though there was two empty tables and the guy was just staring at us and then would go away and he help some other people and come back and I am like oh is there something wrong with these tables? and he was like oh yeah we have two free tables is that okay? I am like yes it is okay I wanna eat my food and go home so we sat down erm picking our food I am going to order I let <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> order her food first yeah and then I was going to order me and my sister's food the woman <trunc>wo</trunc>walked off <pause dur="short"/> she was like have a nice meal girls</u>
<u n="74" who="S0276">what?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0275">I was like what do you mean? we ordered one meal <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> ordered one chicken are we all sharing one chicken?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0275">one quarter <trunc>chick</trunc> no she's bought a wrap a chicken chicken wrap are we sharing that?</u>
<u n="78" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">sorry <unclear> that's your water I'll just leave it for you here</unclear></u>
<u n="79" who="S0275">oh yeah that's okay <pause dur="short"/> I'm like well what do I look likesharing a wrap with three people no so I thought oh she must she must be just coming back or she must have seen like someone in trouble or something she never came back I was standing there like</u>
<u n="80" who="S0276">what the fuck?</u>
<u n="81" who="S0275">what the fuck are you? <pause dur="short"/> oh my god so what happened? did I not make it? am I not going to get food today? that was so <trunc>dread</trunc> anywhos I was gonna go  to the back of the queue and start again but it was so full and I was like mum go to the back to start again and then some woman erm some man sorry started shouting at the other employee telling him calling him a tramp</u>
<u n="82" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0275">because he was taking so long to get the erm guy's order who was in front of him and he stormed out of the erm Nando's I was like oh my goodness let's not get shot up here because it's the thing <unclear/></u>
<u n="84" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0275">there's gangs up there I was like oh god please I don't need to get shot today so I just stayed where I was and then the woman finally came back and then she she was like <pause dur="short"/> I felt like she didn't even notice that I was the same girl waiting because then after I'd ordered my food she was like okay have a nice meal girls <pause dur="short"/> and I thought uh-oh there's only me standing here that's so awkward <pause dur="short"/> anywhos look the fizzy drinks were flat</u>
<u n="86" who="S0276">really?</u>
<u n="87" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah I don't know how that works</u>
<u n="88" who="S0276">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0275">in the machine and it was flat and I had it without ice as well to check and it was still flat <pause dur="short"/> like the Coke was literally flat and the lemonade was like you know when you open it like three times maybe yeah? <pause dur="short"/> I don't know what happened it was disgusting they had no sauces</u>
<u n="90" who="S0276">what?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0275">there was no sauces when I went to get the sauce there was four sauces and then there was like six ketchups there was four <unclear>flavours</unclear> and six ketchups and I was looking at the tables and there was they didn't have any sauce out anyways I saw two sauces out on the tables</u>
<u n="92" who="S0276">no</u>
<u n="93" who="S0275">I know right how can they have no sauce? erm and then our food came and it was burnt it tasted like er <pause dur="short"/> grill</u>
<u n="94" who="S0276">oh</u>
<u n="95" who="S0275">yeah I couldn't eat my coleslaw imagine me <pause dur="short"/> my coleslaw was nasty <pause dur="short"/> me? come on coleslaw I can live off coleslaw in the summer that was all I was eating was Sainsbury's coleslaw out of the box</u>
<u n="96" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="97" who="S0275">I was getting takeaway Nando's coleslaw I made my auntie make me coleslaw like coleslaw I love coleslaw</u>
<u n="98" who="S0276" trans="overlap">but you went you went to Nando's twice in one week</u>
<u n="99" who="S0275"><vocal desc="gasp"/> shut up did I we went on Monday oh no don't tell people that</u>
<u n="100" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="101" who="S0275">I didn't mean to but my sister my sister's best friend is going there with her boyfriend and they wanted her to come they're always making my sister come out with them I feel so bad for her</u>
<u n="102" who="S0276">third wheeling</u>
<u n="103" who="S0275" trans="overlap">third wheeler she said she is professional now</u>
<u n="104" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="105" who="S0275" trans="overlap">if you want tips on how to <unclear/> call her</u>
<u n="106" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0275">she is so stupid erm so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is like no she wants to go to Nando's but not with them so let's go Nando's and obviously if I am going Nando's I've got to er I can't remember <unclear>I've got lots of questions</unclear></u>
<u n="108" who="S0276">they don't normally <unclear/></u>
<u n="109" who="S0275">shit erm we're gonna have to invite <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because you know me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> go around like this erm so that's why we went Nando's only because of my sister but the food I mean when we was eating even the food ordered drink because you see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't eat her chicken and she didn't get a fizzy drink she got er she got a erm cloudy lemonade</u>
<u n="110" who="S0276">oh right</u>
<u n="111" who="S0275">and me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have got the fizzy drink and we are the only ones that ate our chicken so either the drink or the chicken ruined us it was not a joke it didn't last very long <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> it went it came straight out</u>
<u n="112" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="113" who="S0275" trans="overlap">okay <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="114" who="S0276">oh god <vocal desc="laugh"/> oh god</u>
<u n="115" who="S0275">it didn't make it mate I was like shit I didn't even finish my food though that's the thing I didn't finish it</u>
<u n="116" who="S0276">why you poor poor thing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="117" who="S0275">and it just I was so hungry <vocal desc="laugh"/> on the Sunday I was starving and so I had erm some Cheerios</u>
<u n="118" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="119" who="S0275">they didn't last I was food poisoned Nando's food poisoned me</u>
<u n="120" who="S0276">ah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0275" trans="overlap">I couldn't eat all yesterday <pause dur="short"/> so today I'm starving but I haven't got money to eat <unclear/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0276">I know I know</u>
<u n="123" who="S0275" trans="overlap">it's dreadful isn't it? it is so sad</u>
<u n="124" who="S0276">shall I tell you how my Valentine's Day went?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0275">yeah let me know</u>
<u n="126" who="S0276">okay we were going to spend the day in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="127" who="S0275">oh that's cute</u>
<u n="128" who="S0276">and on like at the train station like you know the bridgey bit on my glasses?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0275">oh yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0276">one of the screws popped out</u>
<u n="131" who="S0275">oh no</u>
<u n="132" who="S0276">so I was like shit <pause dur="short"/> and so I was looking up some places for <trunc>Spec</trunc> Specsavers because like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said that they do them</u>
<u n="133" who="S0275">oh yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0276">even though there's a Specsavers in <anon type="place"/> we decided not to go back we decided to go all the way to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="135" who="S0275">you went to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0276">because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wanted to go wanted to show us <anon type="place"/> and they have a Specsavers there but Specsavers didn't do it so we went to the optician across the road which did it for free thankfully</u>
<u n="137" who="S0275">oh good</u>
<u n="138" who="S0276">I was scared in <anon type="place"/> I was scared <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0275"><anon type="place"/> is not fun <anon type="place"/> is not fun why would you want to be in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="140" who="S0276">cos like she <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we wanted like there's Tamil shops there because she wanted to go there and get some snacks which were gorgeous by the way</u>
<u n="141" who="S0275">oh</u>
<u n="142" who="S0276" trans="overlap">really cheap</u>
<u n="143" who="S0275">really?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0276">a samosa for like sixty P</u>
<u n="145" who="S0275">what?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0276">for sixty P</u>
<u n="147" who="S0275">seriously?</u>
<u n="148" who="S0276">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0275">was it hot?</u>
<u n="150" who="S0276">no</u>
<u n="151" who="S0275">oh <pause dur="short"/> but still that's very cheap</u>
<u n="152" who="S0276">it was they were really nice <pause dur="short"/> but it but it was scary</u>
<u n="153" who="S0275">that is scary</u>
<u n="154" who="S0276" trans="overlap">yeah like I don't like <vocal desc="nonsense"/></u>
<u n="155" who="S0275"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0276">and after that we went <anon type="place"/> because we were like</u>
<u n="157" who="S0275" trans="overlap">what near <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="158" who="S0276">yeah near <anon type="place"/> because like it is our friend's birthday</u>
<u n="159" who="S0275">on Valentine's Day?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0276">no no no on Sunday this coming Sunday so we are going out Friday she's going her family is coming to visit this weekend so she wants to spend her actual birthday with her family so we are going out Friday</u>
<u n="161" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh that's so cute</u>
<u n="162" who="S0276">so we was looking for outfits for that and I've never been Forever 21 so I wanted to go there</u>
<u n="163" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0276">three hours <pause dur="short"/> three fucking hours</u>
<u n="165" who="S0275" trans="overlap">no no no</u>
<u n="166" who="S0276" trans="overlap">and do you know what? we didn't even look at all the shop sections</u>
<u n="167" who="S0275">you can't</u>
<u n="168" who="S0276" trans="overlap">we just had to we had to stop</u>
<u n="169" who="S0275">Forever 21 is the devil</u>
<u n="170" who="S0276">it is</u>
<u n="171" who="S0275">I haven't been back there in like two years because I spent all my money there</u>
<u n="172" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0275" trans="overlap">and you spend the whole day there it's dangerous</u>
<u n="174" who="S0276">that's where ninety pounds went <pause dur="short"/> oh the thing was it was actually the total was one hundred pounds but because I had an old student discount it came down to ninety something</u>
<u n="175" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh my god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0276">it was not good and I like I told like I hazed my mum like oh yeah I got lots of things</u>
<u n="177" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh no you liar</u>
<u n="178" who="S0276">and she doesn't actually know the amount but she was like like I made it seem like it was a good idea I was the thing is it is all good stuff and it is all reasonably priced</u>
<u n="179" who="S0275">yes that is the problem that is the problem because you think oh this is reasonable this is on five seven five this is only <pause dur="short"/> and then before you know it <unclear/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0276">it does</u>
<u n="181" who="S0275">literally that happened to me I bought proper jeans and lots of erm like you know the boob tops for the summer</u>
<u n="182" who="S0276">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0275" trans="overlap">shirts and then finally <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> I I said mum can you pay half please?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0275">because I didn't realise it had got that far</u>
<u n="186" who="S0276">and I had to let go a hat because it was fifteen pounds</u>
<u n="187" who="S0275">oh baby love</u>
<u n="188" who="S0276">it was beautiful it's okay</u>
<u n="189" who="S0275"><unclear>next time next</unclear> and then <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<event desc="unintelligible"/>
<u n="190" who="S0276">yeah I <unclear/> I I only have like a hundred and forty pounds left in like in my <trunc>c</trunc> account until <trunc>Ap</trunc> the end of April</u>
<u n="191" who="S0275">wow</u>
<u n="192" who="S0276" trans="overlap">until the end of April</u>
<u n="193" who="S0275">shit <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0276" trans="overlap">so I am going to be in my overdraft in March</u>
<u n="195" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0276">because I'm visiting my friend in March and I</u>
<u n="197" who="S0275" trans="overlap">right you're done then</u>
<u n="198" who="S0276">yeah I am done so I am going to be in my overdraft</u>
<u n="199" who="S0275" trans="overlap">well at least you have been paying off your overdraft so it is not <unclear/> a lot</u>
<u n="200" who="S0276">yeah so I was quite grateful for that</u>
<u n="201" who="S0275">oh fucking hell wait when do we get the next student grant?</u>
<u n="202" who="S0276" trans="overlap">it is some time in April it is like the third or fourth week</u>
<u n="203" who="S0275" trans="overlap">okay I thought it was early I need it to be early</u>
<u n="204" who="S0276"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0275"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I need the same thing</u>
<u n="206" who="S0276">but we may have classes so I won't need to spend money on like boy stuff</u>
<u n="207" who="S0275">I cannot wait until I don't have to do <unclear>boy</unclear> stuff but then again I have to work two days a week <pause dur="short"/> and it's just cheaper to just do the whole week</u>
<u n="208" who="S0276">then erm what did we do? then we wanted to we went to <anon type="place"/> because we wanted paella they have at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="209" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh <unclear>my god</unclear></u>
<u n="210" who="S0276">but they fucking moved or like gone or something</u>
<u n="211" who="S0275">oh no</u>
<u n="212" who="S0276">I'm convinced because all the other people around it knew how good it was kicked them out they've shut like those pubby places are bullies</u>
<u n="213" who="S0275">they are bullies <unclear/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0276" trans="overlap">but <pause dur="short"/> but then we walked to <anon type="place"/> and went into <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0275">are you serious? you guys erm <pause dur="short"/> moved around all Saturday</u>
<u n="216" who="S0276">yeah all Saturday and like my pedometer I walked twice the <trunc>ra</trunc> the <trunc>a</trunc> like the amount I was supposed to walk</u>
<u n="217" who="S0275" trans="overlap">I can imagine</u>
<u n="218" who="S0276">erm</u>
<u n="219" who="S0275">how early did you leave your house?</u>
<u n="220" who="S0276">I nearly said eleven I can't do it eleven is still the bloody morning <vocal desc="laugh"/> er but we went to <anon type="place"/> erm we were so hungry and thirsty we were already queuing but we didn't want to leave</u>
<u n="221" who="S0275">oh I hate that</u>
<u n="222" who="S0276" trans="overlap">so we were already queuing and there were so many fucking footballers obviously Valentine's Day so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was like we'll call them the pipes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0275">why was you calling them pipes?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0276">because like we we like we wanted to like yell something whenever we saw a couple we wanted to like</u>
<u n="225" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="226" who="S0276">so we called them pipes because it is like something random</u>
<u n="227" who="S0275">oh okay yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0276" trans="overlap">and then we made a connection it was like because they are joined together but they are also really gross</u>
<u n="229" who="S0275">oh seriously <unclear/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0276" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah so much kissing and shit</u>
<u n="231" who="S0275">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0276">and like the one behind us she was from like Newcastle I think because my friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is from Newcastle as well</u>
<u n="233" who="S0275">oh is she?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0276" trans="overlap">so the accent works</u>
<u n="235" who="S0275">the Geordie accent</u>
<u n="236" who="S0276">so like as I said she was just like because she was talking to her and her boyfriend's mum on the phone</u>
<u n="237" who="S0275" trans="overlap">oh my god</u>
<u n="238" who="S0276" trans="overlap">and then the one the ones in front of us they were like posh like she had that annoying voice</u>
<u n="239" who="S0275" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0276">you know like posh people have?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0275">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0276">er</u>
<u n="243" who="S0275"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0276">so annoying</u>
<u n="245" who="S0275">oh my god when we were in <anon type="place"/> I didn't see many couples I was so happy there was a lot of groups of friends in the erm <pause dur="short"/> nando's I went to I was so happy but then we went like it was early so we was like let's just go cinema and just watch something we are not watching Fifty Shades my sister's seventeen anyway she can't watch it so we was gonna watch erm the Kingsman right? cos you said it was good and my sister said her friend said it was good too so we are on our way there and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had <unclear>clocked</unclear> that the movie was starting in was six minutes we was twenty minutes away</u>
<u n="246" who="S0276">oh</u>
<u n="247" who="S0275" trans="overlap">and we was going to <trunc>mi</trunc> like it was we would have missed it and <pause dur="short"/> and I hate missing the beginning</u>
<u n="248" who="S0276">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0275" trans="overlap">plus it was going to be full so it was er <pause dur="short"/> valentine's Day and it was evening it was like nine thirty</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
