<text id="SRCD">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:30:02</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-03-13</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0588 S0589</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Walking along the River Thames.</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Landmarks along the Thames, O2 Arena, not owning a car, going on holiday with family, American cup measurements, philosophical questions. </topics>
		<activity>Chatting whilst walking along the Thames from Woolwich towards Greenwich.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, complaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0588">
				<exactage>49</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Standard English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>49 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Trascriber</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0589">
				<exactage>40</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Edinburgh</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Britain</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Standard English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>11 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0588">that's why we have things like planning permission which <anon type="place"/> council don't take any notice of cos they install ugly concrete blocks randomly without asking anybody <pause dur="long"/> but there was that point in history where beer was safer to drink than water</u>
<u n="2" who="S0589">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="3" who="S0588">oh those ducks look so sweet bobbing up and down <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> would probably be quite fascinated to look at them yes <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0589" trans="overlap">ah cos we don't rarely very often open the curtains in the snug but I had them open during the rugby and so straightaway he got up to have a look out and his little eyes</u>
<u n="5" who="S0588">ah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0589" trans="overlap">were so bright</u>
<u n="7" who="S0588">yes he's</u>
<u n="8" who="S0589" trans="overlap">his little chin</u>
<u n="9" who="S0588">mm <pause dur="short"/> but he started</u>
<u n="10" who="S0589" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="11" who="S0588">liking the film we were watching when it</u>
<u n="12" who="S0589" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="13" who="S0588" trans="overlap">had the rats on it</u>
<u n="14" who="S0589">yes</u>
<u n="15" who="S0588">he got quite into it at that point</u>
<u n="16" who="S0589" trans="overlap">yes mm</u>
<u n="17" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's so funny I'm surprised they actually see things on television you'd think they'd sort of not be able to</u>
<u n="18" who="S0589" trans="overlap">well they're not seeing what we are seeing but he's seeing small things</u>
<u n="19" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="20" who="S0589" trans="overlap">moving quickly which is</u>
<u n="21" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0589" trans="overlap">like a scurrying creature <pause dur="long"/> well this was a success wasn't it darling?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0588">mm</u>
<u n="24" who="S0589">it's not the best beer but erm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0588">I'm enjoying it</u>
<u n="26" who="S0589">it's Greene King so this must be a Greene King pub <anon type="place"/> sort of you <trunc>nev</trunc> er normally hear it that way round</u>
<u n="27" who="S0588">it's very nice to see the Thames properly and London properly like this I do think you see London better from the point of view of the Thames you really get a sense of the history</u>
<u n="28" who="S0589">we should take a picture of the pub and we'll send it to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos she's a fan of Thames-side pubs now</u>
<u n="29" who="S0588" trans="overlap">well I mean this is something that we should bear in mind for meeting <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because she could come from her direction and we could come from our direction <pause dur="long"/> it's taken me all this time to actually get round to doing this I cannot believe that that's bloody full time work thing look at all those seagulls on that pier there's a whole gathering of them what's a gathering what is the <trunc>collec</trunc>collective noun for seagulls?</u>
<u n="30" who="S0589">dunno probably flock but it might not be <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="31" who="S0588" trans="overlap">oh of course it is but that's when they're flying isn't it? no no it's really I seem to <pause dur="short"/> there's a flock now they're flying does that mean they're flying? <pause dur="short"/> what about when they're sitting? it would seem like another word would be more appropriate than flock <pause dur="short"/> a gathering <pause dur="short"/> a meeting <pause dur="long"/> there's the DLR</u>
<u n="32" who="S0589">yes there it is darling</u>
<u n="33" who="S0588" trans="overlap">there it is it's going to <anon type="place"/> that's the one we get from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0589">okay let's crack on</u>
<u n="35" who="S0588">yeah let me finish my half pint are you</u>
<u n="36" who="S0589" trans="overlap">it's a bit cold</u>
<u n="37" who="S0588" trans="overlap">refreshed?</u>
<u n="38" who="S0589">yes but cold I want to get</u>
<u n="39" who="S0588" trans="overlap">are you cold? I'm not cold at all</u>
<u n="40" who="S0589">only because that cold beer made me cold</u>
<u n="41" who="S0588">I'm trying to get it down me quickly <pause dur="short"/> what do you think the next pub will be?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0589">well it's on that list I read</u>
<u n="43" who="S0588">where was it?</u>
<u n="44" who="S0589" trans="overlap">er er it's on the peninsula</u>
<u n="45" who="S0588">okay so just as we are going er turning round then is that past the <anon type="place"/> or before?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0589">I don't know <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="47" who="S0588">do you think <trunc>i</trunc>if we did lots of things in <anon type="place"/> it would compensate you for me not wanting to go abroad?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0589">no</u>
<u n="49" who="S0588">it wouldn't?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0589">I don't mind you not wanting to go abroad</u>
<u n="51" who="S0588">according to everybody you must be terribly missing out</u>
<u n="52" who="S0589">well I suppose did you pick up your phone?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0588">the attitude that people have is that my god they feel sorry for me cos I don't like travel</u>
<u n="54" who="S0589">they feel more sorry for me</u>
<u n="55" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I think yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0589" trans="overlap">cos I'm denied</u>
<u n="57" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0589">almost like</u>
<u n="59" who="S0588" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="60" who="S0589" trans="overlap">having an evil step</u>
<u n="61" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="62" who="S0589">mother</u>
<u n="63" who="S0588">erm exactly</u>
<u n="64" who="S0589" trans="overlap"><unclear/> me at home <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="65" who="S0588" trans="overlap">exactly</u>
<u n="66" who="S0589"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="67" who="S0588">thank you exactly that's how it feels cos that's how I'm being made to feel and hence also being blamed that you you're not going away but I'm not stopping you going away but I see what you mean you don't go unless I go cos you love me and hence everybody knows that you're not going because I'm not</u>
<u n="68" who="S0589">going to Greece I might go to Greece this year and I might actually take you</u>
<u n="69" who="S0588" trans="overlap">Greece</u>
<u n="70" who="S0589">this yeah</u>
<u n="71" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0589">but now it would be sort of summery so you'd be terribly worried</u>
<u n="73" who="S0588">no I <trunc>ca</trunc> I can't go in summer</u>
<u n="74" who="S0589">you can if you stay indoors</u>
<u n="75" who="S0588">no the thing is I mean on paper yes but in reality? mm <pause dur="short"/> soon as you go away with anybody there are so many compromises sorry</u>
<u n="76" who="S0589" trans="overlap">like when we went on a we went on a tour of this historic <pause dur="short"/> fort and erm erm palace and it was a mid-July midday <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="78" who="S0589">it was over forty degrees</u>
<u n="79" who="S0588" trans="overlap">oh fuck <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="80" who="S0589"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said when he was getting ready he said it's like being in world war <trunc>t</trunc> one and going over the top <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0588">well</u>
<u n="82" who="S0589" trans="overlap"><trunc>y</trunc>you just feel that this is a mission</u>
<u n="83" who="S0588">it I mean</u>
<u n="84" who="S0589">that's gonna kill you</u>
<u n="85" who="S0588">well I mean yes but it would</u>
<u n="86" who="S0589" trans="overlap">he was not happy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0588" trans="overlap">it is gonna kill you it's gonna give you bloody skin cancer I mean</u>
<u n="88" who="S0589" trans="overlap">that's what mummy's got it now</u>
<u n="89" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I mean and hello your mum's got it sorry but that's why <pause dur="short"/> but you know it's like well oh isn't this lovely? <vocal desc="laugh"/> end up fucking burning and you can't</u>
<u n="90" who="S0589" trans="overlap">that's</u>
<u n="91" who="S0588" trans="overlap">do anything about it cos you can't just say to people erm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0589" trans="overlap">I would erm</u>
<u n="93" who="S0588">erm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0589" trans="overlap">manage I would manage</u>
<u n="95" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I'm burning I'm burning here do you mind if I erm just go away and very quickly find some shade?</u>
<u n="96" who="S0589">the thing is in actual</u>
<u n="97" who="S0588" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="98" who="S0589" trans="overlap">fact if we just went out for a week all mum and auntie <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> do is potter around the garden</u>
<u n="99" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0589">so you could just sit indoors reading and</u>
<u n="101" who="S0588">very hard to</u>
<u n="102" who="S0589" trans="overlap">sipping beer</u>
<u n="103" who="S0588" trans="overlap">actually manage it in reality</u>
<u n="104" who="S0589">and then</u>
<u n="105" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I find</u>
<u n="106" who="S0589">no because they're just pottering around you'd be under pressure to go to the <pause dur="short"/> beach with me during the day I suppose but then then you'd just sit in the <foreign lang="gre">taverna</foreign></u>
<u n="107" who="S0588">mm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0589" trans="overlap">so then you've just got to erm</u>
<u n="109" who="S0588" trans="overlap">mm it's not just that</u>
<u n="110" who="S0589" trans="overlap">to cope with</u>
<u n="111" who="S0588">it's the walks between places where people aren't</u>
<u n="112" who="S0589" trans="overlap">then you've just got to</u>
<u n="113" who="S0588" trans="overlap">bothered about the sun and stuff where I am</u>
<u n="114" who="S0589">then you've just got to cope <vocal desc="misc"/> then you've just got to cope with the actual journey there</u>
<u n="115" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0589" trans="overlap">and back</u>
<u n="117" who="S0588">that's what I'm saying</u>
<u n="118" who="S0589">but potentially of course</u>
<u n="119" who="S0588" trans="overlap">but that's that's potentially very</u>
<u n="120" who="S0589">potentially you could get</u>
<u n="121" who="S0588" trans="overlap">damaging</u>
<u n="122" who="S0589">dropped off in the car then picked up</u>
<u n="123" who="S0588" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0589">gosh we'd manage you</u>
<u n="125" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I don't know it's really hard and especially when <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> keeps bloody asking I I just think oh stop fucking asking</u>
<u n="126" who="S0589" trans="overlap">and darling we could put you in a swimming costume one of those like an actual wetsuit so</u>
<u n="127" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="128" who="S0589">like an <unclear/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0588" trans="overlap">well erm I think the Japanese have invented something that goes completely over your face and it's like</u>
<u n="130" who="S0589" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm</u>
<u n="131" who="S0588" trans="overlap">a baraclava a balaclava but it's erm for sun <pause dur="short"/> I don't mind looking like a complete twat</u>
<u n="132" who="S0589">well you won't get much more industrial landscape than this dear</u>
<u n="133" who="S0588">it's cool oh it's not actually I want to be <trunc>n</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> <trunc>h</trunc> we've lost the Thames <pause dur="short"/> when do we get back to it?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0589" trans="overlap">that way</u>
<u n="135" who="S0588">that's a con</u>
<u n="136" who="S0589" trans="overlap">we're near enough</u>
<u n="137" who="S0588">they said it was a Thames walk</u>
<u n="138" who="S0589">I think we're near enough</u>
<u n="139" who="S0588">we're not near enough</u>
<u n="140" who="S0589" trans="overlap">take my arm dear I'm sleepy</u>
<u n="141" who="S0588">that's the beer</u>
<u n="142" who="S0589">yeah it must be</u>
<u n="143" who="S0588">we're not near enough can't call it Thames walk and then make you walk how many metres away from it are we <pause dur="short"/> would you say? <pause dur="short"/> ten?</u>
<u n="144" who="S0589">twenty</u>
<u n="145" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I've got a brain training game a sort of distances and it goes</u>
<u n="146" who="S0589">oh you'd be terrible at that darling</u>
<u n="147" who="S0588" trans="overlap">and you have to put them order yeah but the thing is</u>
<u n="148" who="S0589" trans="overlap">uhu</u>
<u n="149" who="S0588" trans="overlap">it wouldn't be as difficult if they hadn't changed yards into <trunc>fee</trunc> no feet into bloody yards and then you've metres and then you've got well it's about changing the old measurements into the new measurements which is bloody doubly confusing isn't it? I mean you could get your head around measurements but dunno about old measurements and then you've got ounces and er grams and they're going and I haven't got a fucking clue it's order of <trunc>s</trunc> so you put it in an order so they'll say something like six ounces and then they'll say I dunno five hundred grams</u>
<u n="150" who="S0589">that would be difficult</u>
<u n="151" who="S0588" trans="overlap">and yeah it thank you it is difficult and especially if you well no we're we're er of the age where we had both so I mean we're supposed to know but I'm more in the ounces world than the grams world I must admit</u>
<u n="152" who="S0589">I'm more grams</u>
<u n="153" who="S0588">are you? yeah?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0589" trans="overlap">five hundred grams</u>
<u n="155" who="S0588" trans="overlap">cos er you're that much younger than me you see</u>
<u n="156" who="S0589">half a pound ish</u>
<u n="157" who="S0588" trans="overlap">but I'm now moving into grams more obviously cos things tend to be grams now</u>
<u n="158" who="S0589" trans="overlap">darling at least you don't get asked how much is a cup and a half <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="159" who="S0588">oh for fuck's sake how on earth do you get your head around that one?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0589"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0588">I've rejected all books that are measured in cups I'm sorry I'm not there's enough to deal with in life without fucking cups it's not like a cup is a cup a cup is a cup if it's a liquid a cup if it's flour a cup if it's something else how fucking ridiculous is that? just have one bloody weight please</u>
<u n="162" who="S0589"><unclear/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0588">or one weight for liquid and one weight for which is the British millilitres or</u>
<u n="164" who="S0589">millilitres</u>
<u n="165" who="S0588" trans="overlap">hold on though is the weight?</u>
<u n="166" who="S0589">a fluid ounce you get</u>
<u n="167" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah so it's the same it's an ounce or it's a fluid ounce but it's the same if you were no is it the same?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0589">what? not by volume no</u>
<u n="169" who="S0588">oh <pause dur="short"/> why isn't a liquid just weighed in ounces? why is it fluid ounces? I know it's fluid but why is it not the same?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0589">I love these little <unclear/></u>
<u n="171" who="S0588" trans="overlap">is it cos it's a lot heavier?</u>
<u n="172" who="S0589">well some things are oil would be heavier than water cos it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="173" who="S0588" trans="overlap">oh there are so many things in life to learn I don't mind learning it it's just it's never done is it?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0589" trans="overlap">look darling it's a little miniature railway</u>
<u n="175" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yes sweet <pause dur="short"/> where are we heading now?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0589">gosh look you can see look at all the cement that falls off <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="178" who="S0589" trans="overlap">in those big piles they look like termite mounds</u>
<u n="179" who="S0588">we're looking at another for the benefit of the recording</u>
<u n="180" who="S0589">oh darling</u>
<u n="181" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0589">it annoys me we're not</u>
<u n="183" who="S0588" trans="overlap">no I know</u>
<u n="184" who="S0589"><unclear/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0588" trans="overlap">we I'm just being funny and going</u>
<u n="186" who="S0589">look</u>
<u n="187" who="S0588">we're looking at another thingamajig</u>
<u n="188" who="S0589">look</u>
<u n="189" who="S0588">oh look at that one</u>
<u n="190" who="S0589" trans="overlap">there's so much spillage darling it's created a little sandbank</u>
<u n="191" who="S0588">yeah <pause dur="long"/> so</u>
<u n="192" who="S0589" trans="overlap">that will be the wind the wind blowing it off onto this pathway <pause dur="short"/> it's industrial waste effectively it's just sand</u>
<u n="193" who="S0588">yeah I don't know what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> thinks of us today it's like where the fuck have they gone?</u>
<u n="194" who="S0589">yeah I was thinking earlier on</u>
<u n="195" who="S0588" trans="overlap">he's gonna go off on a</u>
<u n="196" who="S0589" trans="overlap">A he would quite like to explore</u>
<u n="197" who="S0588" trans="overlap">awol</u>
<u n="198" who="S0589">that factory we've just been past</u>
<u n="199" who="S0588" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="200" who="S0589">and B this is well outside his normal roaming territory</u>
<u n="201" who="S0588">it is if he lived here he'd quite enjoy it and he would enjoy looking at the ducks <pause dur="long"/> careful <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>wha</trunc> er what is wrong with using your fucking bell? sorry darling</u>
<u n="202" who="S0589">I think you're a bit tipsy</u>
<u n="203" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="204" who="S0589"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="205" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/> sorry darling half a pint and I'm fucking shouting at cyclists <pause dur="short"/> there's another signpost Thames Path Greenwich Peninsula east mm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>greenwi</trunc>Greenwich Cutty Sark is two and a quarter miles <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> so that's</u>
<u n="206" who="S0589">look darling here's a little er erm shipyard there's little sailing boats that would be pretty</u>
<u n="207" who="S0588">I wish people would use their bells you nearly got run over then</u>
<u n="208" who="S0589">I know you worry about me would have punched the living daylights into him and then thrown his bike into the Thames would you have reported me to the police?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0588"><trunc>wha</trunc> er for what?</u>
<u n="210" who="S0589" trans="overlap">no beating him senseless and then throwing his bike in the Thames had he struck you for instance</u>
<u n="211" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0589" trans="overlap">I would have been merciless</u>
<u n="213" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="214" who="S0589">in my <pause dur="short"/> revenge</u>
<u n="215" who="S0588" trans="overlap">ah <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> really <pause dur="short"/> nice <pause dur="short"/> no I don't like the way they call it a Thames Path and then</u>
<u n="216" who="S0589">ah this the yacht club so there is a pub called The Yacht or at least a bar but it might be this place here <pause dur="short"/> it's shut <pause dur="short"/> we've walked all the way to a yacht club we've done well darling it's like being in er <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0589">oh look at this</u>
<u n="219" who="S0588">we've done very well it's only two and a quarter miles to the Cutty Sark now</u>
<u n="220" who="S0589">didn't is that the one that burnt down?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0588">erm I think it has a couple of times hasn't it? <pause dur="short"/> I mean it can't be the Cutty Sark any more if it's <vocal desc="laugh"/> burnt down twice <pause dur="short"/> er there's like one plank of wood that's left of the original Cutty Sark</u>
<u n="222" who="S0589" trans="overlap">well that's like the philosophical question about the broom</u>
<u n="223" who="S0588" trans="overlap">well the it's the broom is a broom still a broom if you replace the end of it and then you replace the handle?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0589">is it the same broom?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0588">is it the same broom?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0589" trans="overlap">the other philosophical</u>
<u n="227" who="S0588">or is a girl band still a girl band</u>
<u n="228" who="S0589">it's like that</u>
<u n="229" who="S0588">if you keep replacing the members? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="230" who="S0589">but the other philosophical question is</u>
<u n="231" who="S0588">oh</u>
<u n="232" who="S0589">which should we go darling? right</u>
<u n="233" who="S0588"><unclear>why?</unclear></u>
<u n="234" who="S0589">is this a ship sets out <pause dur="short"/> a wooden ship it's on a round-the-world voyage and of course during however long it takes it repairs itself so that by the time it gets back to port none of the original bits are the same but is it still the same ship?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0588">no</u>
<u n="236" who="S0589" trans="overlap">cos normally you'd say yes</u>
<u n="237" who="S0588">well oh god it's a really philosophical question though</u>
<u n="238" who="S0589" trans="overlap">but then oh but there's a secondary part of the question this is there's another ship that follows the first ship and every bit of wood they discard they cobble together to make a boat <pause dur="short"/> so is that? which one when they get back is the</u>
<u n="239" who="S0588" trans="overlap">is the ship? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0589">is the ship that left? the so so when does? this that should be a little er</u>
<u n="241" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="242" who="S0589">bar the yacht club there</u>
<u n="243" who="S0588">yeah it probably is</u>
<u n="244" who="S0589" trans="overlap">oh there's an old man that sails darling sweet he's not that old</u>
<u n="245" who="S0588">he's not he's young <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0589" trans="overlap">he's older than me</u>
<u n="247" who="S0588">he's about the same age I think</u>
<u n="248" who="S0589" trans="overlap">look there's a bit of sculpture</u>
<u n="249" who="S0588">oh yes <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0589">is there <unclear/>? or do you have to be a member?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0588">yeah it doesn't look very public</u>
<u n="252" who="S0589">well but there is The Yacht</u>
<u n="253" who="S0588">well it I don't know that would say The Yacht though wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="254" who="S0589">it would make it more obvious yes</u>
<u n="255" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="256" who="S0589">maybe it was up that bit <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0588">I wonder if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s in er another country at the moment</u>
<u n="258" who="S0589" trans="overlap">probably yes</u>
<u n="259" who="S0588">there's something up there something riverside</u>
<u n="260" who="S0589">I still get her email I'm back</u>
<u n="261" who="S0588">yeah I do as well</u>
<u n="262" who="S0589" trans="overlap">or I get her text and I always reply thanks god</u>
<u n="263" who="S0588">yes <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0589">platinum</u>
<u n="265" who="S0588">riverside</u>
<u n="266" who="S0589">riverside they're gross they we'll have to look we've almost at the er</u>
<u n="267" who="S0588">the Dome</u>
<u n="268" who="S0589">we're not though cos I think it just doubles right back and then comes right</u>
<u n="269" who="S0588" trans="overlap">do you think that's an illusion?</u>
<u n="270" who="S0589">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="271" who="S0588">I've never actually been to the Dome</u>
<u n="272" who="S0589">I went to the</u>
<u n="273" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I've been past it many times</u>
<u n="274" who="S0589">I've been once to go to the Brits launch party</u>
<u n="275" who="S0588">to think they were just gonna build it and then knock it down again I mean how ridiculous is that?</u>
<u n="276" who="S0589">little activity centre <trunc>d</trunc> oh there's the peninsula</u>
<u n="277" who="S0588" trans="overlap">oh sweet</u>
<u n="278" who="S0589">ecology park</u>
<u n="279" who="S0588">yes there it is look</u>
<u n="280" who="S0589">nice</u>
<u n="281" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="282" who="S0589" trans="overlap">look both ways so actually we could have walked all the way round that maybe</u>
<u n="283" who="S0588">it's quite sweet</u>
<u n="284" who="S0589" trans="overlap">it's just basically <trunc>w</trunc> it's just weed beds then</u>
<u n="285" who="S0588">it there's lots of wildlife in there <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0589">loud industrial noises aren't there?</u>
<u n="287" who="S0588">yeah <pause dur="short"/> that's that boat making that noise</u>
<u n="288" who="S0589">is it?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0588">what is <anon type="place"/>? oh it's a er</u>
<u n="290" who="S0589">dull isn't</u>
<u n="291" who="S0588" trans="overlap">customer centre for the flats</u>
<u n="292" who="S0589">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well Royal Greenwich it ain't <pause dur="short"/> look I mean they could have built something like that which is actually pretty horrible <pause dur="short"/> isn't it dear?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0588">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I mean there's actually not much difference</u>
<u n="294" who="S0589" trans="overlap">instead</u>
<u n="295" who="S0588">between council flats and those</u>
<u n="296" who="S0589" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="297" who="S0588">this is what always</u>
<u n="298" who="S0589" trans="overlap">and instead of the riverside</u>
<u n="299" who="S0588">kind of makes me quite</u>
<u n="300" who="S0589" trans="overlap">the riverside used lovely er bricks throughout <pause dur="short"/> even though it's not you know you wouldn't say it's architecturally</u>
<u n="301" who="S0588">no they've done</u>
<u n="302" who="S0589" trans="overlap">amazing</u>
<u n="303" who="S0588" trans="overlap">a good job</u>
<u n="304" who="S0589" trans="overlap">but it's</u>
<u n="305" who="S0588">definitely</u>
<u n="306" who="S0589">it's alright certainly not an eyesore</u>
<u n="307" who="S0588">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's gonna be really nice I mean and it is really nice <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> never been <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> pier ah we can get the boat from there <pause dur="short"/> we could go either way <pause dur="short"/> we could get a boat then to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> for example <pause dur="long"/> yeah of course I might be out of action for a whole week after this walk I don't know what's going to happen <pause dur="short"/> I usually have to pace things <pause dur="long"/> but I don't feel like stopping <pause dur="short"/> and it's getting cold though</u>
<u n="308" who="S0589">it's cold</u>
<u n="309" who="S0588" trans="overlap">it's colder than it was</u>
<u n="310" who="S0589">I'm now glad I'm wearing a woolly hat</u>
<u n="311" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="312" who="S0589">cos having previously gone gone through a period of thinking maybe I didn't need one <pause dur="short"/> and now now I do</u>
<u n="313" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="314" who="S0589">very glad I have <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0588">yep <pause dur="long"/> it's better than landing in Oxford Street and then you've still gotta get home and you're knackered <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> that is horrible</u>
<u n="316" who="S0589">yeah <pause dur="short"/> strange</u>
<u n="317" who="S0588">yep all strange <pause dur="short"/> very strange <pause dur="short"/> that's my general view is it's strange <pause dur="short"/> what is this fucking thing I've been</u>
<u n="318" who="S0589">what is it good for?</u>
<u n="319" who="S0588">dumped in? <pause dur="short"/> it's all strange <pause dur="short"/> very clever but strange <pause dur="long"/> what's the next pub going to be?</u>
<u n="320" who="S0589"><unclear/></u>
<u n="321" who="S0588">oh is that <unclear/>? I thought it was here</u>
<u n="322" who="S0589" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/> probably that's the second longest walk last time would have been that Cornish walk</u>
<u n="323" who="S0588">oh my god</u>
<u n="324" who="S0589" trans="overlap">that you did not enjoy and you were like a <trunc>bothers</trunc> troublesome twosome</u>
<u n="325" who="S0588">oh my god</u>
<u n="326" who="S0589"><unclear/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0588">well you see that is my perfect example <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this is why I don't like going on holiday with families it's like what could I fucking do? go no I'm not going <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="328" who="S0589">you wanted to watch telly</u>
<u n="329" who="S0588">yeah I did wanna watch telly what the fuck's wrong with that? it's a fucking holiday I don't wanna bloody</u>
<u n="330" who="S0589" trans="overlap">the <unclear/> hotel</u>
<u n="331" who="S0588" trans="overlap">wanna bloody</u>
<u n="332" who="S0589">that's just weird</u>
<u n="333" who="S0588" trans="overlap">break my back on a holiday <pause dur="short"/> I was already working really hard <pause dur="short"/> oh but no got to go on this big long walk along the cliffs <pause dur="short"/> and but my point is how can I go no I'm not going? I mean you can't <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can you? hello?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0589">no</u>
<u n="335" who="S0588">so there you go you can't so</u>
<u n="336" who="S0589"><unclear/></u>
<u n="337" who="S0588" trans="overlap">to just go in the first place is a compromise cos you're gonna end up having to do stuff you don't want to do I mean actually stuff that's probably bad for you in fact cos if you're meant to pace yourself because of your energy levels and all sorts for example if you've got ME or something</u>
<u n="338" who="S0589">so look darling <unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> if we crossed the river there's probably some of those weird like Pontoon Dock where the DLR stops</u>
<u n="339" who="S0588">hold on the peninsula we've lost the Millennium Dome that's odd</u>
<u n="340" who="S0589">straight ahead</u>
<u n="341" who="S0588" trans="overlap">oh there it is</u>
<u n="342" who="S0589">they look like cranes</u>
<u n="343" who="S0588">so are we gonna see the peninsula going to the?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0589">it's also the</u>
<u n="345" who="S0588" trans="overlap">hold on are we gonna go that way? there's a pier there the</u>
<u n="346" who="S0589" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="347" who="S0588" trans="overlap">that's the what pier is that Greenwich? no north</u>
<u n="348" who="S0589"><unclear/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0588">no North Greenwich I think Millennium Dome yeah</u>
<u n="350" who="S0589">no North Greenwich is north of the river</u>
<u n="351" who="S0588">oh</u>
<u n="352" who="S0589">isn't it?</u>
<u n="353" who="S0588">can't remember the name of the pier</u>
<u n="354" who="S0589">maybe not actually no you're right it is this side of the water actually</u>
<u n="355" who="S0588">well north of the main Greenwich presumably they're talking about</u>
<u n="356" who="S0589">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="357" who="S0588">look there's a sculpture</u>
<u n="358" who="S0589">yes I mentioned that already</u>
<u n="359" who="S0588">oh</u>
<u n="360" who="S0589">look at the lovely weed bank that's growing here</u>
<u n="361" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0589">that looks</u>
<u n="363" who="S0588">very nice there's er lots of information here <pause dur="long"/> why are we going up here?</u>
<u n="364" who="S0589">got to be safe <pause dur="short"/> just this one then</u>
<u n="365" who="S0588">safe from what?</u>
<u n="366" who="S0589">darling <unclear/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0588">yeah I don't think I want to go back yet</u>
<u n="368" who="S0589">well we'll probably end up having a drink and supper</u>
<u n="369" who="S0588">but I wonder where we'll end up how far would we make it I wonder? suppose if we carried on and carried on we'd end up at Bankside</u>
<u n="370" who="S0589">could this be if I wanted to save a hundred and seventy-six pounds a month</u>
<u n="371" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="372" who="S0589">and commuted to work by doing this walk</u>
<u n="373" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0589">and I'd have to get up at sort of half past four</u>
<u n="375" who="S0588" trans="overlap">hold on though if you cycled how would you? you'd go along here to where? and then you'd you could go across the Millennium Bridge <pause dur="short"/> and then to Holborn from there couldn't you?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0589" trans="overlap">look here's this stupid thing</u>
<u n="377" who="S0588">that nobody uses</u>
<u n="378" who="S0589">I don't think these</u>
<u n="379" who="S0588" trans="overlap">no it would be pretty exhausting but you could</u>
<u n="380" who="S0589">I'd love to climb that ladder <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="381" who="S0588">you'd probably spend the money on food that you'd need for the energy the money you'd save up to <trunc>twe</trunc> two hundred pounds a month probably how much is your travel card? about a hundred and eighty isn't it?</u>
<u n="382" who="S0589" trans="overlap">one seven six well it's probably gone up actually it's maybe one eighty now</u>
<u n="383" who="S0588">yeah <pause dur="short"/> as good as two hundred <pause dur="short"/> crazy <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> that would be pretty knackering <vocal desc="laugh"/> imagine reaching the end of the day and you've still got to get all the way back <pause dur="long"/> no many times I've <trunc>s</trunc>stopped on the ferry on the Clipper there <pause dur="short"/> been on the Clipper there's one there <pause dur="long"/> they're amazing structures though I don't really know why they built it what was the idea? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0589"><unclear>pineapples</unclear> I miss it when you <unclear/> your arm look at that building darling with round windows mum would want to know exactly what that is</u>
<u n="385" who="S0588">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0589"><unclear/></u>
<u n="387" who="S0588">er <pause dur="short"/> loud <unclear>itching</unclear> <pause dur="long"/> no I want my arms free</u>
<u n="388" who="S0589">it's nice and warm and secure</u>
<u n="389" who="S0588">I know later on</u>
<u n="390" who="S0589">couples like walking don't they?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="392" who="S0589">it's mainly couples <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0588">ah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0589" trans="overlap">oh there's something called the Meantime Beer Box</u>
<u n="395" who="S0588">where? is that a pub?</u>
<u n="396" who="S0589">yeah Meantime</u>
<u n="397" who="S0588">where?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0589">we should go there it might be quite fun</u>
<u n="399" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah where is it though? I can't see it</u>
<u n="400" who="S0589" trans="overlap">it's in that behind those buildings there</u>
<u n="401" who="S0588" trans="overlap">oh not along the path?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0589">in fact I remember we once we once erm walked past it when we got dropped off by <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and</u>
<u n="403" who="S0588">yes that was I remember seeing that</u>
<u n="404" who="S0589">yeah what's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s partner called again?</u>
<u n="405" who="S0588"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="406" who="S0589"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="407" who="S0588">where is the next pub? I'm getting tired</u>
<u n="408" who="S0589" trans="overlap">it's funny though if you think how long we've been walking yet when we jump in the car with granny you know we're we're only just beyond <pause dur="short"/> we're only beyond say the TK Maxx or the B and Q</u>
<u n="409" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah but it's a different world not driving</u>
<u n="410" who="S0589">it's a different world</u>
<u n="411" who="S0588">it's a different reality</u>
<u n="412" who="S0589">a different reality</u>
<u n="413" who="S0588" trans="overlap">and your mum is firmly in the reality of driving</u>
<u n="414" who="S0589">look here's the Dome then darling we've never been there</u>
<u n="415" who="S0588" trans="overlap">and so many people are</u>
<u n="416" who="S0589">be the closest you've ever been</u>
<u n="417" who="S0588" trans="overlap">and they only know the reality of driving</u>
<u n="418" who="S0589">darling?</u>
<u n="419" who="S0588">yeah it is <pause dur="short"/> big umbrella <pause dur="long"/> where's the next pub? I want to sit down <pause dur="long"/> look there's a Clipper over there</u>
<u n="420" who="S0589">yeah there it is</u>
<u n="421" who="S0588" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="422" who="S0589"><unclear/> on the pier look here look darling here's another public artwork</u>
<u n="423" who="S0588">I do not like that I don't want to <pause dur="short"/> where I I've lost Canary Wharf now is it gonna pop up again in a minute?</u>
<u n="424" who="S0589">it'll be there <pause dur="short"/> oh look that's where we used to live</u>
<u n="425" who="S0588">is it? I thought I saw</u>
<u n="426" who="S0589" trans="overlap">can you see the little tower?</u>
<u n="427" who="S0588">yeah <pause dur="short"/> is that Anish Kapoor?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0589">erm</u>
<u n="429" who="S0588" trans="overlap">or am I thinking of someone else?</u>
<u n="430" who="S0589">could well be Anish Kapoor sponsored by Mittal with the erm the metal</u>
<u n="431" who="S0588" trans="overlap">no stop it</u>
<u n="432" who="S0589">what went wrong there?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0588">I had decided I did not want to do that and you grabbed it anyway</u>
<u n="434" who="S0589">do you get a lot of arguments you have to transcribe?</u>
<u n="435" who="S0588">er littles ones</u>
<u n="436" who="S0589">like that?</u>
<u n="437" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="438" who="S0589">mainly is it girls telling off boys?</u>
<u n="439" who="S0588">erm yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0589">that was sort of an observation you could have made</u>
<u n="441" who="S0588"><trunc>n</trunc> well that's not really about the language though</u>
<u n="442" who="S0589">no it's not mainly</u>
<u n="443" who="S0588">that was actually quite hard to do</u>
<u n="444" who="S0589">I can hear a gig darling</u>
<u n="445" who="S0588">but there was one thing I</u>
<u n="446" who="S0589" trans="overlap">can you hear the gig?</u>
<u n="447" who="S0588">there was also something and I forgot to put it in oh yeah the use really? really? <vocal desc="laugh"/> er people didn't used to use it in a cynical tone <pause dur="short"/> really? erm try to name the band</u>
<u n="448" who="S0589">are we looking at the back stage area? <pause dur="short"/> well it sounds like erm</u>
<u n="449" who="S0588">it sounds like Dolly Parton</u>
<u n="450" who="S0589" trans="overlap">what's that <trunc>c</trunc> Dolly Parton I was gonna say yeah maybe it's a country and western festival here today darling look there's the backstage area all the talent hanging out</u>
<u n="451" who="S0588">the green room</u>
<u n="452" who="S0589">there's Canary Wharf darling</u>
<u n="453" who="S0588">oh look</u>
<u n="454" who="S0589"><unclear/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0588">the beacon of hope I want a pub <pause dur="short"/> yeah we need a pub now it's far too long without a pub</u>
<u n="456" who="S0589">well do you want to start thinking about doubling back via the Meantime glass box?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0588">no cos that's horrible really it's just on that big road</u>
<u n="458" who="S0589">yeah but then the bus takes us home outside</u>
<u n="459" who="S0588" trans="overlap">oh no horrible</u>
<u n="460" who="S0589">sorry darling</u>
<u n="461" who="S0588">don't wanna ruin it like that</u>
<u n="462" who="S0589"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh am I ruining it?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0588">yeah I'd rather have a boat get a boat</u>
<u n="464" who="S0589">all the people in the roof darling look</u>
<u n="465" who="S0588">oh yeah</u>
<u n="466" who="S0589">are they supposed to be there darling?</u>
<u n="467" who="S0588">yeah <pause dur="short"/> not sure what they're doing <pause dur="long"/> if we double back we've got to walk along a bloody</u>
<u n="468" who="S0589">a big curve in the river isn't it? what are they doing?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0588">there's a walkway I think they're walking on it <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="470" who="S0589">when I was a little boy I went on a fifty mile walk had to get up at about three AM</u>
<u n="471" who="S0588">oh</u>
<u n="472" who="S0589" trans="overlap">didn't get back till midnight</u>
<u n="473" who="S0588">oh my god</u>
<u n="474" who="S0589">there they are it's very steep <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="475" who="S0588">they must be abseiling down that surely <pause dur="long"/> I think it's just a lookout post</u>
<u n="476" who="S0589">yeah no look they're starting to make their way down they must be roped</u>
<u n="477" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="478" who="S0589">very gingerly <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> darling <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0588">right I think one more sit down and then we have a little think about what we do next so next pub we sit down <pause dur="short"/> there's not very many are there? you'd think there'd be more along the way <pause dur="short"/> stop it</u>
<u n="480" who="S0589">stop it am I allowed to do that?</u>
<u n="481" who="S0588">well you are aren't you darling?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0589" trans="overlap">oh dear</u>
<u n="483" who="S0588">yes you are you are allowed getting tired</u>
<u n="484" who="S0589">and grouchy</u>
<u n="485" who="S0588">no I'm not grouchy the river's very nice but I want a boat back not erm a horrible bus ride <pause dur="long"/> there's another notice another signpost <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="486" who="S0589">oh look at that darling <pause dur="long"/> that's a horrible building <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0588">it is a bit odd walking along with <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="sound of wind"/>
<u n="488" who="S0588">careful <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="short"/> what would you call that? a tri-tricycle?</u>
<u n="489" who="S0589">dunno can't be very good for your erm hips I can see a bar look at that darling</u>
<u n="490" who="S0588">is that a hotel or something?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0589">a hotel bar isn't it I'm not sure</u>
<u n="492" who="S0588" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="493" who="S0589">it's open yet though <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="494" who="S0588">ballroom <pause dur="long"/> need loo break need pub</u>
<u n="495" who="S0589">what's it called?</u>
<u n="496" who="S0588">something <trunc>A</trunc> or <trunc>A</trunc>Arora</u>
<u n="497" who="S0589">Arora <pause dur="short"/> ballroom darling <pause dur="short"/> london the O2 <pause dur="short"/> used to be a pier</u>
<u n="498" who="S0588">yeah <pause dur="long"/> I'll be suntanned tomorrow</u>
<u n="499" who="S0589">sorry darling</u>
<u n="500" who="S0588">mm <pause dur="long"/> well there's Canary Wharf over the river</u>
<u n="501" who="S0589">look it's like having <unclear/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0588">yeah so er I see we're <pause dur="short"/> we're going round veering left</u>
<u n="503" who="S0589" trans="overlap">and then we double back for miles</u>
<u n="504" who="S0588">and then <pause dur="short"/> it's so windy</u>
<u n="505" who="S0589">windy</u>
<u n="506" who="S0588">yep</u>
<u n="507" who="S0589">that's one of the words we were looking for</u>
<u n="508" who="S0588" trans="overlap">well I was looking for another word for windy</u>
<u n="509" who="S0589">well windy is</u>
<u n="510" who="S0588" trans="overlap">you said meandering but I don't think that's very descriptive</u>
<u n="511" who="S0589">I think windy is best one so far</u>
<u n="512" who="S0588">too much like windy</u>
<u n="513" who="S0589">they're spelt the same</u>
<u n="514" who="S0588">I think it is spelt the same</u>
<event desc="sound of wind"/>
<u n="515" who="S0589"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0588"><shift new="singing"/> the long and the long and winding road <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="517" who="S0589">that's it winding</u>
<u n="518" who="S0588"><shift new="singing"/> that leads to your door it'll never disappear seen that road before it always leads me here lead me to your door <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="519" who="S0589">what on earth is that thing?</u>
<u n="520" who="S0588">oh fuck there's no sign of a pub anywhere oh my god <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> many times I've been around and many times I've tried many ways you'll never know <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> but still you lead me back to the long winding road <shift new="normal"/> <pause dur="short"/> <shift new="singing"/> has left me full of tears a long long time ago <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0589">well the hotel's clearly open I wonder why no one's in the bar that's where I would be</u>
<u n="522" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0589">yes <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0588">oh this is far too far away from the bloody Thames <pause dur="short"/> and this this is just wasteland now it's not good at all</u>
<u n="525" who="S0589">well it's all being developed</u>
<u n="526" who="S0588">yeah well developed into what?</u>
<u n="527" who="S0589">er hotels</u>
<u n="528" who="S0588">yeah crap</u>
<u n="529" who="S0589">oh look it is a country and western festival he's wearing a Stetson</u>
<u n="530" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah I think that was probably</u>
<u n="531" who="S0589" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0588">Dolly Parton</u>
<u n="533" who="S0589">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="534" who="S0588">mm</u>
<u n="535" who="S0589">oh and she's wearing cowboy boots</u>
<u n="536" who="S0588">ah they're having fun</u>
<u n="537" who="S0589">yes how they met</u>
<u n="538" who="S0588">yes look there's the DLR there</u>
<u n="539" who="S0589">really? yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0588">but there's well <unclear>Jubilee</unclear> I can see the sign</u>
<u n="541" who="S0589">in North Greenwich</u>
<u n="542" who="S0588">mm <vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="long"/> oh I do think we should go to one more place before we go back what do you think?</u>
<u n="543" who="S0589">okay darling <unclear/> where cos that is the <unclear/> cos we wandered when the DLR wasn't working that's where we got the bus from</u>
<u n="544" who="S0588">that's where we get a bus from then it's good to know doesn't look like there's anything <pause dur="short"/> on the horizon literally <pause dur="short"/> and we've not eaten either</u>
<u n="545" who="S0589"><unclear/> er since that's where the buses for the talent</u>
<u n="546" who="S0588">I need the loo</u>
<u n="547" who="S0589" trans="overlap">when you when you play the O2 darling that's where we'll they'll drop you off</u>
<u n="548" who="S0588">yeah <pause dur="long"/> mm now I am getting knackered</u>
<u n="549" who="S0589"><vocal desc="sigh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="550" who="S0588">I mean it's sterile personally in my opinion</u>
<u n="551" who="S0589">it's <unclear/></u>
<u n="552" who="S0588">if you're gonna build something you'd I mean</u>
<u n="553" who="S0589">it's also a boring bit of the walk</u>
<u n="554" who="S0588">yeah completely</u>
<u n="555" who="S0589">there VIP walk</u>
<u n="556" who="S0588">I'm not inspired</u>
<u n="557" who="S0589" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="558" who="S0588">when am I gonna be inspired again? <pause dur="long"/> it's boring</u>
<u n="559" who="S0589">get the <unclear>pers-inf</unclear> no it goes to down <anon type="place"/> high street <pause dur="short"/> am I right?</u>
<u n="560" who="S0588">don't know <pause dur="short"/> yeah it sounds familiar we could get <pause dur="long"/> god</u>
<u n="561" who="S0589">that's what that big net was it's a fucking golf driving range <unclear/> in front of us</u>
<u n="562" who="S0588">I went to a driving range once with my parents they were going to get into golf at one point but</u>
<u n="563" who="S0589">I cannot imagine them</u>
<u n="564" who="S0588">yeah well no the thing is it kind of fits their sort of erm <pause dur="short"/> their demographic did you know snobby middle class</u>
<u n="565" who="S0589">right darling what are we doing?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0588">I don't know what's that over there?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0589" trans="overlap">is that the end of our walk? or do we carry on going up?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0588">I wanted to go to one more place</u>
<u n="569" who="S0589">well there's the Meantime Box</u>
<u n="570" who="S0588">no that's not a place <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0589">why is it not a place?</u>
<u n="572" who="S0588">it's only a place for the beer it's not a place though</u>
<u n="573" who="S0589" trans="overlap">well then define what you meant by one more place</u>
<u n="574" who="S0588">by the river</u>
<u n="575" who="S0589"><vocal desc="laugh"/> okay darling</u>
<u n="576" who="S0588">somewhere pretty and nice</u>
<u n="577" who="S0589">look there's an Irish dancing festival</u>
<u n="578" who="S0588" trans="overlap">not a thing <vocal desc="laugh"/> sweet <pause dur="short"/> not a bloody box on a main road that's not a place <pause dur="long"/> oh looks like there's ages before we get to a place though</u>
<u n="579" who="S0589" trans="overlap">well that's why you've got to make a decision</u>
<u n="580" who="S0588" trans="overlap">mm where does this bus stop go to?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0589">it's not a bus stop I think it's more of a shuttle service is it?</u>
<u n="582" who="S0588">dunno</u>
<u n="583" who="S0589">probably</u>
<u n="584" who="S0588">oh</u>
<u n="585" who="S0589">don't know darling anyway I can't even see the Thames</u>
<u n="586" who="S0588">no</u>
<u n="587" who="S0589">except just look oh that's the Blackwall Tunnel that's the erm I recognise that archway dear</u>
<u n="588" who="S0588">which means what? we</u>
<u n="589" who="S0589" trans="overlap">nothing</u>
<u n="590" who="S0588" trans="overlap">could go to <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="591" who="S0589">we can't walk in the tunnel</u>
<u n="592" who="S0588">oh fuck this is really boring <pause dur="short"/> what's that bit?</u>
<u n="593" who="S0589">don't know darling</u>
<u n="594" who="S0588" trans="overlap">there it's probably an industrial thing</u>
<u n="595" who="S0589">what?</u>
<u n="596" who="S0588">it's got a green sign on it no oh I just wanted to go to one more place <pause dur="short"/> this is crap <pause dur="long"/> I think it's a bit criminal to block it off like that</u>
<u n="597" who="S0589">for a golf range and a car park <pause dur="long"/> I think we're probably gonna end up in the glass box at this rate anyway even though it's not a place it is somewhere warm</u>
<u n="598" who="S0588" trans="overlap">it's not a place</u>
<u n="599" who="S0589" trans="overlap">where we can go to the loo and</u>
<u n="600" who="S0588">I mean is it even open?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0589">yep <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="602" who="S0588">oh for fuck's sake it's got really boring <pause dur="long"/> it was good up until this happened</u>
<u n="603" who="S0589">well now we know darling</u>
<u n="604" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah at the O2 it gets shit <pause dur="short"/> but I thought the Thames walk was meant to carry on past the O2 oh no</u>
<u n="605" who="S0589" trans="overlap">to the Thames Path</u>
<u n="606" who="S0588">yeah well that doesn't look like the Thames Path it looks like away from the Thames Path</u>
<u n="607" who="S0589">you'll end up</u>
<u n="608" who="S0588">I do want to have a sit down and a loo break so we will have to we might have to go to the box <pause dur="long"/> the box that's not a place <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="609" who="S0589">no?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0588">no got disappointed now I wanted to go to another nice place before we go home well if we head back to <anon type="place"/> there's nice places there let's just get on the bus back to <anon type="place"/> we could go to the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> let's do that bus back then stop at the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="611" who="S0589">we're not too far from the glass box now</u>
<u n="612" who="S0588">oh how far?</u>
<u n="613" who="S0589" trans="overlap">might as well see if we can reach it and then</u>
<u n="614" who="S0588" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="615" who="S0589">and if we can't find it then we'll <unclear>gets</unclear> a bus a bus from the <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> tower that is</u>
<u n="616" who="S0588">look how long I want to know though how long before we'd get back to a nice walk by the Thames if you reach this point?</u>
<event desc="sound of wind"/>
<u n="617" who="S0589">come from there because it's such a <pause dur="short"/> bend</u>
<event desc="sound of wind"/>
<u n="618" who="S0588">well maybe you need to start it from here and get a bus from here <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="619" who="S0589">what does that building say that's just down there up ahead in the red?</u>
<u n="620" who="S0588">Emirates</u>
<u n="621" who="S0589">oh that's the hub that's the hub for the er so we've just done a big circle really cos we were there about an hour ago <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0588">do not want to be walking along main roads though and now I'm knackered need food as well <pause dur="long"/> so I think it was nice up until well it was nice till that give or take the odd annoying bit it was nice to the <anon type="place"/> that was nice</u>
<u n="623" who="S0589">come and see what this building is all about</u>
<u n="624" who="S0588">if you want a bus we can get one here</u>
<u n="625" who="S0589">yeah but I'm wondering if that is the brewery there darling</u>
<u n="626" who="S0588">could be</u>
<u n="627" who="S0589" trans="overlap">oh yeah shall we pop in there?</u>
<u n="628" who="S0588">okay</u>
<u n="629" who="S0589">loo break beer break</u>
<u n="630" who="S0588">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="631" who="S0589" trans="overlap">probably have coffee</u>
<u n="632" who="S0588">well it looks looks promising</u>
<u n="633" who="S0589">probably have coffee in there darling</u>
<u n="634" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah oh coffee would be nice actually</u>
<u n="635" who="S0589" trans="overlap">I thought you might like a coffee</u>
<u n="636" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0589">we don't need to go round it though why can't we just walk do you want to climb across?</u>
<u n="638" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0589">is that <unclear/> or not?</u>
<u n="640" who="S0588">well you might get <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="641" who="S0589">there it is that's Meantime Yalla Yalla there Yalla Yalla</u>
<u n="642" who="S0588">is that a brewery is it?</u>
<u n="643" who="S0589">I think they have a brewery <unclear/> yeah <pause dur="long"/> just look at my shoes</u>
<u n="644" who="S0588">good <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they're good shoes of course er oh <vocal desc="laugh"/> I've never been here this is the O2 <pause dur="short"/> look Meantime</u>
<u n="645" who="S0589">is there?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0588">a pub <pause dur="short"/> we've reached a destination darling oh look there's a Meantime pub there</u>
<u n="647" who="S0589">that's where I wanted to go</u>
<u n="648" who="S0588">there's a Wagamama</u>
<u n="649" who="S0589">what's this one?</u>
<u n="650" who="S0588">I don't know something else</u>
<u n="651" who="S0589">bar</u>
<u n="652" who="S0588" trans="overlap">bar restaurant bar there's a Subway there's a Modern British Kitchen</u>
<u n="653" who="S0589">oh I've been to Yalla Yalla before</u>
<u n="654" who="S0588">Lebanese <pause dur="short"/> a great big horrible Subway this looks alright <pause dur="long"/> oh</u>
<u n="655" who="S0589">hello</u>
<u n="656" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">hello</u>
<u n="657" who="S0588">hello <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="658" who="S0589">er just wanna have a look around</u>
<u n="659" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay yeah</u>
<u n="660" who="S0589">is it just this area?</u>
<u n="661" who="UNKMALE" whoConfidence="low">er yes er we do do <unclear/></u>
<u n="662" who="S0588">could go over there have a?</u>
<u n="663" who="S0589" trans="overlap">well shall we look round first and then come back?</u>
<u n="664" who="S0588">okay we're gonna do a little tour and come back <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="665" who="S0589">oh look at that oh that's different</u>
<u n="666" who="S0588"><unclear/></u>
<u n="667" who="S0589">it goes round the corner it's on <unclear/></u>
<u n="668" who="S0588">is there? <pause dur="short"/> is? there's nothing on this side <pause dur="short"/> but that's that's the pub darling Meantime</u>
<u n="669" who="S0589" trans="overlap">what? there's no I think it isn't</u>
<u n="670" who="S0588" trans="overlap">it's Meantime</u>
<u n="671" who="S0589">yeah but I'm not sure you can sit in</u>
<u n="672" who="S0588">it's a pub</u>
<u n="673" who="S0589">it just looks like a a bar</u>
<u n="674" who="S0588" trans="overlap">no I I think it's somewhere you go in <pause dur="short"/> well we can look round further</u>
<u n="675" who="S0589" trans="overlap">weird a pharmacy</u>
<u n="676" who="S0588">it's a yeah that is weird</u>
<u n="677" who="S0589">there's another <pause dur="short"/> girl in the Stetson <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="678" who="S0588">oh I see what you mean <pause dur="short"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> well I think you can go in can't you? <pause dur="short"/> I'd like to go in <pause dur="short"/> rest my weary legs</u>
<u n="679" who="S0589">I'd quite like the <unclear>pizza pub</unclear></u>
<u n="680" who="S0588">oh no</u>
<u n="681" who="S0589" trans="overlap"><unclear>don't know about that</unclear></u>
<u n="682" who="S0588"><unclear/>?</u>
<u n="683" who="S0589">it's er loud <unclear/></u>
<u n="684" who="S0588">yeah <pause dur="short"/> oh</u>
<u n="685" who="S0589">right what to do then darling get a bus <pause dur="short"/> to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0588">yeah this isn't up to much <pause dur="short"/> I would I did like want the loo though but it think I can wait until the <anon type="place"/> if we get a bus</u>
<u n="687" who="S0589">we could pop into Craft <pause dur="short"/> which would be a er have a half</u>
<u n="688" who="S0588">wouldn't it be a bit obvious though?</u>
<u n="689" who="S0589">no I'd have a half</u>
<u n="690" who="S0588">oh I see <pause dur="short"/> oh no that'll take too long <pause dur="short"/> I want to get back to <anon type="place"/> now</u>
<u n="691" who="S0589">that looks alright that</u>
<u n="692" who="S0588">I would like</u>
<u n="693" who="S0589" trans="overlap">sourdough pizza in a wood oven</u>
<u n="694" who="S0588">yeah it does look alright</u>
<u n="695" who="S0589">is it upstairs? that looks empty <pause dur="short"/> I think only down is open</u>
<u n="696" who="S0588" trans="overlap">it's closed <pause dur="short"/> I want to go home to our home territory now</u>
<u n="697" who="S0589" trans="overlap">right well how do we get home?</u>
<u n="698" who="S0588">a bus</u>
<u n="699" who="S0589">yeah but where are the buses?</u>
<u n="700" who="S0588" trans="overlap">where those buses were <pause dur="short"/> they were this way weren't they? <pause dur="short"/> or did we walk past? <pause dur="long"/> er we want one that goes past the <anon type="place"/> and then I want to get comfortable in <anon type="place"/> where it's warm</u>
<u n="701" who="S0589" trans="overlap">in the <anon type="place"/>? or maybe it would be nice in the</u>
<u n="702" who="S0588">or what? you're thinking of the <anon type="place"/> aren't you? I know you are</u>
<u n="703" who="S0589">no I'm thinking of er the <anon type="place"/> probably quite warm in there and there are seats in there</u>
<u n="704" who="S0588" trans="overlap">oh yeah that would be nice hot drinks and all</u>
<u n="705" who="S0589">need a little something to eat though</u>
<u n="706" who="S0588">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I agree</u>
<u n="707" who="S0589">that's where we are <pause dur="long"/> remember we caught a bus from here?</u>
<u n="708" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yes we nearly ended up on the wrong side of the Thames and we'd have had to swim across <vocal desc="laugh"/> north <anon type="place"/> is not south <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> right how long have we done? oh over an hour here might as well keep going then <pause dur="short"/> I'll just get my card out <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="709" who="S0589">oh the <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> goes to <anon type="place"/> road oh fuck it's just pulled out so does the <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> I think darling</u>
<u n="710" who="S0588">erm I think oh there goes the <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> what about well we're in the right place erm how about next time</u>
<u n="711" who="S0589">next time</u>
<u n="712" who="S0588">we get a bus all the way to here and then we join the walk the Thames walk</u>
<u n="713" who="S0589" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="714" who="S0588">from here</u>
<u n="715" who="S0589"><anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="716" who="S0588">yeah and do another walk</u>
<u n="717" who="S0589"><unclear/> no the <unclear>pers-inf</unclear></u>
<u n="718" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="719" who="S0589">oh there is it? what else is there?</u>
<u n="720" who="S0588">we could go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="721" who="S0589"><anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/></u>
<u n="722" who="S0588" trans="overlap">but I want to go back up to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="long"/> four <pause dur="short"/> that one would have <trunc>d</trunc>done</u>
<u n="723" who="S0589" trans="overlap">goes all the way to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="724" who="S0588">if we went all the way to <anon type="place"/> we could go somewhere in <anon type="place"/> instead</u>
<u n="725" who="S0589">I don't think so dear I don't think any of these help us</u>
<u n="726" who="S0588">erm I'm happy to go to <anon type="place"/> though I'd rather go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="727" who="S0589">you will but how long until that <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/>?</u>
<u n="728" who="S0588">we're here we've got a <trunc>choi</trunc> a choice of two</u>
<u n="729" who="S0589"><unclear/> come on <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="730" who="S0588">is it definitely going the right way? <pause dur="short"/> just ask if it's going to <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="731" who="S0589">it's on the way home</u>
<u n="732" who="S0588"><unclear/></u>
<u n="733" who="S0589">it's going the right direction <pause dur="long"/> oh no</u>
<u n="734" who="S0588">oh</u>
<u n="735" who="S0589">do you want them to move darling?</u>
<u n="736" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> this is alright it's good</u>
<u n="737" who="S0589">oh</u>
<u n="738" who="S0588">got a nice fairly empty bus to <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="739" who="S0589">whoee</u>
<u n="740" who="S0588">no well next time I want to plan our next walk now</u>
<u n="741" who="S0589">I don't think we're ever going to do that again</u>
<u n="742" who="S0588">why not? it was good</u>
<u n="743" who="S0589">oh wasn't good enough to repeat though so</u>
<u n="744" who="S0588">okay but I think we should do the next stage of the walk which means getting past</u>
<u n="745" who="S0589">the O2</u>
<u n="746" who="S0588" trans="overlap">the O2 and getting a bus to the O2 and past it and then joining this walk again and then going <pause dur="short"/> I don't know really it's terrible planning really isn't it of mm London councils? <pause dur="short"/> access to the river should be a given really in my opinion <pause dur="short"/> but no it's a bit like someone builds on the land but they hog the river as well <pause dur="long"/> cos past here we could walk all the way to <anon type="place"/> where I used to work and there's a little farm there <pause dur="long"/> did you enjoy that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="747" who="S0589">yes darling thank you very much</u>
<u n="748" who="S0588">mm am I being annoying now? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="749" who="S0589">I'm tired</u>
<u n="750" who="S0588">yes it was quite tiring at least you haven't got to go to work tomorrow</u>
<u n="751" who="S0589">mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="752" who="S0588">er O2's horrible though isn't it?</u>
<u n="753" who="S0589">yeah</u>
<u n="754" who="S0588">even what they've tried to do there with the places to eat and stuff <pause dur="long"/> it was wasteland before wasn't it? but it's kind of a wasteland sort of a wasteland <pause dur="short"/> another form of a wasteland <pause dur="long"/> I think we'll probably go past your brewery</u>
<u n="755" who="S0589">yeah</u>
<u n="756" who="S0588" trans="overlap">then you</u>
<u n="757" who="S0589" trans="overlap">cos that wasn't it was it?</u>
<u n="758" who="S0588">no you can make a mental note of where it is for future reference so you wouldn't do that walk again then?</u>
<u n="759" who="S0589">not what the entirety of what we've just pub that's it Pilot</u>
<u n="760" who="S0588">oh</u>
<u n="761" who="S0589">that was it</u>
<u n="762" who="S0588">that looks nice</u>
<u n="763" who="S0589">well it's a Fuller's pub which is a bit dull</u>
<u n="764" who="S0588">it looks nice though er er I did really want to go to one more place but</u>
<u n="765" who="S0589">so look we'd walk up from there so you wouldn't go all the way round the Dome and cut across the Peninsula</u>
<u n="766" who="S0588">right</u>
<u n="767" who="S0589">that's that walk right down there and carry on down there until you get to the other side of the Thames then you'll skip that great long circuitous route</u>
<u n="768" who="S0588">mm Millennium Village <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="769" who="S0589">look that's a primary school weird so</u>
<u n="770" who="S0588">it's meant to be a a self-contained little village isn't it?</u>
<u n="771" who="S0589" trans="overlap">a community</u>
<u n="772" who="S0588">yeah <pause dur="short"/> a community <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="773" who="S0589">London's favourite village <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="774" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah right</u>
<u n="775" who="S0589">Chinese restaurant</u>
<u n="776" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="777" who="S0589">and there's the Imax darling</u>
<u n="778" who="S0588">oh yeah here we are <pause dur="short"/> nearly home <vocal desc="laugh"/> I wonder what's on at the Imax shall we go and see a film?</u>
<u n="779" who="S0589">tell you what the Beer Box is somewhere it's somewhere over there isn't it?</u>
<u n="780" who="S0588">who knows?</u>
<u n="781" who="S0589">go to TK Maxx</u>
<u n="782" who="S0588"><trunc>ye</trunc></u>
<u n="783" who="S0589">what time is it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="784" who="S0588">it's er</u>
<u n="785" who="S0589">are you allowed to?</u>
<u n="786" who="S0588" trans="overlap">seven past five</u>
<u n="787" who="S0589">are you allowed to <trunc>transcri</trunc> are you recording?</u>
<u n="788" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="789" who="S0589">are you allowed to transcribe nicknames?</u>
<u n="790" who="S0588">I wouldn't transcribe even a nickname I'd anonymise it like I anonymise pets as well have you seen <anon type="name" nameType="n"/>? <vocal desc="laugh"/> have you seen anonymised? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="791" who="S0589"><vocal desc="yawn"/> do you want to come to the broadcast evening do?</u>
<u n="792" who="S0588">what's that?</u>
<u n="793" who="S0589">on Friday</u>
<u n="794" who="S0588" trans="overlap">what's what's it <trunc>i</trunc> what's it for?</u>
<u n="795" who="S0589">the end of the department</u>
<u n="796" who="S0588">oh <pause dur="short"/> oh I dunno that's into London then isn't it?</u>
<u n="797" who="S0589" trans="overlap">do you need anything from B and Q darling?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0588">mm <pause dur="long"/> we've done our spending for the month in TK Maxx I think but we did well <pause dur="short"/> got I got a dustpan and brush didn't I <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="799" who="S0589" trans="overlap">and two bottles of basil infused oils</u>
<u n="800" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="801" who="S0589">for your lunches</u>
<u n="802" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="803" who="S0589">which is good</u>
<u n="804" who="S0588">what else did we get? it was a good shopping trip I got clothes pegs</u>
<u n="805" who="S0589">a proper sieve</u>
<u n="806" who="S0588">a sieve <pause dur="short"/> erm bin liners <pause dur="short"/> and something else that was really good and I can't remember what it was</u>
<u n="807" who="S0589">there's the ghost supermarket</u>
<u n="808" who="S0588">mm <pause dur="short"/> they tried to get it listed</u>
<u n="809" who="S0589">did they?</u>
<u n="810" who="S0588">mm apparently someone tried I wouldn't list it personally <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="811" who="S0589">mental <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="812" who="S0588">why it's such a waste <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="813" who="S0589">it doesn't look a big enough space for an Ikea does it?</u>
<u n="814" who="S0588">no it doesn't but I think they're knocking it down</u>
<u n="815" who="S0589">yeah but I mean the the the</u>
<u n="816" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="817" who="S0589" trans="overlap">land</u>
<u n="818" who="S0588">well yeah they're probably building on all that wasteland bit there I can't wait personally <pause dur="short"/> we will go and buy steak knives <vocal desc="laugh"/> and finally we'll finally get steak knives probably <pause dur="short"/> might might even buy our kitchen in there</u>
<u n="819" who="S0589" trans="overlap">TK Maxx <pause dur="short"/> tK Maxx it'll be shut darling <pause dur="short"/> oh no it's open</u>
<u n="820" who="S0588">no they're probably open till six at least what do you think we'll buy from Ikea when it opens?</u>
<u n="821" who="S0589">plates</u>
<u n="822" who="S0588">the first thing</u>
<u n="823" who="S0589">plates bowls</u>
<u n="824" who="S0588">bowls</u>
<u n="825" who="S0589">glasses a rug</u>
<u n="826" who="S0588">mm probably a rug <pause dur="long"/> <anon type="place"/> we went in there once you wanted to look at interesting spices</u>
<u n="827" who="S0589">H and M is shut <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> right where shall we go then? let's decide so we can just go straight there</u>
<u n="828" who="S0588">I think it's between I don't want to go to the <anon type="place"/> I want to be cosy and warm <pause dur="short"/> so it's either the <anon type="place"/> or the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="long"/> which would you prefer?</u>
<u n="829" who="S0589">I don't know darling <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="830" who="S0588">erm I'll take the opportunity to record your mum when she comes as well I expect you'll play another game of Scrabble <pause dur="long"/> it's amazingly quick isn't it? but when you walk it's</u>
<u n="831" who="S0589" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="832" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/> amazingly long</u>
<u n="833" who="S0589">there's the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="834" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="835" who="S0589">there's the train station there cuddles</u>
<u n="836" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="837" who="S0589">we're almost back at <anon type="place"/> park</u>
<u n="838" who="S0588">yeah <pause dur="long"/> fish and chips would be nice <pause dur="short"/> fish and chips in the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="839" who="S0589">those great big birds <pause dur="short"/> oh it's not a bird is it? it's a fake hawk to keep away</u>
<u n="840" who="S0588">oh is it?</u>
<u n="841" who="S0589">pigeons</u>
<u n="842" who="S0588">it's really clever isn't it? I've heard of those <pause dur="long"/> maybe the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="843" who="S0589">yeah okay <pause dur="short"/> might have a burger</u>
<u n="844" who="S0588">it's comfy isn't it? <pause dur="short"/> a burger mm</u>
<u n="845" who="S0589">and here we are <anon type="place"/> park we came up there</u>
<u n="846" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="847" who="S0589">walked past this building here</u>
<u n="848" who="S0588">we did <pause dur="long"/> and then I think we reached the point where we got very tired by the time we got to the Millennium Dome</u>
<u n="849" who="S0589">yes <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="850" who="S0588">what's that? <vocal desc="laugh"/> what's that going to be?</u>
<u n="851" who="S0589">the <trunc>McDo</trunc> there's the climbing wall</u>
<u n="852" who="S0588">oh</u>
<u n="853" who="S0589">yeah well an advert for it</u>
<u n="854" who="S0588">yeah an advert</u>
<u n="855" who="S0589" trans="overlap">I still didn't notice it though</u>
<u n="856" who="S0588">no <pause dur="long"/> those little beaches are really sweet though <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="857" who="S0589">yes <pause dur="short"/> I suppose they'd be called basins wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="858" who="S0588">would they? <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="859" who="S0589">there it is quick one of the basins <pause dur="short"/> and another here</u>
<u n="860" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="861" who="S0589">it's an even higher tide now <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="862" who="S0588">I might have a cup of coffee I think <pause dur="long"/> getting off soon <pause dur="long"/> mm beautiful art deco cinema <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="863" who="S0589">there's your building you wanted to look at</u>
<u n="864" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="long"/> where does this stop?</u>
<u n="865" who="S0589">outside Sainsbury's and then on the main <unclear/> by the water where we get off</u>
<u n="866" who="S0588">oh <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="867" who="S0589">oh look they've gutted it</u>
<u n="868" who="S0588">they've gutted what? oh yeah they have</u>
<u n="869" who="S0589">our very own Poundland</u>
<u n="870" who="S0588">oh god <pause dur="long"/> mm <pause dur="long"/></u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
