<text id="SRD5">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:00:35</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-17</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0282 S0293</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>At ANON’s home in Guildford, Surrey</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>The recording process, a neighbour, physiotherapy, bad joints, clothes, weight and diets, food</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about what they have been up to lately</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T09</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0282">
				<exactage>55</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Stratford-upon-Avon</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>self employed</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0293">
				<exactage>21</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Guildford</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>21</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>2_secondary</edqual>
				<occupation>unemployed</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>German -- intermediate</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0282">so</u>
<u n="2" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0282">so what that means is that it's really difficult to <trunc>d</trunc> to to translate the files the audio files from the Android phone into MPEGs</u>
<u n="4" who="S0293">right</u>
<u n="5" who="S0282">which are music files</u>
<u n="6" who="S0293">right you sound very techy to me</u>
<u n="7" who="S0282">no I've had to learn this</u>
<u n="8" who="S0293">right sounds riveting</u>
<u n="9" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="10" who="S0282">it is well er no it's quite I mean it's a different language</u>
<u n="11" who="S0293">do you want some more cake?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0282">no thank you</u>
<u n="13" who="S0293">more tea?</u>
<u n="14" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mustn't have more cake I will I've helped myself to more tea and I will have even more tea I should think</u>
<u n="15" who="S0293">that's oh no that's the horrible milk I'll get the better milk</u>
<u n="16" who="S0282">no I've got no it's the good milk in</u>
<u n="17" who="S0293" trans="overlap">no that's no that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh oh for you? oh right okay erm this is ideal for me</u>
<u n="19" who="S0293">no full fat in my tea</u>
<u n="20" who="S0282">so I submitted all my old tapes did you tell <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that I'd edited that tape?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0293">I haven't actually cos she fell and broke her shoulder</u>
<u n="22" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="23" who="S0293">and <unclear/> just went out of her mind at the time I don't know if she <unclear/> worrying about it she she would've said <unclear>something about it</unclear></u>
<u n="24" who="S0282">erm if you hadn't known what she was talking about you wouldn't've you wouldn't've picked it up</u>
<u n="25" who="S0293" trans="overlap">no well I don't I don't think so I mean I <trunc>d</trunc> I happen to know the what she's worried about so</u>
<u n="26" who="S0282">oh yeah no if you when you know what she's talking about</u>
<u n="27" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0282">then er you think oh really?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="30" who="S0282">crikey</u>
<u n="31" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="32" who="S0282">erm if you didn't know what she was talking about she it was so elliptical a reference</u>
<u n="33" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0282">that erm you wouldn't really've understood</u>
<u n="35" who="S0293">well she she's very conscientious about these things as you've gathered</u>
<u n="36" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0293"><unclear/> she will go to her grave with all kinds of secrets I went to the physio the other day and that was jolly useful</u>
<u n="38" who="S0282">you went to where?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0293">I went to I went er to the physio the other day and that was jolly useful</u>
<u n="40" who="S0282">oh what persuaded you to do that?</u>
<u n="41" who="S0293" trans="overlap">well I'd been well I'd been referred to this bloke before</u>
<u n="42" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="43" who="S0293">and er I didn't get on very well with my last physio cos he kept <unclear/> <unclear>stuff which I really don't care I really can't bear to even talk about quite a lot</unclear> <unclear/> and erm er he always held it <unclear/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0282">oh right yes</u>
<u n="45" who="S0293" trans="overlap">and erm and so er and in the end anyway I I didn't end up going to two appointments and er was obviously blacklisted they were furious with me absolutely furious <unclear/></u>
<u n="46" who="S0282">was this a referral? <trunc>w</trunc> did you <trunc>ge</trunc> had you been referred by the?</u>
<u n="47" who="S0293">I'd been referred and then I was referred back a second time yeah I was referred for my back which is the reason well I the reason I wanted to go the er reason I asked for the referral was because I am so bloody stiff all the time I can't move and erm I really can't move any more erm I I I can't put my clothes on and things like that I've been <trunc>t</trunc>been telling you haven't I? for some time how stiff I am and erm I asked them to erm I'll do that afterwards if I start even thinking about it I will not stop talking and erm er <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="48" who="S0282">mm mm <unclear/> so you so you went to the physio? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0293">can't bear it <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I hate it</u>
<u n="50" who="S0282">just pretend that nothing's going on</u>
<u n="51" who="S0293">but I can't when you're <trunc>p</trunc>putting your little pen down it's horrid</u>
<u n="52" who="S0282">sorry</u>
<u n="53" who="S0293">anyway erm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0282">I don't have to do that</u>
<u n="55" who="S0293">erm yeah so I'd already been referred for my back and er then I ended up doing this <unclear/> stuff which drove me mad and erm then I got referred again and I missed two appointments so she was absolutely hopping mad with me so I went in there and I thought oh my god she's gonna be <trunc>s</trunc> she did give me such a hard time and erm actually I said look I'll be perfectly frank what I want is I want a set of exercises cos I am so stiff I don't know what to do with myself and I've got knee pain and back pain and actually she was really very switched on erm and she says yes I am extraordinarily erm stiff <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="56" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="57" who="S0293">I've been you know I keep saying this to everybody but nobody believes me you know I have <trunc>n</trunc> I have a very flat back which is an indicator of how stiff I am and I can't rotate in any</u>
<u n="58" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="59" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> in any dimension</u>
<u n="61" who="S0293">in any way no I can't and I keep saying this to people and I know you know it's not a a major thing but it it makes life quite hard work and also things like I fall off my bike I fall over I I er cos I can't bend to get out of situations</u>
<u n="62" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0293" trans="overlap">I'm all so it's actually quite</u>
<u n="64" who="S0282">but also if you're <trunc>st</trunc> if you're tense</u>
<u n="65" who="S0293"><unclear>exactly</unclear></u>
<u n="66" who="S0282">then you can't fall properly and you can't correct yourself because you need a certain amount of fluidity and relaxation</u>
<u n="67" who="S0293" trans="overlap">yeah yeah so my daily life is more dangerous as a consequence everything is more dangerous about it so</u>
<u n="68" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="69" who="S0293">erm anyway she <trunc>r</trunc> agreed with me that yes it was a level of stiffness that was really quite acute so I I felt quite kind of you know sometimes they look at you as if you're mad you're saying you're stiff you know oh why are you coming? why are complaining about this? I said you know I just need some exercises I need to know what to do but I have to be very careful cos otherwise I set my back off and if I start doing things that set my back off then I just don't don't do the exercises so erm and then she said with the knee which is even more useful she said the reason I'm er she <trunc>sai</trunc> she reckons with <trunc>s</trunc> the correct exercise plan I may actually be able to stop the knee pain because what's happened is my knee caps have moved outwards</u>
<u n="70" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="71" who="S0293">I guess cos of the back and erm I'm very strong on the outside</u>
<u n="72" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0293">but on the inside and therefore they're not being supported correctly</u>
<u n="74" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="75" who="S0293">so if we can build up muscles here</u>
<u n="76" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="77" who="S0293">actually we could probably physically rectify the stress which is oh I've got arthritis but not very bad arthritis</u>
<u n="78" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="79" who="S0293">so I can probably improve the situation a lot myself</u>
<u n="80" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0293">which is what I wanna do you know?</u>
<u n="82" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0293">I'm not saying miraculously cure me I'm saying you know there must be a way of improving life cos again with the knee it's it's incredibly impractical you know you can't get <trunc>dow</trunc> I can't get up and down I can't get out the bath I can't get into my cupboards erm</u>
<u n="84" who="S0282">I've ended up on in a supermarket going to get something off the bottom shelf and thinking I can't get up now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="85" who="S0293" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="86" who="S0282">and having to put a hand on the floor or on the shelf and <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0293">I can't get up I've fallen over</u>
<u n="88" who="S0282" trans="overlap">pull myself up</u>
<u n="89" who="S0293">erm in the street and not been able to get up you know it's really really embarrassing</u>
<u n="90" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0293">erm and I've been in situations with big steps when I actually just can't get out of the situation I'm thinking oh shit what do I do now? <unclear/></u>
<u n="92" who="S0282">mm could be your feet as well</u>
<u n="93" who="S0293">no no I've been <unclear>down</unclear> that alley</u>
<u n="94" who="S0282">have you?</u>
<u n="95" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0282">cos I mean that <trunc>m</trunc>my er the pronation of my knees came out as a consequence of me going to see the podiatrist about pains in my feet and they they they had this little er studio where they made you walk on a treadmill they attached electrodes to your bum and they filmed you erm at the same time so they could see so they could see what your feet were doing your knees your thighs your bum and so I was all one side so one buttock higher than the other my knees were pointing outwards my toes were pointing inwards</u>
<u n="97" who="S0293">yeah but I don't know about you but didn't they just give you thick insoles which you can't get in any shoes you see that's what they did with me</u>
<u n="98" who="S0282">ah they gave me a thick pair of insoles which I can er wear in one pair of shoes and when I have pains in my feet I wear those shoes and if I'm walking a lot or</u>
<u n="99" who="S0293" trans="overlap">oh you see I do have pain I do have pain but a very high arch it's which is the problem</u>
<u n="100" who="S0282">oh I have the opposite I have really low arches</u>
<u n="101" who="S0293" trans="overlap">mm mine are exceptionally high <unclear/> exceptionally high arches so and very high feet er <trunc>m</trunc>my feet are you know very solid and sort of high so but I can't get anything in I can't get them in any shoe even walking shoes so you know it's no bloody good</u>
<u n="102" who="S0282">I think the only way you can go from there is to actually have your shoes made and have them made so that they're the right shape for you</u>
<u n="103" who="S0293">oh mm well my mum's been down this <trunc>ba</trunc> cos we've all got my mum's feet basically</u>
<u n="104" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="105" who="S0293">and <trunc>i</trunc>it it it does limit <trunc>y</trunc>you know my mum used to go round in I don't know white lace up things which are they're just horrible anyway it's</u>
<u n="106" who="S0282">you can get nicer shoes if you have them made</u>
<u n="107" who="S0293">yeah it's just expensive though <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="108" who="S0282">oh yeah no absolutely expensive</u>
<u n="109" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0282">but perhaps you know just one pair really or something</u>
<u n="111" who="S0293">well possibly but I can't imagine <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="112" who="S0282" trans="overlap">a treat for your birthday present</u>
<u n="113" who="S0293" trans="overlap">I can't imagine that <unclear>I mean</unclear> there are many treats that I want at the moment but</u>
<u n="114" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="115" who="S0282">I know</u>
<u n="116" who="S0293">I can't imagine that particular one coming my way but erm I found this in the charity shop it's <unclear/> you know the <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="117" who="S0282">I noticed that it's really nice <unclear/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0293" trans="overlap">but it's it's only size ten which is er you know it's a blow so it doesn't even cross it doesn't even erm fasten but <unclear>the wool</unclear></u>
<u n="119" who="S0282" trans="overlap">it's looks good it's a nice shape</u>
<u n="120" who="S0293">oh my god it's just</u>
<u n="121" who="S0282">let me feel</u>
<u n="122" who="S0293">it's not the feel it's just the colours aren't the colours fantastic?</u>
<u n="123" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh it's soft mm it really matches <trunc>m</trunc></u>
<u n="124" who="S0293" trans="overlap">the <unclear>colour</unclear> of blues and browns I just <unclear>love the colours</unclear></u>
<u n="125" who="S0282">er yes I was looking at it earlier and I couldn't work out if it was er it was brown or grey</u>
<u n="126" who="S0293">I love their colours I just think their colours are every time I go in that shop and I think oh my god <unclear/> so fantastic</u>
<u n="127" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="128" who="S0293">I love er all the colour jerseys but who would spend that kind of money? unless you had silly money I mean have you seen the prices?</u>
<u n="129" who="S0282">well when your children eventually leave home</u>
<u n="130" who="S0293">no no nobody would buy a jersey that expensive</u>
<u n="131" who="S0282" trans="overlap">you can have I don't know I've got a cashmere twinset which was really really expensive really really really expensive but it has lasted for twenty plus year twenty-five years and it still looks as good as new so it's not a false economy</u>
<u n="132" who="S0293">yeah well there is that if you do get good jerseys it does make a difference doesn't it?</u>
<u n="133" who="S0282">yeah cos the rest look so ratty so quick</u>
<u n="134" who="S0293" trans="overlap"><unclear/> my suits are just er er you know I've got a couple of suits which I bought really really early on and they're fine now you know</u>
<u n="135" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0293">er I agree with you about buying good stuff but</u>
<u n="137" who="S0282">oh well it's out of the question now</u>
<u n="138" who="S0293"><unclear>mm</unclear></u>
<u n="139" who="S0282">and anyway I'm changing shape all the time so I'm</u>
<u n="140" who="S0293">how's your weight erm loss thing going?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0282">er well last time I weighed myself I had lost twenty kilos</u>
<u n="142" who="S0293">how much is that in stones?</u>
<u n="143" who="S0282">I have no idea</u>
<u n="144" who="S0293">sounds a lot</u>
<u n="145" who="S0282">there's two point two pounds per kilo</u>
<u n="146" who="S0293">sixteen pounds er no fourteen pounds in a stone fourteen <unclear>and you've lost</unclear> twenty so you've lost two stone er almost</u>
<u n="147" who="S0282">oh is that is that all? I don't want to do it in stone then <trunc>s</trunc> in that <trunc>c</trunc>in that case cos that's really depressing that took a year</u>
<u n="148" who="S0293"><unclear/> two two kilos in a no I'm gonna be wrong about this two pounds</u>
<u n="149" who="S0282">two point two pounds I think a kilo is two point two pounds so twenty kilos is ten kilos is oh no this is ridiculous this is embarrassing I'm not doing I'm sorry it's Friday afternoon and I I can't do maths <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="150" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="151" who="S0282">and I can't <trunc>d</trunc> there's no point it doesn't mean</u>
<u n="152" who="S0293">twenty kilos is I'm just gonna look it up on the computer twenty kilos is how many stone? <unclear/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0282">how long are going to be gone?</u>
<u n="154" who="S0293">three minutes</u>
<u n="155" who="S0282">well</u>
<u n="156" who="S0293"><unclear/> I'm a whizz at this</u>
<u n="157" who="S0282">yes but then what am I gonna do? am I gonna talk to myself for three minutes? I am gonna talk to myself for three minutes <pause dur="short"/> this is just plain sabotage actually <pause dur="long"/> if somebody leaves the room in the middle of a recording to go away and do something for three minutes it's just plainly sabotage <pause dur="long"/> so <vocal desc="sigh"/> this is very nice I had a day out walking with some people and I'm now exhausted cos we've been out for such a long walk and now I'm having lapsang souchong <trunc>t</trunc> lapsang souchong that just shows how tired I am and cake which is a really nice treat at the end of the afternoon <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0293">it's very <trunc>im</trunc>very impressive</u>
<u n="159" who="S0282">is it?</u>
<u n="160" who="S0293">yeah it's over three stone</u>
<u n="161" who="S0282">oh wow well good I hope it shows actually</u>
<u n="162" who="S0293">well it does show</u>
<u n="163" who="S0282" trans="overlap">it's been hard won</u>
<u n="164" who="S0293">well it does show three stone is pretty bloody impressive how much further have you got to go?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0282">er well I don't know if I get back to my sort of erm you know my glory days</u>
<u n="166" who="S0293">no no we're not going for <trunc>glo</trunc> I wouldn't er go for glory days aren't you just going for normal?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0282">well the thing is it depends I need to get back into the clothes that I had when I was working up to the year two thousand and four and and they I can't remember even what size they are but they are my posh clothes and my expensive clothes and my really nice work clothes</u>
<u n="168" who="S0293" trans="overlap">can you not alter the sizes?</u>
<u n="169" who="S0282">they're all packed away I haven't looked at them for ages</u>
<u n="170" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0282">because it's just too depressing I haven't thrown them all I haven't thrown them away because that would just be that would break my heart really and I used to look at them and think oh I'll never get into that but</u>
<u n="172" who="S0293" trans="overlap">I got rid of a lot of mine the smaller ones so wait a minute er <trunc>any</trunc>anyway if you want to get to er your fighting <trunc>s</trunc> fit weight what would <trunc>y</trunc> that be then?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0282">nine and a half</u>
<u n="174" who="S0293">and what are you now?</u>
<u n="175" who="S0282">don't know well last time I weighed seventy-eight kilos so I don't know what that is in stones</u>
<u n="176" who="S0293">you haven't got that long to go then have you? you're doing quite well</u>
<u n="177" who="S0282">no no no I'm I'm getting there it's probably another well it depends how strict I am if I stay on the strictness of the diet I've been on it should be another six months but I'm lately I'm just getting a bit tired and fed up so I haven't been as assiduous and actually <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has not been helping me because he has not been er measuring quantities and he's been starting to go like we were before which is just basically <trunc>m</trunc> you know just not measuring or weighing pasta or portions of food so I shall have to get him back doing that as well and when my dad moves in he's my dad's supposed to be on a diet so we're gonna <trunc>ha</trunc> erm have to start trying to enforce that as well</u>
<u n="178" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="179" who="S0282">but erm my dad is trying to they told they said to my dad he had to lose weight because it was a strain on his heart and of course he and my mother are taking this as being a kind of a question of defeating er you know of confounding a person in authority by by you know eating Cup-a-Soup for the two weeks before you go and see the specialist and then the rest of the time just ignoring</u>
<u n="180" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="181" who="S0282">what you're supposed to be doing</u>
<u n="182" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0282">but anyway</u>
<u n="184" who="S0293">yeah I've er I'm going to get down to my sister's gone down to eight stone eight and a half stone</u>
<u n="185" who="S0282">really? mm that's</u>
<u n="186" who="S0293">she's quite similar build to me she's a bit taller than I am perhaps</u>
<u n="187" who="S0282">oh that's too thin then</u>
<u n="188" who="S0293">which is oh er she's ridiculously thin erm it's you know she's five foot oh actually she is taller than me I reckon she's five foot nine five foot eight five foot nine</u>
<u n="189" who="S0282">well that's just ridiculously thin in that case</u>
<u n="190" who="S0293" trans="overlap">so she <trunc>m</trunc> I the lowest weight I'd be happy if I got down to ten and a half ten and a half would be erm a fine weight to be in my book</u>
<u n="191" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="192" who="S0293">so I've still got another stone to go</u>
<u n="193" who="S0282">well it's not so much about I mean I cos I never knew how much I weighed before really it's just about whether my clothes whether my nice clothes fit</u>
<u n="194" who="S0293">well I know I have to do it that way cos I have to kind of er we put on two stone completely accidentally that was <trunc>w</trunc>well we put on one stone completely accidently</u>
<u n="195" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0293">I knew I was around eleven stone and then we put on a stone</u>
<u n="197" who="S0282">one does one does it's very easy to do that</u>
<u n="198" who="S0293">so erm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0282">but also er it's it's coming off the wagon and stopping being vegetarian because erm in er and actually then not adjusting because if you put meat back in your diet and you then don't</u>
<u n="200" who="S0293">you gotta cut the fat back</u>
<u n="201" who="S0282"><trunc>y</trunc> rack back on the carbs severely and the fat</u>
<u n="202" who="S0293" trans="overlap">the fat as well yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0282">straight away <unclear>to compensate for the meat then</unclear></u>
<u n="204" who="S0293">but you had a very yeah you had a very fatty diet didn't you? very <trunc>f</trunc> I for me coming in to a vegetarian diet is a lot more fat and a lot more carbs than I would eat <unclear/> naturally</u>
<u n="205" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><unclear>well yeah</unclear> yeah oh yeah much more carbs absolutely</u>
<u n="206" who="S0293">but fat actually as well interestingly sort of the creams and the cheeses and the</u>
<u n="207" who="S0282">yeah and pastry and</u>
<u n="208" who="S0293">yeah mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0282">and stuff like that so <trunc>y</trunc>you you have to erm if you er when you're eating on your own on a weekday night you can just have a vegetable stew and throw <unclear/> in one pot but if you invite people round it's very difficult to give them a vegetable stew people really feel hard done by so you have to do a thing to mimic what you would have if you were eating meat which is you know a piece of meat and discreet vegetables</u>
<u n="210" who="S0293" trans="overlap">do you eat much fish?</u>
<u n="211" who="S0282">no not really</u>
<u n="212" who="S0293">you see we eat a lot of fish that's our</u>
<u n="213" who="S0282">I'm not really very partial to fish</u>
<u n="214" who="S0293">mm we eat we're eating as much fish as we can get away with actually</u>
<u n="215" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="216" who="S0293">so we eat fish er <pause dur="long"/> three four <trunc>t</trunc> three times a week at least yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0282">mm well we have now things like canned tuna cos that's always a really quick supper and er we have er and when my day off is Friday so we have fish and chips on Friday night which is also <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s treat as well I had some rock salmon or something the other day which I'd never had before cos I think cod is extraordinarily boring or er having said that when we went to this restaurant on Thursday we had last Thursday I had erm <trunc>sm</trunc> a piece of smoked cod which was beautiful really nice but <trunc>tin</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc>it was all this this er sort of very high end Michelin stars er you know little teeny weeny portions of things so like little scallop about this big</u>
<u n="218" who="S0293"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0282">and er and then they sort of said oh with er you know with parsnips and and actually they must've made one parsnip go round the whole dining room</u>
<u n="220" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0282">because you just got like half a matchstick of parsnip</u>
<u n="222" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="223" who="S0282">it was really quite extraordinary and <trunc>th</trunc>and they had a hierarchy of waiters and erm and so one person came round and was like oh no I can't describe the food to you I shall have to call my colleague so the other colleague had to come and say oh this is a carpaccio of cod with a <unclear/> erm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0293">did you <trunc>d</trunc>dress up to go?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0282">no not particularly</u>
<u n="226" who="S0293">it's so you know I really <trunc>r</trunc> there's no nothing we ever dress up for any more it's <trunc>t</trunc> quite sad really I like</u>
<u n="227" who="S0282" trans="overlap">it is sad</u>
<u n="228" who="S0293">I like dressing up I really do like dressing up and er you know you can't you know Christmas parties no parties ever people dress up these days</u>
<u n="229" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="230" who="S0293"><unclear>or it's</unclear> smart casual I mean they spend lots of money on their casual clothes but it's not</u>
<u n="231" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="232" who="S0293">what I like enjoy doing I like to wear I don't know I like to wear nice fabrics and nice cut things and</u>
<u n="233" who="S0282">there's somebody who's in my erm in this group of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s who is always dressed in a really quirky fashion and she has she buys clothes from this woman who <trunc>d</trunc> who makes clothes out of vintage bits of fabric so she's always wearing something that is extraordinarily quirky with a very quirky print and er erm very <trunc>o</trunc> kind of odd shape and really peculiar buttons and stuff like that and she looks amazing she always wears really bright colours so pink or red or green or blue just vibrant hues and she's very I mean it looks really nice and but she er you know it doesn't matter the rest of us are in jeans and T-shirts and she'll turn up in like a prom dress or something like that or a</u>
<u n="234" who="S0293">it's really cheering though you know</u>
<u n="235" who="S0282">yeah oh yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0293"><unclear/> and you know when I go and see my dad they all notice when you're dressed up</u>
<u n="237" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0293">the old people cos it's gets boring</u>
<u n="239" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0293">it must get so boring looking at old people in boring old clothes mustn't it?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<event desc="sound of phone"/>
<u n="242" who="S0293">oh it's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0282">oh really?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0293">give me a second <pause dur="long"/> darling? hello? <pause dur="short"/> hello? <pause dur="short"/> mm doesn't work for some reason</u>
<u n="245" who="S0282">erm have you got a <trunc>tu</trunc>a different tune for everybody then?</u>
<u n="246" who="S0293">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0282">oh right so how do you know it's her?</u>
<u n="248" who="S0293">cos it says</u>
<u n="249" who="S0282">oh right okay</u>
<u n="250" who="S0293">hello?</u>
<u n="251" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>hello</unclear> it's video</u>
<u n="252" who="S0293">oh god</u>
<u n="253" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="254" who="S0293">video that's very frightening here's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I'll show you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0282">oh no it's gone off</u>
<u n="256" who="S0293">has it?</u>
<u n="257" who="S0282">slide to unlock</u>
<u n="258" who="S0293">hello? oh god</u>
<u n="259" who="S0282"><unclear>there you are</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="260" who="S0293">crashing <pause dur="short"/> hello?</u>
<u n="261" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">hi</u>
<u n="262" who="S0293">it crashes you see if it sees my face</u>
<u n="263" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="264" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> it's not that much of a disaster</u>
<u n="265" who="S0293"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="266" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">er so you're still with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="267" who="S0293">I am yes</u>
<u n="268" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay er</u>
<u n="269" who="S0293">are you around later at all or not? I'd love to chat</u>
<u n="270" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I'm just going to <unclear/> a game of table tennis</u>
<u n="271" who="S0293">oh very good where do you play table tennis? ah blasted phone keeps going down hello?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0282">it might be her connection is she calling from Germany?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="274" who="S0282">well it's gonna be</u>
<u n="275" who="S0293">well normally she's it's really quite good it's brilliant actually this</u>
<u n="276" who="S0282"><unclear>looks happy</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="277" who="S0293">last term we didn't have any contact at all</u>
<u n="278" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and so what? she's got a video on her phone as well? is it worth <trunc>g</trunc></u>
<u n="279" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0282">is it worth doing? can you see? can you actually really see her?</u>
<u n="281" who="S0293">I can't bear it</u>
<u n="282" who="S0282">can't you?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0293"><unclear/> no I can't bear the video calls we had to do that by Skype last time</u>
<u n="284" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="285" who="S0293">and actually it was very grainy</u>
<u n="286" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0293">and we couldn't hear each other properly it drove her absolutely <trunc>nu</trunc> will call later so that's fine just <unclear/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0282">just sounds as though she might be in a place where the</u>
<u n="289" who="S0293">sorry?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0282">it might be that she might in a place where her reception's not good or is your reception alright here?</u>
<u n="291" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0282">I was er we <trunc>w</trunc> I we went to <anon type="place"/> today and erm going to <anon type="place"/> is slightly complicated because it's not very obvious the route and so I set off and my satnav honestly I'm gonna I'm I don't know whether it's do you think it's this area? because er our satnav just does not work our my satnav almost all the way to <anon type="place"/> said it couldn't find a satellite signal and so it just kept switching itself saying can't find a signal can't find a signal <trunc>tr</trunc> turning itself off</u>
<u n="293" who="S0293"><unclear>oh no</unclear></u>
<u n="294" who="S0282">so I was late because by the time I was fiddling with it and I missed a turn off and</u>
<u n="295" who="S0293">oh <unclear>dunno</unclear></u>
<u n="296" who="S0282">goodness knows what</u>
<u n="297" who="S0293">I do find round your area I can't get much of a signal sometimes</u>
<u n="298" who="S0282">it might be that it might be the <trunc>tr</trunc> I don't know if it's the trees</u>
<u n="299" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0282">or whether the soldiers have got some sort of damping <trunc>syst</trunc></u>
<u n="301" who="S0293" trans="overlap">I think there maybe some <trunc>blo</trunc> er there may be some blockage system <unclear>going on</unclear></u>
<u n="302" who="S0282">round the erm round all the barracks er so you can't get a signal on the barracks like in a hospital where you can't get a signal</u>
<u n="303" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0282">cos they've blocked it off</u>
<u n="305" who="S0293">there's something like that round your area definitely</u>
<u n="306" who="S0282">mm I wouldn't be at all people pooh pooh me when I say that</u>
<u n="307" who="S0293">no I wouldn't be surprised</u>
<u n="308" who="S0282">and also er I get this funny buzzing in my ears when I'm on erm the east side of my house</u>
<u n="309" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="310" who="S0282">and I think that there's there may be some electronic thing going on there but everybody says that er I am <pause dur="short"/> erm paranoid and this is not true but I definitely have a ringing in my ears that I don't have at other times when I'm in my living room or in my bedroom</u>
<u n="311" who="S0293">mm oh well I trust your trust your instincts on this thing er I should think the army has all kind of weirdo weird and wonderful things</u>
<u n="312" who="S0282">but I could turn into one of these barmy old ladies who believes that you shouldn't be anywhere near a you know telegraph pole or something who knows</u>
<u n="313" who="S0293">no I'm increasingly increasingly anti anti technology although this has this has been very good cos er <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>y</trunc> er <trunc>y</trunc> <trunc>a</trunc>as you <trunc>intere</trunc>interestingly neither of us like doing Facetime we only like see speaking as if an on a phone it's the only feel or else it makes her feel further away actually</u>
<u n="314" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm oh</u>
<u n="315" who="S0293">if you speak on the phone it's fine</u>
<u n="316" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="317" who="S0293">cos it just feels like an ordinary telephone call</u>
<u n="318" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="319" who="S0293"><unclear>so if</unclear> she's like around the corner and like you know you'll ring your mum up</u>
<u n="320" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0293"><unclear/> feels okay if you start getting Skypy it starts feeling like she's bloody miles away and I think she feels the same way actually so</u>
<u n="322" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="323" who="S0293">she doesn't normally phone me very much she's having such a nice time but erm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0282">well that's that's so good I'm just so pleased about that it's just such a good decision wasn't it?</u>
<u n="325" who="S0293" trans="overlap">mm it's marvellous yeah it's er it's absolutely marvellous and she's you know she's quite proactive about things I don't know she's yeah she's changed er <trunc>de</trunc> has definitely turned a corner unlike our <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who's erm <vocal desc="misc"/> definitely not</u>
<u n="326" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh dear poor kid that's just so not fair but then I don't know whether it's <unclear/> cos she's had that kick back with the exams as well or is it just too much now?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0293" trans="overlap">no <trunc>i</trunc>it it's a disaster at this particular point cos she's got these big college auditions as well just coming up so it's very difficult from a confidence point of view to pick yourself up and erm and and er get out there <trunc>i</trunc>it but on the other hand you know for being in the music industry you've got to be prepared for this</u>
<u n="328" who="S0282">well yes that's true</u>
<u n="329" who="S0293">er because they all have different they like different styles I mean they er <trunc>y</trunc> her and her friend obviously <unclear>different style players</unclear> they're the same standard although her teacher says she should've got it er she teaches both of them</u>
<u n="330" who="S0282">ah</u>
<u n="331" who="S0293">she said she really does reckon <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> should've got it but</u>
<u n="332" who="S0282">and what happens if this other girl bombs out?</u>
<u n="333" who="S0293">she won't bomb out</u>
<u n="334" who="S0282">why not? <pause dur="short"/> cos the thing er the thing that er strikes me about <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is how much she enjoys it</u>
<u n="335" who="S0293">oh she <unclear>definitely does</unclear></u>
<u n="336" who="S0282">and she er she appears not to have very bad nerves and <trunc>sh</trunc> when you <trunc>w</trunc>when we <trunc>s</trunc> when we went to see her in that concert she was so <unclear>full of the</unclear> joy of it</u>
<u n="337" who="S0293"><unclear>definitely</unclear></u>
<u n="338" who="S0282">and she was just so</u>
<u n="339" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="340" who="S0282">into the performance</u>
<u n="341" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="342" who="S0282">and so engaged in everything but</u>
<u n="343" who="S0293">you couldn't get <unclear>really</unclear> more involved than <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> actually</u>
<u n="344" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="345" who="S0293">you really couldn't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wasn't like that</u>
<u n="346" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="347" who="S0293">nobody <unclear>else was like that</unclear></u>
<u n="348" who="S0282" trans="overlap">whereas actually yes and erm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="350" who="S0282">you <trunc>y</trunc>you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> obviously doesn't like it at some level to be in a kind of competitive situation and and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm does get nerves and does lose lose her you know sort of</u>
<u n="351" who="S0293" trans="overlap">this girl oh no no <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s fine on <unclear>her solos</unclear></u>
<u n="352" who="S0282">her calm sometimes</u>
<u n="353" who="S0293" trans="overlap">she she doesn't like she doesn't like erm she doesn't like the orchestra so much she working with a big group of people was hard work for her</u>
<u n="354" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0293">whereas er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just can't get enough of it</u>
<u n="356" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="357" who="S0293">the more people around the better</u>
<u n="358" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0293">and to be in charge of a section she couldn't you couldn't've got a better section leader cos she <unclear>was</unclear> so good</u>
<u n="360" who="S0282" trans="overlap">well I know that's er that's why I'm thinking well you know is there a chance that <trunc>s</trunc> they'll sort of think my goodness what we need is we need <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> back</u>
<u n="361" who="S0293" trans="overlap">she'd be so fair and</u>
<u n="362" who="S0282">you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0293">she'd be so fair but this other girl is er er er er she I know she's quite bossy and whatever <unclear>and er</unclear> sometimes they have terrible section leaders they did last year absolutely bloody awful she has Asperger's and really really bad with them and you just have to put up with em and bear it erm and it does happen <trunc>th</trunc>there's two things erm one <unclear>of them</unclear> leading the section and two doing the solos</u>
<u n="364" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="365" who="S0293">and three preparing the section getting the section to do the work on it but it's it's done you have to move on</u>
<u n="366" who="S0282">well I hope she gets another opportunity</u>
<u n="367" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="368" who="S0282">what's happening about her maths?</u>
<u n="369" who="S0293">she's plodding on</u>
<u n="370" who="S0282">is she? <vocal desc="misc"/> poor sausage</u>
<u n="371" who="S0293">yeah it's it's not erm <vocal desc="misc"/> she is doing a lot of extra classes and things but I don't <vocal desc="misc"/> <vocal desc="sigh"/> I don't think she's really got how important it is but I don't know we'll see</u>
<u n="372" who="S0282">is this will this give her a chance to catch up a bit?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0293">well only she she wouldn't get above a C if even if she worked her bollocks off she couldn't get above a C now</u>
<u n="374" who="S0282">well that's alright it's a pass</u>
<u n="375" who="S0293">yeah oh I'd be perfectly happy with a bloody C I tell you but</u>
<u n="376" who="S0282"><unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="377" who="S0293">it's a shame because I think she could've got a B but erm I'd be very happy with a C er to get a C in German will be a miracle got to go from a U to a C <unclear>I've paid</unclear> for coaching for that oh god bloody coaching</u>
<u n="378" who="S0282" trans="overlap">ah that's er extraordinary isn't it really?</u>
<u n="379" who="S0293">yeah it is and she's very dismissive of it but that's cos she's so pliant about the money she gets terribly worried about paying out money I mean that's part of the problem I have with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is she tries to economise on things so for example reeds she won't buy enough reeds and then she runs out and then <unclear>they're like</unclear></u>
<u n="380" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="381" who="S0293">and you can't order them or she won't do the coaching cos she says it's too expensive or she won't take she hasn't got enough money on her therefore she ends up at a station without enough train fare to get home that kind of thing that kind of thing happens to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> quite a bit</u>
<u n="382" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="383" who="S0293">cos she's so busy trying to save money it doesn't doesn't help really</u>
<u n="384" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0293">a good good attitude but it just doesn't help in the long run like she wouldn't have any money in her account like I like to have a hundred pounds in her account for when she needs money urgently for an audition or reeds or something turns up and otherwise I have to be available at <unclear/> precisely that moment lots of things have deadlines you know you've got to be able to do it sometimes and she wouldn't have it her account and of course we just ended up with me having to do three very complicated transfers against the clock and I'm thinking you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> if you'd only had the bloody money</u>
<u n="386" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0293">it would've been an awful lot easier for all of us</u>
<u n="388" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="389" who="S0293">erm but anyway we'll see</u>
<u n="390" who="S0282">mm so where is she at school at the moment?</u>
<u n="391" who="S0293">yeah she's got an orchestra course she's doing they're doing this concert actually and erm in <anon type="place"/> a symphony concert on Sunday they've got a course and then she goes off to this holiday that we totally disapprove of to Spain without her oboe and without her text books</u>
<u n="392" who="S0282">oh right oh yes</u>
<u n="393" who="S0293">with the girl who's got her place in the orchestra</u>
<u n="394" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="395" who="S0293">so yes so we</u>
<u n="396" who="S0282">do you think their friendship will survive this?</u>
<u n="397" who="S0293"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s quite generous about it actually she <trunc>f</trunc> she couldn't talk to her for a day but she seems to have worked it out</u>
<u n="398" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="399" who="S0293">but then er the girl worked out why <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was so upset it's funny isn't it? that's she's slightly she slightly caught cold she didn't work that bit out I guess if you haven't been in a I dunno I don't know why she hadn't worked out how erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> couldn't care about anything else except <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="400" who="S0282">oh no <vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="401" who="S0293">it's funny but er</u>
<u n="402" who="S0282" trans="overlap">that's er</u>
<u n="403" who="S0293">anyway her teacher her teacher was very good and</u>
<u n="404" who="S0282" trans="overlap">poor kid</u>
<u n="405" who="S0293">her old teacher was really good she we brilliant actually she couldn't couldn't get hold of her teacher this is when you realise they're such fantastic human beings she couldn't get hold of her current teacher so she rang up her old teacher and she's so brilliant at sort of putting it all in perspective and being sensible about it and calming <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> down and understanding the realities of it all she was absolutely fantastic</u>
<u n="406" who="S0282">that's good I mean will will it help that she did it for a year?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0293">oh yeah yeah no it does help yes you can two years</u>
<u n="408" who="S0282">you can you can you can present it that actually for <trunc>person</trunc>personal reasons she couldn't do it <unclear/></u>
<u n="409" who="S0293">you wouldn't want you couldn't lie cos they all they work with these people er all the time people would be able to tell</u>
<u n="410" who="S0282">well in which case everybody will know that there was a change of policy or that there was a decision made so</u>
<u n="411" who="S0293" trans="overlap">well no it wasn't exactly it wasn't as it's not as clear as that they never tell you er it's a very strange email they send through they <trunc>ne</trunc> they're never really clear of the reason</u>
<u n="412" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0293">so they said it's a <trunc>e</trunc> it's a general email they sent through saying that they had to balance er that first and foremost it's the erm <trunc>ha</trunc> er it is does on merit it's meritocratic <trunc>how</trunc> <trunc>how</trunc> the best the person gets the best position however this is balanced out with how this has to be balanced with how much each person would get from continuing in the orchestra so there has to be a balance of whether they feel that she would get enough from continuing in the orchestra or whether somebody else who hadn't been in it before would gain more and I can understand that if you're a <trunc>s</trunc> equal standard</u>
<u n="414" who="S0282">that's very weasely</u>
<u n="415" who="S0293">it's very weasely it basically gives them</u>
<u n="416" who="S0282">and how are they to say? erm I suppose that that you know that's kind of sop cos you're <trunc>s</trunc> then you're supposed to conclude well actually I'm so good now and I've progressed so much</u>
<u n="417" who="S0293">it's weasely</u>
<u n="418" who="S0282">that actually I've got eighty per cent of the value I can get out of this and another year would only give me another twenty per cent and therefore somebody else would</u>
<u n="419" who="S0293">but then on the other hand they're saying it's completely meritocratic</u>
<u n="420" who="S0282">yes</u>
<u n="421" who="S0293">so it's not really it's <trunc>i</trunc></u>
<u n="422" who="S0282">no it's not meritocratic is it?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0293">no</u>
<u n="424" who="S0282">how can?</u>
<u n="425" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="426" who="S0282">no it's either meritocratic or it isn't you can't have meritocratic er mitigated with some other factor</u>
<u n="427" who="S0293">exactly</u>
<u n="428" who="S0282">because then it's it's</u>
<u n="429" who="S0293">yeah er but er it it er <anon type="place"/> is renowned I mean Paul Daniel who is most famous oboist there is never got in to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0282">really?</u>
<u n="431" who="S0293">yes</u>
<u n="432" who="S0282"><unclear/></u>
<u n="433" who="S0293">and erm er we know many stories whereby a teacher would say this is the most definitely will get in this person hasn't got a cat's chance in hell and then that person that hasn't got a cat's chance in hell will get the position and the other one won't so it is very idiosyncratic</u>
<u n="434" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm yes</u>
<u n="435" who="S0293">they never give you any rationale you never know what's really happened there's quite a lot about personality in fact <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> got on very well with this tutor but I don't think she's she had a terrible injury so I don't think she'd seen much of <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> er operating so she probably didn't realise how serious she was erm it's a variety of things there always are always are a variety of things</u>
<u n="436" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="437" who="S0293">I mean if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> er when she got chucked out it was for very good reason and er but we were very lucky cos he felt so bad <pause dur="short"/> well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s teacher knew him very well and and he she made him ring her up and that was brilliant because he said you know you didn't know the pieces well enough you you <trunc>y</trunc> and she was she was <trunc>l</trunc> she didn't</u>
<u n="438" who="S0282">she was winging it again</u>
<u n="439" who="S0293" trans="overlap">practise it she was winging it yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0282"><vocal desc="misc"/> yes</u>
<u n="441" who="S0293">and and you know that was a reality to that and it it was a terrible shock but er you know there was some reality to it</u>
<u n="442" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="443" who="S0293">erm anyway <unclear/></u>
<u n="444" who="S0282">I don't know perhaps it's better if you have an experience like that somewhere along the line when you</u>
<u n="445" who="S0293">it is you have to have it you have to have it</u>
<u n="446" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm so it just teaches you what happens</u>
<u n="447" who="S0293">well you have to <unclear>be</unclear></u>
<u n="448" who="S0282" trans="overlap">when you don't</u>
<u n="449" who="S0293">you have to be robust enough to deal with the knocks you can't be a musician and many many good musicians fall by the way at this stage</u>
<u n="450" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="451" who="S0293">or at music college cos they can't can't cope with the rejection if they've always been the best</u>
<u n="452" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="453" who="S0293">and suddenly they start getting knocks</u>
<u n="454" who="S0282">but then on the other hand this is where it starts getting serious because it's <trunc>y</trunc>you know beyond a certain age nobody's going to stand up and clap you and beam all over their face and be pleased to see you standing on a stage just cos you're you as your parents and your friends and your aunties and uncles et cetera would do you know you become just another musician in an orchestra one of however many perhaps you're cannon fodder you're certainly paid a shitty amount of money you know and actually the reality of being a musician as an adult is is you're not a gilded youth any more at all you're a hack</u>
<u n="455" who="S0293">no no no</u>
<u n="456" who="S0282">and the transition from gilded youth to hack must also be</u>
<u n="457" who="S0293" trans="overlap">it's a really rough transition</u>
<u n="458" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="459" who="S0293">it's really rough and and and interestingly now I've gone through it with the kids I think it's more interesting because <pause dur="short"/> they are trained to such a high level and they dedicate themselves from such a young age all of these kids will've been practising serious amounts of time from fourteen onwards</u>
<u n="460" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0293">you know it's they are adults in their playing</u>
<u n="462" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="463" who="S0293">from the age of fourteen onwards</u>
<u n="464" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="465" who="S0293">and then as you say they just become any old hack who's sort of hired for a pittance to do you know play a tune <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="466" who="S0282" trans="overlap">mm yes</u>
<u n="467" who="S0293">and it <unclear/></u>
<u n="468" who="S0282">and nobody notices you again and actually you're probably sitting in the dark most of the time</u>
<u n="469" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0282">cos erm you know you're just you're just at the back and super you know just I don't know just</u>
<u n="471" who="S0293">well that's why <unclear/></u>
<u n="472" who="S0282" trans="overlap">you might as well be playing the triangle or something ping</u>
<u n="473" who="S0293">but it's a society unto itself I think the musicians all appreciate each each other so <unclear/></u>
<u n="474" who="S0282">oh yeah there must be a benefit there must be a benefit to it I mean I suppose I don't know <unclear>perhaps is it a bit like being</unclear> an artist? or?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0293" trans="overlap">yes it is an artist</u>
<u n="476" who="S0282">any any other kind of performing really that that actually the comradeship of your peers and being part of the little</u>
<u n="477" who="S0293" trans="overlap">well they know whether you're good or they know whether you're good or not</u>
<u n="478" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah no</u>
<u n="479" who="S0293">and you are creating music and er you know you know whether you're doing it well or not <unclear/> about personal satisfaction I think</u>
<u n="480" who="S0282" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0293">for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know like with er with the <anon type="place"/> she actually really didn't care whether she got through or not all she cared about was whether she felt she had done her best</u>
<u n="482" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0293">it was about it was a personal thing</u>
<u n="484" who="S0282">no</u>
<u n="485" who="S0293">it was <unclear/> she could stand up in front of her contemporaries and feel pride in what she had produced and she could and that's it wasn't anything to do with anybody else <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's just whether she could actually say she actually played like she wanted to</u>
<u n="486" who="S0282">yeah and what was really nice when we went to that concert is other people seeing other people around going oh that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> oh that's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and coming up and saying oh hello <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="487" who="S0293"><unclear>what was that one</unclear>?</u>
<u n="488" who="S0282">when we went up to the <anon type="place"/> to see what was the name of that musician that whose piece we listened to that time? when we went up to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> on that Saturday night at the <anon type="place"/> there was that modern beginning with A a modern composer</u>
<u n="489" who="S0293">oh <unclear/> Adès?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0282">Adès?</u>
<u n="491" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="492" who="S0282">is it Adès?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="494" who="S0282">and I really liked that music</u>
<u n="495" who="S0293">I oh I I we saw erm the Tempest which is an opera by Adès which I think is bloody brilliant it's it's a film you <trunc>sh</trunc> if you ever get a chance to see it</u>
<u n="496" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="497" who="S0293">it's it's quite weird but I thought it was wonderful</u>
<u n="498" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="499" who="S0293">yeah well mm we shall <trunc>s</trunc> we shall see but erm <trunc>w</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s actually won a competition she's won a concerto competition and she's doing erm a performance up at erm the new well it's a new concert hall in <anon type="place"/> it's called <anon type="place"/> it's just opposite the <anon type="place"/> centre it's part of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="501" who="S0293">and it's huge and she's doing that in December so she's got big things coming up</u>
<u n="502" who="S0282">oh well that's good</u>
<u n="503" who="S0293" trans="overlap">so it's yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0282">and what did you say erm that erm what did you say that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> et cetera were coming round to have a look at a gym? to have a look at oh no to have a look at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0293" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house</u>
<u n="506" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s house not er at a gym I thought oh my god</u>
<u n="507" who="S0293" trans="overlap"><unclear/> no no no <trunc>th</trunc>they're coming round to socialise really</u>
<u n="508" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="509" who="S0293"><unclear/> <unclear>go out for a drink</unclear></u>
<u n="510" who="S0282">and is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> coming as well? or just?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0293">no</u>
<u n="512" who="S0282">no cos he's on holiday</u>
<u n="513" who="S0293"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't socialise with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't come down ever</u>
<u n="514" who="S0282">doesn't he?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0293">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is very antisocial he plays he plays golf but he doesn't he goes on the golf trips but he doesn't doesn't socialise otherwise</u>
<u n="516" who="S0282">mm they were down at our house the other day mending the boiler again again something else went wrong but it's a three-way valve and they always go wrong it's very boring indeed it drives me bonkers you wake up in the middle of the night and you think what's that noise? you think it's the boiler what is the what time is it? <unclear/> why is the boiler going? and of course because it's the the valve has blocked it's still just going like billy-o and it's the middle of the night and all the radiators are boiling hot and the water is piping hot and everything and it won't switch itself off because the valve is stuck in the open position it's really frustrating</u>
<u n="517" who="S0293">mm mm yeah they are annoying we when we do the kitchen we need a new boiler I guess <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will talk to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="518" who="S0282" trans="overlap">how far have you got on with?</u>
<u n="519" who="S0293">nowhere</u>
<u n="520" who="S0282">nowhere?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0293">we've got the plans for <trunc>buil</trunc> we've got building regs plans now</u>
<u n="522" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh <unclear>and er</unclear></u>
<u n="523" who="S0293"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> saw the builder but he can't do us till next year so I don't think any builder's going to be able to do us until next year <unclear/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0282">oh it's frustrating isn't it?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0293">to be honest there's quite a few things we have to do ourselves and we're not progressing with those you know we've got to change some guttering we've got to move a flower bed we've got to empty the sheds get rid of the sheds you know there's quite a lot of stuff we have to do</u>
<u n="526" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="527" who="S0293">which erm we're not really addressing at the moment we've got to get</u>
<u n="528" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no it's very frustrating</u>
<u n="529" who="S0293" trans="overlap">skips in and we've got to actually</u>
<u n="530" who="S0282">it's very satisfying getting a skip</u>
<u n="531" who="S0293">I know well I want to get one now cos it's the only way I'm going to get <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to empty the bloody sheds and we've got just we've emptied <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s loft which is a huge <unclear/> and to be fair to him he did it himself erm which was well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> helped him</u>
<u n="532" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="533" who="S0293">erm but that is a huge relief cos we did a whole load of old carpets and god knows what else <unclear/></u>
<u n="534" who="S0282">oh that's terrible and you imagine that they're still gonna be alright and you look at them and you think <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="535" who="S0293">they probably would've been alright but you know there comes a point when you just don't have the will to lay these things do you?</u>
<u n="536" who="S0282">no and actually also we rolled up the carpet in one room in our house to put to to put the wardrobe in new wardrobe what I didn't realise is once you've rolled up the carpet the last thing you should do is walk on it because when the guy came round and I said oh can you relay that carpet he said no I can't cos it's all creased up if I lay it now you're gonna have to call me back in about three weeks' time because when all the creases have have unfolded from it again it will be too loose so therefore you have to lay it back down and not pin it down for the next sort of three or four weeks and when call me back after that when all the creases have gone and then I'll then I'll pin it back down again</u>
<u n="537" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="538" who="S0282">that and he sort of said has anybody been <trunc>wor</trunc> walking on there so <unclear/> said er er well yeah didn't realise we weren't supposed to so so it's <trunc>ve</trunc> so once they've been rolled up in the loft for however long I would imagine they're never gonna lie flat again actually</u>
<u n="539" who="S0293">no</u>
<u n="540" who="S0282">they're not rolled down to a piece of cardboard like they were in the first place</u>
<u n="541" who="S0293">no</u>
<u n="542" who="S0282">they're just sort of sloppily thrown up there likewise lino</u>
<u n="543" who="S0293">and the other thing well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s friends have just been sleeping on them and <unclear/> sleeping on em</u>
<u n="544" who="S0282">oh yeah</u>
<u n="545" who="S0293">but erm the other thing is I suspect this bloody project is gonna end up er exponentially must more expensive than we'd anticipated</u>
<u n="546" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="547" who="S0293">because actually when it comes to it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s beginning to realise that he can't do certain things himself and he hasn't got he just hasn't got the time</u>
<u n="548" who="S0282">is that his knees as well?</u>
<u n="549" who="S0293">it's just time hasn't go the time erm</u>
<u n="550" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="551" who="S0293">you know er</u>
<u n="552" who="S0282">er <unclear/> I was gonna say earlier as well is have you do you ever have massages? cos er if you had massages that I think that would help as well</u>
<u n="553" who="S0293">I don't find anybody I trust cos the cos I've had a back problem I'd only want to do it with somebody I really trust for massage</u>
<u n="554" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="555" who="S0293">I wouldn't go for a general massage cos some people can <trunc>bu</trunc>bugger me up</u>
<u n="556" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="557" who="S0293">and there are people that that are good but I would only go on personal recommendation</u>
<u n="558" who="S0282">yeah no quite but I was wondering if that might help really</u>
<u n="559" who="S0293">it's expensive expensive <unclear/></u>
<u n="560" who="S0282">yeah all these things are expensive</u>
<u n="561" who="S0293">but actually that's what my mum used to do thinking about it she did yoga massage and she that helped her with her stiffness so perhaps that is something well I'll try these exercises and see cos I've been doing quite a lot of swimming recently and I thought well it has helped I have got</u>
<u n="562" who="S0282">well that <trunc>sh</trunc> ought to help a bit yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0293">well yeah but it it actually hasn't helped on the lower back it doesn't hasn't er it helps in terms of pain and it helps in er terms of general strength but it doesn't help it has helped to a certain extent with the knee but it hasn't helped getting up and dressing and moving around type things</u>
<u n="564" who="S0282">mm mm</u>
<u n="565" who="S0293">so er</u>
<u n="566" who="S0282">and when was the last time you had a new mattress?</u>
<u n="567" who="S0293">er fifteen years ago it was a good one</u>
<u n="568" who="S0282" trans="overlap"><unclear/> perhaps you should get a new mattress</u>
<u n="569" who="S0293" trans="overlap">well I know we've been thinking about that we probably do need a new mattress</u>
<u n="570" who="S0282">my actually er my er cos er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has one of <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s fetishes is about mattresses and he always used to say I like a really really firm mattress so he we went out and bought a we had to go to <anon type="place"/> to buy this mattress and we got the hardest one in the shop which he insisted was the only one he could sleep on and we slept on that for I don't know er for I can't remember how long and in the end I had to say to him I cannot sleep on this mattress any more because actually you know what? it is really seriously doing my hip in and my left hip I had</u>
<u n="571" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="572" who="S0282">I <trunc>ha</trunc> er my hip was out of joint really just a bit kind of erm just I don't know unbalanced? or <trunc>tw</trunc> slightly twisted? or slightly tense? er I don't know I was kind of cocking my hip a bit</u>
<u n="573" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="574" who="S0282">for such a long time and I just had a permanent hip ache so I had to go on my left-hand side and in the end I had to say to him look we will have to get we'll have to get a softer mattress so we did get a softer mattress</u>
<u n="575" who="S0293">why don't you do er <trunc>t</trunc>two two <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="576" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and then ah well no and then we had erm and then we got a softer mattress still wasn't enough and my hip was still bad and then in the end I bought a <trunc>mat</trunc> I bought a new bed and a new mattress without consulting him and I got a more expensive mattress and one that I've got more padding and one that had more independent springs which means that actually that it it's much more responsive to your individual weight and protuberances</u>
<u n="577" who="S0293">ours was an incredible expensive bed we bought</u>
<u n="578" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="579" who="S0293">because actually interestingly as you say we have were having a terrible time and I was in agony at night and hadn't slept for years and we were <trunc>s</trunc> you know some friends said <unclear>look how about a bed</unclear>? we'd only just inherited beds and whatever we'd never bought one so we bought a really high quality bed and it's been really really good</u>
<u n="580" who="S0282">yeah</u>
<u n="581" who="S0293">it's it's difficult to know whether we <unclear/> actually would improve matters or not er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can still sleep on it <unclear/> it's not bad the bed</u>
<u n="582" who="S0282">well the thing the thing is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said that he had to have a hard mattress he sleeps he sleeps whatever he's sleeping on so actually it hasn't mattered to him at all that we've got a soft mattress he's been absolutely fine but it's been much much better for me but it's taken an awful long time for my hip to get better after that my hip was bad for ten years but the other thing that helped me was t'ai chi</u>
<u n="583" who="S0293">yeah you see I can't do anything like that at the moment cos I fall over</u>
<u n="584" who="S0282">no but it helps with that it's been proven scientifically proven don't give me that look</u>
<u n="585" who="S0293">no no no <unclear/></u>
<u n="586" who="S0282">scientifically proven in <trunc>a</trunc><trunc>a</trunc>ancient Japanese people <vocal desc="cough"/> Chinese people <vocal desc="cough"/> that it improves your balance</u>
<u n="587" who="S0293" trans="overlap">I'm not very good at <unclear>those</unclear> classes to be honest</u>
<u n="588" who="S0282">no it is a pain in the arse</u>
<u n="589" who="S0293">I I erm I I'm not a very groupie person</u>
<u n="590" who="S0282">you can get Youtube videos and you can get</u>
<u n="591" who="S0293">yeah I'm not <trunc>rea</trunc> I'm also very bad at following things cos I don't know my right and left <unclear/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0282">oh yeah no yeah that's very <unclear>bad</unclear></u>
<u n="593" who="S0293" trans="overlap">it's really <unclear>bad</unclear> <unclear/> I can't follow a video <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="594" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah</u>
<u n="595" who="S0293">it's twenty past five</u>
<u n="596" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I know</u>
<u n="597" who="S0293">come on homework it's gonna be a nightmare otherwise tomorrow come on</u>
<u n="598" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="599" who="S0293">I've bought some Kitkats for tonight</u>
<u n="600" who="S0282">and you're not having one unless you've done your homework</u>
<u n="601" who="S0293" trans="overlap">but you do need to get some homework done</u>
<u n="602" who="S0282">no shame bribing your child with Kitkats that's terrible</u>
<u n="603" who="S0293">well I er I I er I bring up <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> completely differently you should see her packed lunches they're absolutely ridiculous</u>
<u n="604" who="S0282">chock-a-block with crisps sweeties</u>
<u n="605" who="S0293" trans="overlap">crisps everything the lot</u>
<u n="606" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/> jelly cubes</u>
<u n="607" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="608" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="609" who="S0293"><unclear/> things I completely banned from the other children but I've just given up well just not I haven't given up but bringing her differently it is interesting how I'm bringing her up it's just different and I have to bring her up differently cos she is a different child</u>
<u n="610" who="S0282">she's a different animal that girl she's been that way</u>
<u n="611" who="S0293">and er she she's on board now with packed lunches</u>
<u n="612" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="613" who="S0293">she</u>
<u n="614" who="S0282" trans="overlap">well if she as long as she eats something</u>
<u n="615" who="S0293">exactly</u>
<u n="616" who="S0282">just eat anything girl <unclear/></u>
<u n="617" who="S0293">well exactly I came to the point where she was eating a lolly for lunch you know it is better than a lolly <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="618" who="S0282">yes quite</u>
<u n="619" who="S0293">erm</u>
<u n="620" who="S0282">she's got the will of a</u>
<u n="621" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="622" who="S0282">stubbornness of a whatever</u>
<u n="623" who="S0293">she's quite funny actually cos for somebody who doesn't really take school very seriously she actually does do her homework it's quite amazing to me I haven't had any kind of detentions for not doing it or anything</u>
<u n="624" who="S0282">oh that's quite good cos she's not yeah she's not actually getting detention she's not actually you're not actually being hauled up</u>
<u n="625" who="S0293"><unclear>no</unclear></u>
<u n="626" who="S0282">to have little you know discussions with the headmaster about you know</u>
<u n="627" who="S0293"><unclear/> well they may be being being very cautious cos she's known to be emotionally vulnerable I don't know</u>
<u n="628" who="S0282" trans="overlap">ah right okay</u>
<u n="629" who="S0293">but I haven't</u>
<u n="630" who="S0282">yeah but then on the other hand actually that's the worst possible thing that could happen to her because then she'll just turn out to be a monster when she's thirty cos she'll she'll just be expecting people to stay out of her way</u>
<event desc="sound of phone"/>
<u n="631" who="S0282"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="632" who="S0293">hi darling</u>
<u n="633" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">hello how are you? are you free to talk?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0293">I'm not free to talk at the moment I've got <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> with me can are you free at any other time to talk to me?</u>
<u n="635" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">erm yeah no I'll phone back later <unclear>then</unclear></u>
<u n="636" who="S0293">could you <trunc>s</trunc> could you ring me a bit later? would that be possible?</u>
<u n="637" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah yeah no that's fine I'll ring you later</u>
<u n="638" who="S0293">are you alright?</u>
<u n="639" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah no no I'm fine</u>
<u n="640" who="S0293">been doing the orchestra course today?</u>
<u n="641" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">yeah <unclear/> <unclear>playing like</unclear> solidly apart from <unclear/> one other break I've playing solidly for like <unclear/> since nine o'clock this morning</u>
<u n="642" who="S0293">oh</u>
<u n="643" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="644" who="S0293">oh dear so you ought to go outside and rest yourself have a bit of a walk round</u>
<u n="645" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> lying lying down <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="646" who="S0293"><unclear>well</unclear> go and have a walk outside</u>
<u n="647" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh no I need to lie down then we've got dinner and then we're gonna go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="648" who="S0293">mm sounds absolutely riveting</u>
<u n="649" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it's fine I'll <unclear/></u>
<u n="650" who="S0293">okay well give me a ring er later yeah okay that'd be nice thanks</u>
<u n="651" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay <unclear/> just a quick thing</u>
<u n="652" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="653" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">just a quick thing erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> er messaged me on Facebook <unclear/> being like oh erm me erm like basically <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is gonna bring nan or something like that</u>
<u n="654" who="S0293">yes</u>
<u n="655" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">down to <anon type="place"/> or something</u>
<u n="656" who="S0293">yes yeah</u>
<u n="657" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">she was like erm I just thought I'd check with you which weekend would be best for you?</u>
<u n="658" who="S0293">oh okay</u>
<u n="659" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="660" who="S0293">well let's talk about that this evening let's <trunc>w</trunc>we'll work out an <trunc>e</trunc><trunc>e</trunc> an <trunc>eveni</trunc> an an er a weekend this evening</u>
<u n="661" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay this evening yeah okay</u>
<u n="662" who="S0293">yeah okay okay</u>
<u n="663" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">okay then bye</u>
<u n="664" who="S0293" trans="overlap">lots of love bye</u>
<u n="665" who="S0282">bye</u>
<u n="666" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="667" who="S0282">what are you cooking for tonight?</u>
<u n="668" who="S0293">er salmon and chips we er it's the</u>
<u n="669" who="S0282">oh right</u>
<u n="670" who="S0293">it's the only reason <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> comes home on a Friday</u>
<u n="671" who="S0282"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="672" who="S0293">we're creatures of habit we are</u>
<u n="673" who="S0282">ah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0293"><vocal desc="laugh"/> actually <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't eat any vegetables</u>
<u n="675" who="S0282">doesn't he?</u>
<u n="676" who="S0293">no no</u>
<u n="677" who="S0282">god he's such a nice man he is so nice</u>
<u n="678" who="S0293">he is a nice man he's very nice he's quite funny he doesn't er <trunc>h</trunc>he doesn't do anything weird or wonderful he's very very kind of traditional</u>
<u n="679" who="S0282">very very conventional mm</u>
<u n="680" who="S0293" trans="overlap">traditional yes very conventional</u>
<u n="681" who="S0282">but that's well that's <unclear/></u>
<u n="682" who="S0293">he looked after his father who had <trunc>s</trunc> very serious Alzheimer's and was doubly incontinent and god knows what else for about ten or fifteen years</u>
<u n="683" who="S0282">oh did he really?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="685" who="S0282">er is he he's not married? is he not married?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0293">he was married</u>
<u n="687" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="688" who="S0293">and it didn't fall apart anything to do with him <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="689" who="S0282">oh</u>
<u n="690" who="S0293">it was very sad he was very in love with her they met when they were about fifteen I think and erm</u>
<u n="691" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="692" who="S0293">she just went off with somebody else but <unclear/></u>
<u n="693" who="S0282"><unclear>mm</unclear></u>
<u n="694" who="S0293">they had two children and whatever and he he has girlfriends now and again</u>
<u n="695" who="S0282">oh well that's mm okay</u>
<u n="696" who="S0293">but he was a very <trunc>c</trunc>committed family man</u>
<u n="697" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="698" who="S0293"><unclear/> both his children living with him and that kind of thing</u>
<u n="699" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="700" who="S0293">so mm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is a funny bloke I don't er I don't I can't get my head round <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at all I think he's a bloke's bloke I don't think he talks to women really or he he might charm them but he doesn't he's not kind of</u>
<u n="701" who="S0282">he's just about started speaking to me he'll talk to me now</u>
<u n="702" who="S0293">doesn't talk to me you see at all</u>
<u n="703" who="S0282">no he'll talk to well he'll talk to me about boilers and stuff not not anything about anything <unclear>else than</unclear> boilers but you know it's quite interesting that when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was there one day they insist they both insisted on talking to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="704" who="S0293" trans="overlap">they're men's men</u>
<u n="705" who="S0282">and they might as well not bother I I was er saying to I nearly felt like saying to them why are you talking? there there's no point talking to him and in fact they left him instructions as to how to clean the filter and I think he probably he <trunc>b</trunc> he maintains he's done it once but I thought to myself if they if they've had to come round again cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hasn't cleaned that filter I shall be really cross because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has not cleaned the filter again and there's no point in asking <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to clean the filter he did it once as far as he's concerned you know that's it you know you're not that you do it every six months he can't possibly remember something as repetitive as that although I have to say he is getting <trunc>mu</trunc> far more practical in his old age at least</u>
<u n="706" who="S0293">I'm getting more impractical you see cos living with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I get terribly impractical</u>
<u n="707" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="708" who="S0293">I used to be quite a practical person not at all now</u>
<u n="709" who="S0282">no well I suppose it's very easy to leave it to them but erm but anyway erm did you say that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had a lathe and everything?</u>
<u n="710" who="S0293">yep buried</u>
<u n="711" who="S0282">is it? don't throw it away</u>
<u n="712" who="S0293">no no he wouldn't give it away</u>
<u n="713" who="S0282"><unclear>no</unclear>? <vocal desc="laugh"/> there was I was on the the the other person on this course was a barrister who erm who erm has got a <trunc>ki</trunc> I don't know must have his own <trunc>hou</trunc>house with all his own tools and makes his own long longbows <trunc>ma</trunc> er <unclear>sell</unclear> <trunc>l</trunc>longbows and has now and has got a lathe <trunc>h</trunc> that he bought off somebody for a hundred quid when the person got bored</u>
<u n="714" who="S0293">that's what that's what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to get him all the stuff from auctions</u>
<u n="715" who="S0282" trans="overlap">oh right oh right okay</u>
<u n="716" who="S0293">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has got a shed full of unbelievably high-end wood turning tools</u>
<u n="717" who="S0282">oh right I'll have to bring in my things to show you</u>
<u n="718" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="719" who="S0282">I I was quite pleased with them actually</u>
<u n="720" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="721" who="S0282">although it was so tiring we were just discussing today with the others about how our brains don't work properly any more since we had chemotherapy</u>
<u n="722" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="723" who="S0282">we're all in the same boat it really really fries your brain so it takes such a long time for you brains to come back and by the end of Tuesday and by the end of Wednesday I was so</u>
<u n="724" who="S0293"><unclear/> aspect of work isn't it?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0282" trans="overlap">tired</u>
<u n="726" who="S0293">it's what</u>
<u n="727" who="S0282">that er <trunc>i</trunc> this guy was telling me he was sort of saying right okay start with your tool over here bring it round like this use that hand as a lever that hand as a fulcrum go in this direction and by the end of the afternoon I was like <vocal desc="misc"/> er I couldn't make my brain tell my arm what to do especially my right arm the right-hand side of my body seems to be completely unbiddable and my brain is just like not sending messages it's like I was supposed to have my elbow up here and do this with my elbow and my brain is saying okay elbow move and my elbow is just not going anywhere</u>
<u n="728" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="729" who="S0282">and the man's going no no not like that no not like that no not like he's he's very very patient and but I'm gonna have to have some more classes and not do all day just do half a day at a time because by the end of the day I was just completely</u>
<u n="730" who="S0293" trans="overlap">expensive hobby though isn't it? it's very expensive these classes</u>
<u n="731" who="S0282" trans="overlap">it is an expensive hobby</u>
<u n="732" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="733" who="S0282">but the thing is that if you erm once you've got the tools and once you've got your own stock of wood it's fine</u>
<u n="734" who="S0293">once you've got the tools <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's a mega investment</u>
<u n="735" who="S0282">I know the tools are very expensive</u>
<u n="736" who="S0293">and you can buy endless tools <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had them coming in for years every time they went down the pub er a new one would come in by the back gate</u>
<u n="737" who="S0282">really?</u>
<u n="738" who="S0293">he'd think I wouldn't notice</u>
<u n="739" who="S0282">well we only use four? five? different tools</u>
<u n="740" who="S0293" trans="overlap">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got an awful lot of them</u>
<u n="741" who="S0282">has he?</u>
<u n="742" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="743" who="S0282">well it's the lathe that's the most expensive I should imagine you pick up the tools if you if you er kept an eagle eye open cos I've never you know I wouldn't've known what I was looking at</u>
<u n="744" who="S0293"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s your man</u>
<u n="745" who="S0282">is he really?</u>
<u n="746" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="747" who="S0282">I need to pal up with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> despite his girlfriend</u>
<u n="748" who="S0293">yeah she's got a bit better recently</u>
<u n="749" who="S0282">has she?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0293">I had a couple of evenings which weren't quite so bad</u>
<u n="751" who="S0282">she is weird</u>
<u n="752" who="S0293">yeah she she can be very strange</u>
<u n="753" who="S0282">she was very weird at your party</u>
<u n="754" who="S0293">mm she gets very nervous I think that's partly it</u>
<u n="755" who="S0282">I think yes it was kind of she was <trunc>d</trunc> being highly irritating I thought</u>
<u n="756" who="S0293">mm <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is absolutely er happy with her so that's that's good</u>
<u n="757" who="S0282">well that's really nice but she's got one of what we call a Muttley laugh in our house</u>
<u n="758" who="S0293">a what laugh?</u>
<u n="759" who="S0282">Muttley laugh</u>
<u n="760" who="S0293">what does that mean?</u>
<u n="761" who="S0282">do you know like Wacky Races on the television when we were young?</u>
<u n="762" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="763" who="S0282">it was a cartoon</u>
<u n="764" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="765" who="S0282">and there was a racing car driver who had a dog called Muttley and the dog would go <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="766" who="S0293">oh yes</u>
<u n="767" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="768" who="S0282">it's a particular kind of weird laugh that people have</u>
<u n="769" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="770" who="S0282">so she was very much like that</u>
<u n="771" who="S0293">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="772" who="S0282">so anyway we can stop in a minute it's nearly there you do realise you've helped me to earn twenty quid? near enough fifty-two minutes it's only a few minutes to go <pause dur="short"/> so what are your so this weekend in <anon type="place"/> what erm my husband keeps asking me questions about it</u>
<u n="773" who="S0293">I don't</u>
<u n="774" who="S0282">and and I keep saying I really don't know</u>
<u n="775" who="S0293" trans="overlap"><unclear/> don't don't don't come if it's er <unclear/></u>
<u n="776" who="S0282">well it's not that it no it's not that it's not that actually</u>
<u n="777" who="S0293">it feels like <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc>if er it</u>
<u n="778" who="S0282">no I tell you what</u>
<u n="779" who="S0293" trans="overlap">we very rarely we very rarely ask people to to come down and I guess cos it's so such a <unclear>sort of</unclear> special place to us in a funny kind of way</u>
<u n="780" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="781" who="S0293">and erm I guess it may not be like that for other people and and er I guess er I can quite easily take offence actually when people don't seem <trunc>t</trunc>seem to like it so I really wouldn't it's not a big deal coming down cos we <unclear/></u>
<u n="782" who="S0282">no no no I I tell you I can tell you exactly what the problem is first of all <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had got a week off last week</u>
<u n="783" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="784" who="S0282">secondly I was supposed to go to hospital on Monday for an appointment and then thirdly there's that weekend which involved taking the Monday off work now Monday's at work for him are really big days they have really big meetings with the permanent sector on a Monday and with all the senior managers and stuff like that</u>
<u n="785" who="S0293">well that's why I'm saying just don't don't bother come a different time</u>
<u n="786" who="S0282">so no no no no no well that it won't help because it'll be always be a Monday but because erm</u>
<u n="787" who="S0293">no it won't always be a Monday er it is this time cos of the half-term</u>
<u n="788" who="S0282">mm well okay okay but er because my appointment was cancelled and he went into work this Monday he then relaxed a lot more because he thought that out of four out of four Mondays in the month he was taking three of them off which er leaves him quite vulnerable because that means that he's not in the room when really quite big decisions get made about his work</u>
<u n="789" who="S0293">well I quite understand that <unclear/></u>
<u n="790" who="S0282" trans="overlap">and stuff like that but because I didn't have a hospital appointment on Monday</u>
<u n="791" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="792" who="S0282">it means that he is now far more relaxed</u>
<u n="793" who="S0293">but even so</u>
<u n="794" who="S0282">about</u>
<u n="795" who="S0293">even so we <trunc>w</trunc><trunc>wai</trunc> you can wait and we can go on a Friday sometime we just <unclear/> didn't get the Friday dates during half-term this time sometimes we get Friday Saturday Sunday but we didn't this time <unclear/></u>
<u n="796" who="S0282" trans="overlap">no no no no no that's fine now he's all square and but also he's just been he's been arsey about he's just being arsey he's being arsey with me that's the point he's not being arsey with anybody else he's just being arsey with me and also maintaining also the other thing of course is he maintains it was the first he'd heard of it well actually I then found a note of a phone conversation he's had with you where it was quite plain that he'd talked to you about it he swore blind that this was he'd never heard of it before but which is just him again being arsey with me really but erm so the Friday</u>
<u n="797" who="S0293">yeah er I think we will drive down in our car so if you drive over here</u>
<u n="798" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="799" who="S0293">we wouldn't leave before probably eight I think not early</u>
<u n="800" who="S0282">eight what?</u>
<u n="801" who="S0293">seven seven thirty at night</u>
<u n="802" who="S0282">at night?</u>
<u n="803" who="S0293">seven</u>
<u n="804" who="S0282">not in the morning?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0293">yeah no no no no on Friday</u>
<u n="806" who="S0282">oh well that yes and oh right okay</u>
<u n="807" who="S0293"><trunc>s</trunc><trunc>s</trunc> er maybe <trunc>s</trunc>maybe seven eight nine ten yeah maybe seven seven thirty <unclear>something</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="808" who="S0282">oh right okay to avoid the traffic and everything</u>
<u n="809" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="810" who="S0282">okay oh well that makes that puts completely different complexion on things as well</u>
<u n="811" who="S0293">I think probably seven thirty</u>
<u n="812" who="S0282">okay</u>
<u n="813" who="S0293">I'll talk to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> tonight but er it it wouldn't be any earlier than that</u>
<u n="814" who="S0282">oh well no that's fine</u>
<u n="815" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="816" who="S0282">because that's fine</u>
<u n="817" who="S0293">wouldn't be earlier than seven definitely</u>
<u n="818" who="S0282">okay oh no cos the other thing about him is he's extraordinarily conscientious I've left him at home today and he will've worked all day without stopping he was at his desk at eight o'clock this morning and he will've sat there absolutely all day and he won't've <trunc>st</trunc> he won't've shifted out of his chair all day and he he is extraordinarily self-disciplined and he was like oh well I have to cos he was like oh I can't possibly skive any work on Friday as well that's er no I can't I can't do that that would be wrong if I skived and it's like well actually I'm sure they owe you loads of hours quite frankly</u>
<u n="819" who="S0293">mm yeah</u>
<u n="820" who="S0282">oh no that makes that makes it very much easier as well</u>
<u n="821" who="S0293">but I I wouldn't do it if it's if it's difficult <unclear/></u>
<u n="822" who="S0282">no it's not that it's no it's not that it's difficult it's <trunc>ab</trunc> no no it's absolutely fine with me it's just that er you know it really is er broader circumstances that he's in</u>
<u n="823" who="S0293"><unclear/> I know but that means we <trunc>c</trunc>we could do a different we can do <unclear/> different time</u>
<u n="824" who="S0282" trans="overlap">that's just leading him to be an awkward sod really no no he'll be <trunc>f</trunc> it'll do him good</u>
<u n="825" who="S0293">we just go we haven't had many well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hasn't got any any more leave so that's why we can't take well why couldn't we take the Friday? we couldn't take the Friday cos the kids are at school and <unclear>we're taking the kids</unclear> <unclear/> and then they're off on Monday so we've got that <trunc>ha</trunc> we've got that weekend at <anon type="place"/> er sometimes we get erm in the holidays we get Friday Saturday Sunday but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s got that this time</u>
<u n="826" who="S0282">right</u>
<u n="827" who="S0293">and in fact it's better for us this way round because <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s gotta go there's concerts going on <unclear/> but anyway so <unclear/> this way yeah so it'll be erm it will be wet so you'll need full waterproofs you need proper walking shoes</u>
<u n="828" who="S0282">when you say full waterproofs?</u>
<u n="829" who="S0293">er oh just a mac <unclear/></u>
<u n="830" who="S0282">I've got that is that enough?</u>
<u n="831" who="S0293"><trunc>i</trunc>it's just got to be really waterproof</u>
<u n="832" who="S0282">that says waterproof breathable</u>
<u n="833" who="S0293">I'll I'll bring you a spare mac with me you can I'll bring another one with me just in case it's not as good</u>
<u n="834" who="S0282">and I have got</u>
<u n="835" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="836" who="S0282">I have got proper walking boots</u>
<u n="837" who="S0293">yeah and erm probably be helpful if you brought have you got erm double sheets? just for an ordinary double bed</u>
<u n="838" who="S0282">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="839" who="S0293">so if you bring a bottom sheet and a duvet cover and pillow cases that's probably a good idea actually bring pillows</u>
<u n="840" who="S0282">okay</u>
<u n="841" who="S0293">cos the pillows are not fantastic there are pillows there but you might want your own ah no bring pillows it's a good idea to bring pillows</u>
<u n="842" who="S0282">okay</u>
<u n="843" who="S0293">erm <pause dur="short"/> probably enough there I didn't count there's a lot lots of duvets there I haven't counted pillows recently <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s done a clear out there's loads of blankets loads of duvets</u>
<u n="844" who="S0282">we're fine with blankets really I'd <unclear/> we haven't got a problem <unclear/></u>
<u n="845" who="S0293"><unclear/> well duvets there's loads of duvets <unclear>there so bring a double</unclear> duvet <unclear/></u>
<u n="846" who="S0282" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="847" who="S0293">and erm er we get there about ten thirty at night and we'd light the fire and then we would Saturday morning we are collecting <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> from <anon type="place"/> station at eleven so I suspect we'll take <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her friend over swimming in that area and we will go <trunc>po</trunc><trunc>possi</trunc>possibly to <anon type="place"/> castle</u>
<u n="848" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="849" who="S0293">if you're interested I don't know if you've been to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="850" who="S0282">er er er not for</u>
<u n="851" who="S0293"><unclear/></u>
<u n="852" who="S0282" trans="overlap">not for decades not decades and decades</u>
<u n="853" who="S0293">we might go <trunc>t</trunc>we might go to <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/> castle <unclear/></u>
<u n="854" who="S0282" trans="overlap">alright okay yeah <anon type="place"/> no <anon type="place"/>'s always nice</u>
<u n="855" who="S0293">erm</u>
<u n="856" who="S0282">and last time I went to <anon type="place"/> I was so ill that I actually bloody didn't get out of the car</u>
<u n="857" who="S0293">er and then er so we'll probably do that in the morning</u>
<u n="858" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="859" who="S0293">and then collect her at eleven oh I don't know how we're gonna do it actually maybe we'll <trunc>t</trunc> collect her and then go into <anon type="place"/> I don't know how we'll do it anyway something like that and then erm <pause dur="short"/> we'll do a walk <pause dur="short"/> possibly round the <trunc>t</trunc> if the weather's alright we could do a walk round the <anon type="place"/> in the evening and erm there's some fantastic walks <unclear/> some really brilliant walks through the woods it's just spectacularly beautiful actually when we went last weekend very wet but it was lovely lovely and then on Sunday we would probably go down to the <anon type="place"/> and have a walk erm and er <pause dur="long"/> er <pause dur="short"/> well we could go out out and about there's places to go there's <anon type="place"/> but actually <anon type="place"/>'s <unclear>on a</unclear> Saturday so we'd have to think about that work out what we do</u>
<u n="860" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="861" who="S0293">on Monday well mixture basically of I don't know</u>
<u n="862" who="S0282">mm no that sounds really nice</u>
<u n="863" who="S0293">mm</u>
<u n="864" who="S0282">haven't been that way for a bit</u>
<u n="865" who="S0293">yeah</u>
<u n="866" who="S0282">we had a holiday in erm just between <anon type="place"/> and <anon type="place"/> over Easter and that was</u>
<u n="867" who="S0293">you've only been to the old cottage haven't you? you haven't been to the new one?</u>
<u n="868" who="S0282">no I haven't seen the new one</u>
<u n="869" who="S0293">the new one's different it's erm</u>
<u n="870" who="S0282">mm</u>
<u n="871" who="S0293"><trunc>i</trunc>it's better I mean it's not better it's just erm higher quality er build put it er <trunc>in</trunc>internally built if you see my point</u>
<u n="872" who="S0282">mm well it's such a long time since I was there that erm</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
