<text id="SRDJ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:18:41</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-17</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0247 S0248</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>At home</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>How hard it is to learn Spanish / different language learning methodologies / Nations where people speak two languages (Catalan/Castillian etc.) </topics>
		<activity>An account of our Spanish learning efforts</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, complaining, advising</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T15</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0247">
				<exactage>61</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Liverpool</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Liverpudlian</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>EFL teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0248">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Hitchin, Herts</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern/London</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>5</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>london</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired Quantity surveyor</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0247">okay <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> we've trying to learn Spanish now for</u>
<u n="2" who="S0248">how long ago do you think how long?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0247" trans="overlap">well it's over ten years isn't it?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0248">really? I don't really I know it's not a consistent thing we've done is it? you have more than me but it's it I don't really seem to be any further forward</u>
<u n="5" who="S0247">well I'm sure we are a little but then</u>
<u n="6" who="S0248" trans="overlap">don't think I am</u>
<u n="7" who="S0247">we first started erm going to Spanish classes when we were going to go to Argentina for a holiday</u>
<u n="8" who="S0248">and that was two thousand and five wasn't it?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0247">two thousand and three</u>
<u n="10" who="S0248">wasn't it? so it's over ten years</u>
<u n="11" who="S0247" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's over ten years</u>
<u n="12" who="S0248">oh</u>
<u n="13" who="S0247">mm <pause dur="short"/> but of the different ways because we started off with erm evening classes</u>
<u n="14" who="S0248">yeah</u>
<u n="15" who="S0247">and then we've done things like listen to cassettes and the Michel Thomas CDs</u>
<u n="16" who="S0248" trans="overlap">I had those Michel Thomas things where you</u>
<u n="17" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="18" who="S0248">just had to <trunc>list</trunc> er listen to some <trunc>w</trunc> text listen to some words with baroque music playing in the background</u>
<u n="19" who="S0247">oh that was ridiculous wasn't it yeah?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0248" trans="overlap">not try and actually make any attempt to actually remember it</u>
<u n="21" who="S0247">yes</u>
<u n="22" who="S0248">but just supposedly you were meant to walk wake up in the morning</u>
<u n="23" who="S0247">and it was there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="24" who="S0248" trans="overlap">and you just knew it</u>
<u n="25" who="S0247">yes</u>
<u n="26" who="S0248">you were just like a native</u>
<u n="27" who="S0247">and do you remember that tape you had where the erm they said it they read something out in a normal voice and there was a whispering voice as well?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0248">no I don't remember that <pause dur="short"/> was another idea was it?</u>
<u n="29" who="S0247" trans="overlap">it's the it was another idea it sort of played the music and it <trunc>shel</trunc> it told the story of erm of Adele and Peter and <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0248" trans="overlap">oh I remember Adele and Peter yes</u>
<u n="31" who="S0247">and in Guadalajara in Mexico</u>
<u n="32" who="S0248">I do remember it very well</u>
<u n="33" who="S0247">and then you had a track where it just played the music and somebody was whispering in the background</u>
<u n="34" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yes I do I do remember it</u>
<u n="35" who="S0247">the Spanish and that <trunc>w</trunc> the idea of that was that it would stick in your mind but</u>
<u n="36" who="S0248">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0247">I'm not sure</u>
<u n="38" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah well it certainly I their names have stuck in my mind I remember their names</u>
<u n="39" who="S0247" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0248">what they said</u>
<u n="41" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="42" who="S0248"><trunc>r</trunc> I really have no idea</u>
<u n="43" who="S0247" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="44" who="S0248">they were quite fond Peter was quite fond of Adele I remember</u>
<u n="45" who="S0247">yes he he did quite fancy her didn't he?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah I think in in the end he</u>
<u n="47" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0248">yeah</u>
<u n="49" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="50" who="S0248">that's all he really cared about was</u>
<u n="51" who="S0247">yes</u>
<u n="52" who="S0248">getting off with Adele more than learning Spanish I feel</u>
<u n="53" who="S0247" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0248">although he probably had to do one to achieve the other</u>
<u n="55" who="S0247">I think he already spoke Spanish</u>
<u n="56" who="S0248">did he?</u>
<u n="57" who="S0247">yes</u>
<u n="58" who="S0248">he just pretended he didn't?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0247">no no I think you're getting two things mixed up <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="60" who="S0248" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0247">you're getting the Michel Thomas CDs mixed up with the Peter and Adele story</u>
<u n="62" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> you always have one person who gets it right in those things and one person who's a who's a bit of a duffer</u>
<u n="63" who="S0247" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yes <pause dur="short"/> one one gets it right and one gets it wrong yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> but <trunc>u</trunc> <trunc>t</trunc> erm going to classes do you you only really did that one that we did with erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in <anon type="place"/> didn't you?</u>
<u n="64" who="S0248" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> yeah</u>
<u n="65" who="S0247">I've done some additional ones I took</u>
<u n="66" who="S0248" trans="overlap">you went to the erm institute didn't you in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="67" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I also did another night class in <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0248">I don't remember that</u>
<u n="69" who="S0247">well you didn't go <pause dur="short"/> I went on my own</u>
<u n="70" who="S0248">where was it?</u>
<u n="71" who="S0247">in in er <anon type="place"/> school</u>
<u n="72" who="S0248">oh</u>
<u n="73" who="S0247">but she was hopeless that teacher <pause dur="short"/> a really really bad teacher</u>
<u n="74" who="S0248">okay</u>
<u n="75" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0248">blame the teacher</u>
<u n="77" who="S0247">well I do blame the teacher <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's <trunc>u</trunc> because in a in a in an evening class of two hours erm we hardly spoke <pause dur="short"/> the <trunc>e</trunc> the only time we ever spoke was to read you know she might say <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will you read out number three? you know and I would read out number three and then you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will you read out number four?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0248" trans="overlap">it's no good is it? it's really no good</u>
<u n="79" who="S0247" trans="overlap">we we didn't ever speak in any Spanish and the teacher spoke English erm <trunc>b</trunc> a good ninety per cent of the time so everything she did was in English and although I think when you're learning the basics you need to learn in your your own language but you know they need to be rehearsing the the language that you know so <pause dur="short"/> I I <trunc>d</trunc> was very disappointed with that teacher</u>
<u n="80" who="S0248">you do <pause dur="short"/> I mean some people are obviously far better than others at learning languages</u>
<u n="81" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="82" who="S0248">and we do all know the optimum way to learn it is to learn it when you're young and you know you you you you <unclear/> and so</u>
<u n="83" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah but you can't be young if you're not young can you?</u>
<u n="84" who="S0248">but I mean</u>
<u n="85" who="S0247" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0248">we've actually tried different methods of learning <pause dur="short"/> er obviously you've gotta learn the grammar but then you you know you probably gotta be around people where Spanish is spoken</u>
<u n="87" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0248">otherwise you just don't really have the <trunc>ge</trunc> have the confidence to to carry on with it or the you know the</u>
<u n="89" who="S0247">mm and <trunc>al</trunc> it always gets better when we go on holiday to Spain doesn't it? so <trunc>i</trunc> if we have a week in Spain by the end of the week you know we know more we feel more confident we recognise more yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0248" trans="overlap">erm when we went to <anon type="place"/> I was I remember speaking to people not not you know but really trying and</u>
<u n="91" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0248">really feel slightly I was getting somewhere</u>
<u n="93" who="S0247">yes</u>
<u n="94" who="S0248">but I don't seem to have carried on with I mean that's totally my own fault</u>
<u n="95" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0248">but it just seems a bit unachievable to me so and the older I get I <trunc>d</trunc> I don't mind you know we both say we can look at a new a fairly er you know a newspaper or certainly a comic and understand most of the you know of what it's on about</u>
<u n="97" who="S0247">mm mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0248">but do I actually having to be able to <trunc>d</trunc> to speak it erm you can ask questions at people but to actually hold a conversation with people just personally seems to be a bit beyond me apart from</u>
<u n="99" who="S0247" trans="overlap">mm I think we could <trunc>r</trunc></u>
<u n="100" who="S0248">very basic things</u>
<u n="101" who="S0247">mm yes I mean I do think we could get there and you start with the basics don't you? so you go into shops and order stuff and you you know can ask for a meal and you can even you know elaborate on what you do and don't want and complain and book hotel rooms <pause dur="short"/> so it all starts from there really doesn't it? and then you build it up</u>
<u n="102" who="S0248">I can't get away from the fact that you sort of have an English phrase and you sort of translate it literally from the English words</u>
<u n="103" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0248">and and you know it might not really make any sense</u>
<u n="105" who="S0247">well it won't will it?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0248" trans="overlap">you can't actually obviously don't know it it's</u>
<u n="107" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0248">an obvious fact</u>
<u n="109" who="S0247">yes mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0248" trans="overlap">but the fact is you have to totally you know <trunc>o</trunc> for the most part</u>
<u n="111" who="S0247">mm mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0248">you have to learn a whole new way of <trunc>sa</trunc> not only</u>
<u n="113" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="114" who="S0248">different</u>
<u n="115" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0248">words you have <trunc>whol</trunc> er er learn a whole new way of saying things</u>
<u n="117" who="S0247">yes but it's but <trunc>s</trunc> but some some of it erm you do without thinking so for example in Spanish if you put the adjective after the noun <pause dur="short"/> you know if you say <foreign lang="spa">camisa negra</foreign> you don't think anything of that you don't think oh why am I saying shirt black instead of black shirt?</u>
<u n="118" who="S0248">no</u>
<u n="119" who="S0247">do you? you just accept it so it's it's only an extension of that that you naturally need to let your brain develop these different patterns</u>
<u n="120" who="S0248">I mean it's obvious that we've if we were really serious about it we've got to at least have a lot of <trunc>y</trunc> tape recordings of you know constantly</u>
<u n="121" who="S0247">mm mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0248">whether you're answering them back or not that would be better obviously</u>
<u n="123" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0248">but at least have you know the Spanish language playing in your ear to actually get used to the speed of it</u>
<u n="125" who="S0247" trans="overlap">I think so yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="126" who="S0248">and and because you just hear I hear Spanish people speak now and you know sometimes unless you know you might be <trunc>go</trunc> a number or a colour or a name basically I can't really understand anything they've said</u>
<u n="127" who="S0247">no but <trunc>u</trunc> we've had this conversation before haven't we? that does get better</u>
<u n="128" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0247">you you might not understand what they're saying but erm you need to be able to recognise where the words are starting and ending and stuff like that which when you don't understand anything it's just a a stream of gibberish <pause dur="short"/> so if we heard a Japanese person speaking you know we wouldn't recognise anything at all would we? not even the pauses in between sentences</u>
<u n="130" who="S0248">no</u>
<u n="131" who="S0247">but with Spanish we should be at least identifying occasional words</u>
<u n="132" who="S0248" trans="overlap"><unclear>like those</unclear></u>
<u n="133" who="S0247">and getting used to the patterns of where they stop and start</u>
<u n="134" who="S0248">no <trunc>y</trunc>yeah</u>
<u n="135" who="S0247">I mean I think that does get better definitely</u>
<u n="136" who="S0248">well it must do hopefully you know if you <trunc>k</trunc> if you persist with it <pause dur="short"/> I mean it we always used to laugh about them we've said it so often but er the fact was that we both neither of us we both took French for four or five <trunc>n</trunc> I was never particularly good at learning French I again was</u>
<u n="137" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0248">okay with the with <trunc>th</trunc><trunc>th</trunc>the the to write it down but no good at speaking it <pause dur="short"/> but as soon as you try and learn Spanish words all this French comes into your head</u>
<u n="139" who="S0247">yeah it's very funny that isn't it? yeah yes</u>
<u n="140" who="S0248" trans="overlap">well it's really really odd</u>
<u n="141" who="S0247">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> but I've <trunc>t</trunc></u>
<u n="142" who="S0248" trans="overlap"><unclear>I mean</unclear></u>
<u n="143" who="S0247">I've heard that so many times</u>
<u n="144" who="S0248">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0247">since from other people about other languages yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0248" trans="overlap">but it's it's a saying it's a it's a truism isn't it?</u>
<u n="147" who="S0247">yeah but it just shows you that your brain is able to sort of switch throw a switch between languages so it's got a</u>
<u n="148" who="S0248"><unclear/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0247">English language and then at the moment it's got everything else hasn't it? so</u>
<u n="150" who="S0248" trans="overlap">we shouldn't we can be the wrong switch though</u>
<u n="151" who="S0247">yeah <pause dur="short"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0248">no idea</u>
<u n="153" who="S0247">I was talking to a girl a couple of weeks ago who speaks four or five different languages</u>
<u n="154" who="S0248">I can't imagine how people can do that</u>
<u n="155" who="S0247">well two of them she was she was raised with but with bilingual parents <pause dur="short"/> and I can't remember what the languages were but let's say she spoke German and Italian from being a child <pause dur="short"/> and and then she additionally was er in <anon type="place"/> to learn or to improve her English <pause dur="short"/> and er she also spoke French which she was doing at school <pause dur="short"/> erm and I said that to her about <trunc>d</trunc> you know doesn't it become a jumble? and she said yeah it does sometimes that you know when she's searching for the right word you know and she can't think of the right word you know in any language so her brain'll throw up whatever it can think of <pause dur="short"/> and also <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who er obviously is very good in English now <pause dur="short"/> at I mean <trunc>adv</trunc>advanced level English <pause dur="short"/> and speaks the the two variations of Spanish both erm Catalan and Castilian</u>
<u n="156" who="S0248">does he?</u>
<u n="157" who="S0247">oh yeah cos he's</u>
<u n="158" who="S0248" trans="overlap">what?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0247">he's from <anon type="place"/> so his</u>
<u n="160" who="S0248">yeah I know that</u>
<u n="161" who="S0247">his first language is</u>
<u n="162" who="S0248" trans="overlap">well why would he speak Castilian then?</u>
<u n="163" who="S0247">well it's it's because Catalan is the minority language</u>
<u n="164" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="165" who="S0247">and Castilian is sort of like the official Spanish language <pause dur="short"/> so all people who live in Catalonia erm you know the the same as people live in the Basque country speak in Basque you know they all speak their first language Catalonian Basque whatever <pause dur="short"/> and then additionally they'll speak Castilian because that's the language of the government and the you know all that and</u>
<u n="166" who="S0248" trans="overlap">and yeah I mean I suppose it's <unclear>coherent but</unclear></u>
<u n="167" who="S0247" trans="overlap">but he says that sometimes when he speaks to his mum on the phone erm he can't remember the word in <trunc>th</trunc> you know he he he's he'll remember the English word for something it would need to be an obscure word</u>
<u n="168" who="S0248">mm yeah yeah</u>
<u n="169" who="S0247">you know but he can't remember the right word in in erm Catalan or Castilian but he can sometimes remember it in English you know? so that's a weird thing isn't it?</u>
<u n="170" who="S0248">mm it is <pause dur="short"/> it is <pause dur="short"/> no I didn't know and I did you know I'm not sure it really applies someone like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s dad or <trunc>d</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum or mum and dad</u>
<u n="171" who="S0247" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0248">if they really are Catalan speakers I'm not sure they can all speak Castilian you know? but I suppose a lot of them can especially</u>
<u n="173" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="174" who="S0248">the younger ones it they would</u>
<u n="175" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="176" who="S0248">I don't mean</u>
<u n="177" who="S0247">mm mm</u>
<u n="178" who="S0248">I don't I don't think that <pause dur="short"/> you know you say that all Dutch people speak English <pause dur="short"/> if you ever meet any old Dutch people they don't speak English</u>
<u n="179" who="S0247">okay so let's take a an example nearer to home then if you go to Ireland</u>
<u n="180" who="S0248">mm mm</u>
<u n="181" who="S0247">erm the the you could probably find a <trunc>f</trunc> a handful of people who only speak Gaelic and don't speak English</u>
<u n="182" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0247">but everybody else that lives there all the four million people or whatever who live in Ireland who speak Gaelic and not all of them do but the ones who do speak Gaelic also speak English</u>
<u n="184" who="S0248">that's true but a lot of them only speak well as you say there's not many Gaelic speakers alone but there'll be a lot of people who don't have don't speak Gaelic at all</u>
<u n="185" who="S0247">yeah but the but it's it's <trunc>n</trunc> it's not that you know it I mean it's</u>
<u n="186" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="187" who="S0247">I dunno what the proportions are I don't know the numbers <pause dur="short"/> alright what about even nearer to home Wales?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0248">yeah well it's it's only</u>
<u n="189" who="S0247">they're all taught it <trunc>t</trunc> in schools Welsh</u>
<u n="190" who="S0248" trans="overlap"><trunc>y</trunc><trunc>y</trunc> they they are but they stopped <trunc>t</trunc>teaching it for a <trunc>g</trunc> for a for a number of years <pause dur="short"/> and so one time there's still a lot of you know <trunc>p</trunc>people who never learnt it all really</u>
<u n="191" who="S0247" trans="overlap">no but we're not saying <trunc>th</trunc> <trunc>y</trunc> <trunc>or</trunc> you're tackling this from the wrong way round <pause dur="short"/> we're saying that people who know the minority language would also know the majority language</u>
<u n="192" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0247">so in the case of Catalonia</u>
<u n="194" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0247">Catalonians would also know Spanish</u>
<u n="196" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0247">you know <trunc>m</trunc> Gaelic speakers would also know English <pause dur="short"/> welsh speakers would also know English <pause dur="short"/> you were saying that it you thought in Catalonia that you would get people who only spoke Catalonian you know and didn't speak Spanish and that that would be a sizeable proportion</u>
<u n="198" who="S0248">I would've still thought there would be fair number of people</u>
<u n="199" who="S0247" trans="overlap">well you'll have to google it cos I think you're wrong</u>
<u n="200" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> I mean how different are they?</u>
<u n="201" who="S0247">erm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0248">does it say?</u>
<u n="203" who="S0247">they're <trunc>n</trunc> they're not <trunc>th</trunc> they they are different</u>
<u n="204" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="205" who="S0247">but they are there are a lot of similarities</u>
<u n="206" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="207" who="S0247">and often he'll tell me a word he'll say this is erm <trunc>u</trunc> the word for this is so and so and then he'll say oh <trunc>s</trunc> hang on a minute no that's the Catalan word the Spanish word is <pause dur="short"/> and it and it'll be something similar yeah</u>
<u n="208" who="S0248" trans="overlap">but the Basque language was really totally different</u>
<u n="209" who="S0247" trans="overlap">Basque is completely different</u>
<u n="210" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="211" who="S0247">yeah they</u>
<u n="212" who="S0248">I mean</u>
<u n="213" who="S0247">well we <trunc>kn</trunc> we we</u>
<u n="214" who="S0248" trans="overlap">you know just look totally different a load of what was it? a load of Ks?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0247">Ks and Xs and yeah</u>
<u n="216" who="S0248" trans="overlap">a load of Ks load of Xs yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0248">and and er the place we stayed in started</u>
<u n="219" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="220" who="S0248">started <trunc>w</trunc> and ended with Z</u>
<u n="221" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="222" who="S0248">you know you just</u>
<u n="223" who="S0247">which was place was that with a Z?</u>
<u n="224" who="S0248" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> we stayed in</u>
<u n="225" who="S0247">it didn't start with a Z did oh <trunc>d</trunc> oh it did didn't it?</u>
<u n="226" who="S0248">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0247">yeah yes</u>
<u n="228" who="S0248">started and ended</u>
<u n="229" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0248">with a Z</u>
<u n="231" who="S0247">yeah <pause dur="short"/> well <pause dur="short"/> no that was a weird place wasn't it?</u>
<u n="232" who="S0248" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="233" who="S0247">they they <trunc>th</trunc><trunc>th</trunc>they told us that the language was unrelated to anything else wasn't it?</u>
<u n="234" who="S0248" trans="overlap">think they say it was the <trunc>condi</trunc> they found some roots in what was it Polish or?</u>
<u n="235" who="S0247">some somewhere</u>
<u n="236" who="S0248">but <trunc>u</trunc> it's <trunc>som</trunc>somewhere completely different</u>
<u n="237" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="238" who="S0248">not</u>
<u n="239" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0248">not not Mediterranean at all</u>
<u n="241" who="S0247">no that would be worth having a look for actually</u>
<u n="242" who="S0248" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="243" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="244" who="S0248"><trunc>tud</trunc></u>
<u n="245" who="S0247">but no but I suppose we just have to keep on don't we really just? I mean look we <trunc>d</trunc> I don't look at my notes I don't practice enough you know I we said we were <trunc>I</trunc> well I said we were gonna have a song a week</u>
<u n="246" who="S0248">a song a week?</u>
<u n="247" who="S0247">every week we'd have a a Spanish song and we'd have the lyrics and we'd practice and we didn't even do it once did we? and I type things into a I've got a program called Anki which is for erm vocabulary <pause dur="short"/> and for <trunc>s</trunc> enthusiastically I typed you know for several week but I didn't I stopped doing that <pause dur="short"/> I think it's quite difficult to to persevere really and we can't we haven't even got the excuse that we haven't got time</u>
<u n="248" who="S0248">I have no excuses at all</u>
<u n="249" who="S0247" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0248">once every <trunc>f</trunc> er once every month or so and really quite much more regularly than that lately I've been thinking well I I need some sort of project <pause dur="short"/> and I can't really think you know I don't really like making corn dollies so I I er I thought I'll learn Spanish</u>
<u n="251" who="S0247">well and now you're thinking that corn dollies might be quite a <trunc>ni</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="252" who="S0248" trans="overlap">I'm thinking of going into corn dolly work now actually <pause dur="short"/> I think it better I've just gotta go and go and get myself some corn</u>
<u n="253" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="254" who="S0248">got a big batch arriving tomorrow</u>
<u n="255" who="S0247"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> you could erm make some model aeroplanes</u>
<u n="256" who="S0248">why am I er why <trunc>c</trunc> model <trunc>e</trunc> let me make some dollies <pause dur="short"/> anyway no I've been telling myself come on learn Spanish <pause dur="short"/> but I can't get down to it</u>
<u n="257" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="258" who="S0248">and I'm not a particularly you know I like reading <pause dur="short"/> er you know I <trunc>c</trunc> I don't want to just but I I find it very hard to <trunc>g</trunc></u>
<u n="259" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0248">actually think when I I I just bothers me somewhat about <pause dur="short"/> I'm just gonna forget this or I'm not really gonna use it</u>
<u n="261" who="S0247" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="262" who="S0248">I know I know there's you know <trunc>th</trunc><trunc>th</trunc><trunc>th</trunc><trunc>th</trunc>the the prizes the benefit is of of is just learning <pause dur="short"/> and knowing you've achieved it if if if you can do it</u>
<u n="263" who="S0247" trans="overlap">oh absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="264" who="S0248">I know that <trunc>i</trunc>it's the the the sense of accomplishment is is the <trunc>m</trunc> is the major thing <pause dur="short"/> but I can't imagine myself getting to that point I think <pause dur="short"/> it's almost you know we <trunc>d</trunc> all know that we'd love to play a musical instrument <pause dur="short"/> we will know how beneficial it would be <pause dur="short"/> but really we know how difficult it is <trunc>espec</trunc> you know for us anyway</u>
<u n="265" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="266" who="S0248">and we're not like this in everything we're quite good I'm quite good at <trunc>s</trunc> crosswords and things like this which you you which I improve at <pause dur="short"/> but when I've tried to learn a musical instrument I I <trunc>b</trunc> I <trunc>d</trunc> don't feel any improvement how ever hard I try</u>
<u n="267" who="S0247">mm</u>
<u n="268" who="S0248">every time I pick up the guitar or what have you it's like the first time I ever picked it up</u>
<u n="269" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0248">you know I've seen some people try and learn gold and and and they're just utterly useless</u>
<u n="271" who="S0247"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0248">and they play for a time and they might miss it less less often than they used to <pause dur="short"/> but this you know they don't really ever really</u>
<u n="273" who="S0247">mm mm</u>
<u n="274" who="S0248">go anywhere <pause dur="short"/> it's the older people young <trunc>one</trunc></u>
<u n="275" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="276" who="S0248">young ones</u>
<u n="277" who="S0247">mm mm</u>
<u n="278" who="S0248">always</u>
<u n="279" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0248">pick it up to a degree</u>
<u n="281" who="S0247">mm mm<pause dur="short"/> but I <trunc>st</trunc> I still think it's worth persevering with the Spanish maybe in September we ought to join another night class</u>
<u n="282" who="S0248">ah dear just you you gonna you had a <unclear>site</unclear> <pause dur="short"/> I don't what what <trunc>the</trunc> how it worked if it you know whether I said something and it said it back to me or <trunc>ha</trunc> you said it was quite a good site is this the one you've already been talking about?</u>
<u n="283" who="S0247">no that's a program Anki <pause dur="short"/> the site is</u>
<u n="284" who="S0248" trans="overlap">is that the one that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was on about?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0247">no that's something else <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="286" who="S0248">the the who a friend of his used to work on it or something</u>
<u n="287" who="S0247" trans="overlap">yes that's that's called Readlang which</u>
<u n="288" who="S0248">yeah</u>
<u n="289" who="S0247">is a it's well actually it's quite good because <trunc>i</trunc><trunc>i</trunc>if you install it it enables you to click on any Spanish and up pops the translation</u>
<u n="290" who="S0248">oh well yeah there's</u>
<u n="291" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0248">quite a few of those I think some are better than others obviously</u>
<u n="293" who="S0247" trans="overlap">and the <pause dur="short"/> and then the er software remembers the words you've clicked on <pause dur="short"/> so later on it'll say do you remember you know <foreign lang="spa">camisa negra</foreign>?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0248" trans="overlap">okay yeah yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0247">and so it it helps by recycling them so it's that is probably quite</u>
<u n="296" who="S0248">mm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0247">worth having a look at <pause dur="short"/> but the one I was going to show you was just the BBC's erm Spanish learning site have you seen that?</u>
<u n="298" who="S0248" trans="overlap">mm mm <pause dur="short"/> no I don't think I have</u>
<u n="299" who="S0247">okay well we'll have a look at that this afternoon if you like</u>
<u n="300" who="S0248">okay</u>
<u n="301" who="S0247">yeah</u>
<u n="302" who="S0248">okay</u>
<u n="303" who="S0247">okay <pause dur="short"/> alright then will that do us for now do you think?</u>
<u n="304" who="S0248">yes <pause dur="short"/> yes we done</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
