<text id="SRFV">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:09:13</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-10-20</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0253 S0274</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>coffee shop, Liverpool</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Museums, Parking, Work, Shopping, Weddings, Moving house, Christmas and presents, Interview for a Masters, Money, Future Plans, Pets</topics>
		<activity>Two friends in a coffee shop</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0253">
				<exactage>26</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birkenhead</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Merseyside</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>26</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>English Language teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0274">
				<exactage>26</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Liverpool</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Liverpudlian</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Birkenhead</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>liverpool</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>social worker</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0274">he used he used to take me in there as well</u>
<u n="2" who="S0253">what café was it?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0274">I can't remember what it was called but again <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I had the <unclear>footie stickers</unclear> erm that's when I burnt my arm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0253">you burnt your arm?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0274" trans="overlap">I scalded my hand yeah</u>
<u n="6" who="S0253">how?</u>
<u n="7" who="S0274">er cappuccino went all over it</u>
<u n="8" who="S0253">were you drinking a cappuccino?</u>
<u n="9" who="S0274">yeah I was</u>
<u n="10" who="S0253">I was gonna say how cultured is that mate?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="12" who="S0253">get get my son a cappuccino</u>
<u n="13" who="S0274">babyccino please</u>
<u n="14" who="S0253">how old were you?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0274">I think I was about eight seven or eight yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0274" trans="overlap">but luckily because they were so fast they were able to get me a</u>
<u n="18" who="S0253">mm</u>
<u n="19" who="S0274">to the <pause dur="short"/> er kitchen put my ice in cold ice cold water my arms like</u>
<u n="20" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0274">so yeah I was lucky so there was no scar yeah</u>
<u n="22" who="S0253">that's really good</u>
<u n="23" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="24" who="S0253">when erm when my uncle was a kid he erm someone had put a a tea towel on or they'd rested a pan of scouse on a tea towel like a boiling hot pan of scouse and erm my uncle like pulled the tea towel he was only little like a toddler and he pulled the pan of scouse over the top scald</u>
<u n="25" who="S0274" trans="overlap">scalded</u>
<u n="26" who="S0253" trans="overlap">scalding hot I mean he was <trunc>al</trunc> he was alright he wasn't scared for life with it</u>
<u n="27" who="S0274">really?</u>
<u n="28" who="S0253">yeah they got again they got if you get if you can get on burns really really quickly like</u>
<u n="29" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="30" who="S0253">you act instantly then it</u>
<u n="31" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0253">it's the <trunc>dam</trunc> it's the the nerves like all the skin gets damaged it's like</u>
<u n="33" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0253">the longer it's on there erm <pause dur="short"/> I once this is like Darwin awards I erm <pause dur="short"/> I once er burned my fingers like got really serious burns on my hands my <trunc>ha</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I came in from school and a microwave there was like there was a toffee sponge but it was like the you know it was just like a cold toffee sponge right?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="36" who="S0253">but you know I I put I put it on the <trunc>micro</trunc> in the microwave for like <pause dur="short"/> er <vocal desc="laugh"/> twenty minutes or something like that so like molten toffee on the top like bubbling toffee so I went to get it out and a blob of toffee fell on my hand right? what happens it encased these three fingers but the outside went hard and the inside was still molten hot so instantly I ran to the tap to try and get it off put cold water on it freezing cold water but all it did was harden the outside of it</u>
<u n="37" who="S0274" trans="overlap">jesus</u>
<u n="38" who="S0253">and the inside was still boiling hot <trunc>a</trunc> so the reason I was so badly burned was because it was just such a long it had been on my hand so long it was the most painful thing honestly so I had to pull boiling toffee off my hands</u>
<u n="39" who="S0274">how old were you?</u>
<u n="40" who="S0253">erm I was old enough to know better</u>
<u n="41" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="42" who="S0253"><trunc>ol</trunc> old enough to use a microwave erm about fourteen</u>
<u n="43" who="S0274">jesus</u>
<u n="44" who="S0253">and er yeah it it really I was that was like for about a week I had to like I couldn't sleep at night cos the pain was that bad in those fingers so I had to I just had to sit with like I used to sleep with my hand in a cup of water</u>
<u n="45" who="S0274">it was that bad?</u>
<u n="46" who="S0253">I honestly couldn't bear it it was awful there's nothing you can do really once it's burned they just have to</u>
<u n="47" who="S0274" trans="overlap">all that from hot toffee</u>
<u n="48" who="S0253">hot toffee all that for a toffee sponge or something</u>
<u n="49" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="50" who="S0253">yeah but</u>
<u n="51" who="S0274" trans="overlap">I bet I bet that never gets suggested in the bedroom</u>
<u n="52" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="53" who="S0274">you know how I feel about hot toffee</u>
<u n="54" who="S0253">yeah I don't think I <trunc>wou</trunc> I don't think it would come up anyway but now now especially not with my my <vocal desc="laugh"/> complex about about about getting burned</u>
<u n="55" who="S0274">I mean I'll show you that book I meant that he's it's quite sad really he wrote fourteen books Vince Flynn the American guy but it</u>
<u n="56" who="S0253" trans="overlap">didn't I'm trying find</u>
<u n="57" who="S0274" trans="overlap">he died he died of erm I can't remember was it erm bowel cancer I think</u>
<u n="58" who="S0253" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="59" who="S0274" trans="overlap">I think but he yeah <unclear/> but really well written</u>
<u n="60" who="S0253">how old was he when he died?</u>
<u n="61" who="S0274">erm he looked like he I think I don't think there's a picture on that one there was in the first one</u>
<u n="62" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="63" who="S0274">er he looked to me like he was in his mid-forties</u>
<u n="64" who="S0253">I remember</u>
<u n="65" who="S0274" trans="overlap">or I think he's got some involvement in the government he did have cos in that book at the start he says erm out of respect for the secret service it says patterns and er plans at the White House had been changed</u>
<u n="66" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="67" who="S0274">so he I think he maybe has been</u>
<u n="68" who="S0253">you find a lot of people who have worked in the military</u>
<u n="69" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0253">make good writers don't they? cos they have that</u>
<u n="71" who="S0274" trans="overlap">well I is it John le Carré didn't he he was he was Oxford but he he worked for the British intelligence</u>
<u n="72" who="S0253" trans="overlap">probably yeah</u>
<u n="73" who="S0274" trans="overlap">is it him I think yeah he's yeah</u>
<u n="74" who="S0253">yeah erm you know and Tom Clancy was he ever in the navy or something? was he in?</u>
<u n="75" who="S0274">yes but I think he was yeah Navy SEALs I think yeah</u>
<u n="76" who="S0253">yeah <pause dur="short"/> obviously you've got like your Andy McNabs and people like that who</u>
<u n="77" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah he's been writing books that I've I've not looked at any but I</u>
<u n="78" who="S0253">have you <trunc>nev</trunc> have you never read Bravo Two Zero?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0274">no <pause dur="short"/> is it good?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0253">I mean I it was from his books that when I was when I was kid and I was really into like military stuff you know</u>
<u n="81" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="82" who="S0253">my dad like when I when I was when I was a bit older my dad gave it to me</u>
<u n="83" who="S0274" trans="overlap">that was when your dad looked at you and was like that's my boy</u>
<u n="84" who="S0253">yeah yeah that was my lad before I became a</u>
<u n="85" who="S0274"><unclear>whinge</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="86" who="S0253" trans="overlap">a a wuss yeah before I became a literary wuss erm <pause dur="short"/> you know I think I read a lot of books to make my dad like you know proud</u>
<u n="87" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="88" who="S0253">like not proud but like <pause dur="short"/> you know you wanna</u>
<u n="89" who="S0274" trans="overlap">associated with yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0253">like something to talk about isn't it really? <pause dur="short"/> as all all little boys do</u>
<u n="91" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0253" trans="overlap">but erm so he he used to give me these really like complex spy novels with like <vocal desc="laugh"/> sort of you know an erotic</u>
<u n="93" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0253">an erotic part in it halfway through like some fella comes</u>
<u n="95" who="S0274" trans="overlap">she <unclear/></u>
<u n="96" who="S0253">yeah like <vocal desc="laugh"/> some fella comes home on leave halfway through and you're like</u>
<u n="97" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="98" who="S0253">okay <pause dur="short"/> he gave me this one and it was about that big it was like a proper doorstop it was called Storming Intrepid and it was a really complicated story about erm how <trunc>sa</trunc> how satellites are used for spying across the world and just oh my god I remember trying to read it as a kid about twelve and I was just like</u>
<u n="99" who="S0274">it was what you didn't realise it was actually an instruction manual</u>
<u n="100" who="S0253">yeah what was the one I was reading? but erm</u>
<u n="101" who="S0274">we were talking about actually erm I dunno if noticed I Am Pilgrim that came out came out a few <trunc>mon</trunc> I read that I've just <trunc>fini</trunc></u>
<u n="102" who="S0253" trans="overlap">which one?</u>
<u n="103" who="S0274">I Am Pilgrim</u>
<u n="104" who="S0253">no</u>
<u n="105" who="S0274">Terry Hayes I've just finished reading it and that was a spy one but it's a murder mystery as well as a er <pause dur="short"/> like counterterrorism</u>
<u n="106" who="S0253">right</u>
<u n="107" who="S0274" trans="overlap">well and the interlink sort of erm what do you call it? erm <pause dur="short"/> coincidentally</u>
<u n="108" who="S0253">wow</u>
<u n="109" who="S0274">erm <pause dur="short"/> but it at first I was like <pause dur="short"/> where's this going? and after some chapters I thought why has he put so much detail into this one main part?</u>
<u n="110" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0274">but then it kind of worked and then at the end when I've read his like but later on he said erm I understand that this is quite a weighty novel and people may seem to think that this is not really appropriate but he said if you're into your what is it? if you're into your hard booze and your quick liquor and stuff then it's maybe not for you but if you don't mind having a bit of a journey then this and I thought</u>
<u n="112" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0274" trans="overlap">do you know what? to be fair <pause dur="short"/> cos it's like you follow erm <pause dur="short"/> it starts in this scene in this erm erm East Siding apartments</u>
<u n="114" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="115" who="S0274">just after nine eleven literally I think like a week after or something and there's a woman erm in a bathtub and she's been mutilated like you can't recognise her because her face has been stripped so</u>
<u n="116" who="S0253">right</u>
<u n="117" who="S0274"><unclear/> and all like her fingertips have gone so there's no way of <trunc>identi</trunc> er fying her</u>
<u n="118" who="S0253"><trunc>Brea</trunc> Breaking Bad style</u>
<u n="119" who="S0274">basically and</u>
<u n="120" who="S0253"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="121" who="S0274">you've got his guy who's like you've got this LA cop but then you've got this New York cops and everything and you've got this guy who's kind of no one's mentioned his name but he's the one they're <unclear/></u>
<u n="122" who="S0253">right</u>
<u n="123" who="S0274">and then it turns out he's a former like <pause dur="short"/> cIA sort of like top government sort of</u>
<u n="124" who="S0253" trans="overlap">is it a <trunc>consp</trunc> is it involve conspiracy and all that stuff?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0274">no no no no erm and then basically he gets called back into the service because he's a guy who they call the Saracen</u>
<u n="126" who="S0253">the <trunc>s</trunc> the Saracen?</u>
<u n="127" who="S0274">yeah he was mujahideen fighter erm in Afghanistan</u>
<u n="128" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="129" who="S0274">who's managed to erm make smallpox make a strand of it that erm can't be vaccinated against</u>
<u n="130" who="S0253">lovely</u>
<u n="131" who="S0274">and so it's er yeah it does sound a bit erm but it's really good</u>
<u n="132" who="S0253">I'm not sure this is a book I'd like to pick up right now</u>
<u n="133" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0253">my anxieties about <pause dur="short"/> oh er these things are pretty <vocal desc="laugh"/> pretty high at the moment</u>
<u n="135" who="S0274">and it what I think what's quite good is that he does kind of say it in the start which sets it for the rest of the book cos you think come on that's a bit unlikely that you'd find that but he does kind of make a point of it he talks about some of his former cases and he says well that time was pure luck but</u>
<u n="136" who="S0253">right</u>
<u n="137" who="S0274" trans="overlap">that I would have been able to crack any and you think oh right but at the end I don't know who Terry is I recognised their name but erm a lot of the people who contributed who he thanks were like screenwriters and stuff like that</u>
<u n="138" who="S0253" trans="overlap">wow</u>
<u n="139" who="S0274">so I dunno what his</u>
<u n="140" who="S0253" trans="overlap">maybe he's an actor or</u>
<u n="141" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="142" who="S0253" trans="overlap">a director or something like that</u>
<u n="143" who="S0274">maybe give a different name on it I don't know</u>
<u n="144" who="S0253">that's cool</u>
<u n="145" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0274">but it was it was there was like nine hundred pages</u>
<u n="148" who="S0253"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0274">I know</u>
<u n="150" who="S0253">did you read it?</u>
<u n="151" who="S0274">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="152" who="S0253">bloody hell</u>
<u n="153" who="S0274">but it's cos of the work I'm doing and I've got the time I thought whilst I've got the time</u>
<u n="154" who="S0253">I think <vocal desc="sigh"/> sometimes I think I'd like that if I could er I mean obviously you'd you'd I'd be bored out of my mind but I <trunc>re</trunc> like whenever whenever you just hit the train</u>
<u n="155" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0253" trans="overlap">like from mine I used to I used to get a bit annoyed at the staff cos half the time they wouldn't be at the window and when they were there like they'd be there on like Candy Crush Saga on their phones</u>
<u n="157" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0253">or they'd be reading but then I thought like well I'd be doing the same if <trunc>yo</trunc> if</u>
<u n="159" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0253" trans="overlap">cos the way their day was it's like people wouldn't show up every fifteen minutes</u>
<u n="161" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="162" who="S0253">so you've got that just gaps in your day where there's nothing to do and <trunc>tr</trunc> you know <anon type="place"/> station doesn't get that dirty</u>
<u n="163" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="164" who="S0253">so there's nothing to do so they just sit and read all day but they must they must get through like</u>
<u n="165" who="S0274">yeah well obviously like <pause dur="short"/> I'm on to my <pause dur="short"/> I'm on to like my fifth to sixth book now so it's like mid-September erm</u>
<u n="166" who="S0253" trans="overlap">bloody hell <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="167" who="S0274">erm</u>
<u n="168" who="S0253">you wouldn't</u>
<u n="169" who="S0274" trans="overlap">I've noticed my speed's been going up the rate at which I read</u>
<u n="170" who="S0253" trans="overlap">you get you become a better reader I think</u>
<u n="171" who="S0274">yeah and I've noticed already in terms of like erm even over in the space of a month I mean I know I I think I forget that like I notice a difference I've studied for the MA for two years I've just come on to reading reading journals er article books that</u>
<u n="172" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="173" who="S0274">are associated with the social workers I was out of work when I were doing that and I know it's my vocabulary just like sort of <pause dur="short"/> I dunno not so much</u>
<u n="174" who="S0253">it was really good <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0274">but really structured</u>
<u n="176" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0274">er not so much now if we were talking but you know when I was writing and I'd look back and sort of go jesus did I write that?</u>
<u n="178" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0274">erm but even like a month reading like a lot has meant the words that I wouldn't normally use I would go like and also I'm having a better er guess at the meanings of words</u>
<u n="180" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0274">even though I've I've never really properly read it and then cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> asked me she was said to me why what's stoic? and in that Vince Flynn he uses that book that word a lot and from knowing it obviously my brain's sort of <unclear>formated</unclear> it and gone</u>
<u n="182" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="183" who="S0274">well what's I I said oh it was someone who doesn't really show their emotions</u>
<u n="184" who="S0253">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0274" trans="overlap">and blah blah blah and then she guessed yeah yeah I suppose and then she looked at and <trunc>sh</trunc> yeah it does kind of <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/> so it was</u>
<u n="186" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0274" trans="overlap">that was quite nice cos and I think being able to stick the tendencies that we all have I think what's nice with a book is you start something and you finish it and you complete it see what I mean? and it's almost like a mini sort of</u>
<u n="188" who="S0253">I I think I have the opposite problem I'm incapable of finishing anything</u>
<u n="189" who="S0274">right</u>
<u n="190" who="S0253">like a really struggle to finish books I start them I love I <trunc>l</trunc> what I like is starting things I would I'm although I'm I'm not sure what this says about me on a psychological level but</u>
<u n="191" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="192" who="S0253">I'm very good at starting things and I start with a lot of momentum <pause dur="short"/> and then I burn myself out so</u>
<u n="193" who="S0274">mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0253">I give it er at the start of a book I will get really into it and get obsessed with it and then when I get I don't like to finish things cos I like to I hate the idea that I'm enjoying something so much and it's</u>
<u n="195" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="196" who="S0253" trans="overlap">gonna be finished</u>
<u n="197" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0253">you know some books where you're sad when you've finished them?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="200" who="S0253">and often I find that if I've really enjoyed a book I'll read it I could read ninety percent of it in the space of a a week or something like that</u>
<u n="201" who="S0274" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0253">and then it'll take me another three weeks to finish fifteen pages because I just</u>
<u n="203" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="204" who="S0253">won't pick it up cos I don't <pause dur="short"/> I don't want I know it's really strange unless unless some some books you have to finish</u>
<u n="205" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="206" who="S0253" trans="overlap">some books you have to know like</u>
<u n="207" who="S0274">well obviously with these <trunc>b</trunc> <unclear>ones</unclear> you've got to to cos you're kind of like well</u>
<u n="208" who="S0253" trans="overlap">the</u>
<u n="209" who="S0274" trans="overlap">what's gonna yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0253">but er a lot of the books I read there's no real <pause dur="short"/> there's no real resolution at the end of it often some of them are but some of them end quite <pause dur="short"/> I don't know sort of there's always like a kind of point at the end but it's not quite</u>
<u n="211" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="212" who="S0253">it's not quite what you want so I guess that's why like I've kind of I've got in the habit and I think since university as well because really oddly when <trunc>y</trunc> when you study when you study literature you don't have to look at the whole book the the point of it is not the whole novel as a as a whole</u>
<u n="213" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="214" who="S0253" trans="overlap">it's it's</u>
<u n="215" who="S0274" trans="overlap">you take out a chapters at <unclear>all</unclear></u>
<u n="216" who="S0253" trans="overlap">you <trunc>jus</trunc> well half of the time you take it out of bloody context <vocal desc="laugh"/> and like you're trying to read it you're trying to read sections of it obviously you might read the whole book you you often you're just reading you're taking a section of a book <pause dur="short"/> and then trying to make a you know make assumptions based on that section of the book <pause dur="short"/> without really relating it to the rest of the novel</u>
<u n="217" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="218" who="S0253">some so obviously some some some literary study is about the whole novel but very often it's <pause dur="short"/> you you're taking a sentence and you you know you're you're focusing on what that sentence means in its own context and stuff so I think that's why like I'm not a good reader because I'm too</u>
<u n="219" who="S0274" trans="overlap">you're almost a bit like a journalist in a sense I suppose then like an editor isn't it? just go and er</u>
<u n="220" who="S0253" trans="overlap">that's what I tell people <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> yeah</u>
<u n="221" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="222" who="S0253">when they ask me what I do</u>
<u n="223" who="S0274">but it's that's really the same skills isn't it? like</u>
<u n="224" who="S0253">it's</u>
<u n="225" who="S0274" trans="overlap">that's why I've always found it funny when they had like journalism degrees you'd be like but I'm sure the best journalists are not going to uni to do journalism they've been er worked in politics or they've worked in an area</u>
<u n="226" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="227" who="S0274" trans="overlap">linked to something or other</u>
<u n="228" who="S0253" trans="overlap">the the the big I mean that that's the funny thing about about about journalism as a career I don't I don't I don't claim to know much about it but <pause dur="short"/> I think what you should like the people who are hired by like big newspapers and get I mean get given a chance to write have life experiences because they've it's cos they've lived like in</u>
<u n="229" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0253" trans="overlap">war zones or they've</u>
<u n="231" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0253">or they've travelled or they've studied people out of their own interest or they're they're environmentalists and but</u>
<u n="233" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="234" who="S0253">they haven't <trunc>ev</trunc> they've never studied journalism in their life they just it there's there's something</u>
<u n="235" who="S0274" trans="overlap">so they've got natural passion and flair and knowledge to be able to write like you say like a decent article that's obviously</u>
<u n="236" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0274" trans="overlap">will be get or like or like something you'd do you'd be like proofread it from someone and</u>
<u n="238" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="239" who="S0274" trans="overlap">faults you know to make it more sort of concise but yeah</u>
<u n="240" who="S0253">it's like I mean it I mean obviously like I think a lot of people really love him I I've read a few of his books like you know Hunter S Thompson who wrote like Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas and things like that?</u>
<u n="241" who="S0274">see I watched that film with you guys but</u>
<u n="242" who="S0253">no don't</u>
<u n="243" who="S0274" trans="overlap">I</u>
<u n="244" who="S0253" trans="overlap">don't don't don't base Hunter S Thompson on</u>
<u n="245" who="S0274" trans="overlap">I just I <trunc>d</trunc></u>
<u n="246" who="S0253" trans="overlap">the Johnny Depp movie</u>
<u n="247" who="S0274">I I think because <pause dur="short"/> I've never been in the drugs scene or</u>
<u n="248" who="S0253" trans="overlap">into drugs</u>
<u n="249" who="S0274" trans="overlap">or anything like to me it's it's very erm <pause dur="short"/> I've not actually just just I read the book before but <pause dur="short"/> erm</u>
<u n="250" who="S0253">it's unrelatable</u>
<u n="251" who="S0274">yeah that's it</u>
<u n="252" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="253" who="S0274">if anything it I'm quite like</u>
<u n="254" who="S0253">I just don't particularly like that film</u>
<u n="255" who="S0274">uhu</u>
<u n="256" who="S0253">it's and it's it's not and I think I think cos I when I when we lived with like them lot I I kind of got put off it because of you know like they'd watch it like ten times a week and be like ha ha drugs but</u>
<u n="257" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah I think</u>
<u n="258" who="S0253">the the point is is that he he was a bit of a you know he he did he did take some strange some strange drugs Hunter S Thompson and <pause dur="short"/> but he's also a very good he was also a very you know a very important writer at the</u>
<u n="259" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="260" who="S0253" trans="overlap">time and things like that and</u>
<u n="261" who="S0274">cos you never think of that as a well in terms of <trunc>tr</trunc> it's cos you maybe think of it is <pause dur="short"/> I know he's done a lot of shit films in the past couple of years erm</u>
<u n="262" who="S0253">Ben Stiller?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Johnny Depp</u>
<u n="264" who="S0253">Johnny Depp?</u>
<u n="265" who="S0274">yeah erm but you know he cos you cos you were talking about Fear and Loathing in Las Las Vegas</u>
<u n="266" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0274">erm it but <trunc>c</trunc> The Rum Diary?</u>
<u n="268" who="S0253">mm</u>
<u n="269" who="S0274">and I know I've got a bit of a thing but do you know when I watched that nothing really happens but I loved it</u>
<u n="270" who="S0253">but that that's Hunter S Thompson as well</u>
<u n="271" who="S0274">is it?</u>
<u n="272" who="S0253">no it's not the Rum <trunc>Diar</trunc> who's The Rum Diaries by? <pause dur="long"/> yeah it is erm I might have to google it on my phone</u>
<u n="273" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah cos erm I dunno I <trunc>wa</trunc> I think I watched about two thirds of it and I thought I love this cos it was just</u>
<u n="274" who="S0253" trans="overlap">Rum Diary</u>
<u n="275" who="S0274">it it made me think of cos obviously I love rum you know</u>
<u n="276" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>obvio</trunc> obviously I love rum</u>
<u n="277" who="S0274">but I dunno it kind of made me thinking thing that could so easily be you</u>
<u n="278" who="S0253">me?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0274">as in sorry myself</u>
<u n="280" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0274">no that could be so you could so easily become a <pause dur="short"/> cos I like drinking everything like</u>
<u n="282" who="S0253">pretty <trunc>su</trunc></u>
<u n="283" who="S0274" trans="overlap">cos</u>
<u n="284" who="S0253" trans="overlap">pretty <trunc>su</trunc></u>
<u n="285" who="S0274" trans="overlap">it's</u>
<u n="286" who="S0253" trans="overlap">pretty <trunc>su</trunc></u>
<u n="287" who="S0274" trans="overlap">a pattern isn't it?</u>
<u n="288" who="S0253">it's it's either Hunter S Thompson or someone equally <pause dur="short"/> messed up <pause dur="short"/> pretty sure yeah pretty sure it's Hunter S Thompson</u>
<u n="289" who="S0274">yeah I know I wasn't on Google</u>
<u n="290" who="S0253">I'm just gonna google The Rum Diaries <pause dur="short"/> is <pause dur="short"/> he also wrote er one called The <unclear>Royal</unclear> Tax you might like that give that a go</u>
<u n="291" who="S0274">yeah? The <unclear>Raw</unclear> Shark Tax?</u>
<u n="292" who="S0253">the <unclear>Royal</unclear> Shark Tax or something <pause dur="short"/> give that one a go I know what you mean though about about it like that that kind of <pause dur="short"/> I guess people kind of go like I think I think a lot of <pause dur="short"/> let's see <pause dur="short"/> erm The Rum Diary Hunter S Thompson yeah there's a novel in <pause dur="short"/> and you were was I've never seen The Rum Diary is it good?</u>
<u n="293" who="S0274">what's he called his name again?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0253">Hunter S Thompson</u>
<u n="295" who="S0274">Hunter S Thompson <pause dur="short"/> do you know what's really nice though? that when I feel like I've found something you can't beat</u>
<u n="296" who="S0253">in reading?</u>
<u n="297" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="298" who="S0253">it's one of life's great pleasures</u>
<u n="299" who="S0274">it is</u>
<u n="300" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I'm I'm told <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="301" who="S0274">it's</u>
<u n="302" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I've <vocal desc="laugh"/> never finished anything myself</u>
<u n="303" who="S0274">cos I mean I dunno it's like cos my dad was a big reader and he but he loved he would read Charles Dickens novels constantly</u>
<u n="304" who="S0253">really?</u>
<u n="305" who="S0274">yeah probably <unclear/></u>
<u n="306" who="S0253" trans="overlap">it's it's</u>
<u n="307" who="S0274" trans="overlap">do you know what I mean? you know</u>
<u n="308" who="S0253">they say they say say he's the best Charles Dickens don't they?</u>
<u n="309" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0253">apparently it's just the best</u>
<u n="311" who="S0274">he <trunc>u</trunc> he used to and his cos his favourite Bond film was erm <pause dur="short"/> well his favourite film was <vocal desc="sigh"/> Scrooge with the black and white one</u>
<u n="312" who="S0253">not quite</u>
<u n="313" who="S0274" trans="overlap">that's</u>
<u n="314" who="S0253">not Scrooged with Bill Murray?</u>
<u n="315" who="S0274">no</u>
<u n="316" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="317" who="S0274">not that one er</u>
<u n="318" who="S0253">yeah I know the</u>
<u n="319" who="S0274" trans="overlap">so I suppose for me now that he's <pause dur="short"/> he's gone</u>
<u n="320" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="321" who="S0274">but he's not I suppose reading in a sense is kind of it's a it's a connection in a way I find cos he well he loved reading</u>
<u n="322" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="323" who="S0274">erm I dunno if it's quite er cos we're only human and we like getting compliments don't we? but there's a new girl started in work</u>
<u n="324" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="325" who="S0274">and she's from like quite she went to yeah I know went to went to private school you know <anon type="place"/> academy</u>
<u n="326" who="S0253">it's a good school that</u>
<u n="327" who="S0274">she's like very well spoken and you know she's a <trunc>lo</trunc> lovely person you know</u>
<u n="328" who="S0253" trans="overlap">how old is she?</u>
<u n="329" who="S0274">erm she's <trunc>th</trunc> she's twenty-four</u>
<u n="330" who="S0253">what's her name?</u>
<u n="331" who="S0274"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="short"/> she's she lives in she lives by the erm</u>
<u n="332" who="S0253"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0274">yeah very much I'd say I'm sure somewhere in your circle would have known them like you know</u>
<u n="334" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="335" who="S0274" trans="overlap">her father and she's been working with me for about the past month and in initially it's like like the job the joke we had isn't it when we were in uni is that people see me oh right yeah he lives in <anon type="place"/> area that's all there is</u>
<u n="336" who="S0253" trans="overlap">he's a divvy</u>
<u n="337" who="S0274">he yes he is and the other night we were sat there cos she as on a on a <unclear/> and er <pause dur="short"/> she just sort of said to me cos she was asking me and like we were talking about things and I was like oh yeah <trunc>m</trunc> and I was talking about yourself and I said oh yeah I'm finally gonna meet the major for tomorrow it's he did erm literature and then he wants to get into publishing and all this and I was talking about like and where we used to go and you know <unclear/> bloody hell you it's quite surprising you're like pretty cultured aren't you?</u>
<u n="338" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="339" who="S0274">and I was like never thought of myself as that and I went well I like I thanks yeah I was just</u>
<u n="340" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0274">that was quite nice of her to say that</u>
<u n="342" who="S0253">I think I have the opposite problem I think people always assume I'm really cultured and I'm really not I'm like I'm really like</u>
<u n="343" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="344" who="S0253">uncultured</u>
<u n="345" who="S0274"><unclear/></u>
<u n="346" who="S0253">I'm not at all like I think</u>
<u n="347" who="S0274">if you think about the debates we used to have at you were the only person and I used to love it when we were living in uni and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was obviously doing politics and you was doing like they were so intertwined and we'd talk about things</u>
<u n="348" who="S0253">oh yes</u>
<u n="349" who="S0274">we'd talk about things for ages do you know what mean? so it's</u>
<u n="350" who="S0253">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0274">erm do you know what I mean? so I used to love that</u>
<u n="352" who="S0253">I dunno I think I I I think I think studying stuff like maybe a bit more cultured I guess but I mean I guess I guess it's a relative term you know it's not like you can can be cultured or not cultured but</u>
<u n="353" who="S0274" trans="overlap">I think</u>
<u n="354" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I think I think people often presume that I'm like I'm I think one I think it's like that I think people presume that I'm really really really into like fiction I'm not I like I like reading but I don't really like</u>
<u n="355" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0253" trans="overlap">reading like whole novels that</u>
<u n="357" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="358" who="S0253">erm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0274">well I know now that it's like reading patches <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="360" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> like reading what?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0274">patches of it yeah</u>
<u n="362" who="S0253" trans="overlap">patches of novels</u>
<u n="363" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="364" who="S0253" trans="overlap">bits of novels I like er I I sort of like the ideas of the ideas of things more so if I can <pause dur="short"/> ah I dunno I I've I've <trunc>star</trunc> I've started reading like I know it sounds really stupid but reading like journals and non-fiction more than <pause dur="short"/> fiction that's</u>
<u n="365" who="S0274" trans="overlap">see that's funny cos obviously I've come off that path all of I've done that for two years</u>
<u n="366" who="S0253" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you're sick of it</u>
<u n="367" who="S0274">and sick of it yeah so now I wanna you know</u>
<u n="368" who="S0253">absolutely sick of it</u>
<u n="369" who="S0274"><trunc>ag</trunc> agent doodle pants do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="370" who="S0253">mm</u>
<u n="371" who="S0274" trans="overlap">and sort of jumping of a plane with a machine gun or a <unclear/></u>
<u n="372" who="S0253" trans="overlap">it's like children's novels <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="373" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="374" who="S0253">the spy who can redraw his redraw his <unclear/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0274" trans="overlap">Dougal plane yeah I've just thought of a character yeah Dougal</u>
<u n="376" who="S0253">just just write a kids' book agent</u>
<u n="377" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="378" who="S0253">agent doodle pants</u>
<u n="379" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="380" who="S0253">think of a and he like he and he has</u>
<u n="381" who="S0274"><unclear/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0253">penny crayon but he like draws his own surroundings</u>
<u n="383" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="384" who="S0253">draw his way out of the thing</u>
<u n="385" who="S0274">I mean yeah</u>
<u n="386" who="S0253">stop recording</u>
<u n="387" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="388" who="S0253">shit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="389" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="390" who="S0253">our million dollar idea</u>
<u n="391" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0253">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0274">no it's erm no yeah so it's <pause dur="short"/> but then like you're saying there but it's funny isn't it because <pause dur="short"/> when someone says cultured and they think like for example this person <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> she's like a lovely person but it's all very much kind of like she she wouldn't look out a place in <anon type="place"/> and I was joking with her like you know what I mean? but to me that's not cultured that's like to me that's kind of playing the scene you know it's it's</u>
<u n="394" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="395" who="S0274">playing a part whereas to me it's culture is about having social awareness</u>
<u n="396" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="397" who="S0274">of knowing yourself like I know that I go to the gym cos I like to exercise and keep healthy but also cos I'm body conscious and also because</u>
<u n="398" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="399" who="S0274">it gives me confidence <pause dur="short"/> and then but it's I think it's being aware of you know we psychoanalyse everyone but an understanding of why the the way people are I suppose that's</u>
<u n="400" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="401" who="S0274">that's social work but if you do it properly you come away with you go you understand why people the motives rather than <trunc>peo</trunc> you know it's it's a fixed state of</u>
<u n="402" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="403" who="S0274" trans="overlap">like you now oh well they're gonna be set well why are they doing that?</u>
<u n="404" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0274" trans="overlap">what what influenced someone and what what you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="406" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="407" who="S0274">so then I think once you have an understanding that you better understand people</u>
<u n="408" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="409" who="S0274">and you know what I mean so it's er</u>
<u n="410" who="S0253">yeah I think so</u>
<u n="411" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0253">I think I think I <pause dur="short"/> I I I used to think there's like there's a problem between <pause dur="short"/> people think that culture is about class as in like</u>
<u n="413" who="S0274">and knowing when all the like</u>
<u n="414" who="S0253">like</u>
<u n="415" who="S0274">Diwali holidays are and stuff like</u>
<u n="416" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="417" who="S0274">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="418" who="S0253">no but you <trunc>sai</trunc> well you said like you know <pause dur="short"/> your dad was from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="419" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="420" who="S0253">and he was very well read and it's weird how like you'd think as those things as like somehow opposed</u>
<u n="421" who="S0274">classic isn't it?</u>
<u n="422" who="S0253" trans="overlap">like</u>
<u n="423" who="S0274" trans="overlap">big screen TV on a working class <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="424" who="S0253">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="425" who="S0274" trans="overlap">and isn't yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0253" trans="overlap"><trunc>ye</trunc> but you kind of you sort of people often think of like being like being well read and somehow somehow a preserve like being middle</u>
<u n="427" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0253" trans="overlap">class but it's not at all like</u>
<u n="429" who="S0274">no</u>
<u n="430" who="S0253">and <pause dur="short"/> I mean I used to I used to love when I worked in Waterstones what I really liked about it was generally it was like you could <trunc>j</trunc> you could tell a a lot of the customers that used to come in were like just guys like your dad like working class fellas who maybe later on in life had just found this love of reading</u>
<u n="431" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0253">and it was</u>
<u n="433" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="434" who="S0253" trans="overlap">brilliant because like they <trunc>c</trunc> you could just tell some people I <trunc>remem</trunc> I've seen <trunc>cu</trunc> I'd see customers come in one day pick up a book and then about three days later they'd be back</u>
<u n="435" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0253">and they'd be back and then</u>
<u n="437" who="S0274" trans="overlap">getting the next</u>
<u n="438" who="S0253" trans="overlap">they'd they'd be there every week</u>
<u n="439" who="S0274" trans="overlap">one of the author yeah</u>
<u n="440" who="S0253" trans="overlap">they would they were hooked and <pause dur="short"/> and then they well these guys who like erm <trunc>may</trunc>maybe you get maybe they were bored like on in life or</u>
<u n="441" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I don't know what it was but <pause dur="short"/> you know there was people who maybe had never really picked up a book before and and all of a sudden cos they maybe though oh it's you know it's not</u>
<u n="443" who="S0274">it's for those clever <trunc>fath</trunc> yeah</u>
<u n="444" who="S0253" trans="overlap">it yeah it's not for me</u>
<u n="445" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0253">and then you realise you can understand anything if you you you know if you sit and read something and you're interested in it you can you can get it and that was what was really nice about that job sometimes was like <pause dur="short"/> you know and if you wanted to read about biology tomorrow you could read about biology and no one can stop you</u>
<u n="447" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="448" who="S0253" trans="overlap">from having a read</u>
<u n="449" who="S0274">it <trunc>ye</trunc> do you know what it's a there's a film on that you've got Netflix haven't you <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="450" who="S0253">is it called is it called Good Will Hunting?</u>
<u n="451" who="S0274">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="452" who="S0253">me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> watched it the other night <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had never seen it</u>
<u n="453" who="S0274">has she not?</u>
<u n="454" who="S0253">it blew her mind</u>
<u n="455" who="S0274">is that what made Ben Affleck then? and it's</u>
<u n="456" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="457" who="S0274" trans="overlap">Matt Damon was it?</u>
<u n="458" who="S0253">they got an Oscar for that didn't they?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0274">yeah cos they wrote it didn't they?</u>
<u n="460" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="461" who="S0274">erm</u>
<u n="462" who="S0253">but isn't it rumoured that like there's that joke on Family Guy but isn't it rumoured that it was like</u>
<u n="463" who="S0274" trans="overlap">it was just one of them</u>
<u n="464" who="S0253" trans="overlap">one it was all Matt Damon</u>
<u n="465" who="S0274">oh right yeah</u>
<u n="466" who="S0253" trans="overlap">and Ben Affleck's just chilling</u>
<u n="467" who="S0274">yeah somehow I can see that but</u>
<u n="468" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="469" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah erm and then that would be judging erm</u>
<u n="470" who="S0253">cos his wicked smart</u>
<u n="471" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm the film Detachment with erm Brody what's his name? er is it Adrien Brody?</u>
<u n="472" who="S0253">Adam or Adrien there's two <pause dur="short"/> cos the</u>
<u n="473" who="S0274" trans="overlap">the one off The Pianist?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0253">Adrien Brody</u>
<u n="475" who="S0274">Adrien Brody</u>
<u n="476" who="S0253">Adam Brody is the guy from The OC</u>
<u n="477" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="478" who="S0253">and stuff like that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="479" who="S0274">oh it's er oh it does my head in erm <pause dur="short"/> it's it's again it's a film that doesn't really have <pause dur="short"/> any major end it's</u>
<u n="480" who="S0253">what's it called? the film</u>
<u n="481" who="S0274">Detachment</u>
<u n="482" who="S0253">Detachment</u>
<u n="483" who="S0274">it's about a <trunc>tea</trunc> he's a supply teacher in America a secondary school</u>
<u n="484" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="485" who="S0274">and basically as the film goes on he hates his life he's like <pause dur="short"/> having a midlife crisis but he's kind of he's very intelligent and very aware very well read and kind of like a guy who you talk to for hours can make other people feel happy and he shows kindness to other people but he can't find that happiness himself</u>
<u n="486" who="S0253">right</u>
<u n="487" who="S0274">erm and it's so and they're sort of showing the stresses of an inner city school that's you know obviously in quite a deprived area</u>
<u n="488" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0274">the teachers are getting <pause dur="short"/> told this that and the other and they put this they're very passionate and <pause dur="short"/> it's a brilliant film it's very quite sad</u>
<u n="490" who="S0253">sounds good that</u>
<u n="491" who="S0274">but it's it's on Netflix and I'd definitely watch it</u>
<u n="492" who="S0253">Detachment?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0274">there's me going <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> mate there's this film with teachers and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I love it because I think I mean you need that like I mean <pause dur="short"/> I know I'm a very deep person you know that from erm from the years</u>
<u n="494" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="495" who="S0274">but I think you do need sometimes someone who isn't quite well no not to say she's not deep</u>
<u n="496" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> a simpleton</u>
<u n="497" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="498" who="S0253">you need to find yourself a <trunc>simpl</trunc> no I know what you mean</u>
<u n="499" who="S0274" trans="overlap">but</u>
<u n="500" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I mean it's a</u>
<u n="501" who="S0274" trans="overlap">but I would I I would sit there for hours and you know you know talk about something so like <pause dur="short"/> important to me or what like</u>
<u n="502" who="S0253">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="503" who="S0274">current affair like kind of that time when I was saying to you I would have read a read a bit of postmodernism and stuff and you're like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> just and I was like the world's just <trunc>f</trunc> it's it's fucked up <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and it's like what and I remember one time you almost said to me what was it? erm <pause dur="short"/> we were talking in <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="place"/> and we were having a few drinks and I think someone in work had been doing my head in</u>
<u n="504" who="S0253">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="505" who="S0274">and you just said to me <unclear/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you can't expect to have that same respect off other people</u>
<u n="506" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="507" who="S0274" trans="overlap">and it's funny how a simple sentence like that can make you go yeah it's kind of like and again</u>
<u n="508" who="S0253">kind of like a skinny white Buddha</u>
<u n="509" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="510" who="S0253">essentially</u>
<u n="511" who="S0274">that's it yeah so er but that's what I love off <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> because you know she's <pause dur="short"/> things don't bother her in the same way it does me</u>
<u n="512" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0274" trans="overlap">and I think that goes well and <pause dur="short"/> I think what again it's it's something <pause dur="short"/> I think like with the master's erm cos you know for my erm whatchamacallit my dissertation I got a sixty-seven</u>
<u n="514" who="S0253">that's really good</u>
<u n="515" who="S0274">I was er three percent off a first and it was pure but do you know what though? you know the most best part? I did all that by myself I did those fifteen thousand words I'd never got my lecturer to look over it or anything or took and</u>
<u n="516" who="S0253">that's brilliant</u>
<u n="517" who="S0274">most of the people there they were pretty much writing an interesting</u>
<u n="518" who="S0253" trans="overlap">do do you do you feel like you do you feel like you think you really came on then from your degree</u>
<u n="519" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="520" who="S0253">to your master's?</u>
<u n="521" who="S0274">definitely my degree I was still dealing with my dad</u>
<u n="522" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="523" who="S0274">definitely I was dealing with the fact that <pause dur="short"/> you know my mum and relationship with my mum and everything you know</u>
<u n="524" who="S0253">housemates didn't make it easy for you did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="525" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="527" who="S0274">well no mate if I</u>
<u n="528" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I think I think you should I think if you hadn't lived with us you would have done much better</u>
<u n="529" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no it's erm I think it amazed me <pause dur="short"/> er more showing to the person I am</u>
<u n="530" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="531" who="S0274">but also it's er it's been a deliberate path to go and where I am now and then go and do social work and yeah I I'm probably the happiest I am now</u>
<u n="532" who="S0253">good</u>
<u n="533" who="S0274">it I was <trunc>hap</trunc> I think I was great then I was you know I would never <pause dur="short"/> wish those times away I love them times but</u>
<u n="534" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="535" who="S0274" trans="overlap">it's great in the context you know what I mean? whereas now I'm quite I quite like the fact that you know and yourself and you know everyone's gone off doing their own thing and</u>
<u n="536" who="S0253">you're settled</u>
<u n="537" who="S0274">that's it yeah and just it's it's it's like it's nice</u>
<u n="538" who="S0253" trans="overlap">you spend you spend like <pause dur="short"/> I always I feel like <pause dur="short"/> I dunno I think I'm still I'm I'm not quite there yet I'm still I'm I'm I'm alright I'm happy with what I'm happy but</u>
<u n="539" who="S0274">mm</u>
<u n="540" who="S0253">I feel like I'm still trying to like adjust everything and make everything you know like <pause dur="short"/> proper whereas I felt like like er I think my favourite time would probably be like maybe the couple of years after university</u>
<u n="541" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="542" who="S0253">cos uni was so hard for me cos I just you know</u>
<u n="543" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="544" who="S0253">lost my lost my marbles so</u>
<u n="545" who="S0274">I always have it envisaged I remember the er I think it was like twelve cans of Red Bull</u>
<u n="546" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="547" who="S0274">and you just wouldn't open the door</u>
<u n="548" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="549" who="S0274" trans="overlap">and you'd be like no me I'm it's great because I got to know you and be like yeah okay just he needs to be left sorry</u>
<u n="550" who="S0253" trans="overlap">well I'm still that way I'm still like</u>
<u n="551" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="552" who="S0253">I'm still obsessive but just in different ways now but like erm so for me like after uni it was like having no responsibility and not really worrying too much about you know a degree and once you <trunc>wh</trunc> not worrying too much about my future and that was the best time for me cos I just had no burdens whatsoever <pause dur="short"/> and I'm <trunc>st</trunc> the problem for me with teaching has been that like <pause dur="short"/> because like because I'm so like you know really try and perfect everything and make everything perfect</u>
<u n="553" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="554" who="S0253">so I think since I've been teaching I've I've found that like been really struggling because you can't perfect it</u>
<u n="555" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="556" who="S0253">nothing <trunc>ev</trunc> nothing's ever perfect especially in like language teaching <pause dur="short"/> it's like you never you you you <pause dur="short"/> you could be the best teacher in the world all the will I the world and you know you never you <trunc>nev</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> you're never gonna get anyone fluent immediately</u>
<u n="557" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="558" who="S0253" trans="overlap">if you know what I mean and I find that really hard to not perfect something instantly <pause dur="short"/> so like I feel like <pause dur="short"/> I dunno I I feel like I need to do something where <pause dur="short"/> I I just for a while I'm not saying I don't wanna go back to teaching but I wanna find that kind of like contentment and be like</u>
<u n="559" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="560" who="S0253" trans="overlap">you know I'm just doing my job and I'm going home and my job's my job and I can do it well and then I can go home and I'm not worrying too much</u>
<u n="561" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="562" who="S0253" trans="overlap">about it all the time and I guess that's work</u>
<u n="563" who="S0274">I'm sure that's what they call drive isn't it? that ultimately makes you a good teacher and</u>
<u n="564" who="S0253"><vocal desc="sigh"/> it's like I was I like <trunc>t</trunc> two of the <trunc>be</trunc> like you know it's weird isn't it? like two weeks before you know we finished teaching there were two of the best lessons I've ever had today just <pause dur="short"/> you know <trunc>j</trunc> it was you know it was difficult like new students in the class and stuff but it just everything went really well and tomorrow like <trunc>yo</trunc> you just like you just have an absolute breakdown halfway through the class not me personally but</u>
<u n="565" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="566" who="S0253">everyone just stopped doing stuff and <pause dur="short"/> it's weird how it goes but I think like <pause dur="short"/> a lot of my friends are like you at the moment they <pause dur="short"/> they're at that point where they're just you know they're getting they're engaged and they they're getting houses and stuff and they're not they're not frantically scrambling round trying to like you know do do do new stuff all the time and they're just kind of</u>
<u n="567" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="568" who="S0253" trans="overlap"><unclear/> a bit</u>
<u n="569" who="S0274">and I think there's a there's a point there where like like what was I watching the other day? erm that book I wanna get for erm ask my mum for Christmas it's a</u>
<u n="570" who="S0253" trans="overlap">which one?</u>
<u n="571" who="S0274">it's a <trunc>pho</trunc> photography book by Don McCullin I think it is? very famous war <trunc>corresp</trunc> like photographer erm</u>
<u n="572" who="S0253">I think I think I might have seen it</u>
<u n="573" who="S0274">it's on Netflix I watched it and the whole time I was just mesmerised the whole time</u>
<u n="574" who="S0253" trans="overlap">what what Don McCullin's on Netflix?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="576" who="S0253">as what like a lecturer or something or</u>
<u n="577" who="S0274">no he's he's a <trunc>photo</trunc> a well ran for the</u>
<u n="578" who="S0253" trans="overlap">is this a documentary?</u>
<u n="579" who="S0274">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="580" who="S0253">and it's on Netflix?</u>
<u n="581" who="S0274">yeah a a photographer and but he never likes to be <trunc>know</trunc> called he said I don't wanna be called a war photographer because that somehow suggests that I condone it he said that I see myself as humanitarian</u>
<u n="582" who="S0253">right</u>
<u n="583" who="S0274">this guy is just so I'm gonna use the word but just so cultured and just like it but the great thing is he's even from a really really rough part of London</u>
<u n="584" who="S0253">right</u>
<u n="585" who="S0274">backing like I think twenties or thirties like thirties maybe <vocal desc="laugh"/> he literally like he'll be talking away like very like you know sort of academical or something and it's like cos then you know the next time I was round the corner and</u>
<u n="586" who="S0253" trans="overlap">and how's your father?</u>
<u n="587" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="588" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="589" who="S0274">he's talking about like you know the place I grew up in <pause dur="short"/> where you had to fight where you had to get out of there and he said you know he's casually talking about the time he was taking a picture of like all the working men going</u>
<u n="590" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="591" who="S0274">into one factory and it's</u>
<u n="592" who="S0253" trans="overlap">having having a knees up</u>
<u n="593" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and this guy was like giving him grief so he he had to you know I had to sort him out do you know what I mean? then back to it but it's just brilliant cos it was kinda like cross <trunc>cul</trunc> you know what I mean? cultural mix</u>
<u n="594" who="S0253">there's something there's something so like like authentic about people like I dunno what it is but it's like it's like people like that I mean who's who <trunc>wr</trunc> have you ever heard of a book you'd like this book it's called The Glass Arena</u>
<u n="595" who="S0274">no</u>
<u n="596" who="S0253">I think it's called A Glass Arena <pause dur="short"/> john trying to think</u>
<u n="597" who="S0274" trans="overlap">the internet</u>
<u n="598" who="S0253">write it down</u>
<u n="599" who="S0274">do you know what? I'll go on to my Amazon</u>
<u n="600" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="601" who="S0274">it's offline and talk about being</u>
<u n="602" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="603" who="S0274">and I've got an Amazon app but it is useful for that</u>
<u n="604" who="S0253">you'll be the death of the high street <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="605" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="606" who="S0253">erm and it's it's I think it's John maybe John Healy or something erm</u>
<u n="607" who="S0274" trans="overlap">so what's it called? The Glass</u>
<u n="608" who="S0253">The Glass or was it The Grass Arena? The Glass or Grass</u>
<u n="609" who="S0274">The Glass Castle?</u>
<u n="610" who="S0253">no that's it so definitely the something Arena <pause dur="short"/> maybe The Grass Arena</u>
<u n="611" who="S0274">The Grass Arena?</u>
<u n="612" who="S0253">I think so</u>
<u n="613" who="S0274">oh The Grass Arena by John Healy?</u>
<u n="614" who="S0253">John Healy yeah</u>
<u n="615" who="S0274">oh it's an autobiography?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0253">well more or less but it's about it's about his experiences of being homeless and it was</u>
<u n="617" who="S0274" trans="overlap">oh wow</u>
<u n="618" who="S0253">it I I read it but cos it's on</u>
<u n="619" who="S0274" trans="overlap">oh I find that now I find I find this now after doing my dissertation imagine doing a little extract from an autobiography</u>
<u n="620" who="S0253">should have spoke to me then <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="621" who="S0274">sorry go on I'll just save that to my wish list</u>
<u n="622" who="S0253" trans="overlap">erm but in you know what I mean? it's like er you kind of I remember reading it I read like a profile on on John Healy John Healy <pause dur="short"/> and because he's because he's a person who has like this real lived experience and he's you know been homeless he's you know his life suffered you know he's he suffered through his life and things like that and now he has this like well he might have passed away but the last thing I read about him he erm he had like a picture of his little studio space and he had this tiny little space in London where he wrote from and you just got <trunc>th</trunc> there's something about people like that that <trunc>y</trunc> you know there's good writers and then there's kind of there's people who you really buy into like their experiences and things like that and you can't fake that it's like</u>
<u n="623" who="S0274" trans="overlap">I'm gonna have to yeah I'm gonna have to check that one out man</u>
<u n="624" who="S0253">yeah it's like it's like you were saying there about like about these like these photojournalists and things like that</u>
<u n="625" who="S0274">yes</u>
<u n="626" who="S0253">there's people who do it you know and because they've been given the chance they've been gifted the chance</u>
<u n="627" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="628" who="S0253" trans="overlap">to do something</u>
<u n="629" who="S0274">whereas this was his like it would be like your this was a general passion</u>
<u n="630" who="S0253">yeah you know he'd had to he must have had to overcome a lot to to to become you know</u>
<u n="631" who="S0274">well is he he said things like as a kid you know like his dad used to let him draw on the kitchen <pause dur="short"/> kitchen wall and he used to like to draw and paint</u>
<u n="632" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="633" who="S0274">a man of that era allowing his son to do that do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="634" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="635" who="S0274">he was like probably working how many? <trunc>te</trunc> ten hours a day twelve hours a day in a factory</u>
<u n="636" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="637" who="S0274">do you know what I mean? it's obviously straight away you're thinking that far to have the talent and then recognise it but</u>
<u n="638" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="639" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah no that's it and the whole time I was just mesmerised by this documentary</u>
<u n="640" who="S0253">but like</u>
<u n="641" who="S0274" trans="overlap">it's literally from the sixties he's been in every erm conflict</u>
<u n="642" who="S0253">wow</u>
<u n="643" who="S0274">erm apart from when er <unclear/> took overtook The Times</u>
<u n="644" who="S0253">right</u>
<u n="645" who="S0274" trans="overlap">was it The Times? and Andrew <trunc>N</trunc> is it Andrew Neil <trunc>overto</trunc> he became the editor</u>
<u n="646" who="S0253">right</u>
<u n="647" who="S0274" trans="overlap">er and basically he didn't want they didn't want The Times to be like an actual he said you know a like a real paper and cos it used to be like it just you know</u>
<u n="648" who="S0253" trans="overlap">they wanted it more tabloid and stuff?</u>
<u n="649" who="S0274">yeah they wanted the sponsors <pause dur="short"/> so he was kind of shifted out <pause dur="short"/> and he said he kind of had to break away from that and do like he'd done like wildlife books and stuff like that you know photography</u>
<u n="650" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="651" who="S0274">erm but he he he was really deep because he was talking like <pause dur="short"/> he'd get back flash flashes back cos he's witnessed people getting executed <pause dur="short"/> do you know what I mean? and he was like that so it's it's erm <pause dur="short"/> and he'd you know he said he'd lost his wife and you know that was his fault but but he said he needed to do it</u>
<u n="652" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="653" who="S0274">he he needed to show the world what was happening he said he couldn't he can't explain it to anyone but and it was just wow</u>
<u n="654" who="S0253">and and those those people just people like that and stories like that really <pause dur="short"/> are <pause dur="short"/> are you know you just they like really inspiring people</u>
<u n="655" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="656" who="S0253">it <pause dur="short"/> I mean it it's it's like it's like these it's like these journalists who you know are <trunc>st</trunc> are still in Syria like are still knocking about in Syria like and I was I there's a really it was erm it was in <trunc>G</trunc> I was in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s the other week and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had GQ magazine and I was <trunc>readi</trunc> there was a there was a four-page spread about about how how sort of what's the word? <pause dur="short"/> you think of like you know kidnapping journalists and Western journalists like</u>
<u n="657" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="658" who="S0253" trans="overlap">and things like that you think of it as this kind of high trade it's not it's really bland and it's very much like we'll give you this money for this journalist or or the American we'll give you a bit more</u>
<u n="659" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="660" who="S0253">and they just trade them round <pause dur="short"/> only occasionally will they will someone buy them up and then use them as some kind of political thing</u>
<u n="661" who="S0274">mm</u>
<u n="662" who="S0253">half the time it's just to make money and they just generate revenue off them</u>
<u n="663" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="664" who="S0253">and they they go up in price and down in price very very banal I guess you could say erm <pause dur="short"/> so they but you just you know when you've got to <pause dur="short"/> you you know the stuff that's come out of like you know like <pause dur="short"/> from Syria and Iraq and things like that you've gotta <pause dur="short"/> you know you've gotta have some you you know you need something different haven't you to to</u>
<u n="665" who="S0274" trans="overlap">totally</u>
<u n="666" who="S0253" trans="overlap">go in to to to really want to show the world that erm to be the person</u>
<u n="667" who="S0274">to know that the nine percent chance you are gonna get snatched if you're not working for the BBC or something</u>
<u n="668" who="S0253" trans="overlap">or shot</u>
<u n="669" who="S0274">but then there was that guy wasn't there working for the BBC who got took I can't remember his name <pause dur="short"/> and that guy Henning guy again you'd look at him and wouldn't think would you? but he had this raw passion that he needed to go in and help</u>
<u n="670" who="S0253" trans="overlap">it's the need to help people</u>
<u n="671" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="672" who="S0253" trans="overlap">and and and everything was you know everyone said to him like you know the <trunc>Bri</trunc> the British you know the British Embassy said well they they can't stop you from travelling they're not allowed to stop them</u>
<u n="673" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="674" who="S0253">but they can say they have warnings that say</u>
<u n="675" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="676" who="S0253">we strongly recommend you don't go <pause dur="short"/> and you know with his his his need to help other people</u>
<u n="677" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="678" who="S0253">you know and that's the difference like that that's this is what some people just amazing people and and</u>
<u n="679" who="S0274" trans="overlap">definitely</u>
<u n="680" who="S0253" trans="overlap">er you know it's <pause dur="short"/> you don't have to do you don't have to do grand things to be a great person but when you realise people you just bloody hell like</u>
<u n="681" who="S0274" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="682" who="S0253">they should you know erm you know and and that's the you you learn a lot about yourself cos I honestly think to myself like <pause dur="short"/> you know</u>
<u n="683" who="S0274">it makes you look at yourself <unclear/> doesn't it?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0253">oh absolutely can <vocal desc="laugh"/> and you couldn't pay me</u>
<u n="685" who="S0274" trans="overlap">no no I</u>
<u n="686" who="S0253">you couldn't pay me to well <pause dur="short"/> and that's the thing about these journalists half of them aren't half of them of them didn't get paid they're not even doing it for any money or any kind of financial incentive some of them some of them will make a bit they <trunc>ca</trunc></u>
<u n="687" who="S0274" trans="overlap">from a if they sell a picture or something yeah</u>
<u n="688" who="S0253">yeah pictures and and and things like that and you can make a good bit of money on it but they're salaried they're not</u>
<u n="689" who="S0274">no</u>
<u n="690" who="S0253" trans="overlap">and the <trunc>pa</trunc> half the time the papers that they work for they or the <pause dur="short"/> they they don't care about them they're not <pause dur="short"/> all they're worried about is getting the getting the story and getting the pictures</u>
<u n="691" who="S0274">mm</u>
<u n="692" who="S0253">it's really sad but</u>
<u n="693" who="S0274">it it but</u>
<u n="694" who="S0253" trans="overlap">what compels people?</u>
<u n="695" who="S0274">you're totally right the the</u>
<u n="696" who="S0253" trans="overlap">amazing</u>
<u n="697" who="S0274" trans="overlap">people that you hear of like that you just think <pause dur="short"/> and the thing is when people do things not for <pause dur="short"/> the erm acknowledgement they just do it</u>
<u n="698" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="699" who="S0274">cos they <pause dur="short"/> they really feel that's</u>
<u n="700" who="S0253">there's erm <pause dur="short"/> I can't remember there's a there's like a a proverb about that isn't it that's just like <pause dur="short"/> doing something that like if you do something without being acknowledged I can't remember what it is I think you might know it</u>
<u n="701" who="S0274">no I don't <pause dur="short"/> being Irish <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="702" who="S0253">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> being being an Irish <pause dur="short"/> erm yeah it's</u>
<u n="703" who="S0274">mm</u>
<u n="704" who="S0253">but sometimes sometimes I wish that like I had a bit more a bit more grit maybe and</u>
<u n="705" who="S0274">yeah that's where I was saying before like you were saying like you know this age like your friends like you're saying <unclear>a film set</unclear> and all that but that's where I start go er there is there is a side of me though that goes <pause dur="short"/> I I need to go and make <pause dur="short"/> a story I need to go and make something</u>
<u n="706" who="S0253" trans="overlap">but you but you will be helping people though</u>
<u n="707" who="S0274">yeah and then I think I realise like when we went travelling around Europe I loved it but I realised I was like a home bird</u>
<u n="708" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="709" who="S0274">that's when I think I realised</u>
<u n="710" who="S0253">yeah I'd be the bravest man in the world if there was a clean toilet around</u>
<u n="711" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="712" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> as long as there was a nice bathroom</u>
<u n="713" who="S0274">except with</u>
<u n="714" who="S0253" trans="overlap">if I could take one with me</u>
<u n="715" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="716" who="S0253">if I could have a nice bathroom me I wouldn't mind going anywhere</u>
<u n="717" who="S0274" trans="overlap">but you know what? halfway through I <trunc>thi</trunc> I think I'm sure you probably did I was totally accustomed to those god awful <trunc>toi</trunc></u>
<u n="718" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="719" who="S0274" trans="overlap">those er Portakabin if anything I've er</u>
<u n="720" who="S0253" trans="overlap"><unclear/> room <unclear/></u>
<u n="721" who="S0274" trans="overlap">if if I didn't smell that mm revolting er chemical smell I was like er I'm not going in there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="722" who="S0253">yeah <pause dur="short"/> no it's erm</u>
<u n="723" who="S0274">can you remember though going to that hostel in Bratislava and just being like <pause dur="short"/> after being there for a week and then going to that <pause dur="short"/> amazing</u>
<u n="724" who="S0253">which one?</u>
<u n="725" who="S0274">it was where remember the French girls? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="726" who="S0253">oh yeah</u>
<u n="727" who="S0274">and remember when I kicked off on the middle of the well I didn't kick off but when the French girls were talking to us</u>
<u n="728" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="729" who="S0274">and then they're saying right oh we're talking English now are we? <vocal desc="laugh"/> now like</u>
<u n="730" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah no like like you understand this</u>
<u n="731" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="732" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="733" who="S0274">and the two of their faces was like that</u>
<u n="734" who="S0253">yeah <pause dur="short"/> obviously they were saying it was like a game of chess</u>
<u n="735" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="736" who="S0253">picking up women was like oh that's a healthy attitude</u>
<u n="737" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="738" who="S0253">they must what's that book called? The Game The Rules of the Game</u>
<u n="739" who="S0274">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="740" who="S0253">I think they all must have read that that was their holiday reading</u>
<u n="741" who="S0274" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I remember when the girl that was talking to me was gorgeous and she was Parisian and she said it's often the case of Parisian people cos a lot of them are quite wealthy so she said er <trunc>ye</trunc> what did she say? they're dicks but</u>
<u n="742" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="743" who="S0274">and I was like you're amazing I wanna marry you</u>
<u n="744" who="S0253">what's French for marry me?</u>
<u n="745" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="746" who="S0253">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="747" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="748" who="S0253" trans="overlap">they were they were they <trunc>w</trunc> they <trunc>w</trunc> they they they were alright in the end weren't they? we had a <unclear/></u>
<u n="749" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah well there was the one there was always the one lad who talked to us I think it was the er the Asian lad</u>
<u n="750" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="751" who="S0274">and then the other two made out as if they couldn't speak English</u>
<u n="752" who="S0253"><vocal desc="gasp"/> the audacity</u>
<u n="753" who="S0274">I know erm <pause dur="short"/> see er that's when I was like oh are we speaking English now or are we or not something like that thinking we've we've never come across this Scouse sort of</u>
<u n="754" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="755" who="S0274">what is this?</u>
<u n="756" who="S0253">confrontation</u>
<u n="757" who="S0274">yeah so</u>
<u n="758" who="S0253" trans="overlap">are you English?</u>
<u n="759" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="760" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="761" who="S0274">yeah so er but no yeah so definitely watch that man that's brilliant that</u>
<u n="762" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I will</u>
<u n="763" who="S0274" trans="overlap">Don McCullum</u>
<u n="764" who="S0253">one thing one thing it</u>
<u n="765" who="S0274">it wasn't in Waterstones I was very surprised it's the <trunc>fam</trunc> he's done the famous pictures of the Vietnam soldier who's shell shocked and it's just his face like that you'll known that you'll have seen it</u>
<u n="766" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I'll know I've seen it</u>
<u n="767" who="S0274" trans="overlap">from working in Waterstones</u>
<u n="768" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="769" who="S0274">and it's just a picture of his face and his eyes are like that and he explains for all his pictures but with a</u>
<u n="770" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="771" who="S0274">a bit of context at the time like the political or whatever conflict and it's just you're just like that</u>
<u n="772" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="773" who="S0274">yeah so definitely when you've maybe time to yourself</u>
<u n="774" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm gonna have plenty <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="775" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="776" who="S0253">yeah I've got to dunno I'm gonna fire off a few well not many jobs I was gonna fire off a couple of job applications this afternoon</u>
<u n="777" who="S0274"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I know how it is though mate because like I finished what? I finished in August and</u>
<u n="778" who="S0253" trans="overlap">have you been applying for jobs?</u>
<u n="779" who="S0274">well I've not <trunc>appl</trunc> I'm I've joined an agency erm and once I get my</u>
<u n="780" who="S0253" trans="overlap">a secret agency</u>
<u n="781" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> er actually I'm getting er some book book ideas</u>
<u n="782" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="783" who="S0274">erm <pause dur="short"/> once I've got my HCPC licence which I <trunc>shou</trunc> I've paid for I should get this week then they can start putting my forward for social work jobs</u>
<u n="784" who="S0253" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="785" who="S0274">that's like</u>
<u n="786" who="S0253" trans="overlap">so this this is a licence to practise?</u>
<u n="787" who="S0274">yeah erm licence to thrill er</u>
<u n="788" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so what so what area of social work do you wanna go into?</u>
<u n="789" who="S0274">I've got experience in the adults you see because I've had statutory experience</u>
<u n="790" who="S0253">right</u>
<u n="791" who="S0274">so at the moment he's gonna find me that but I'm just gonna say it's erm <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>f</trunc> find me er children's as well but I need to get off my arse and do a <trunc>chil</trunc> generic children's application so that when jobs come up I can fire them at once <pause dur="short"/> I can</u>
<u n="792" who="S0253" trans="overlap">do they come up through NHS?</u>
<u n="793" who="S0274">er sometimes</u>
<u n="794" who="S0253">cos if you if you're on NHS jobs cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> does this like</u>
<u n="795" who="S0274">yes</u>
<u n="796" who="S0253">I I dread applying for I I dread applying for jobs and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s just like it's like oh yeah just copied and pasted like she has like cos cos on NHS jobs you have this <trunc>prof</trunc> they have this like it's</u>
<u n="797" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah er someone was telling me</u>
<u n="798" who="S0253" trans="overlap">just the <unclear/></u>
<u n="799" who="S0274" trans="overlap">about that yeah</u>
<u n="800" who="S0253">because you've got a little pro forma and</u>
<u n="801" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="802" who="S0253">you half the time you've got applications saved and you just send them off to like</u>
<u n="803" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="804" who="S0253" trans="overlap">and it's it's mad</u>
<u n="805" who="S0274">and it's</u>
<u n="806" who="S0253" trans="overlap">obviously you've gotta tailor them and you can't just be like</u>
<u n="807" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I worked in an ice cream factory</u>
<u n="808" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I've got experience of <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="809" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="810" who="S0253">working in a</u>
<u n="811" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="812" who="S0253" trans="overlap">cinema I know a lot about psychology</u>
<u n="813" who="S0274" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but yeah that's someone was telling me about that but I dunno I kind of been in like I want a job I'm hoping to get an interview with this <pause dur="short"/> one I applied for I dunno I'm I've kind of found myself <pause dur="short"/> even though I don't really like doing this job anymore <pause dur="short"/> I'm a little bit content at the moment cos it's been so <unclear>erm packed</unclear> for two years of like being in uni like near you know like four days a week then working and having like one day off</u>
<u n="814" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="815" who="S0274">I quite I dunno I'm quite liking just going and having a book to read or going to the gym and then nothing you know worrying too much about</u>
<u n="816" who="S0253">I think I think that I think that's a nice place to be in and I wouldn't I wouldn't go away from that immediately</u>
<u n="817" who="S0274">mm</u>
<u n="818" who="S0253">cos that's what I feel like now like I feel I've been doing you know I've been in I've been in the same place for three years</u>
<u n="819" who="S0274">mm</u>
<u n="820" who="S0253">you know and I've got very much you know I'm saying I'm saying I was saying <trunc>befo</trunc> or moaning before saying it's it's it's stressful it's <trunc>n</trunc> it's not that stressful you know and it's quite a nice job</u>
<u n="821" who="S0274">mm</u>
<u n="822" who="S0253">like <pause dur="short"/> every day I get to speak to <pause dur="short"/> people from all over the world and you know it's a very rewarding job it's really nice and it's it's it's lovely but</u>
<u n="823" who="S0274" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="824" who="S0253">so I'm kind of part of me thinks oh god like you know if if can I could I ever like like I just work on my own all the time it's just me</u>
<u n="825" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="826" who="S0253">sometimes <trunc>someti</trunc> I go I go a lot of days without seeing another member of staff I go in and sign in I do the classes I go home just</u>
<u n="827" who="S0274">yeah?</u>
<u n="828" who="S0253">yeah it's very <pause dur="short"/> yeah so part of me kind of thinks like could I really work like a big organisation again like?</u>
<u n="829" who="S0274">yeah true</u>
<u n="830" who="S0253">have I have I still got my teamworking skills? or will I be just like</u>
<u n="831" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="832" who="S0253">just a low <unclear/></u>
<u n="833" who="S0274" trans="overlap">whilst using your initiative <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="834" who="S0253">yeah well it's these these these are all good words for my CV</u>
<u n="835" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="836" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> erm you know and I think I I kind of you know I I was so comfortable for a long time it part of me feels a bit nervous about you know doing something else because I've done this but if you you you know you don't you don't have to change you you can just stay the same but if you wanna change then you've got you've gotta make a leap haven't you?</u>
<u n="837" who="S0274" trans="overlap">it's always <trunc>ye</trunc> yeah you're right and there's always that but you it the annoying thing is you know when you've done it and you go why have I been sat <unclear>under</unclear> my arse like when I I did that application for the <anon type="place"/> job and I was like that wasn't hard okay yeah you have to think for a day or two</u>
<u n="838" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="839" who="S0274">and get someone to look over it but really like you know what I mean? but I think the problem for me at the moment I dunno for you but if you are working a a lot of hours like at a certain <unclear>time</unclear> and you kind of when you do have that time you just kind of like it's almost like you're recharging and</u>
<u n="840" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="841" who="S0274">so</u>
<u n="842" who="S0253">that's on Friends they always talk about the fear <pause dur="short"/> you know on</u>
<u n="843" who="S0274" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="844" who="S0253" trans="overlap">that one with Rachel where like she's the it's like <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>sh</trunc> Chandler tells her to quit her job I think and it's like you won't you won't apply for another job unless you get the fear</u>
<u n="845" who="S0274">yeah that's it yeah</u>
<u n="846" who="S0253" trans="overlap">and she quits her job and then she's skint</u>
<u n="847" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="848" who="S0253">and <pause dur="short"/> it's erm <pause dur="short"/> but you know <trunc>te</trunc> I mean I could <pause dur="short"/> I could you know I could probably get another job in another school and <pause dur="short"/> I could carry on teaching I think for years but <pause dur="short"/> and I wouldn't mind doing that but I just feel a bit I feel a bit stuck really I feel a bit there's no there's no the only way I could the only way I could progress would be if you did like it's called a Delta a diploma erm and that makes but then that's it I mean obviously you can go on and do like you once once you've got a Delta it's it's a three-month <pause dur="short"/> it's a three-month qualification no less but it's it takes a long time to do erm <pause dur="short"/> and then but once you've got that that's the the limit really</u>
<u n="849" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="850" who="S0253">and that's not a bad thing cos it's a really tough qualification but you you're kind of saying to yourself that er like <pause dur="short"/> I can the only career I could do is either be a teacher or to to be a manager of a language school that that's kind of what you can do and you know it's the there's it's good money and stuff like that and it's a good job but you know I just kind of I just feel a bit like</u>
<u n="851" who="S0274">you've done that now yeah</u>
<u n="852" who="S0253">yeah and not only that like I know a lot of managers or language schools and you know a lot of my friends are quite quite you know they're doing er sort of on the border of that kind of job <pause dur="short"/> and it's just you know financially you have to be if you wanna be financially stable you know you've got to really find a good place and a</u>
<u n="853" who="S0274" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="854" who="S0253" trans="overlap">really good school and <pause dur="short"/> I dunno I just I think I'm gonna try something else for a bit and then</u>
<u n="855" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="856" who="S0253">go back to it <unclear/></u>
<u n="857" who="S0274" trans="overlap">I think it's good though that you know you're thinking of doing the publishing master's I think it's brilliant</u>
<u n="858" who="S0253">yeah I mean it's only obviously that's helped with you know <pause dur="short"/> it but that that's kind of that's kind of helped with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> like kind of saying you know she if we had to go to Edinburgh then but I'll still do it even if if if she doesn't get the the job in Edinburgh I'll still</u>
<u n="859" who="S0274" trans="overlap">would you do it here?</u>
<u n="860" who="S0253">well it's it's like a three grand might be worth</u>
<u n="861" who="S0274">oh god yeah yeah</u>
<u n="862" who="S0253" trans="overlap">might be worth might be worth moving to Edinburgh wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="863" who="S0274">definitely will mm</u>
<u n="864" who="S0253">cos cos I'm gonna have to pay for it myself so</u>
<u n="865" who="S0274">mm</u>
<u n="866" who="S0253">I might as well erm <pause dur="short"/> you know take a bit of a risk</u>
<u n="867" who="S0274"><unclear/> <pause dur="short"/> fucking hell everyone's moving away</u>
<u n="868" who="S0253">we might not be this is the thing is like er I'm really I'm really wary of like talking to people about this stuff cos</u>
<u n="869" who="S0274">I know it's</u>
<u n="870" who="S0253">cos if it doesn't come good then you're just like a bit of a divvy</u>
<u n="871" who="S0274" trans="overlap">it's almost like it's a it's it's an idea that you don't quite you <trunc>m</trunc> you don't want people to take bits of it away isn't it it's your it's I know what you mean yeah</u>
<u n="872" who="S0253">it it's like it keeps you sane your little dreams doesn't it?</u>
<u n="873" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="874" who="S0253">your little visions of how life's gonna be like</u>
<u n="875" who="S0274">that's it I mean cos for me the reason I wanna get a job in <anon type="place"/> because once you've been in there for a few years then you can work anywhere <pause dur="short"/> you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="876" who="S0253" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="877" who="S0274">and you can go and work in an organisation and stuff like that whereas I kind of feel it would just be pointless me working <anon type="place"/> for two years to then go and do an organisation job that you wouldn't necessarily need that qualification it would just be a longer road to get to there then so <pause dur="short"/> plus I wanna be in the thick of where like</u>
<u n="878" who="S0253" trans="overlap">that's that's what I'm like</u>
<u n="879" who="S0274">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="880" who="S0253">I <trunc>ju</trunc> I I wanna <pause dur="short"/> I wanna do something that's like <pause dur="short"/> <trunc>th</trunc> it's like changing and evolving</u>
<u n="881" who="S0274">mm</u>
<u n="882" who="S0253">all the time and <pause dur="short"/> I wanna <pause dur="short"/> I I think that's the thing for me I feel like my job <pause dur="short"/> can be quite not repetitive but <pause dur="short"/> when you when you've kind of stuck the course books</u>
<u n="883" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="884" who="S0253" trans="overlap">and and you can do your own stuff but when you're doing the same course</u>
<u n="885" who="S0274">mm</u>
<u n="886" who="S0253">all the time like you know I've I've taught the same course like about a hundred times</u>
<u n="887" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="888" who="S0253">and I just feel like if I do it again I'll I'll go mad er because it</u>
<u n="889" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="890" who="S0253">it's even if you <pause dur="short"/> you know because you know I dunno and I just I wanna do something where it's like it's like really really like outrageously challenging and</u>
<u n="891" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="892" who="S0253" trans="overlap">a bit scary I wanna be scared</u>
<u n="893" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="894" who="S0253">you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="895" who="S0274">yeah like an academic thrill ride</u>
<u n="896" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah yeah a roller coaster if you will</u>
<u n="897" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="898" who="S0253">an emotional roller coaster</u>
<u n="899" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="900" who="S0253">but I want you know how cos then and if and if I just if but you know if I can't do it then I'll I'll do something else but</u>
<u n="901" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah I mean I think the worst thing is is those that haven't tried isn't it?</u>
<u n="902" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="903" who="S0274" trans="overlap">do you know what I mean? I think as you're talking there is I think <pause dur="short"/> I think we're probably quite similar is that I'm <trunc>probab</trunc> like I think the reason I never really took up reading in terms of leisurely reading in the time that I knew you and with university cos I knew in my head I didn't have the time to commit to it and I</u>
<u n="904" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="905" who="S0274" trans="overlap">don't like to fail not I I I</u>
<u n="906" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="907" who="S0274" trans="overlap">and I don't think erm in the sense where I don't do stuff cos I think I'm gonna fail but cos I know I would like I will trudge and trudge through something to get it I won't have something unfinished</u>
<u n="908" who="S0253">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="909" who="S0274">erm so I think that's why I needed that but so it's a it's you know it's the thing to have isn't it? you want this sort of I <trunc>thi</trunc> it's probably the mentality I use in my training and stuff like that it's kind of like</u>
<u n="910" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="911" who="S0274">that's self-discipline isn't it? and like going okay it's shit and you know doing this but you get it done and you</u>
<u n="912" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah I <vocal desc="sigh"/> I think that's that's I'll tell you what I have I have I have like a certain fear of of of like when I I get nervous I'm typing out job applications no one's watching you and no one's reading what I'm writing</u>
<u n="913" who="S0274">mm</u>
<u n="914" who="S0253">and I can always delete and edit and that's and that's the wonderful thing typewriters you know like using a typewriter</u>
<u n="915" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="916" who="S0253">it's like you can</u>
<u n="917" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="918" who="S0253">you can <vocal desc="misc"/> yeah oh I'd better start again</u>
<u n="919" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="920" who="S0253">you know but you can erm you know you can edit and you know redact and things like that and but I still feel nervous when I'm doing it and it's because I'm nervous about like you know getting rejected or</u>
<u n="921" who="S0274" trans="overlap">I think <trunc>some</trunc> that's it isn't it I think sometimes as we're only human you're overthinking every paragraph going how are they gonna perceive that? are they gonna think he hasn't took when</u>
<u n="922" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="923" who="S0274" trans="overlap">really you need to have that sort of it's almost like self-confidence certain of us we need to go well no I'm gonna write this and it's</u>
<u n="924" who="S0253" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I mean so I've got I I'm better at that cos the reason the reason I was so bad in uni is because I couldn't finish anything cos I couldn't finish a sentence I'd be like oh it's not right I need to change it</u>
<u n="925" who="S0274" trans="overlap">and you sat or your whole course just</u>
<u n="926" who="S0253">I was</u>
<u n="927" who="S0274" trans="overlap">and then the man appeared</u>
<u n="928" who="S0253">it took me I</u>
<u n="929" who="S0274" trans="overlap">and then he <trunc>w</trunc></u>
<u n="930" who="S0253">how how long how long did you how long did did it take you to write like what was your longest stint on an essay?</u>
<u n="931" who="S0274">well I wouldn't <trunc>g</trunc> I wouldn't go by the undergraduate cos that discount</u>
<u n="932" who="S0253" trans="overlap">go on no go on what was the longest time you spent on an essay as an undergraduate? be honest like typing it out?</u>
<u n="933" who="S0274">it would be like I I remember I did one cos I</u>
<u n="934" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="935" who="S0274">I wanted to go and see <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> that night</u>
<u n="936" who="S0253">oh yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="937" who="S0274">yeah erm</u>
<u n="938" who="S0253">oh well</u>
<u n="939" who="S0274" trans="overlap">I think I did it like in three hours yeah</u>
<u n="940" who="S0253">that's the longest time <pause dur="short"/> no <trunc>wha</trunc> that was the shortest time</u>
<u n="941" who="S0274">yeah the <trunc>sh</trunc></u>
<u n="942" who="S0253" trans="overlap">what was the longest?</u>
<u n="943" who="S0274">going off this one see the problem is I don't work on it see I obviously I type it quite quick</u>
<u n="944" who="S0253">right</u>
<u n="945" who="S0274" trans="overlap">but I'll do I'll do my reading and notes beforehand</u>
<u n="946" who="S0253">yeah you always did that didn't you?</u>
<u n="947" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah so</u>
<u n="948" who="S0253" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="949" who="S0274">my writing's never long but reading notes usually would take me especially the master's I'd do it over like two weeks to a month</u>
<u n="950" who="S0253">right</u>
<u n="951" who="S0274">so</u>
<u n="952" who="S0253">but what I'm saying is when when you were an undergraduate you you had like a similar workload to me but you would you would be very direct you'd be like this has to be finished by this day</u>
<u n="953" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="954" who="S0253">so and I've I'm doing this and doing this that leaves me four days so I'm gonna finish this in four days</u>
<u n="955" who="S0274">yeah that's true yeah</u>
<u n="956" who="S0253">whereas what I would do is I'd start my essays like three weeks before the deadline</u>
<u n="957" who="S0274">yeah I remember that and then</u>
<u n="958" who="S0253">they they'd take me three weeks because I'd sit there and I because I had so much time on my hands</u>
<u n="959" who="S0274">you'd delete a copy I remember</u>
<u n="960" who="S0253">oh god I'd delete like I used to I <trunc>alwa</trunc> I used to delete whole essays I used to write an essay and then delete it</u>
<u n="961" who="S0274" trans="overlap">I know I I remember your voice you'd be like oh he's done like a thousand words and he's he's just got rid of them</u>
<u n="962" who="S0253">I know</u>
<u n="963" who="S0274">but that was the difference that was where</u>
<u n="964" who="S0253" trans="overlap">but but please ask me to email me my</u>
<u n="965" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="966" who="S0253" trans="overlap"><unclear/> before you do business yeah just <trunc>ju</trunc> <unclear>such as</unclear> words toss them in</u>
<u n="967" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="968" who="S0253">but erm and that's the thing so it's like I erm everything was like painstaking with me</u>
<u n="969" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="970" who="S0253">and that's why I like with with job applications I'm I'm sitting there and I'm I'm writing them out and then I'm like <pause dur="short"/> you know like like and I kind of get nervous and then I delete stuff and it's just really stupid</u>
<u n="971" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="972" who="S0253">what I'm saying is I've I've got a bit better than I was at uni I've learned to be a bit more fearless so I've sent out letters and things like that and then I email people and you know ask about like work experience and stuff and then <vocal desc="laugh"/> the other day like I was feeling really like you know brave and I was like so I've just got it was on the Monday and I was like right not messing around now I'm gonna email a bunch of people see if I can get some freelance work like just some checking and proofreading <pause dur="short"/> so I erm so I emailed Macmillan who are like probably the biggest ELT publisher <pause dur="short"/> technically erm so <vocal desc="laugh"/> I emailed Macmillan but and I was like I just I just balls ballsally like you know was like you know just just enquiring about any kind of like er freelance work and then <vocal desc="laugh"/> like I was just like I'm not gonna overthink this press send and then like as soon as I looked at the sent box it was like I'd I'd put I think I'd put Macmilla</u>
<u n="973" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="974" who="S0253">Macmilla like I hadn't put the L on <trunc>Macmill</trunc> the N on Macmillan and I just like</u>
<u n="975" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="976" who="S0253">when you're applying for like</u>
<u n="977" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="978" who="S0253">a proofreading job</u>
<u n="979" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's amazing</u>
<u n="980" who="S0253" trans="overlap">like when you're trying to say you're trying sort of sell your proofreading skills to someone and you're like yeah I'm good</u>
<u n="981" who="S0274">you should have sent one five minutes later saying ah that was a deliberate ploy so the</u>
<u n="982" who="S0253" trans="overlap">did you notice my error?</u>
<u n="983" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="984" who="S0253">erm and and that's the problem is like I kind of got this confidence and I was just like yeah just send it out you're a good writer you can <trunc>j</trunc></u>
<u n="985" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="986" who="S0253">you know you've got good grammar you've got good punctuation just send it and then</u>
<u n="987" who="S0274" trans="overlap">I <trunc>kn</trunc> I know do you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="988" who="S0253" trans="overlap">Macmilla <pause dur="short"/> and then it was just like</u>
<u n="989" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="990" who="S0253">and it wasn't even like embedded in the text so it was like it was the the the title of the email like the subject it was like <trunc>j</trunc> flashed up Macmilla oh</u>
<u n="991" who="S0274">oh but I know what you mean though</u>
<u n="992" who="S0253" trans="overlap">embarrassing</u>
<u n="993" who="S0274" trans="overlap">cos it's not not to that level but I have to email like I email the service manager for the jobs</u>
<u n="994" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="995" who="S0274">cos it had been ages since I'd applied and I thought ah well if I haven't got an interview I I wanna ask for feedback and <vocal desc="laugh"/> like knocking on the <anon type="place"/> council door</u>
<u n="996" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="997" who="S0274">but she emailed me back the next day and she was very polite and she said oh thanks very much for your email she's like <trunc>sh</trunc> I've been busy erm we're gonna be shortlisting next Monday so she said if you've got and it's so you'll hear last and I was like oh right</u>
<u n="998" who="S0253">so you'll hear</u>
<u n="999" who="S0274">er hopefully a week Monday I might hear that I've hopefully fingers crossed</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0253" trans="overlap">good luck</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0274" trans="overlap">that got an interview cheers erm <pause dur="short"/> but before sending it was like right okay yeah and then I sent it and I went shit shit have I have I imagine sending the service manager of <anon type="place"/> council like you know I've like put like dick on it or something like if <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="1002" who="S0253">why would you write this?</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0274">exactly but</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0253">do you normally write dick in emails?</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0274">not not really but you know these things that</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1007" who="S0274">anxiety sort of takes over and I'm like</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1009" who="S0274">I'm like <unclear>scanners</unclear> and <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="1010" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0274">but it was alright though er</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0253">I have I have I've not not I've not I've never written dick in an email but I've like <vocal desc="laugh"/> I have done stuff like that or you know one thing that spellchecker doesn't always pick up is erm cos again if you frantically edit things</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0253">you will type a sentence and you will go to you might say such as <pause dur="short"/> and then you'll be like oh it doesn't sound right so you do the you start to search as and then you're right and you'll continue the thought and you'll say such as something and it never picks up if you write things like such as such as <pause dur="short"/> cos that's like that's okay so like and these things or a double double articles</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0253">oh no double articles it does pick up but erm <pause dur="short"/> yeah check your work</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1018" who="S0253">just check your writing</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0274">that's what I mean yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> Macmillas</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0253">Macmillas</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0274">probably thought you were applying for like a I I dunno a brewery or something do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1022" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah Macmilla <trunc>t</trunc> Macmilla time but it was I mean it I just had to laugh I mean it was only speculative anyway and they emailed me back and just said to be honest like our <trunc>da</trunc> they said our database is like we've got like five hundred freelancers they're not looking for anymore he said if we advertise something then but I mean you know you're at the the <trunc>ro</trunc> you're at the bottom of the pile</u>
<u n="1023" who="S0274" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> otherwise fuck off</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1025" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1026" who="S0253">it wasn't that bad it was just er the you know they they they have to control the number of applications they get</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0253">you you have to empathise because <pause dur="short"/> you know it's a skill that <pause dur="short"/> you know it's not something that everyone can do but it's a skill that it's not</u>
<u n="1029" who="S0274">I've heard you have to train in Japan for two years</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0253">yeah in a sense like</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1032" who="S0253">no it well generally they they want they want erm you can get like certificates from like the society</u>
<u n="1033" who="S0274" trans="overlap">that is not the definitive <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1034" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you could you can you can <pause dur="short"/> you <trunc>ye</trunc> yeah you can train with like the Society of Proofreaders and get like accredited certificates and things like that and you know it's sort of had to you have to regulate this this job cos otherwise anyone can just say well I can read quite well and</u>
<u n="1035" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1036" who="S0253">cos like cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> a <trunc>proo</trunc> he works from the village and he's a proof reader erm and then and he just landed on the job but it's you know they've got to protect jobs like that because otherwise if everyone just said oh I can do it</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0274">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0253">then you know you can't it's not it's not professionalised so they erm <pause dur="short"/> so obviously they're gonna say like listen they were just honest and just said like we've got five hundred we've got five hundred people on on the you know on the on the bank we don't need any more but if we do here's the thing and he was very polite so at least he got back to me</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0274" trans="overlap">well it's good that he emailed you back isn't it? yeah</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0253">yeah rather than being like Macmilla?</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0274">douche</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0274">delete</u>
<u n="1044" who="S0253">what an idiot so er yeah that was pretty that was pretty bad</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0274">I suppose it's a less</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0253" trans="overlap">you've gotta you've gotta laugh</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0274">it's a lesson there for everyone isn't it?</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I'm I'm trying to think of other parallels and do you watch The Apprentice?</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0274">no</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0253">you never watch that? I er I I had never watched it until the other day and I found it hilarious but</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0274" trans="overlap">I've seen the little intros of them like talking about themselves</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0253">I think they're told I think they're kind of</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0253" trans="overlap">told to be stupid</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0253">like cos like the guys</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0274" trans="overlap">he tried to sell me an investment deal <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="1058" who="S0253">they're <trunc>irr</trunc> er irrepressibly arrogant</u>
<u n="1059" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="1060" who="S0253">but I think it they're intentionally you know</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah it's like going on Big Brother isn't it?</u>
<u n="1062" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0274" trans="overlap">it's one of those</u>
<u n="1064" who="S0253">they're not gonna pick some bland guy who's just like yeah I just wanna get on with everyone really</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1066" who="S0253">it's like they want the guy who's like I'm gonna confront everyone I've got some awful <unclear/></u>
<u n="1067" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1068" who="S0253">erm and there's there was this really funny bit where they were trying to sell a jumper to erm the buyer like er it was in it was in some fancy London fashion shop probably erm like you know where it's like a hundred quid a a jumper or something? and erm so and it was an awful jumper it was it was called on air and the idea it had a camera in the jumper it was just a terrible idea right and it lit up</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it lit up?</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0253">right and and the guy giving the pitch like the the team leader like giving the pitch to them <pause dur="short"/> he he <vocal desc="laugh"/> like you're trying to sell them a jumper and he's like obviously I wouldn't wear this in public</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1072" who="S0253">and the guy's just like what? so I guess that was kind of like an equal faux pas it's like</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0274">brilliant</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0253">it's contradicting exactly what your job is</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1076" who="S0253">to do</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0274">oh</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0253">pretty stupid</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0274">it sounds awful that <pause dur="short"/> it's</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0253">erm yeah The Apprentice is er yeah</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0274">there you go there's er</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0253">er yeah it's it's I don't really like it that much by <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s really into it so</u>
<u n="1083" who="S0274">I think I did to be fair I did watch a bit of the last season but it was more just I think when I was in work sometimes if</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0274">we'd got a spare like half an hour whatever it was just like yeah</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0253">I don't really like it do you watch much TV?</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0274">erm yeah I watched that Educating the East End</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0253">that's really good</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0274">but do you know what though? it's kind of a thing you <trunc>nee</trunc> you know I watch it going out on a Thursday do you know what I mean? so the old little thing like but <pause dur="short"/> mate other than that <pause dur="short"/> apart from your Question Time on a Thursday oh I asked I asked er to go on that this week</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0253">did you?</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0274">but I haven't heard back so <unclear/> I mean the main thing is</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0253" trans="overlap">where is it? is it being filmed in Liverpool?</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0274">yeah I made the mistake though didn't I like I should have questioned her and I just like it probably at the most generic do you know what I mean like who do you vote for like blah de blah</u>
<u n="1094" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0274">you know what's your topic of the discussion when I really should have been out there like er I dunno I <trunc>sup</trunc> I support Animal Farm do you know what I mean the the</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1097" who="S0274">party that do that do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0253">what's Animal Farm? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1099" who="S0274">it erm there's that book isn't it? er</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0253">yeah I know about the book</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0274">yeah I dunno just in my head</u>
<u n="1102" who="S0253">do you mean do you mean like come across as like a raving</u>
<u n="1103" who="S0274">yeah it's like</u>
<u n="1104" who="S0253" trans="overlap">sort of like</u>
<u n="1105" who="S0274">nutter</u>
<u n="1106" who="S0253">leftie radical</u>
<u n="1107" who="S0274">you never know on Wednesday I could get a phone call and said oh someone's pulled out</u>
<u n="1108" who="S0253">it's er it's <trunc>int</trunc> do do you reckon <pause dur="short"/> do you reckon they want people with moderate views or they want people with</u>
<u n="1109" who="S0274" trans="overlap">I think they try and balance</u>
<u n="1110" who="S0253">right</u>
<u n="1111" who="S0274">and obviously cos Liverpool's quite staunchly Labour</u>
<u n="1112" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1113" who="S0274" trans="overlap">like probably have like and they give you the age bracket so it goes from like twenty-five to thirty-five so <pause dur="short"/> there's probably that many people but it frustrates me sometimes when people get on there cos they often don't speak and you're well why have you gone on it?</u>
<u n="1114" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1115" who="S0274" trans="overlap">do you know what I mean? they have</u>
<u n="1116" who="S0253" trans="overlap">it must be nerve racking though I mean like</u>
<u n="1117" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1118" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I don't know I don't I I don't know a lot about <trunc>pol</trunc>politics</u>
<u n="1119" who="S0274">I <trunc>thi</trunc> they choose they're just current issues you know what I mean? like last week it was erm <pause dur="short"/> er the the erm <pause dur="short"/> the dickhead lord Browne Broon or whatever his name is made the comment that he's disability minister</u>
<u n="1120" who="S0253">oh yeah</u>
<u n="1121" who="S0274">and he made you know working for about two pound and hour and then</u>
<u n="1122" who="S0253">where do they get them?</u>
<u n="1123" who="S0274">he's renowned he's made comments like that in the past he's an idiot but erm <pause dur="short"/> they say he's more of a policy maker which which is why Labour are going well don't you think that's kind of worrying that that's his discourse that he's using?</u>
<u n="1124" who="S0253">they're gonna jump on it aren't they?</u>
<u n="1125" who="S0274">but then cos it was in Berkshire obviously it was quite predominantly Tory and they were attacking the Labour woman I can't remember her name going oh you're using this as a a political <unclear>ploy</unclear> well it's like well yeah they are politicians but it was like <trunc>sh</trunc> but no he what he said was in extremely offensive and the whole time I was thinking there's nobody here with a disability they've asked don't really give a shit what you think doesn't matter what I think let's have someone with a disability</u>
<u n="1126" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1127" who="S0274">erm so the so there was things like that</u>
<u n="1128" who="S0253" trans="overlap"><trunc>ye</trunc>yeah</u>
<u n="1129" who="S0274">and it it's more topical really erm</u>
<u n="1130" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I I used to watch it I used to I used to like it when I was when I used to when I did politics in sixth form I used to watch it</u>
<u n="1131" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah used to have</u>
<u n="1132" who="S0253" trans="overlap">did is David Dimbleby still doing it?</u>
<u n="1133" who="S0274">yeah he's there I mean <pause dur="short"/> I I just love it cos it is a mixture obviously of your Tory one side you have your Labour the one side and then you've usually got like a</u>
<u n="1134" who="S0253" trans="overlap">like a cultural type of</u>
<u n="1135" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah you've got</u>
<u n="1136" who="S0253" trans="overlap">bit like</u>
<u n="1137" who="S0274" trans="overlap">like a <trunc>wri</trunc></u>
<u n="1138" who="S0253" trans="overlap">a writer or</u>
<u n="1139" who="S0274" trans="overlap">or I'll I quite like it when erm the Liberty one was on it I can never pronounce her name</u>
<u n="1140" who="S0253">er <trunc>Cha</trunc> Chakrabarti?</u>
<u n="1141" who="S0274">that's it yeah</u>
<u n="1142" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1143" who="S0274">she's very good erm and they had like this reverend guy he's alright but I don't like it sometimes where they're just playing to like the popular sort of thing you'd like to see everything but it's not it's either or it's but it's not really what's gonna</u>
<u n="1144" who="S0253">I read I read a good <trunc>artic</trunc> <vocal desc="laugh"/> I read a good article erm and it was there was a lad who he's a he was a he's a <trunc>con</trunc> he said like you know he's a Conservative I think he's like I think I can't remember what it was he's he's like a young maybe the representative of Young Conservatives or something like that</u>
<u n="1145" who="S0274" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1146" who="S0253">and there was a show on BBC three and it was like getting young people to talk about issues and stuff like that and it was trying to trying to bridge that gap in politics between you know young disaffected people</u>
<u n="1147" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1148" who="S0253">who who you know want want a voice and things like that and I think it was you know Rick Edwards? I think it was him who hosted it but it was this article you know I mean I don't necessarily agree with a lot of what this guy probably believes you know it's <trunc>po</trunc> his views on whatever but what I quite it was just really he wrote this really funny article and he said that when the they got someone so he was invited to come on this political talk show and he said when you get when you get invited on to this things <pause dur="short"/> erm there's normally like the stooge there's normally the one who has the most unpopular views</u>
<u n="1149" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="1150" who="S0253">who's who's basically there to take to to to defend to defend themselves and against like vitriol for about you know an hour</u>
<u n="1151" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="1152" who="S0253">erm it could would like like cos by a lot of people who don't agree erm <pause dur="short"/> and I didn't you know as I say I don't <trunc>agre</trunc> necessarily agree with his politics but he said it was really funny he said he he walked in the room and he looked at the rest of the panel and he was like I wonder where the guy is who's gonna have to defend all the views? oh</u>
<u n="1153" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1154" who="S0253">it's me cos there was no one in like he was</u>
<u n="1155" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1156" who="S0253">he was as right wing as they came and he was he said he's like you know he's sort of <pause dur="short"/> you know he's it's somewhere between like the Tories and Lib Dems he said but in a in a crowd of young people who were obviously you know generally tend to be a lot more <pause dur="short"/> a lot more left wing and a lot more</u>
<u n="1157" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1158" who="S0253">you know but also a lot more what's the word? like staunch in their views and would or will not will not shy away from attacking people</u>
<u n="1159" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="1160" who="S0253">he said he looked round the room and was just like</u>
<u n="1161" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1162" who="S0253">oh for god's sake <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1163" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1164" who="S0253">it just really made me laugh cos that's how these shows are made</u>
<u n="1165" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1166" who="S0253" trans="overlap">aren't they like it's</u>
<u n="1167" who="S0274" trans="overlap"><trunc>to</trunc> totally yeah</u>
<u n="1168" who="S0253">it's to get get like someone who get someone who can you know sometimes they can just do defend their policies and that's great but it just it really made me laugh that that cos he he must have absolutely bricked it</u>
<u n="1169" who="S0274">oh god</u>
<u n="1170" who="S0253">be terrified wouldn't you?</u>
<u n="1171" who="S0274">I know yeah</u>
<u n="1172" who="S0253">but erm yeah no <trunc>di</trunc> I only watch I watch Newsnight that's about</u>
<u n="1173" who="S0274">yeah I watch that sometimes it's on all the time that</u>
<u n="1174" who="S0253">yeah it's I think it's on a bit more</u>
<u n="1175" who="S0274" trans="overlap">and This Week is quite good sometimes with <trunc>tha</trunc> that's Andrew O'Neil I think isn't it? or it's Andrew or was it Andrew Neil?</u>
<u n="1176" who="S0253">was it</u>
<u n="1177" who="S0274">he used to be The Times editor erm</u>
<u n="1178" who="S0253">right okay</u>
<u n="1179" who="S0274">but that's quite good cos they oh Esther McVey was on it the other day oh she does my nut in</u>
<u n="1180" who="S0253">who's Esther McVey?</u>
<u n="1181" who="S0274">she's the MP for Greasby and Frankby and she's the minister of I think is she still the minister for disabilities? <pause dur="short"/> I think she's still the minister for that</u>
<u n="1182" who="S0253">mm</u>
<u n="1183" who="S0274">she used to be a weather weather girl erm her dad and family own the flying school in John er John Lennon Airport</u>
<u n="1184" who="S0253">oh wow</u>
<u n="1185" who="S0274" trans="overlap">running a business basically <trunc>sh</trunc> her position like many of them was bought</u>
<u n="1186" who="S0253">right</u>
<u n="1187" who="S0274" trans="overlap">you know <unclear>mini</unclear> funded her old campaign and stuff like that and she what life experience has she got?</u>
<u n="1188" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1189" who="S0274" trans="overlap">you know she's come from a you know I'm not saying that anybody comes from a well upbringing hasn't got experience to give to the table but it's not and she just irritates me cos she's just that classic sort of like practiced erm sort of script and it's like erm it was she was defending well she wasn't defending the guy who said that you know but just she's oh it annoys me because at the at the grass roots of it all no matter how they say they're all very like Labour and that and Tories are very similar Tories believe in an organic system where you have your rich and your poor and it's oh well get over the <pause dur="short"/> no do you know what I mean? at the end of the day that's the core values of it</u>
<u n="1190" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1191" who="S0274" trans="overlap">and they say I I hate it when people attack people for being a bit like well why can't we do this with a conscience? oh we can't be pragmatic and have a conscience yes you can most of most of if you look at the Tories most of their policies are reactionary austerity measures that's a reaction well oh oh oh we won't spend anything</u>
<u n="1192" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1193" who="S0274">what about I can never say it <trunc>Keyn</trunc> Keynesianism I can never say it what his idea was is that if you</u>
<u n="1194" who="S0253">Keynesian?</u>
<u n="1195" who="S0274">that's it if you if you give people money they'll</u>
<u n="1196" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1197" who="S0274" trans="overlap">flood the market and the economy because people spending that's gonna like getting the coils going again</u>
<u n="1198" who="S0253">well if I look at my my education in A Level was</u>
<u n="1199" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1200" who="S0253">I don't know what <trunc>Keynes</trunc> Keynesian economics is but I know I know how to say it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1201" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but that's it but I mean again but I know</u>
<u n="1202" who="S0253" trans="overlap">isn't Keynesian economics trickle-down economics?</u>
<u n="1203" who="S0274">I think so I think I don't really know but again that's when I'm conscious that I don't have that much <pause dur="short"/> well you you could say it would go two ways can't you? I don't have that great er when it's economics but then if I did would I be corrupted by it?</u>
<u n="1204" who="S0253">yes</u>
<u n="1205" who="S0274">do you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1206" who="S0253">I think you would</u>
<u n="1207" who="S0274">do you know what I mean? so it's cos if you if you're in something <pause dur="short"/> like for example I'm gonna wanna go hopefully get into social services you are bound like your experience had on <pause dur="short"/> placement it there was a lot <unclear/> that didn't like it you were judging people's abilities disabilities by how much money they get do they meet that criteria?</u>
<u n="1208" who="S0253">really?</u>
<u n="1209" who="S0274">yeah that's how it's run <unclear>like that</unclear> it's awful erm <pause dur="short"/> you you can't you can't measure a person's mental health thing though or whatever er</u>
<u n="1210" who="S0253">in economics</u>
<u n="1211" who="S0274">that that's it erm</u>
<u n="1212" who="S0253">but it I think</u>
<u n="1213" who="S0274">but then if you were or</u>
<u n="1214" who="S0253" trans="overlap">but <trunc>i</trunc> but if er if these services erm are increasingly privatised then that well the <vocal desc="laugh"/> in in private systems it has to happen that way doesn't it?</u>
<u n="1215" who="S0274">mm</u>
<u n="1216" who="S0253">cos how else do you do it?</u>
<u n="1217" who="S0274">exactly I mean <pause dur="short"/> there is a lot of goodness that comes that comes out of it like you know to be fair a lot of social <trunc>enter</trunc></u>
<u n="1218" who="S0253">like services</u>
<u n="1219" who="S0274">social enterprise as kind of people raise sort of racking their brains and thinking of what they can do and you know free services are out there you know government does pay for them mostly</u>
<u n="1220" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1221" who="S0274">via the contract but in the same sense this is what makes me well I guess so annoyed and that's why I was watching it like they'll blame immigration and erm they'll blame er oh it's the it's like they got us into like er this mess and you think yeah but then you're letting the likes are Starbucks and big companies get off with major amount of billions of tax and</u>
<u n="1222" who="S0253" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1223" who="S0274" trans="overlap">you're paying how much into the MOD? through all these you know paying how much for a missile? and you know it's</u>
<u n="1224" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1225" who="S0274"><trunc>y</trunc> you you know you're given this tax break oh yes it's twelve grand now or ten grand before you pay tax but then you're thinking yeah but the people who are earning billions are getting that as well</u>
<u n="1226" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I read I read about that it's like</u>
<u n="1227" who="S0274">it's very clever like</u>
<u n="1228" who="S0253" trans="overlap">isn't it isn't it isn't it proportionately so it's like the tax</u>
<u n="1229" who="S0274" trans="overlap">people</u>
<u n="1230" who="S0253" trans="overlap">the tax break for people are earning the lower bracket is nowhere near as good as the tax break for those</u>
<u n="1231" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1232" who="S0253">who are <trunc>ear</trunc> so you</u>
<u n="1233" who="S0274" trans="overlap">but it's very cleverly done</u>
<u n="1234" who="S0253">so so <pause dur="short"/> it it wouldn't it wouldn't it would in a sense there'll be people who are in the lower bracket paying for the tax breaks of those on the higher bracket?</u>
<u n="1235" who="S0274">essentially but because</u>
<u n="1236" who="S0253" trans="overlap">and like they're balancing it off</u>
<u n="1237" who="S0274">cos I mean I'm one of those people now and oh but yeah I've noticed like my <pause dur="short"/> tax that I pay is a lot less</u>
<u n="1238" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1239" who="S0274">but then the way things everyone and oh the cost of living's going up and then you know the way everything is is changing <trunc>y</trunc> you don't people don't think of that they don't think of the <pause dur="short"/> the wider thing they think of the</u>
<u n="1240" who="S0253" trans="overlap">the cost</u>
<u n="1241" who="S0274" trans="overlap">instant don't they? and they go well how much is how much do you wanna spend in Tesco? how much do you spend to like gas and electricity?</u>
<u n="1242" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1243" who="S0274" trans="overlap">those are going up you now</u>
<u n="1244" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1245" who="S0274" trans="overlap">you know it doesn't compare with er so</u>
<u n="1246" who="S0253">one thing that saddened me in sort of <pause dur="short"/> and sort of resonated with me a bit was the other day where it was about <pause dur="short"/> the opportunities for for young people now like job opportunities</u>
<u n="1247" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1248" who="S0253">and I guess I guess the thing is that you can have a you can have a social conscience you know and you try you can you can be someone who who says you know I have a social conscience and things like that <pause dur="short"/> but and I but I hate the way like <pause dur="short"/> you sort of you're kind of forced into you know worrying about your pay and worrying about your pay cheque cos you <trunc>al</trunc> you always have a lifestyle to protect</u>
<u n="1249" who="S0274">yeah true</u>
<u n="1250" who="S0253">you know and I <trunc>thi</trunc> I hate that kind of feeling of like competition and you know I have to compete with like you know I have to <trunc>co</trunc> I have to compete with people to <pause dur="short"/> I dunno to to work and stuff like that and <pause dur="short"/> you know it's like I was thinking about like you know me and my colleague <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> who we both got made redundant at the same time but suddenly we've gone from being colleagues and working together on</u>
<u n="1251" who="S0274" trans="overlap">to essentially yeah</u>
<u n="1252" who="S0253">I mean we both live in the same geographical area we've got the same qualifications we both</u>
<u n="1253" who="S0274" trans="overlap">it's not Battle Royale</u>
<u n="1254" who="S0253">it basically is</u>
<u n="1255" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1256" who="S0253">it's dog eat dog and we're not friends anymore but it's but like I mean I'm not saying I think like that and I'm not I'm not that cynical</u>
<u n="1257" who="S0274" trans="overlap">no no I know</u>
<u n="1258" who="S0253" trans="overlap">but I hate the fact that part of me is worried about that and part of me</u>
<u n="1259" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1260" who="S0253" trans="overlap">is thinking of god like well you know if that's just one person that I know firsthand</u>
<u n="1261" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="1262" who="S0253">who's in the same boat as me then what is there to say there's not maybe maybe er and probably <pause dur="short"/> there's there's hundreds of us you know all vying for the same thing it's really scary</u>
<u n="1263" who="S0274">forget about them</u>
<u n="1264" who="S0253">forget about her</u>
<u n="1265" who="S0274">hey</u>
<u n="1266" who="S0253">thanks <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1267" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/> that's the idea just I think that's one thing where I when I'm applying for this I I've I've</u>
<u n="1268" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I don't think of about it</u>
<u n="1269" who="S0274">yeah cos I think no you just you're going this is me and and I hate that word selling yourself you're not no you're not you're not selling yourself you're just this is me this is the ability I've <trunc>ha</trunc></u>
<u n="1270" who="S0253" trans="overlap">I <trunc>thi</trunc></u>
<u n="1271" who="S0274" trans="overlap">do I fit your team do I fit with your mind-set?</u>
<u n="1272" who="S0253">I think yeah I think that's <trunc>def</trunc> that's a really it's it it goes without saying but I mean that's a really <pause dur="short"/> like if you were telling someone how to go about applying for jobs I think that's the best way to do it don't think of don't think of your application in relation to other people's I mean obviously you <trunc>shou</trunc> people will say oh try and try and make yourself stand out from</u>
<u n="1273" who="S0274" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="1274" who="S0253" trans="overlap">the crowd <pause dur="short"/> but <pause dur="short"/> it if you present the things as they are <pause dur="short"/> you know and you you as long as if you fill your if you fill your applications with sort of what's the word? you know just recycled</u>
<u n="1275" who="S0274">yeah</u>
<u n="1276" who="S0253">team player and all that stuff then you're not gonna get anywhere and I think if you just state things as they are</u>
<u n="1277" who="S0274" trans="overlap">they want they want at the end of the day if you're looking through a thousand applications you wanna read a story don't you?</u>
<u n="1278" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1279" who="S0274">do you know what I mean? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1280" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="1281" who="S0274">you know you don't wanna you're gonna be getting the same thing about I did this and then I did this and I did this but it's like well actually from this experience I learnt this and that that went on to you know what I mean?</u>
<u n="1282" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1283" who="S0274">oh I just not I went to Africa and built huts you know and that's great but you know what I mean? but actually like I don't like yourself I I've worked in an English language school for three years</u>
<u n="1284" who="S0253">I think I think I'd much rather a candidate who who went to Africa</u>
<u n="1285" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1286" who="S0253"><vocal desc="laugh"/> rather than just someone who'd like <trunc>c</trunc> sort of lazily worked in a school</u>
<u n="1287" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1288" who="S0253">I think that's a much better candidate from me but er but yeah I know what you mean it's erm</u>
<u n="1289" who="S0274">I mean obviously mine's probably similar to yours in the sense that even though it's totally the thing is I've got to make sure I've I know current legislation and current topics of you know change and kind of stuff stuff like that</u>
<u n="1290" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1291" who="S0274" trans="overlap">but once you've got past that it's okay well put that down now you've seen that <pause dur="short"/> this is my experience and this is how it it's me and me personally I'm a</u>
<u n="1292" who="S0253">yeah</u>
<u n="1293" who="S0274">yeah so</u>
<u n="1294" who="S0253">yeah I think I think I think that's what I'm trying to do with the applications I'm writing at the moment but another got another few days to write them I'm just like <pause dur="short"/> I'm trying to <pause dur="short"/> I'm trying not to overthink them and trying not to think too much about oh you know I'm I'm I'm writing them properly I'm not like just kind of</u>
<u n="1295" who="S0274" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1296" who="S0253">you know drawing pictures on the page for something like that but</u>
<u n="1297" who="S0274"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1298" who="S0253">but erm you know just trying to be a bit more free and just think okay well you know <pause dur="short"/> it's obvious that you know all this stuff's obvious</u>
<u n="1299" who="S0274" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="1300" who="S0253">trying trying <trunc>t</trunc> I guess it's trying to like I'll stop this I guess</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
