<text id="SRND">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:13:11</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-10-13</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0428 S0432</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Cambridge University Press – Printing House</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Holidays, time off, Valencia, </topics>
		<activity>Holiday Time</activity>
		<conv_type>discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T17</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0428">
				<exactage>27</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Aylesbury, Buckinghamshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Eastern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>1 year 8 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Language Research Co-ordinator</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified; Italian -- level unspecified; French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0432">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>White British</nat>
				<birthplace>Lincoln</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>East Midlands/ East Anglia</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Gamlingay, Cambridgeshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>10 months</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Language Research Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>Spanish -- level unspecified; Chinese -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="2" who="S0432">erm</u>
<u n="3" who="S0428">where did you go on holiday?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0432"><vocal desc="laugh"/> Lanzarote</u>
<u n="5" who="S0428">did you enjoy it?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0432" trans="overlap">erm yeah really good it was so relaxing I can't remember oh it was <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0428">never heard of that</u>
<u n="8" who="S0432" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I I don't know what it means <pause dur="short"/> do you? no? it's just it was really nice I <trunc>d</trunc> I wasn't sure if the beaches were gonna be black sand cos a lot of the erm beaches in Lanzarote and The Canary Islands are <trunc>volcan</trunc> volcano islands aren't they or something</u>
<u n="9" who="S0428">yeah volcanic</u>
<u n="10" who="S0432">volcanic yeah so some of the beaches are black but</u>
<u n="11" who="S0428">was the one was yours black?</u>
<u n="12" who="S0432">no it was normal I was like what's everyone talking about?</u>
<u n="13" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low">laugh</u>
<u n="14" who="S0428">I really want to go to The Canary Islands</u>
<u n="15" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0428">I'm always shocked when you look at a map to see where they are in my head they're just off Spain but actually they're much closer to Africa</u>
<u n="17" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/> yeah that's what I think as well and then <pause dur="short"/> cos I don't think when you're on a plane you have no sense of how far you go I mean obviously you know how long you're on there for and it was four hours which is quite long but I didn't <trunc>exp</trunc> when they explained <trunc>th</trunc>this erm skin care advisers <trunc>they</trunc>they're like okay even if you've been to Lanzarote before you still need to know the know about the climate here cos we're so close to Africa and you're like what</u>
<u n="18" who="S0428">really? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="19" who="S0432" trans="overlap">are we? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0428">oh so do you have to be really careful with sun cream there?</u>
<u n="21" who="S0432">yeah cos the is it UV?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="23" who="S0432">erm something to do with the UV rays are</u>
<u n="24" who="UNKMULTI" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">stronger</u>
<u n="25" who="S0432">than like <pause dur="short"/> any like the just Spain or somewhere</u>
<u n="26" who="S0428">that's mental</u>
<u n="27" who="S0432" trans="overlap">so you have to and like the cos of the winds as well it's really windy so you don't feel I mean the wind is not really hot it's not really cold either but I guess you don't feel the heat as much</u>
<u n="28" who="S0428">I guess maybe because <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="29" who="S0432">yeah and she said about prickly heat as well because of sweat</u>
<u n="30" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh my mum gets that</u>
<u n="31" who="S0432">cos you're yeah I got it not this time but the time I went before <pause dur="short"/> erm I got it like across here and it's something to do with like sun cream blocking your pores and you're <trunc>s</trunc> and you're sweating or I don't know</u>
<u n="32" who="S0428">oh nice</u>
<u n="33" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="34" who="S0432">I don't know it's pretty gross <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="35" who="S0428">yeah I'd like to go</u>
<u n="36" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah I'd recommend it my two of my friends have been to Cape Verde that's a bit I think that's a bit further south</u>
<u n="37" who="S0428">is that the Portuguese one? I think</u>
<u n="38" who="S0432" trans="overlap">is that yeah is that not part of The Canary Islands? I would get I don't know I get really confused</u>
<u n="39" who="S0428">I have no idea maybe</u>
<u n="40" who="S0432">and they said that's really nice and there's actually like a an official mirage is that what it is? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0428">what does that mean?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0432">it's you know if you're like in the desert and you're you're a bit like disillusioned with what's going on cos you're really hot you're thirsty you like you it's almost like hallucinating</u>
<u n="43" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="44" who="S0432">but apparently there is actually everybody sees the same thing I don't I don't really get it</u>
<u n="45" who="S0428" trans="overlap">wow I'm gonna have to look at that on the internet</u>
<u n="46" who="S0432">yeah like she was my friend was like you have to go and see this they it's like a erm tour like a trip</u>
<u n="47" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="48" who="S0432">they actually take people on a trip to go see it</u>
<u n="49" who="S0428">that's crazy</u>
<u n="50" who="S0432" trans="overlap">I don't know if it's like <pause dur="short"/> the light and the heat you know the heat waves that you can see</u>
<u n="51" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/> like when you're <trunc>on</trunc> in a car and sometimes when you're going along even it's a really hot day and when you look at the road and it's like</u>
<u n="52" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah it looks almost wet doesn't it?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0428">yeah and you're like woah<vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="54" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="55" who="S0428">I remember the first time I saw that and I was like what's that?</u>
<u n="56" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="long"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah it's strange isn't it? <trunc>I</trunc> it's weird that you can see it</u>
<u n="57" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="58" who="S0432">but yeah <trunc>it's</trunc> I I presume it's something to do with that and things behind</u>
<u n="59" who="S0428">yeah the colours maybe</u>
<u n="60" who="S0432" trans="overlap">like what yeah yeah</u>
<u n="61" who="S0428">I'm not a scientist</u>
<u n="62" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="63" who="S0432" trans="overlap">no no idea she might just be joking</u>
<u n="64" who="S0428">yeah sounds so lovely like so relaxing though</u>
<u n="65" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> it does it is it's really nice but you're going to have a great time in Valencia or Madrid?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0428" trans="overlap">I am so excited</u>
<u n="67" who="S0432">do you how long were you in each place for?</u>
<u n="68" who="S0428">so on next Wednesday in <trunc>th</trunc> in the evening I arrive in Madrid really late at eleven o'clock but my friend is working he does he gives guided food tours of Madrid</u>
<u n="69" who="S0432" trans="overlap">okay <pause dur="short"/> yeah food tours? oh wow</u>
<u n="70" who="S0428">yeah that's his job</u>
<u n="71" who="S0432">I'd love to go on one of those</u>
<u n="72" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="73" who="S0428">yeah I know hopefully I might go on one of his afternoon ones the next day</u>
<u n="74" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="75" who="S0428">erm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0432">so this is after our presentations?</u>
<u n="77" who="S0428" trans="overlap">so after our presentation I'll go home and get my suitcase get go to the airport fly to Madrid he'll pick me up well I'll meet him in town</u>
<u n="78" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0428">and I'm staying at his house and then I have one whole day <trunc>so</trunc> so I have the whole of the Thursday in Madrid and I've got another friend erm called <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> who lives there but last time I was in Madrid I set my two friends up but then it kind of ended</u>
<u n="80" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0428">so now I have to see them separately</u>
<u n="82" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="83" who="S0432">oh no</u>
<u n="84" who="S0428">and I don't want to tell the other one really cos they don't see each other and it was just a bit awkward and everything</u>
<u n="85" who="S0432">they don't talk anymore</u>
<u n="86" who="S0428">no</u>
<u n="87" who="S0432">oh</u>
<u n="88" who="S0428">but I want to see them both they're both like she's my she's my friend from Valencia and her job moved to Madrid</u>
<u n="89" who="S0432">okay</u>
<u n="90" who="S0428">and then he's we went to uni together we did erasmus together me and the other guy</u>
<u n="91" who="S0432">ah okay</u>
<u n="92" who="S0428">yeah and then and then on Friday at about lunchtime I'll catch the AVE down to Valencia</u>
<u n="93" who="S0432">ah yeah</u>
<u n="94" who="S0428">which is like only an hour and a half it's so speedy <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="95" who="S0432" trans="overlap">I can't I can't believe how quick it is <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="96" who="S0428">I know and then I'll have Friday evening it's my friend's cafe's fifth birthday</u>
<u n="97" who="S0432" trans="overlap">ah that's so exciting</u>
<u n="98" who="S0428">and then Saturday Sunday Monday Tuesday and then I fly back at about fly back really late on Tuesday evening and so I'll be back here for Wednesday</u>
<u n="99" who="S0432">oh really?</u>
<u n="100" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0432" trans="overlap">do you not want the day off on Wednesday?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0428">erm because I'm going to away at the end of November as well I want to keep my days</u>
<u n="103" who="S0432">oh yeah where are you going at the end of November?</u>
<u n="104" who="S0428">I'm not sure we were going to go to Iceland</u>
<u n="105" who="S0432">oh yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0428">but it's <trunc>s</trunc> the flights are really expensive and I think we can get cheaper flights at a different time of year maybe it's too late but there are really cheap flights to Sweden erm</u>
<u n="107" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="long"/> oh that would be nice why don't you stay in that erm <pause dur="short"/> see if you can stay in that van the campervan or something you showed me the fire truck?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah yeah that's in Norway yeah</u>
<u n="109" who="S0432" trans="overlap">is that Norway? yeah</u>
<u n="110" who="S0428">then I I could go yeah</u>
<u n="111" who="S0432">I'd love to I really should like look into go there cos that was amazing</u>
<u n="112" who="S0428" trans="overlap">it's amazing it's so cute yeah I'll send you the details</u>
<u n="113" who="S0432">yeah I think have you shown?</u>
<u n="114" who="S0428" trans="overlap">did I?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0432">I don't know if you just showed me a picture actually</u>
<u n="116" who="S0428">and then but I think I've still got quite a bit of holiday and I might just take off like a week before Christmas or something</u>
<u n="117" who="S0432">mm I was I don't know if we're allowed to like how cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> already got because it's Christmas on the Friday</u>
<u n="118" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="S0432">so Christmas Eve is Thursday so we have to be in the office Monday Tuesday Wednesday</u>
<u n="120" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="121" who="S0432">but how <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s already got those three days off are we allowed to book it as well?</u>
<u n="122" who="S0428">I think so</u>
<u n="123" who="S0432">because I've still got four and a half days left plus the day in lieu from the Festival of Ideas</u>
<u n="124" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0432">so that's still like a full week plus half a day so I don't know I don't know whether to take three of them for those three</u>
<u n="126" who="S0428">I think yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0432">I mean I don't really think I'm gonna take a full week off between now and Christmas</u>
<u n="128" who="S0428">yeah it's crazy cos I was like <vocal desc="gasp"/> I haven't got much holiday and now <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="129" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah that's what I thought I've saved them and now I've got loads <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's why I took the week off for Lanzarote just cos</u>
<u n="130" who="S0428">and when you're new you don't want to take loads of holiday</u>
<u n="131" who="S0432">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> eh and how many days have you got left?</u>
<u n="132" who="S0428">I can't remember I have to look when I get back</u>
<u n="133" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0428">I think <pause dur="short"/> I think I've got like well including this trip so I haven't booked my November trip I think I've still got like nine days</u>
<u n="135" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh really?</u>
<u n="136" who="S0428">plus one in lieu maybe it's like two weeks left</u>
<u n="137" who="S0432">wow</u>
<u n="138" who="S0428">which is loads like <trunc>d</trunc> like are there ten days Christmas?</u>
<u n="139" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="140" who="S0432">so you so you even though you haven't booked a trip for the end of November have you booked days off?</u>
<u n="141" who="S0428">no but I'm going to book them probably my friend just confirmed erm like that he's like booked his holiday</u>
<u n="142" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0428">and that he's like his company is more strict so</u>
<u n="144" who="S0432">oh</u>
<u n="145" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="146" who="S0432">yeah so I could take three then and then my boyfriend's brother was on about fireworks' night</u>
<u n="147" who="S0428" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="148" who="S0432">and he said about going over to theirs in <anon type="place"/> so I don't know whether if just <unclear>out?</unclear>  just take the day after off</u>
<u n="149" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="150" who="S0432" trans="overlap">the day off afterwards if it's not a weekend or something <trunc>jus</trunc> just to have it off</u>
<u n="151" who="S0428">yeah I was thinking of just taking some Mondays</u>
<u n="152" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="153" who="S0428">just having some three day weekends and doing some nice stuff I want to go to Bristol to see my friend and that would be lovely to just</u>
<u n="154" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah just that one extra day</u>
<u n="155" who="S0428">yeah it makes a really big difference we could just have like four day weekends until Christmas</u>
<u n="156" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0432" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've had last week was a four day week cos I had the Monday off</u>
<u n="158" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0432">this week I've got the Friday off</u>
<u n="160" who="S0428">oh because of the wedding oh the hen do</u>
<u n="161" who="S0432" trans="overlap">hen do <pause dur="short"/> then the week after I've taken the Monday so I've got another four day week well I won't know what's hit me when I come back for five days <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="162" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> come back for yeah</u>
<u n="163" who="S0432" trans="overlap">it's really nice though isn't it? I think <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said that didn't she?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0428">yeah</u>
<u n="165" who="S0432">just never to <trunc>take</trunc> don't take full week off just have loads of four day weeks</u>
<u n="166" who="S0428">I'm really excited about going on holiday I really need <trunc>t</trunc> a break I think</u>
<u n="167" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh are you just going to relax when you're in Valencia?</u>
<u n="168" who="S0428">yeah just</u>
<u n="169" who="S0432">oh</u>
<u n="170" who="S0428">I might go out on the cos my friend has an orange farm so I want to go out but he's working in some field like far away so I'm not sure if this time's gonna work</u>
<u n="171" who="S0432" trans="overlap">ah you said yeah <pause dur="long"/> mm</u>
<u n="172" who="S0428">but</u>
<u n="173" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh if you do get well get lots of photos anyway so I can see</u>
<u n="174" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> yesterday I was speaking to my friend erm who's a pilot and I was like I'm coming to Valencia and he was like I'm in a I'm in a plane right now and he sent me some photos from the plane</u>
<u n="176" who="S0432">oh really <pause dur="long"/> oh god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0428">and I was like careful <vocal desc="laugh"/> like are you allowed to be on Whatsapp and like drive a plane at the same time</u>
<u n="178" who="S0432" trans="overlap">concentrate on the sky <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="179" who="S0428">yeah and so he <vocal desc="laugh"/> he was sending me and I was like that doesn't look like Valencia and he was like no it's not</u>
<u n="180" who="S0432" trans="overlap">what from above?</u>
<u n="181" who="S0428">yeah like out the window</u>
<u n="182" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh wow</u>
<u n="183" who="S0428">but it was <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0432">ah</u>
<u n="185" who="S0428">so yeah I was like <vocal desc="misc"/> don't think that's Valencia</u>
<u n="186" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="187" who="S0432"></u>
<u n="188" who="S0428">but I'm so <trunc>excite</trunc> I'm just so excited to see Valencia again I love it</u>
<u n="189" who="S0432" trans="overlap">I'm so gonna have to go cos I'm gonna be so jealous when you get back and start talking about it I'm like shh no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="190" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0428"><vocal desc="laugh"/> shh yeah it's such an amazing city</u>
<u n="192" who="S0432" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="193" who="S0428">I think one day I'll live there again I love it so much</u>
<u n="194" who="S0432">yeah I would I won't like ever rule it out living there cos yeah it's really nice</u>
<u n="195" who="S0428" trans="overlap">no <pause dur="short"/> yeah it's just to me it's the perfect city</u>
<u n="196" who="S0432">mm</u>
<u n="197" who="S0428">it's like the right size you've got the mountains the sea the weather the language the culture</u>
<u n="198" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="199" who="S0428">there's</u>
<u n="200" who="S0432">even like it's it's even pretty isn't it? like <trunc>regard</trunc> like the old river</u>
<u n="201" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah it's unique there there there can't be another city in the world that has the river that like the way Valencia has the river</u>
<u n="202" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> really likes it as well cos he said cos sometimes when you go to Spain it's a lot of it's like under construction and cos they obviously take forever to build anything cos of the summer <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="203" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="204" who="S0432">but he said it was just so pretty and he didn't think he was in Spain <trunc>he</trunc> I don't know he was just like it feels really nice and</u>
<u n="205" who="S0428">to live it's just the perfect place</u>
<u n="206" who="S0432" trans="overlap">cos it's quite compact as well isn't it? that it feels but it's busy enough to feel like you're in a city</u>
<u n="207" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and there's so much going on that you can you can go to what I love about Valencia is you can be like I want this kind of night I want to go to this kind of thing and you can go to the different areas</u>
<u n="208" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah mm the different squares</u>
<u n="209" who="S0428">yeah so you can say like</u>
<u n="210" who="S0432" trans="overlap">and like real like areas of it and I don't know <unclear/> districts or something I don't know what they're called <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0428" trans="overlap">yeah like the yeah so you can have like a like a night out in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="212" who="S0432">yeah</u>
<u n="213" who="S0428">but then you can have you go to the centre and then</u>
<u n="214" who="S0432" trans="overlap">yeah oh it's so nice</u>
<u n="215" who="S0428">mm yeah lovely</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
