<text id="SRNT">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:42:04</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-08-18</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0144 S0281</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Speaker's house, Brighton</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Colleagues</relationships>
		<topics>Scottish referendum, job interview, colleague, my daughter, present situation</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about recent news and present personal situation.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling, making arrangements </conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0144">
				<exactage>36</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>London</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Norwich, Norfolk</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>8</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Lecturer</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0281">
				<exactage>65</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Brighton</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city></hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>30</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0281">so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> how are you doing?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm alright</u>
<u n="3" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="4" who="S0281">what's so funny?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0144">huh? er nothing <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah so you were saying about the Scotland thing</u>
<u n="6" who="S0281">well yeah I mean it's gonna be really big isn't it? just wondering if everybody er you know people had thought about the ramifications of the yes</u>
<u n="7" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="8" who="S0281">I mean presumably if if they say no</u>
<u n="9" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="10" who="S0281">then erm there will be benefits you know and all the top politicians have said they're going to get more regional powers and you know all the rest of it</u>
<u n="11" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="12" who="S0281">but if they say no then er I don't know what do you think?</u>
<u n="13" who="S0144">er well like I think they're gonna say no that's what everything's indicating</u>
<u n="14" who="S0281">you reckon?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="16" who="S0281">I dunno</u>
<u n="17" who="S0144">cos</u>
<u n="18" who="S0281">I mean there's a poll the other day said they're the yes vote was fifty-two percent to fifty or</u>
<u n="19" who="S0144">oh really?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="21" who="S0144">oh okay</u>
<u n="22" who="S0281">but no to forty-eight I think one poll said they were four points ahead</u>
<u n="23" who="S0144">uh okay erm well</u>
<u n="24" who="S0281">in fact today I saw er another report I think it was in The Guardian that erm it really is more split down the middle and that the way it's going to be be decided is gonna be on the the don't knows people how haven't actually</u>
<u n="25" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="26" who="S0281">made up their mind</u>
<u n="27" who="S0144">yeah cos that's</u>
<u n="28" who="S0281">it's that close</u>
<u n="29" who="S0144">that's about six percent isn't it or something? don't know yeah yeah like don't think I've not don't know how interested I am in it really cos I don't know it's not gonna affect me and</u>
<u n="30" who="S0281">well it is</u>
<u n="31" who="S0144">is it?</u>
<u n="32" who="S0281">well yeah</u>
<u n="33" who="S0144">how?</u>
<u n="34" who="S0281">well if Scotland leave right then erm if you should ever want to go to Scotland <vocal desc="laugh"/> I don't know if you ever would do but I mean would you need a passport to get in?</u>
<u n="35" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="36" who="S0281">erm would you need er some money to er set their their own currency to get there</u>
<u n="37" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="38" who="S0281">erm on a on a national level er both economies are gonna be er affected by it</u>
<u n="39" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="40" who="S0281">I mean already er the financial institutions er said they're gonna pull out er from Scotland</u>
<u n="41" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="42" who="S0281">erm and erm I mean <trunc>al</trunc>also in terms of erm the the British logo I mean what's Britishness gonna mean any more?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0144">mm that's true yeah I I think Scotland are <trunc>go</trunc> the ones that are gonna suffer eventually I I I think I think they've got it cushty at the moment they way they've got the deals with London I mean free education at university education you know they really are they gonna be able to keep that? I dunno erm but I was thinking I I would I was looking at the exchange rate with the pound cos the pound's <trunc>dep</trunc> devalued as well because of all this</u>
<u n="44" who="S0281">really?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0144">erm because of the <trunc>unc</trunc>uncertainty of it</u>
<u n="46" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="47" who="S0144">and I was thinking I wish I'd sent a load of money back <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos if if they er if they say no then the value of the pound is gonna shoot up again isn't it?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0281">erm</u>
<u n="49" who="S0144">I reckon so it would have been a good time to change some money</u>
<u n="50" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I don't know does does this have to be on to be for it to be recording?</u>
<u n="51" who="S0144">eh</u>
<u n="52" who="S0281">because have we been talking just four minutes?</u>
<u n="53" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0281">oh okay</u>
<u n="55" who="S0144">yeah I don't think it has to be on I mean my one switches off when it's still recording and even even if someone else erm if I get a message or something comes through</u>
<u n="56" who="S0281">yeah doesn't affect it</u>
<u n="57" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah it still it still gets I don't know what your phone does just check it at the end I suppose</u>
<u n="58" who="S0281">yeah I suppose so</u>
<u n="59" who="S0144">should be alright it's still going</u>
<u n="60" who="S0281">yeah okay right</u>
<u n="61" who="S0144">yeah so what how soon are they gonna find out the results do you know?</u>
<u n="62" who="S0281">I don't know that's one thing that I I haven't heard but erm there's I think there's gonna be a a bit of a transition period I mean if they do say yes</u>
<u n="63" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0281">I mean if that that's gonna be huge <unclear>man</unclear></u>
<u n="65" who="S0144">mm yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0281">I think it's gonna affect us I actually haven't thought it through to be honest but er I think it's gonna affect us all more than you said ah I don't care</u>
<u n="67" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0281">it wont affect me but I I think it will cos it'll affect the the I was gonna say British economy but we're</u>
<u n="69" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="70" who="S0281">I mean the English economy</u>
<u n="71" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="72" who="S0281">erm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="74" who="S0281">but in if you're a Scot er today I mean the I suppose this was coming from the no camp</u>
<u n="75" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="76" who="S0281">that erm er the National Health Service that that would be effected</u>
<u n="77" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="78" who="S0281">erm and er there's something else I cant remember that be have a negative effect on it</u>
<u n="79" who="S0144">yeah I mean would they still have the NHS?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0281">well presumably no</u>
<u n="81" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah so I don't know I mean what does <trunc>independ</trunc> is independence like an absolute clean break or can they still transfer some of the systems across? I don't know</u>
<u n="82" who="S0281">well yeah it it is as it says independence for Scotland so</u>
<u n="83" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0281">they would have to presumably apply for membership of the EU</u>
<u n="85" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0281">which isn't I mean it I should imagine that they would</u>
<u n="87" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="88" who="S0281">get accepted but erm there are other countries with er issues you know like Spain</u>
<u n="89" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="90" who="S0281">er they've got a separatist movement with</u>
<u n="91" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="92" who="S0281">Basques</u>
<u n="93" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0281">there's Belgium</u>
<u n="95" who="S0144">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="96" who="S0281">well erm where does this stop?</u>
<u n="97" who="S0144">yeah but I think it's a good thing breaking down rather than becoming one global super state</u>
<u n="98" who="S0281">well</u>
<u n="99" who="S0144">I I prefer it go in that direction than the other direction</u>
<u n="100" who="S0281">I I tend to think the opposite point of view really</u>
<u n="101" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah?</u>
<u n="102" who="S0281">yeah because I'm I mean idealistically</u>
<u n="103" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="104" who="S0281">I think we should be breaking down borders and barriers instead of erecting them</u>
<u n="105" who="S0144">yeah idealistically yeah but I mean what I worry about is if you take away the <unclear>band</unclear> then you're gonna have one government for for everyone</u>
<u n="106" who="S0281"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="107" who="S0144">which</u>
<u n="108" who="S0281">ah well that that's never gonna happen is it?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0144">erm I don't know I don't know</u>
<u n="110" who="S0281">well how how would it happen?</u>
<u n="111" who="S0144">mm well first of all you'd have EU and then like an Asian kind of union and North America union which they're kind of getting into place already and that would have one kind of level above that as well I dunno</u>
<u n="112" who="S0281">yeah I'll have to look into the</u>
<u n="113" who="S0144" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0281">crystal ball about that but</u>
<u n="115" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="116" who="S0281">whenever that comes around I wont be here to see it</u>
<u n="117" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but then yeah Scotland as well would they lose they'd have to build all these trade agreements wouldn't they with the countries as well</u>
<u n="118" who="S0281">but</u>
<u n="119" who="S0144">but they wouldn't have the UK trade agreements with China and they'd have to presumably set up all their own import export agreements with <vocal desc="laugh"/> all these different countries</u>
<u n="120" who="S0281" trans="overlap">well presumably yeah any international agreements with the UK</u>
<u n="121" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0281">would then be presumably invalid for Scotland</u>
<u n="123" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="124" who="S0281">but there again would it still be valid for the UK?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0281">because the UK would no</u>
<u n="127" who="S0144">was no longer <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="128" who="S0281">wouldn't be the same as before</u>
<u n="129" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="130" who="S0281">I mean there are you know</u>
<u n="131" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="132" who="S0281">the Jimmy Cliff song</u>
<u n="133" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0281"><shift new="singing"/> there are more questions than answers <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="135" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="136" who="S0144">yeah I gah I dunno I haven't really I haven't really looked into it really</u>
<u n="137" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="138" who="S0144">I've always thought oh they'll just vote no <unclear/></u>
<u n="139" who="S0281">no the two Scots we know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> you know they're on opposite sides</u>
<u n="140" who="S0144">are they? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="141" who="S0281">mm you don't know them?</u>
<u n="142" who="S0144">no</u>
<u n="143" who="S0281"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is vehemently er on the no side</u>
<u n="144" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="145" who="S0281">he thinks it's gonna be an absolute disaster</u>
<u n="146" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="147" who="S0281">if they vote yes and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> er I haven't er er spoken to her about it but from what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> told me he he said that she's strongly for it</u>
<u n="148" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="149" who="S0281">you know</u>
<u n="150" who="S0144">mm who is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>? I don't know</u>
<u n="151" who="S0281">erm she's got very strange erm surname <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> or something she's a very tall thin lady</u>
<u n="152" who="S0144">where does she work?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0281">oh at at the university she's er erm she's er the the er erm I've forgotten the er the the title now erm but she's erm helping one of my students with his er <trunc>th</trunc> doctorate well it's not a doctorate yet but his er dissertation</u>
<u n="154" who="S0144">oh okay</u>
<u n="155" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="156" who="S0144">mm yeah I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at <anon type="place"/> as well he's <unclear/></u>
<u n="157" who="S0281" trans="overlap">he er he's for it</u>
<u n="158" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="159" who="S0281">he I spoke to him the other night</u>
<u n="160" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="161" who="S0281">and he said</u>
<u n="162" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well he's from the Highlands isn't he? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="163" who="S0281">oh right okay</u>
<u n="164" who="S0144">think he's from Inverness or <unclear/></u>
<u n="165" who="S0281">so and he said he when he was back there he said you know the the gut reaction of the most of the people he spoke to were he said there's no doubt it's gonna be a yes</u>
<u n="166" who="S0144">really?</u>
<u n="167" who="S0281">yeah that's what he said</u>
<u n="168" who="S0144">yeah I think maybe it's people round Edinburgh that are the kind of nos <unclear/></u>
<u n="169" who="S0281">it could be regional I've seen regional maps</u>
<u n="170" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="171" who="S0281">you know with the blue and red</u>
<u n="172" who="S0144">I guess yeah when you get start getting to the Highlands and can see all them voting yes</u>
<u n="173" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="174" who="S0144">Glasgow maybe as well I dunno I dunno all speculation on my behalf don't <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="176" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> are you gonna go down this Sunday? for music or?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0281">no no I'll I'll be back on my way back home on the train</u>
<u n="178" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0281">so and I've gotta get up early Monday morning</u>
<u n="180" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="181" who="S0281">er</u>
<u n="182" who="S0144">this is the problem <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0281">gotta sort out this visa business</u>
<u n="184" who="S0144">yeah yeah well I think I dunno I don't think Sundays are gonna be the same as last year anyway cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said he's not going any more</u>
<u n="185" who="S0281">really?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="187" who="S0281">oh that's a shame</u>
<u n="188" who="S0144">cos he's got seven lessons on a Monday</u>
<u n="189" who="S0281">really? seven?</u>
<u n="190" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0281">wow</u>
<u n="192" who="S0144">so that's why he wasn't there for the planning</u>
<u n="193" who="S0281">oh that's a shame cos he's a great guitarist</u>
<u n="194" who="S0144">yeah yeah erm</u>
<u n="195" who="S0281">oh dear</u>
<u n="196" who="S0144">well maybe if he can get it planned beforehand he can get down there but he's still gotta get up early and</u>
<u n="197" who="S0281">yeah and do it</u>
<u n="198" who="S0144">and do it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="199" who="S0281">how can you do seven lessons in a day?</u>
<u n="200" who="S0144">mm I don't know how long they are</u>
<u n="201" who="S0281">mm I went for a erm er an interview for er a job the other day and er it was held in a er a coffee bar</u>
<u n="202" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="203" who="S0281">yeah <trunc>wi</trunc> and and the er it was half coffee bar and half office and erm the person er I'd I'd spoken to on the phone said er to come down and talk to her boss</u>
<u n="204" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>be back in a minute</unclear></u>
<u n="205" who="S0281">and erm who turned out to be quite a tasty young lady actually</u>
<u n="206" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0281">and erm she said oh <unclear/> it'd it'd involve er working at a high school</u>
<u n="208" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="209" who="S0281">I said okay she but you'd have to start this Wednesday</u>
<u n="210" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="211" who="S0281">and er it would be three lessons on a Wednesday</u>
<u n="212" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0281">er three forty minute lessons and one on Friday and I said well yeah and the pay wasn't great and er out of that I'd have to get the taxi fare so <trunc>y</trunc></u>
<u n="214" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="215" who="S0281">it's ridiculous you know</u>
<u n="216" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0281">and er I said well what time will you start? and she well you'd have to be there for eight o'clock</u>
<u n="218" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="219" who="S0281">I said <trunc>n</trunc>no no there's no no</u>
<u n="220" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0281">no so but then she said well we're we are in touch with er different businesses would you be interested er doing some kind of er teaching with their staff and I said well yeah and she said erm well can you give us a a sort of demonstration? I said well I can but I mean normally you've got to have some materials</u>
<u n="222" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="223" who="S0281">so she said well we've got some here and it was a conversational about about checking into a hotel</u>
<u n="224" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="225" who="S0281">and er I I did a quick er lesson plan in my head and got them the the two women</u>
<u n="226" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="227" who="S0281">you know the boss and the one I'd been in contact with to role play the roles as a students</u>
<u n="228" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="229" who="S0281">and erm use that as it and well I seemed to go alright it was weird though giving a year since I've done a demo lesson</u>
<u n="230" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah it must be weird how did that erm kindergarten thing go</u>
<u n="231" who="S0281">oh</u>
<u n="232" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="233" who="S0281">absolutely horrendous</u>
<u n="234" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="235" who="S0281">I I should never have done it I mean I only did it out there cos I didn't wanna get it in the neck from the wife you know</u>
<u n="236" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="237" who="S0281">oh you know you're not trying to find work so only I knew I mean they're they're two year olds right and erm</u>
<u n="238" who="S0144">oh</u>
<u n="239" who="S0281">I went there and they're sitting on their stools in the front there and erm the the woman erm was telling me how it's gonna work you know show on the use this board and use this and this here's the book and this is what the object of the lesson is that you know say hello and my name is and erm oh oh there's one girl had a tantrum went off</u>
<u n="240" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0281">hid in a tent so then there were five</u>
<u n="242" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="243" who="S0281">er one one little kid wouldn't say anything he refused to you know I I was doing my level best to try and you know enthusiastic and <unclear/></u>
<u n="244" who="S0144">er</u>
<u n="245" who="S0281">oh it was</u>
<u n="246" who="S0144">will they</u>
<u n="247" who="S0281">I kept looking at my watch you know and it seemed like the time was going backwards</u>
<u n="248" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="249" who="S0281">and ah</u>
<u n="250" who="S0144">ah man though though it was good though it was only what six of them?</u>
<u n="251" who="S0281">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="252" who="S0144">you thought there was gonna be like forty or something</u>
<u n="253" who="S0281">oh no no no</u>
<u n="254" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0281">ah I said I I knew er it was just a few minutes into the lesson it was gonna be a farce</u>
<u n="256" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="257" who="S0281">ah</u>
<u n="258" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you wont be doing that again then?</u>
<u n="259" who="S0281">no no no I I should have I should have put my foot down from the start</u>
<u n="260" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0281">and said no but I was just trying trying to avoid an argument you know?</u>
<u n="262" who="S0144">yeah well it's difficult when you're trying to keep all your options open <unclear>isn't it</unclear> so</u>
<u n="263" who="S0281" trans="overlap">yeah well</u>
<u n="264" who="S0144"><unclear/></u>
<u n="265" who="S0281">I thought maybe you know optimistically it might be alright</u>
<u n="266" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="267" who="S0281">if all the kids were cos I've I've taught kids before but</u>
<u n="268" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="269" who="S0281">but not that level you know it's too you know</u>
<u n="270" who="S0144">well it's a bit of a change isn't it from what you've been doing really? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="271" who="S0281">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0144">well it's a completely different job really isn't it? it's not you you call it teaching but it's not it's not really under the same umbrella is it? its more entertaining I suppose</u>
<u n="273" who="S0281">well I mean I I I just I just shouldn't never have happened</u>
<u n="274" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="275" who="S0281">but yeah several different options coming up you know</u>
<u n="276" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="277" who="S0281">see what happens</u>
<u n="278" who="S0144">yeah yeah did you get to speak to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that night down in the er café?</u>
<u n="279" who="S0281">yeah yeah we were speaking you know a little bit</u>
<u n="280" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="281" who="S0281">telling her all my woes and so on</u>
<u n="282" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0281">but people don't really wanna hear about that you know they <unclear/> get troubles on their own but always thought that erm you know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is er the one people go to with their troubles you know <trunc>ma</trunc>maybe she's fed up with the role but erm but I I you know went to er yoga class which is last night</u>
<u n="284" who="S0144">oh okay is she still doing that?</u>
<u n="285" who="S0281">yeah well she started again last night after two months</u>
<u n="286" who="S0144">oh okay yeah</u>
<u n="287" who="S0281">and er there are only two of us now instead of three but erm</u>
<u n="288" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah who else was there?</u>
<u n="289" who="S0281">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> from first year office</u>
<u n="290" who="S0144">oh right</u>
<u n="291" who="S0281">and er erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wasn't there</u>
<u n="292" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="293" who="S0281">but erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was telling me that she got plans to expand</u>
<u n="294" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="295" who="S0281">did you hear about that?</u>
<u n="296" who="S0144">yeah I dunno I dunno</u>
<u n="297" who="S0281">what she told me again is is er something that sounds like <unclear>set</unclear> up with the way I had this interview where somebody had got this idea for this coffee bar but it was on here where you live somewhere</u>
<u n="298" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="299" who="S0281">so there's no passing trade</u>
<u n="300" who="S0144">no it's all gonna be from the uni which I think I've told her I think it's she's gonna be on dangerous ground because it's working you know it's not doing a little thing on the side it's actually starting a business on the doorstep of your employee employer</u>
<u n="301" who="S0281">but she wouldn't be she didn't tell me she was actually thinking about starting a business she was <trunc>jus</trunc></u>
<u n="302" who="S0144">well no she's gonna put it through channels so it isn't actually her but she's gonna be doing classes</u>
<u n="303" who="S0281">well she was talking to me about the possibility of erm <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> taking on the coffee bar part of it</u>
<u n="304" who="S0144">I'd had I lose track of what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s doing</u>
<u n="305" who="S0281">yeah I know I know</u>
<u n="306" who="S0144">and then she just she flits between these ideas</u>
<u n="307" who="S0281">it's amazing I don't I don't know where she gets it from cos she she's got she's been working website</u>
<u n="308" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0281">you know for for yoga</u>
<u n="310" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah I saw that yeah it looks quite good</u>
<u n="311" who="S0281">and</u>
<u n="312" who="S0144">she put a lot of work into it</u>
<u n="313" who="S0281">then there's this idea about er erm the other website erm that she's got together about teaching teachers</u>
<u n="314" who="S0144">well yeah</u>
<u n="315" who="S0281">erm apparently she told me last night somebody contacted her about that I don't she hadn't spoken to her about it for so long that I thought it was <unclear/> she'd almost forgotten about it and then she said this weekend she's she's starting a doctorate</u>
<u n="316" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="317" who="S0281">so I dunno she she's filling her life with all these things I don't know if she's gonna cope with it and</u>
<u n="318" who="S0144">yeah I mean yeah she needs to pick one thing and work on that I think mm yeah she's doing this it's like a one year doctorate thing isn't it? it's not like a PHD it's a</u>
<u n="319" who="S0281">one year one</u>
<u n="320" who="S0144">well it's a what is it? <pause dur="short"/> erm it's like a diploma I I'm not sure what it I'm not sure what it is</u>
<u n="321" who="S0281">no I thought it she told me it was a PHD</u>
<u n="322" who="S0144">but I think it's a one year <trunc>cour</trunc> er I dunno I dunno it's the ed ed doc is it? or some or I dunno ah I don't know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I don't know what she's doing <vocal desc="laugh"/> kinda stopped asking really</u>
<u n="323" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="324" who="S0144">it's different every time I ask <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="325" who="S0281">yeah well the adjective scatterbrain you know</u>
<u n="326" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="327" who="S0281">comes to mind</u>
<u n="328" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="329" who="S0281">well I got her I finally got her to admit that she turns her phone off or the sound down you know</u>
<u n="330" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="331" who="S0281">before she was trying to give me all this bullshit about oh I put it in my bag and it turns itself off</u>
<u n="332" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="333" who="S0281">you know like it's got a mind of its own</u>
<u n="334" who="S0144">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> so how is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="335" who="S0281">ah well again</u>
<u n="336" who="S0144">last time I <unclear>was</unclear> very</u>
<u n="337" who="S0281">very worrying aspect</u>
<u n="338" who="S0144"><unclear>so is</unclear></u>
<u n="339" who="S0281">there's erm well there's that we went back again er on er Sunday I think it was er for a second test and they said you've gotta go back again in another two weeks for another test</u>
<u n="340" who="S0144">right</u>
<u n="341" who="S0281">but I don't know it if she because we talk to her sometimes and like she doesn't answer us</u>
<u n="342" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="343" who="S0281">is it just because she doesn't want to or is it she she doesn't hear?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="345" who="S0281">so it's difficult and then she's got this more or less semi permanent problem with er it's cold or is it pollution?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="347" who="S0281">well that and</u>
<u n="348" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="349" who="S0281">she's she's coughing and then she's developed this erm like COD this compulsive obsessive disorder thing where erm which varies I mean sometimes it's</u>
<u n="350" who="S0144">squinting yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0281">squinting blinking thing</u>
<u n="352" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0281">and when I sort of told her that she's got to stop you know make Daddy happy stop doing this</u>
<u n="354" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="355" who="S0281">and she did and then she's got this other thing about keep pulling her dress up like this</u>
<u n="356" who="S0144">right</u>
<u n="357" who="S0281">to <unclear>my</unclear> shoulder and sometimes going like this</u>
<u n="358" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="359" who="S0281">and you know all combined I think well what</u>
<u n="360" who="S0144">what's going on?</u>
<u n="361" who="S0281">yeah it's a it's a it's a er is it physical? is it psychosomatic? is it er signs of mental problems</u>
<u n="362" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="363" who="S0281">I don't know but</u>
<u n="364" who="S0144"><trunc>may</trunc>maybe it stems from if she has got problems with her ears maybe its knocked her confidence erm</u>
<u n="365" who="S0281">well she'd done fairly well at school</u>
<u n="366" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="367" who="S0281">erm and I asked her the other day <unclear/> I was I was erm do you remember from the coupling series the with the the sock?</u>
<u n="368" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="369" who="S0281">just talking to you</u>
<u n="370" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="371" who="S0281">do you remember that one?</u>
<u n="372" who="S0144" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="373" who="S0281">so I did that with her I I put one of my socks on my hand</u>
<u n="374" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="375" who="S0281">and got her to talk to the sock erm and did a funny voice</u>
<u n="376" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="377" who="S0281">er like erm so she wasn't actually</u>
<u n="378" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0281">talking directly to me</u>
<u n="380" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="381" who="S0281">and asked her you know if she was happy at school cos now she's boarding and she said yeah fine and what are the other girls like? erm felt well they're alright erm except one snores</u>
<u n="382" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="383" who="S0281">and er so I said what about your teacher? is she nice? said yeah erm do you like her? yeah and there were no problems? no so</u>
<u n="384" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="385" who="S0281">I don't know so the I mean for me there are only two sources possible sources of er for the problem one is school or one is home</u>
<u n="386" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="387" who="S0281">and she obviously like me she doesn't want to be a boarder</u>
<u n="388" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="389" who="S0281">it's her mother's decision really <trunc>basic</trunc></u>
<u n="390" who="S0144">do you have like teachers' days and things? like parents' evenings? what <unclear/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0281" trans="overlap">mm well there was a teachers' day the other day wasn't there?</u>
<u n="392" who="S0144">the teachers have give you any any feedback on you know how she is in class and</u>
<u n="393" who="S0281" trans="overlap">oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="394" who="S0144">and that's all positive?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0281">well yeah it's quite good</u>
<u n="396" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="397" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="398" who="S0144">ah it's difficult isn't it I mean I think I was always a worry for my parents you know cos I was always really quiet and I was and I was always popular cos I was always good at sport and you I always I always did well at school but I I always felt I always wanted to be <unclear>a loner</unclear> even though I wasn't <unclear> a loner</unclear> but I always kind of wanted to be so I just kinda sat there in class not saying anything and not answering questions and things and and for me yeah for me that was cos of my upbringing cos I live with weird stuff going on I suppose</u>
<u n="399" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="400" who="S0144">and it was my confidence</u>
<u n="401" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="402" who="S0144">that affected it but I dunno man trying to get inside a kid's head at that age is is pretty hard especially when they're quite guarded</u>
<u n="403" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="404" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="405" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I mean her mother said to her the other day why why didn't you tell me you know you had this problem with your ear? and of course she's she's scared you know</u>
<u n="406" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="407" who="S0281">because a couple of years back three years I think it was we yeah took her up to erm erm main hospital to get her checked and received the fright of her life when they they found this erm blockage and right up the top of the nose and they weren't sure whether it was er something that was at the top of the nose growing up or it was something from the brain coming down</u>
<u n="408" who="S0144">oh my god</u>
<u n="409" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="411" who="S0281">well you can imagine how we felt</u>
<u n="412" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="413" who="S0281">and er they did some tests and erm thankfully I mean we found out it wasn't coming down</u>
<u n="414" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="415" who="S0281">so it was a growth there and they gave us medicine to reduce it and erm but er</u>
<u n="416" who="S0144">so did that really affect her? or it affected you?</u>
<u n="417" who="S0281">well it effected all of us all three of us erm</u>
<u n="418" who="S0144">so maybe you know it could be something</u>
<u n="419" who="S0281" trans="overlap">I mean my wife thinks it's a total waste of time and money</u>
<u n="420" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="421" who="S0281">erm she had an operation</u>
<u n="422" who="S0144">ah</u>
<u n="423" who="S0281">and the medicine seemed to work but now we've got a recurrence of er nose problem</u>
<u n="424" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="425" who="S0281">and chest now</u>
<u n="426" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="427" who="S0281">but I mean how much of that is <unclear>pollution</unclear>?</u>
<u n="428" who="S0144">mm <vocal desc="laugh"/> but I mean chest that could be if she's not I dunno if she's not breathing properly then</u>
<u n="429" who="S0281">constantly coughing</u>
<u n="430" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="431" who="S0281">this cough constant cough</u>
<u n="432" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="433" who="S0281">but I said to her the other night look I said I want you to</u>
<u n="434" who="S0144">but that can be kind of OCD as well</u>
<u n="435" who="S0281">well it can be I said and I put my hand on her chest and I said look now stop please stop this</u>
<u n="436" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="437" who="S0281">and and she did you know</u>
<u n="438" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0281">and and and the you know the movement with the shoulders I had my hands quite strongly on the shoulders to stop her moving</u>
<u n="440" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0281">and she eventually did</u>
<u n="442" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="443" who="S0281">so I I don't know whether <trunc>some</trunc></u>
<u n="444" who="S0144">something's bothering her eh? mm yeah maybe she's worried about something <vocal desc="laugh"/> maybe worried about I mean if she's getting the stuff again with her nose maybe she's worried about that</u>
<u n="445" who="S0281">oh well I mean she's really scared about hospitals you know</u>
<u n="446" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="447" who="S0281">I mean when we went for the went for the test the other day</u>
<u n="448" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="449" who="S0281">she was right within the hospital but of course you know we had another blood test again</u>
<u n="450" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="451" who="S0281">and er she's very brave about it but erm she's she does have a fear I mean she is but she's frightened of everything</u>
<u n="452" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="453" who="S0281">she she won't go to the well I mean under duress of going to the bathroom on her own</u>
<u n="454" who="S0144">really?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0281">yeah and when when she gets in there all the lights have gotta come on even the lights of the heating in the shower</u>
<u n="456" who="S0144">really?</u>
<u n="457" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="458" who="S0144">ah where'd she get that from?</u>
<u n="459" who="S0281">I don't know</u>
<u n="460" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> but how does she like erm the <unclear>boarding</unclear>? she must do it on her own</u>
<u n="461" who="S0281">well she must do but</u>
<pause dur="long"/>
<u n="462" who="S0144">er no she's a sweetie man</u>
<u n="463" who="S0281">yeah she is <pause dur="short"/> well I mean if it weren't for her then I wouldn't be so worried about you know what's going on at the moment</u>
<u n="464" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="465" who="S0281">but I don't know how many years I've got left around</u>
<u n="466" who="S0144">no one does</u>
<u n="467" who="S0281">well yeah I know but given my you know medical background it's erm it's even less certain and but it's hardly a day goes by that I don't think about death</u>
<u n="468" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="469" who="S0281">and they're of course they're aware any time somebody dies you know always the first thing I look at is how old were they and what was it?</u>
<u n="470" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="471" who="S0281">mm erm brother of my best mate er erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's er he died of lung cancer a couple of weeks ago the funeral was erm last week</u>
<u n="472" who="S0144">mm but is there I don't know is there any point thinking about it? erm I don't it might be easy for me to say but er <pause dur="short"/> I dunno</u>
<u n="473" who="S0281">well there's no there's no point really but but the mind goes there you know?</u>
<u n="474" who="S0144">mm yeah we I I think you know like we were saying earlier it's like a big transition thing you know so that once you've got it all</u>
<u n="475" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="476" who="S0144">everything's gonna come into place soon</u>
<u n="477" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="478" who="S0144">and then you know I mean the ground's just moving at the moment isn't it wherever they so once that stops shaking</u>
<u n="479" who="S0281">yep</u>
<u n="480" who="S0144">you can get on with it again I think you'll be fine <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="481" who="S0281">I bloody hope so</u>
<u n="482" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="483" who="S0281">it's er it's a long change to</u>
<u n="484" who="S0144">yeah been a tough time huh? <vocal desc="laugh"/> very tough time but how do you feel about not being at <anon type="place"/> any more?</u>
<u n="485" who="S0281">well it's certainly a big wrench</u>
<u n="486" who="S0144">mm but they have what like six years was it?</u>
<u n="487" who="S0281">seven</u>
<u n="488" who="S0144">seven years mm so that must be tough like when it wasn't your decision as well when it</u>
<u n="489" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0144">you know that age</u>
<u n="491" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="492" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="493" who="S0281">I mean the the I've been very lucky in that erm I moved out of my office and literally straight from my office to this new one</u>
<u n="494" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="495" who="S0281">with one of my one to one students helping me</u>
<u n="496" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="497" who="S0281">got his car and just checked his erm dissertation and er he offered to take me <unclear/> are just moved from there to there and it was amazing</u>
<u n="498" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="499" who="S0281">and I don't know but erm there's another place in the High Street erm the guy just erm taken over the travel agent shop yeah?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0144">right</u>
<u n="501" who="S0281">and he's er he's got that business going but he's also he is also a graduate of <anon type="place"/> erm two thousand and nine I think</u>
<u n="502" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="503" who="S0281">and er he erm he's got this thing about er he wants to start up about you know finding universities for students and you know</u>
<u n="504" who="S0144">mm mm</u>
<u n="505" who="S0281">that kind of thing same</u>
<u n="506" who="S0144">big business here</u>
<u n="507" who="S0281">well yeah no that's that's the business where I was today</u>
<u n="508" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="509" who="S0281">doing doing the same thing and it's also the same type of business where erm er I've been doing some work where they're paying me fifty pound an hour</u>
<u n="510" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="511" who="S0281">and er for doing <unclear/> <trunc>per</trunc>perhaps erm so er and I got er I didn't tell anybody but I got two weeks work er a couple of weeks ago out of them erm I was er it was a <unclear>preceding</unclear> course and they had eight students and they wanted me to teach them writing</u>
<u n="512" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="513" who="S0281">and to give them an advanced taste er of what's gonna come come their way erm this semester</u>
<u n="514" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0281">in the <unclear>ceiling</unclear> so erm I got er well I was er hour and a half a day plus on Friday in the afternoon we had er we're doing a feedback on presentations so that is another er hour in the afternoon</u>
<u n="516" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="517" who="S0281">I think so I got a thousand quid for that</u>
<u n="518" who="S0144">wow <vocal desc="laugh"/> well that's alright and this is gonna be frequent stuff?</u>
<u n="519" who="S0281">well no that was a one off because it was you know <unclear>preceded</unclear> courses would be just once a year</u>
<u n="520" who="S0144">mm mm</u>
<u n="521" who="S0281">and erm and I don't think you've got erm you know various people trying to find me work well yeah another thing from <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he sent me this thing called Vericant</u>
<u n="522" who="S0144">furry cunt?</u>
<u n="523" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0281">I say old boy</u>
<u n="525" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="526" who="S0281">erm no erm it's a basically assessing students speaking</u>
<u n="527" who="S0144">right</u>
<u n="528" who="S0281">and er it's an American organisation they say they prefer Yanks</u>
<u n="529" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="530" who="S0281">but if you are from a native speaking country and it's between fifteen and twenty-eight no fifteen twenty-four dollars an hour</u>
<u n="531" who="S0144">right what do you do?</u>
<u n="532" who="S0281">er listen to erm students talk and give them</u>
<u n="533" who="S0144">what on the phone?</u>
<u n="534" who="S0281">er well recordings</u>
<u n="535" who="S0144">oh recordings</u>
<u n="536" who="S0281">yeah and er give them er rate their speaking ability there are three criteria there's an overall er feedback and then there's three criteria you fill in and then you give them some feedback on how to improve on each one</u>
<u n="537" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="538" who="S0281">and er so that's another thing I've got to follow up but just I haven't had time to fart lately you know?</u>
<u n="539" who="S0144">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="540" who="S0281">I've got so many things</u>
<u n="541" who="S0144">yeah well that's a good thing innit? better than having nothing</u>
<u n="542" who="S0281">well absolutely but it I mean with the with this you know problem came up again well not again but came up today</u>
<u n="543" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="544" who="S0281">and er then I've got er well I had another one to one lesson this afternoon and she booked again for next week</u>
<u n="545" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="546" who="S0281">er Tuesday and I've got another well I've got a lesson tomorrow about TOFL and I've never done TOFL before so I had to erm get on the er the internet and I've I've got a couple of books er copied erm but haven't got any information from them</u>
<u n="547" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="548" who="S0281">dunno how that's gonna go so anyway</u>
<u n="549" who="S0144">yeah</u>
<u n="550" who="S0281">got the one lesson erm lesson tomorrow and another one erm on Monday it's as I say the work's promising</u>
<u n="551" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="552" who="S0281">it's just that as you mentioned before it's just in the ground stop movement it's</u>
<u n="553" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> mm yeah you'll get there <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="554" who="S0281">and erm my er sister erm <unclear/> nace niece one of my sister one of my sister's daughters er sent me an email erm saying about this visa problem and she said she would show it to her er she got in contact with her MP and said er that I should er write an email specifying what the problems are</u>
<u n="555" who="S0144">mm</u>
<u n="556" who="S0281">and she would forwards forward it and he'd look into it</u>
<u n="557" who="S0144">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="558" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="559" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/> well that's good</u>
<u n="560" who="S0281">but does no but it's just so much insecurity</u>
<u n="561" who="S0144">yeah well you've got so many things on your plate anyone would be feeling the same <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> don't don't look at it as an individual thing as like just all these things you've got every single person would be a bit stressed out you know?</u>
<u n="562" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="563" who="S0144">don't don't beat yourself up about it <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="564" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="565" who="S0144">it's a difficult time that's what it is you know? and you're doing the right thing to get out of it I mean you're you're opening all these avenues these new directions that will hopefully blossom into more stability</u>
<u n="566" who="S0281">mm</u>
<u n="567" who="S0144">so you're doing exactly the right thing</u>
<u n="568" who="S0281">I don't even know which country I'm gonna end up in</u>
<u n="569" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="570" who="S0281">really <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="571" who="S0144">yeah yeah erm do you want me to see if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think she's cooking do you want me to see if she's got enough dinner? you hungry?</u>
<u n="572" who="S0281">mm well be nice</u>
<u n="573" who="S0144"><unclear/> I don't know what she's doing</u>
<u n="574" who="S0281">shall I stop it now?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0144">no yeah okay <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <pause dur="long"/> yeah don't know where she is she's probably fixing her toenail or something</u>
<u n="576" who="S0281">oh okay</u>
<u n="577" who="S0144">did you just did you hear about her toe?</u>
<u n="578" who="S0281">no</u>
<u n="579" who="S0144">well she ripped her big toenail off</u>
<u n="580" who="S0281">oh my god</u>
<u n="581" who="S0144">at work</u>
<u n="582" who="S0281">wow</u>
<u n="583" who="S0144">just caught it on the desk the whole thing just came off</u>
<u n="584" who="S0281">wow that must have been painful?</u>
<u n="585" who="S0144" trans="overlap">well kind of lifted up like that so she couldn't get her sandals off</u>
<u n="586" who="S0281">oh my god</u>
<u n="587" who="S0144">she went to the erm clinic</u>
<u n="588" who="S0281">yeah</u>
<u n="589" who="S0144">they didn't wanna touch it <vocal desc="laugh"/> they sent her to the hospital and go pulled it right off straight off</u>
<u n="590" who="S0281">oh bloody hell</u>
<u n="591" who="S0144">so she's got this big open wound now very sore and had to keep cleaning it and it's just a pain <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="592" who="S0281">oh my goodness</u>
<u n="593" who="S0144">so yeah she's quite upset by it really</u>
<u n="594" who="S0281">okay right well on that note erm</u>
<u n="595" who="S0144"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="596" who="S0281">I guess we'll er stop</u>
<u n="597" who="S0144">yeah how long was that?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0281">forty-two minutes</u>
<u n="599" who="S0144">okay it's felt like fifteen</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
