<text id="SRRQ">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:49:05</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-11-30</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q4</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0517 S0558</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>(ANON’s home, Fradley, Staffs)</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Children, trip, A-levels, shopping</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about children and friends.</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T18</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0517">
				<exactage>47</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Sutton Coldfield</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lichfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>14 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Self employed - marketing &amp; Proofing services</occupation>
				<socgrade>C1</socgrade>
				<nssec>3</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- working knowledge; German -- Working knowledge</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0558">
				<exactage>50</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Birmingham</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>UK</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Midlands</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Lichfield</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>24 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>midlands</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Sales Rep/ Lunchtime Supervisor</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>there</unclear></u>
<u n="2" who="S0558">I should've finished <vocal desc="laugh"/> this shouldn't I?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0517">well that's alright</u>
<u n="4" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/></u>
<u n="5" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">so go on <vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="6" who="S0558" trans="overlap">so tell me <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0517">did <trunc>the</trunc> go on</u>
<u n="8" who="S0558">it was at a glimpse cos it was a bit dark but the two nights I dropped <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> off at erm home after the show</u>
<u n="9" who="S0517">oh yes yeah</u>
<u n="10" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came the one night <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came the other night and er he's literally opened the door and a quick wave</u>
<u n="11" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="12" who="S0558">have they both lost weight? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="13" who="S0517">they might've done</u>
<u n="14" who="S0558" trans="overlap">cos it looked to me like they might've done because obviously <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s been trying cos of <trunc>hi</trunc>his diabetes well they both it was a quick it was a quick glimpse it was literally and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="15" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh do you know erm they were here on Saturday night and I wouldn't've noticed that's terrible</u>
<u n="16" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh so maybe not then</u>
<u n="17" who="S0517">but they were <pause dur="short"/> actually that's not true I did look at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and think he had lost a little bit of weight I didn't notice with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> if I'm honest</u>
<u n="18" who="S0558">right right</u>
<u n="19" who="S0517">but he quite possibly had because cos he's trying he's really trying with his diabetes and in actual fact he'd had another test cos I asked him how it was and his blood pressure was fine</u>
<u n="20" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="21" who="S0517">that was all under control now they've changed the tablets and the diabetes he was he was down er what's the number they give you? I don't know the number er was it six?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear>if it's below five I think it's good isn't it</unclear>?</u>
<u n="23" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and I think he was at six or something so erm although apparently once you've been diagnosed diabetic they won't take that away but he's <trunc>maint</trunc> he's controlling it now just through what what he eats so</u>
<u n="24" who="S0558">that's good</u>
<u n="25" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so it's good mm</u>
<u n="26" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="27" who="S0517">but he might've done I never said to them but they bought us those chocolates you can have a chocolate if you want <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos there's only a few left there's a few left</u>
<u n="28" who="S0558">you do spoil me when I come here</u>
<u n="29" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="30" who="S0558">all the time</u>
<u n="31" who="S0517">so did erm did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> get off alright?</u>
<u n="32" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>?</u>
<u n="33" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="34" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s mum had turned up to pick them up pick him up and he went out and then he comes running back in he says oh mum I've forgotten I haven't got my bank card <unclear>trailing</unclear> around couldn't find his bank card</u>
<u n="35" who="S0558"><unclear/> does he need his bank?</u>
<u n="36" who="S0517">well he didn't just in case cos he only had a <trunc>l</trunc> about er a little bit of cash</u>
<u n="37" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="38" who="S0517">cos he was gonna hire some waterproof wellies erm not wellies <vocal desc="laugh"/> waterproof wellies waterproof trousers</u>
<u n="39" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="40" who="S0517">and he didn't have any</u>
<u n="41" who="S0558">I think we've got some waterproof trousers at home</u>
<u n="42" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah well they were only like a pound weren't they to hire?</u>
<u n="43" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="44" who="S0517">they were a pound twenty or something to hire I said oh I'm not buying them <trunc>h</trunc>hire them so erm er anyway didn't have much cash but he said it's alright mum if there's anything I'll take my bank card so he's running round couldn't find it so she's waiting outside so we were just grabbing together a few extra <vocal desc="laugh"/> a few extra pounds</u>
<u n="45" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh I see</unclear></u>
<u n="46" who="S0517">just in case you know he wanted to buy anything</u>
<u n="47" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh</u>
<u n="48" who="S0517">I don't think there's anything to</u>
<u n="49" who="S0558">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s took twenty pound</u>
<u n="50" who="S0517">I think he probably ended up with about twenty</u>
<u n="51" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I don't think</u>
<u n="52" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll <trunc>spe</trunc>spend it in the service station on the way there</u>
<u n="53" who="S0558">oh yeah yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you know? and they'll easily get through money there</u>
<u n="55" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah and they were going to McDonald's this morning for breakfast</u>
<u n="56" who="S0517" trans="overlap">this morning all of that yeah so that's what it was really <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think so we were scrubbing round for money while erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was waiting outside right what do you fancy? I'll tell you what there is</u>
<u n="57" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">so there's</u>
<u n="59" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">anything sort of toffee or caramelly or is usually my favourite</u>
<u n="60" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh really? Turkish delight <unclear/></u>
<u n="61" who="S0558" trans="overlap">no definitely not that one</u>
<u n="62" who="S0517">that one's gone there's a strawberries and cream what's that one?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0558">I don't know <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="64" who="S0517">Cornish sea salt fudge?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0558">oh that'll do</u>
<u n="66" who="S0517">that's that one I believe scuse fingers</u>
<u n="67" who="S0558">thank you</u>
<u n="68" who="S0517"><unclear/> don't know what that one is</u>
<u n="69" who="S0558">you're spoiling me</u>
<u n="70" who="S0517">well it was <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they only came round for a takeaway cos I had said to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I haven't seen you in ages come and have erm come round for a drink but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> had invited the boys to watch the fight there was a fight on or something no I didn't know either which <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was going to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't go he wasn't bothered but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was going to go to it so they ended up coming round early and they'd been down to <anon type="place"/> to visit <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s new nephew</u>
<u n="71" who="S0558">ah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0517">so he said oh well well if you're driving up from <anon type="place"/> I'll get us a takeaway</u>
<u n="73" who="S0558">ah that's nice</u>
<u n="74" who="S0517">so anyway they bought me flowers they bought chocolates they bought <vocal desc="laugh"/> they bought drinks I'm only ordering us a takeaway really it was no trouble <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="75" who="S0558" trans="overlap">she's so lovely isn't she?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0517">it was no trouble so anyway we're still eating the chocolate <unclear/></u>
<u n="77" who="S0558">erm when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got that paper round</u>
<u n="78" who="S0517">mm?</u>
<u n="79" who="S0558">that conversation that developed <unclear/> erm you know the story don't you? I told you?</u>
<u n="80" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah yeah</u>
<u n="81" who="S0558">yeah he came around with a bunch of flowers for me</u>
<u n="82" who="S0517">oh did he?</u>
<u n="83" who="S0558">yeah and I said oh</u>
<u n="84" who="S0517" trans="overlap">ah for recommending him?</u>
<u n="85" who="S0558">yeah he said thank you like you know? for recommending me for the paper round I said oh you're welcome I said oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> can I give you a hug?</u>
<u n="86" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0558">cos you don't know at that age do you?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="89" who="S0558">and I said can I give you a hug? and he said yes so I gave him a big hug and I text <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> oh thank you so much you know? you didn't need to do that but er very much appreciated</u>
<u n="90" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0558">and erm it was lovely that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> brought them <trunc>rou</trunc> I thought it was lovely that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> brought them round and I asked I asked permission for a hug and he let me</u>
<u n="92" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low">mm</u>
<u n="93" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="94" who="S0558">ah</u>
<u n="95" who="S0517">oh how funny</u>
<u n="96" who="S0558">it's like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> though this morning <pause dur="short"/> are you finding like? cos they're growing up and becoming more independent and I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear>this morning</unclear> I said oh have a good time and all this and that and he said oh I will he said oh it's it's going to be hard though you know? it's work and I said yes but it'll be enjoyable because you'll be with your friends</u>
<u n="97" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="98" who="S0558">and then of an evening you can all chill out a little bit</u>
<u n="99" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0558">I said you're not working all day and all night I said so it'll be really nice and he said yeah so I said to him well can I give you a big hug?</u>
<u n="101" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="102" who="S0558">cos you know if you just go to hug them</u>
<u n="103" who="S0517">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hasn't hugged me in ages <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll hug me er daily</u>
<u n="104" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="105" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> hasn't hugged me he won't no</u>
<u n="106" who="S0558" trans="overlap">it's it's it's like just coming down from school talking about them growing up and being independent</u>
<u n="107" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="108" who="S0558">just a snippet of er you know? Jeremy Vine or whatever erm a lady saying how children are forever growing and becoming independent and you have to seize the opportunity for example the the example she gave was one of her children er</u>
<u n="109" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0558">made enquiries or showed interest one day when she was chopping carrots</u>
<u n="111" who="S0517">oh?</u>
<u n="112" who="S0558">so she went through it with them here you are you chop she was there to help them if they wanted any help or questions but she said you have to seize the opportunity when they show willing so going back to the hug</u>
<u n="113" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0558">if I find sometimes if I go to hug <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> cos I want to and he's not in the mood I can almost feel like pushed away</u>
<u n="115" who="S0517" trans="overlap">ah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="116" who="S0558">do you know what I mean? cos he's not in mood I think oh he doesn't wanna hug me</u>
<u n="117" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah mum get off me <unclear/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0558" trans="overlap">so I'm like oh can I have a hug? and he went yeah</u>
<u n="119" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0517">because the bus wasn't leaving until ten thirty this morning was it?</u>
<u n="121" who="S0558">no and yet they didn't seem to have be any er you know? no no we don't have to go to school mum because you know? they've said we'll have to er work when we get there so</u>
<u n="122" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and yet they didn't yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0558">I can't it's all a bit blasé</u>
<u n="124" who="S0517">well they're being dropped to erm <anon type="place"/> aren't they?</u>
<u n="125" who="S0558">and then walking down into <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="126" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm I know cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s case was quite <unclear>big</unclear> he left and I said well where's your coat? he said I've packed it I said it's going to rain I said it's raining at no it's not raining I said unpack it no no he said I won't unpack it he said I don't want my coat on the coach I said for goodness sake</u>
<u n="127" who="S0558">so he's walked to and from McDonald's? he's going to get wet</u>
<u n="128" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="129" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="130" who="S0517">yes how ridiculous and he was adamant he was not unpacking his coat</u>
<u n="131" who="S0558">oh bless him</u>
<u n="132" who="S0517"><unclear>not</unclear> bless him <unclear>I thought</unclear> god <trunc>wha</trunc> er he didn't pack till last last night</u>
<u n="133" who="S0558">oh I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> pack your case Saturday <trunc>afternoo</trunc> well pack your case on Saturday because if there's anything you need then we've got Sunday to go out and get it like you know?</u>
<u n="134" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm oh that's organised</u>
<u n="135" who="S0558">cos one of his casual jogger trousers type thing</u>
<u n="136" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0558">he he's wore <pause dur="short"/> it must've been cos the only painting I know that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s done was for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> when she when he did all the fencing</u>
<u n="138" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh when she moved in? oh well did he have paint on them?</u>
<u n="139" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="140" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="141" who="S0558">so so he they're fine for around the house like <unclear>but he said</unclear></u>
<u n="142" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh yeah but also for the fieldwork they're doing</u>
<u n="143" who="S0558">well for the fieldwork yeah erm <pause dur="short"/> so I think he's took has he took them when he's out and about in the day? oh I don't know but we've got him another pair for of an evening when he comes back erm</u>
<u n="144" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh I don't even know what <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I left him to it but of course he was out all day Saturday on this he had a two day PE thing in <anon type="place"/> park</u>
<u n="145" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh did he?</u>
<u n="146" who="S0517">orienteering apparently at A level it's harder to get a practical mark in a second subject a second like like like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> plays tennis</u>
<u n="147" who="S0558">right</u>
<u n="148" who="S0517">but I mean he has actually got a few to choose from he could do hockey or er but er he could do tennis umpiring or all sorts but apparently the teachers have said that that they fall down a bit on the grades for the second practical so they had organised an orienteering in the park <anon type="place"/> park they've got an outside company in that was teaching them and then they were gonna be assessed and it was an opportunity for those that did well to to use that as the grade</u>
<u n="149" who="S0558">right</u>
<u n="150" who="S0517">so it was everybody had to go that was doing the A level PE so Friday and Saturday he spent the days in <anon type="place"/> park <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was rubbish at it and er by all accounts so was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> they I think they both failed the</u>
<u n="151" who="S0558"><vocal desc="gasp"/> oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="152" who="S0517">the first and second one <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <unclear>he was saying</unclear> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="153" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> failed? he shouldn't with all his Scouts experience</u>
<u n="154" who="S0517">well he shouldn't should he? really <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said they were just hopeless between them</u>
<u n="155" who="S0558" trans="overlap">no <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="156" who="S0517">so but I mean he was taking it very light-heartedly because he didn't need the erm the the grade if you like he just er so of course <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I were driving into town on erm Saturday and I said I wonder how <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s getting on send him a text so <trunc>d</trunc> so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> sent him a text which just said take er take the next right</u>
<u n="157" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0517">then go left</u>
<u n="159" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="160" who="S0517"><unclear>all of this</unclear> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> came up how are you getting on? he said oh well I've failed <trunc>w</trunc> I've failed level one and level two level three is next and that's the hardest <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="161" who="S0558">oh no</u>
<u n="162" who="S0517" trans="overlap">is there any point? but anyway my point was so he didn't get back till like five o clock on Saturday</u>
<u n="163" who="S0558" trans="overlap">Saturday</u>
<u n="164" who="S0517">and then of course cos of he'd had all his outdoor clothes and walking boots for those two days orienteering he said will you wash all of this mum? for me to take <vocal desc="laugh"/> away on Monday?</u>
<u n="165" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="166" who="S0517">which he didn't actually give to me till <trunc>sa</trunc> Sunday morning so he couldn't pack till last night cos I had to wash and dry all of his</u>
<u n="167" who="S0558">stuff</u>
<u n="168" who="S0517">stuff that he'd worn the last two days that he wanted to then take</u>
<u n="169" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0517">typical</u>
<u n="171" who="S0558">I to be honest I haven't I haven't interfered with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he's packed his own case and apart from these joggers <unclear/></u>
<u n="172" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I did buy him his Marigolds though cos that made me laugh</u>
<u n="173" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="174" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> when it was on the packing list Marigolds <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0558" trans="overlap">well <unclear/> cos I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> what colour Marigolds would you like?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh right I didn't I just bought yellow I didn't ask actually whether he wanted pink <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0558" trans="overlap">well I <unclear/> well erm I did <trunc>s</trunc> I did say to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> you can have yellow pink or blue and he said I'll have blue</u>
<u n="178" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="179" who="S0558">I couldn't find any blue</u>
<u n="180" who="S0517">no I haven't seen blue for a while actually</u>
<u n="181" who="S0558">no I haven't no and I know you can because I've got a pair in my under my kitchen sink</u>
<u n="182" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="183" who="S0558">so we ended up picking them up from whilst we were at Asda and then it was like oh do you want them fleece-lined?</u>
<u n="184" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0558">do you want heavy duty?</u>
<u n="186" who="S0517" trans="overlap">who knew there was such <vocal desc="laugh"/> who knew there was such a choice?</u>
<u n="187" who="S0558" trans="overlap">do you want plain pink? or yellow pink with a lining? so he he's ended up taking</u>
<u n="188" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="189" who="S0558">I think it was a pack <pause dur="short"/> cos I said to him you'd be better with the lined ones because your hands sweat in them don't they? horrible gloves</u>
<u n="190" who="S0517">yeah they do</u>
<u n="191" who="S0558">so I said you'd be better with the lined ones I said so take them</u>
<u n="192" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="193" who="S0558">and and if you're <trunc>i</trunc> you know if you're not that bothered he's got a pack of <unclear/></u>
<u n="194" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh has he got the <trunc>di</trunc>disposable ones?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0558">no no no erm just er a pack of the yellow ones</u>
<u n="196" who="S0517">oh okay okay</u>
<u n="197" who="S0558" trans="overlap">but I think there's two or three pairs in there</u>
<u n="198" who="S0517"><unclear>oh yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="199" who="S0558">so depending on what they're doing</u>
<u n="200" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s just gone with one</u>
<u n="201" who="S0558"><unclear/> if he wants</u>
<u n="202" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he won't even wear them knowing him I can't imagine he will</u>
<u n="203" who="S0558">and when did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have his last tetanus?</u>
<u n="204" who="S0517">er I don't know when was he er when do they <trunc>s</trunc> when er do they have a booster in school?</u>
<u n="205" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear/> I don't know but I've got <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> down as a last tetanus for two thousand and two</u>
<u n="206" who="S0517">and do they last ten years?</u>
<u n="207" who="S0558">well that's what I thought</u>
<u n="208" who="S0517">do they not <unclear/> do they not still remind you? do they not have <trunc>t</trunc>?</u>
<u n="209" who="S0558">well I thought they did because when er when I got that date I I needed for something I can't remember what it was to put when he'd had his last tetanus so I phoned the doctors up and said oh I'm completing this form for school they need it out</u>
<u n="210" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="211" who="S0558">are you able to help me? she said oh yes that's no problem at all tap tap tap tap told me the date and I said okay I said and do you do a recall when he's due?</u>
<u n="212" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="213" who="S0558">do you recall them in? she said yes we do so I'm thinking with the nature of what they're doing I'm assuming they're gonna be in soil and ponds and</u>
<u n="214" who="S0517">I've no idea didn't never even occurred to me but the doctors hadn't recalled him in for a a booster?</u>
<u n="215" who="S0558" trans="overlap">no they haven't</u>
<u n="216" who="S0517">oh so he must still <unclear/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0558" trans="overlap">so I'm going I'm gonna I'm going to need to phone and just say <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="218" who="S0517">on the form the medical form we had to fill out before they went it didn't ask did it?</u>
<u n="219" who="S0558">yeah on the one he brought home the weekend</u>
<u n="220" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh did it?</u>
<u n="221" who="S0558">he brought one home the weekend about erm bedwetting asthma er that sort of thing that they had to take back today</u>
<u n="222" who="S0517"><vocal desc="gasp"/> he hasn't taken it back he hasn't taken the form back</u>
<u n="223" who="S0558" trans="overlap">they did the one before <vocal desc="laugh"/> well they did the one before</u>
<u n="224" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I don't think he gave me a form did he give me a form?</u>
<u n="225" who="S0558">it was just one A4 sheet</u>
<u n="226" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he did give me no he gave me the clipped thing that had the all the information on the thing and that was that and then he and he did say to me oh there's another form</u>
<u n="227" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yes that was about a week or so ago</u>
<u n="228" who="S0517">but you don't need to send that back cos we've we've done that or something</u>
<u n="229" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="230" who="S0517">and that was it</u>
<u n="231" who="S0558">but no yeah exactly the same but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s brought one home that we had to complete and it was about asthma and</u>
<u n="232" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll forge it it wouldn't surprise me in the slightest he'll've found that and forged it</u>
<u n="233" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="234" who="S0517">cos it it hasn't come to me I haven't seen it</u>
<u n="235" who="S0558">well I thought</u>
<u n="236" who="S0517">and did that one say when did they last have their tetanus?</u>
<u n="237" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yes that was the one asking the question</u>
<u n="238" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh well that's</u>
<u n="239" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="240" who="S0558">cos I thought to myself oh my goodness me I hope due to the nature of what they're doing they don't say oh he can't go on it because he's <unclear/></u>
<u n="241" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh no cos they'd've sent it way in advance wouldn't they?</u>
<u n="242" who="S0558">well that's what I was thinking</u>
<u n="243" who="S0517" trans="overlap">they should've</u>
<u n="244" who="S0558">that's a bit remiss of them isn't it? if</u>
<u n="245" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><unclear>but</unclear> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has not we haven't I haven't filled out that form</u>
<u n="246" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="247" who="S0517">I haven't had a call <trunc>consi</trunc> you'd think they'd've collected them up wouldn't you? before they set off</u>
<u n="248" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="249" who="S0517">I <unclear>haven't heard</unclear> and I've been in all day I have had the vacuum on this morning upstairs <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="250" who="S0558">and he's not been dropped off? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="251" who="S0517">and he's not come home</u>
<u n="252" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0558">so I assume he's gone I don't know</u>
<u n="254" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh <unclear/></u>
<u n="255" who="S0517">did <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> take his laptop?</u>
<u n="256" who="S0558">no</u>
<u n="257" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't cos it did say on there didn't it? that they could if they wanted</u>
<u n="258" who="S0558" trans="overlap">no unless he's took his Ipad</u>
<u n="259" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> didn't take anything just his phone</u>
<u n="260" who="S0558" trans="overlap">dunno <unclear>well</unclear> he hasn't got a laptop anymore <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> has he?</u>
<u n="261" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="262" who="S0558">oh no cos he sold it to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> didn't he to buy his desk computer?</u>
<u n="263" who="S0517">oh okay well anyway they've gone to be honest with you he was so annoying on Sunday I think we were all quite pleased to see the back of him for four days <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="264" who="S0558" trans="overlap">glad to see the back of him</u>
<u n="265" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I were looking forward to it</u>
<u n="266" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="267" who="S0517">cos <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s gone now not back till Thursday night</u>
<u n="268" who="S0558">oh is it just the two of you?</u>
<u n="269" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so it's just me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="270" who="S0558">oh how lovely</u>
<u n="271" who="S0517">so I said oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> this'll be lovely just us</u>
<u n="272" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="273" who="S0517">he might be inviting his new girlfriend over tomorrow <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="274" who="S0558"><trunc>i</trunc>is this the new one the last one you told me that was <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="275" who="S0517" trans="overlap">he he's only had two so this is his second one</u>
<u n="276" who="S0558" trans="overlap">so this is after</u>
<u n="277" who="S0517">so this is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I haven't met her yet I don't know anything about her I don't know if she's coming but <vocal desc="laugh"/> he said to me a few days ago when does <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> go away? so I said next week so I said I might ask <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> round when he's gone</u>
<u n="278" who="UNKFEMALE" trans="overlap" whoConfidence="low"><unclear/> mm</u>
<u n="279" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="280" who="S0517">when he's gone but <unclear>yeah actually</unclear> very wise <unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="281" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh isn't it funny how?</u>
<u n="282" who="S0517"><unclear/> he was such a pain yesterday <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> he was just irritating everyone you know? when he <unclear/></u>
<u n="283" who="S0558">just in what way? just like attitude? or?</u>
<u n="284" who="S0517" trans="overlap">just yeah attitude and answering back and winding his brother up about everything and anything you know? oh drove me mad</u>
<u n="285" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="286" who="S0517">got to last night I said shouldn't you go and stand outside now and wait for <vocal desc="laugh"/> the <unclear/> to pick you up for eight o'clock last night <trunc>wh</trunc> or whenever they got back from the football <unclear>go on go go</unclear></u>
<u n="287" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh gosh</u>
<u n="288" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/> bless him</u>
<u n="289" who="S0558">oh bless him</u>
<u n="290" who="S0517" trans="overlap">bless him</u>
<u n="291" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0517">but er oh</u>
<u n="293" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> spends quite a lot of time up in his bedroom <pause dur="short"/> you know?</u>
<u n="294" who="S0517">does he?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0558">yeah he spends loads of time up in his bedroom he's either doing his homework bless him</u>
<u n="296" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="297" who="S0558">or he might be playing on catch up or something or he's on on Playstation with his friends but it's not excessive Playstation so I don't mean we never see him and you know? it's it's</u>
<u n="298" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no no no well <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s up there on his phone or on his laptop but that's that's about it</u>
<u n="299" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="300" who="S0517">he came <vocal desc="laugh"/> he <trunc>s</trunc> he said to me the other day he said mum I said what? he said we need to have a little talk I said oh god what have you done <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? what have you done?</u>
<u n="301" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="302" who="S0517">he said <vocal desc="laugh"/> he said well the thing is I wasn't gonna tell you but I think I should I said what? what? he goes I'm failing all my A levels I said you can't be I said <vocal desc="laugh"/> we're only in the we haven't even finished the first term of the first year</u>
<u n="303" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="304" who="S0517">you can't be failing them all he said I I <trunc>g</trunc> I just got Es E in geography E in sociology I said oh he said I've gotta give every I've gotta give up tennis I've gotta give everything up he said I'm out every night so I said that's a bit hasty</u>
<u n="305" who="S0558" trans="overlap">so he's recognised that</u>
<u n="306" who="S0517">I <trunc>sai</trunc> he said oh I did think to myself</u>
<u n="307" who="S0558" trans="overlap">gosh is this my boy? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0517">no no he said he said to me I did think to myself oh I could just you know not say anything and just enjoy playing tennis for the next two years but I did think maybe that'd be a waste of two years I said well well done you he said and I do think I ought to try and get my A levels I said so do I I said and we're not classing an E as a as a good grade no he said we're not</u>
<u n="309" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I said right okay <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos er technically it's a pass and we're not classing it you know? no so he said he was all set to give everything up everything and I said don't be ridiculous to him I said I'll do you a timetable</u>
<u n="311" who="S0558" trans="overlap">no you've got to have some</u>
<u n="312" who="S0517">it's just that he when he goes out for <trunc>t</trunc>tennis you know it's quarter past five till half past six and then we get back quarter to seven and then he hasn't eaten his meal so by the time he's ready to start by the time I've organised it cos I've had to go and pick him up and fed him you know it's half seven and by that time he can't really be bothered to start</u>
<u n="313" who="S0558" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="314" who="S0517">he'd be so we've er <vocal desc="sigh"/> I said well we'll draw you up a timetable and on a Tuesday you can do two hours <unclear/> he said oh you're supposed to be doing way more than you did for your GCSEs and I'm not doing anything I said well clearly if you're getting Es <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="315" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="316" who="S0517">he said the only one that I'm doing work for is PE he said and do you know why I'm doing that? I said no he said because they're like they did in the GCSE if you don't hit your target grades at every single thing you're doing they send a letter home and make you stay to a booster session on a Friday night which is what they used to do for GCSE he said and I didn't want a letter home and I didn't want to have to stay so I said and and you're hitting your target? yes he said I said so clearly you can do it you just need to put the time in</u>
<u n="317" who="S0558" trans="overlap">he's capable mm</u>
<u n="318" who="S0517">so he's like you know <unclear/></u>
<u n="319" who="S0558">mm but <unclear/></u>
<u n="320" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I said well that's alright I <trunc>s</trunc> I said good for you I said I'm really pleased that you've said you want to</u>
<u n="321" who="S0558" trans="overlap">absolutely yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0517">you want to do it you don't wanna waste two years he said yeah and also there is parents' evening coming up so you probably would've found out</u>
<u n="323" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="324" who="S0517">I said probably might've <vocal desc="laugh"/> might've been mentioned so</u>
<u n="325" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="326" who="S0558">yeah we've got that haven't we next week?</u>
<u n="327" who="S0517">is it next week? <pause dur="short"/> is it next Thursday? is it the?</u>
<u n="328" who="S0558" trans="overlap">the tenth night after <anon type="place"/> got a very busy week next week</u>
<u n="329" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh yeah who's <trunc>g</trunc> who how many have you got going to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="330" who="S0558">twenty-two</u>
<u n="331" who="S0517">twenty-two?</u>
<u n="332" who="S0558">so far</u>
<u n="333" who="S0517">who's going?</u>
<u n="334" who="S0558">right I knew you'd ask me this so I've memorised the list</u>
<u n="335" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="336" who="S0558">right me</u>
<u n="337" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="338" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her friend</u>
<u n="339" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="340" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="341" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="342" who="S0558">cos <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <trunc>ca</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s wife <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="343" who="S0517" trans="overlap">really?</u>
<u n="344" who="S0558">they're going out I said well bring him <vocal desc="laugh"/> bring she said I can't believe it she said me and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> have got something planned</u>
<u n="345" who="S0517"><unclear/> oh</u>
<u n="346" who="S0558">cos when we went</u>
<u n="347" who="S0517">it's only girls isn't it?</u>
<u n="348" who="S0558">yeah but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s alright I don't mind <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="349" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="350" who="S0558">erm when we took them to the show and we went over for the Chinese <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I walked over to pick the girls up from the concert</u>
<u n="351" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="352" who="S0558">and walked back and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> mentioned something about oh I love erm being er sort of like shopping of an evening I <trunc>s</trunc> I said oh I love evening shopping I said one because it's quieter but I <trunc>d</trunc> I just really enjoy going out in the evening and shopping yeah</u>
<u n="353" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it's more relaxing yeah yeah</u>
<u n="354" who="S0558"><vocal desc="cough"/> and erm of course I sent her this thing oh you're going to love this arranging a ladies' Christmas night out blah evening blah blah blah and she text</u>
<u n="355" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="356" who="S0558">I can't believe it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I</u>
<u n="357" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><unclear>oh she's out</unclear></u>
<u n="358" who="S0558">so I said well if <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wants to come along like you know? rather than her miss out so that's them that's three</u>
<u n="359" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh that's nice <unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0558">then there's you</u>
<u n="361" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="363" who="S0517"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hopefully</u>
<u n="364" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> hopefully</u>
<u n="365" who="S0517">possibly <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0558">possibly <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and I think I've included <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I haven't included <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="367" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="368" who="S0558">erm I haven't included <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> cos you haven't said yet whether <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s coming or not</u>
<u n="369" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh sorry <trunc>y</trunc>yeah she would like to</u>
<u n="370" who="S0558">she is? right so so us three</u>
<u n="371" who="S0517" trans="overlap">she would yeah <unclear>sorry</unclear></u>
<u n="372" who="S0558">you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> let's do definites is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> a definite now?</u>
<u n="373" who="S0517">er er <trunc>y</trunc>yes</u>
<u n="374" who="S0558">more or less</u>
<u n="375" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="376" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> then we've got</u>
<u n="377" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="378" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and somebody called <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I think her name was and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> might come she hasn't confirmed that yet her friend <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> erm it was the lady who should've turned up yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh the one that was meant to be there the other week? yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0558">then there's erm <vocal desc="sigh"/> right <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in the village who I used to clean for</u>
<u n="381" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="382" who="S0558">plus one cos he <unclear>used</unclear> to talk to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about <unclear>his shop</unclear> erm <pause dur="short"/> gosh I've gotta think now</u>
<u n="383" who="S0517">is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> coming?</u>
<u n="384" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="385" who="S0517">mm and her mum?</u>
<u n="386" who="S0558">her mum and her sister <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="387" who="S0517">oh okay gosh</u>
<u n="388" who="S0558">so three yeah <unclear/> <unclear>with her</unclear> erm</u>
<u n="389" who="S0517">but quite a few but <unclear/> to remember all those</u>
<u n="390" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="391" who="S0517">but tell you what concerns me <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> is when everybody wants to pay you know what <unclear/></u>
<u n="392" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh I know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="393" who="S0517">we could be there till three in the morning with the way they do it</u>
<u n="394" who="S0558">well at people are people are probably I don't know</u>
<u n="395" who="S0517">I don't know I</u>
<u n="396" who="S0558">I think she'll have more staff than just <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="397" who="S0517">do you?</u>
<u n="398" who="S0558">yeah I reckon she might <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might even be there</u>
<u n="399" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="400" who="S0558">fetching and carrying and then there's another lady that helps her</u>
<u n="401" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I mean it'll be lovely so are we taking wine with us?</u>
<u n="402" who="S0558">well I'm going to send a text out to everybody</u>
<u n="403" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="404" who="S0558">with the postcode and say it's arrive from seven</u>
<u n="405" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="406" who="S0558">and I need to give brief directions when driving into <anon type="place"/> village cos the postcode is the village</u>
<u n="407" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><anon type="place"/> yes right</u>
<u n="408" who="S0558">so I shall just put erm enter <anon type="place"/> village</u>
<u n="409" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="410" who="S0558">down the tree-lined driveway across the cattle grid first left</u>
<u n="411" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="412" who="S0558">and then you'll see the big hall on your left-hand side up the driveway</u>
<u n="413" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><unclear/> hall yes yeah yeah just past the <unclear/></u>
<u n="414" who="S0558">yeah erm so yeah she's gonna provide all the glasses and she's gonna put some nibbles on so what she'll include in the text is tea and coffee tea and coffee available <trunc>ho</trunc>however if you'd like a soft drink or for non-drivers a glass of wine please bring</u>
<u n="415" who="S0517">or the other way round you meant that if you'd like a glass of wine offer non-drivers a soft drink</u>
<u n="416" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah</u>
<u n="417" who="S0517">I knew what you meant <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="418" who="S0558">yes yes well spotted</u>
<u n="419" who="S0517">yeah okay</u>
<u n="420" who="S0558">erm</u>
<u n="421" who="S0517">bring some so sort of bring your own okay</u>
<u n="422" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><trunc>bri</trunc>bring your your own you know?</u>
<u n="423" who="S0517">so who who are you taking? obviously <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and her friend</u>
<u n="424" who="S0558">oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> that's another lady who's coming <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> from athletics</u>
<u n="425" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="426" who="S0558">she she does know where it is but she <trunc>d</trunc> she said she will make her way to my house</u>
<u n="427" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="428" who="S0558">because then she <trunc>c</trunc> she can either jump in with me or somebody else or she can take people because she will have to drive back to <anon type="place"/> anyway</u>
<u n="429" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right right okay</u>
<u n="430" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can't come these are two ladies I sit with every Tuesday</u>
<u n="431" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="432" who="S0558">erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> can't come cos she works</u>
<u n="433" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="434" who="S0558">on a Wednesday night</u>
<u n="435" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I didn't know whether to mention it to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> but I sort of want <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> to drop <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> home from football</u>
<u n="436" who="S0558">yeah I haven't mentioned it to her</u>
<u n="437" who="S0517">no perhaps I won't then I'll just ask if she <trunc>wa</trunc> because <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't finish football till seven</u>
<u n="438" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0517">oh I mean we won't be there for seven anyway erm <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> has something to do with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> at <trunc>n</trunc> six thirty I think she drops him off at rugby and I said oh <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s just finishing tennis at rugby which of course is as you now know <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="440" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="441" who="S0517">across the way</u>
<u n="442" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="443" who="S0517">so er she said that's fine they'll organise bringing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> home</u>
<u n="444" who="S0558">right</u>
<u n="445" who="S0517">and then <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'ll be ready to go at twenty to seven <pause dur="short"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't finish football till seven so providing and he's playing with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s son so providing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> maybe <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'ll drop them both home? we just need to sort it out but we likely won't leave the village here till twenty to quarter to seven but that's okay half past seven yeah</u>
<u n="446" who="S0558" trans="overlap">but you'll still be there by half past yeah</u>
<u n="447" who="S0517">and also I spent so much last time I was there</u>
<u n="448" who="S0558">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="449" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="450" who="S0558">no no no I know same here <unclear/></u>
<u n="451" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and talking of spending so much did you get <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s text about the Neal's Yard products? the twenty percent off</u>
<u n="452" who="S0558" trans="overlap">twenty percent discount</u>
<u n="453" who="S0517">and I thought you are <trunc>s</trunc> are you still having the party on the fourth? because I can't <unclear/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0558">no I can't do this coming Friday?</u>
<u n="455" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="456" who="S0558">no no no I can't do the fourth</u>
<u n="457" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="458" who="S0558">no that's why I haven't sent a text out or anything to anybody</u>
<u n="459" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="460" who="S0558">but potentially well for two reasons if I'm honest <pause dur="short"/> one it's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> comes home</u>
<u n="461" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="462" who="S0558">and I'm thinking oh er he might be in the mood for telling us all about it and I don't wanna miss that opportunity</u>
<u n="463" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and also they've said an eleven o'clock return haven't they? but they have also said that that it could be earlier</u>
<u n="464" who="S0558">it could be earlier</u>
<u n="465" who="S0517">could be half nine couldn't it? and that's right in the middle of the evening</u>
<u n="466" who="S0558">yeah and and if you're hosting and you're saying oh I'll be back in half an hour</u>
<u n="467" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><unclear/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="468" who="S0558">I did I don't mind but other people might think oh you know?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0517">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="470" who="S0558">erm and two I was thinking well if it's before the <anon type="place"/> trip people might spend at Neal's Yard and may not have any money for <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="471" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah that's true actually</u>
<u n="472" who="S0558">and if</u>
<u n="473" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="474" who="S0558" trans="overlap">you know?</u>
<u n="475" who="S0517">well cos I <trunc>d</trunc> I wasn't there wasn't much I I really particularly wanted to buy</u>
<u n="476" who="S0558" trans="overlap">so</u>
<u n="477" who="S0517">and then I thought well if you're mad if you <trunc>th</trunc>there was something not to buy it at twenty percent off</u>
<u n="478" who="S0558">I know</u>
<u n="479" who="S0517">so there was something in there for er <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s the new mother and baby cos she's got dreadful stretch marks oh god really bad stretch marks</u>
<u n="480" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh bless her bless her</u>
<u n="481" who="S0517">but I thought a pot of that might be nice and it was it was twenty pounds but well twenty percent off you know? you may as well get it for sixteen it makes sense doesn't it?</u>
<u n="482" who="S0558" trans="overlap">absolutely</u>
<u n="483" who="S0517">so I did just ask that and then I'm thinking what am I going to order at <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s party? but if you're not having one then that'll be easier</u>
<u n="484" who="S0558" trans="overlap">well I don't I don't know I was gonna run this by you today I don't know whether to have one on Thursday the seventeenth? <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="485" who="S0517">thing is will she have got? if anybody's waiting on Christmas presents will she have got the order in in time?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0558">don't know cos I said this didn't I? I did stipulate</u>
<u n="487" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="488" who="S0558">look what if people come and nobody buys because of the time of year? and</u>
<u n="489" who="S0517">yes yeah</u>
<u n="490" who="S0558" trans="overlap">you know you don't want it to be a wasted evening for her but</u>
<u n="491" who="S0517">I know she wants to</u>
<u n="492" who="S0558" trans="overlap">she's not too bothered is she?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0517">no she's not she's not or you could just leave it till the New Year because by the seventeenth I just don't think people'll be still looking for Christmas presents especially that we then can't take away there and then and have to wait for the order</u>
<u n="494" who="S0558">but do we just have it as a girly night? not even people worrying about as a</u>
<u n="495" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh we could do</u>
<u n="496" who="S0558">just as a girly get-together</u>
<u n="497" who="S0517">we could do</u>
<u n="498" who="S0558">what do you think of the seventeenth though?</u>
<u n="499" who="S0517">is that a Thursday did you say?</u>
<u n="500" who="S0558">do you think people will come if <pause dur="short"/> if they've gotta go to work the next day? but then it doesn't have to be a late night does it?</u>
<u n="501" who="S0517" trans="overlap">well it's the last day it's the last day for a lot of people isn't it? <unclear/></u>
<u n="502" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear/> the last day for <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> it'll be the last</u>
<u n="503" who="S0517">yes it probably would be <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="504" who="S0558"><trunc>s</trunc>shall I do that then?</u>
<u n="505" who="S0517">do it</u>
<u n="506" who="S0558">I'll check with <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> tonight but he's erm it's the <unclear/> <unclear>works do</unclear> I'm absolutely convinced</u>
<u n="507" who="S0517">oh the Friday night?</u>
<u n="508" who="S0558" trans="overlap">so he won't need me to pick him up or anything on the Thursday night I and I would imagine it'll be Scouts I think that's the night of the <anon type="place"/> trip so <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> will be out</u>
<u n="509" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="510" who="S0558">erm</u>
<u n="511" who="S0517">is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> still doing the Scouts?</u>
<u n="512" who="S0558">no she finished now</u>
<u n="513" who="S0517">oh she's finished? so she won't be there so it'll just be <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> going off to the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0558"><unclear/> yeah</u>
<u n="515" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="516" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="517" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="518" who="S0558">yeah so <unclear>I might go</unclear> for the seventeenth then</u>
<u n="519" who="S0517">yeah do that</u>
<u n="520" who="S0558"><unclear/></u>
<u n="521" who="S0517" trans="overlap">still don't know what er I mean I did like I did like it and it did feel nice</u>
<u n="522" who="S0558">mm</u>
<u n="523" who="S0517">but I'm still very happy with what I currently use</u>
<u n="524" who="S0558">mm <unclear/> to be honest with you <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I couldn't afford to buy that</u>
<u n="525" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I might I might</u>
<u n="526" who="S0558">I mean I'm having my nails done now on a regular basis and</u>
<u n="527" who="S0517" trans="overlap">I know it's quite</u>
<u n="528" who="S0558">it's it's having to come in it's having to come out the shopping money</u>
<u n="529" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="530" who="S0558">do you know what I mean? I haven't got a surplus twenty pound</u>
<u n="531" who="S0517">no well you need to get earning some extra <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="532" who="S0558">yes need to <unclear/></u>
<u n="533" who="S0517">no I know what you mean I know what you mean</u>
<u n="534" who="S0558">do you know what I mean? so I'm I'm it's you know</u>
<u n="535" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and I know like it it's similar in price to what I currently buy however</u>
<u n="536" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="537" who="S0517">what I buy I can I get discounts when I buy online</u>
<u n="538" who="S0558">well</u>
<u n="539" who="S0517">you go through various sites and you get them</u>
<u n="540" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="541" who="S0517">I don't ever buy it full price</u>
<u n="542" who="S0558">no neither do I</u>
<u n="543" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so actually I'm er <trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>i</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> it would be probably a bit more expensive so I'm not prepared I might get the hand stuff that was nice</u>
<u n="544" who="S0558" trans="overlap">no mm</u>
<u n="545" who="S0517">that erm</u>
<u n="546" who="S0558">little <unclear/></u>
<u n="547" who="S0517" trans="overlap">you know that exfoliating</u>
<u n="548" who="S0558">mind you do you know? I <trunc>fe</trunc> I felt that evening my hands were really dry</u>
<u n="549" who="S0517">oh really?</u>
<u n="550" who="S0558">yeah I was looking at them and they looked</u>
<u n="551" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="552" who="S0558">and I thought maybe I just put too well you know? maybe</u>
<u n="553" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="554" who="S0558">the the <trunc>e</trunc> the amount was too much or</u>
<u n="555" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mine mine mine were fine actually but <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="556" who="S0558">didn't like last forever</u>
<u n="557" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but I mean it I I <trunc>d</trunc> I I wouldn't necessarily buy but I'd do it as a girly night</u>
<u n="558" who="S0558">yes yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> yeah we'll do that then the seventeenth before Christmas  yeah</u>
<u n="559" who="S0517">I'll bring some mince pies if you like</u>
<u n="560" who="S0558">yeah we can have a mince pie can't we?</u>
<u n="561" who="S0517">I've made a few</u>
<u n="562" who="S0558">glass of wine</u>
<u n="563" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="564" who="S0558">some <trunc>mul</trunc> I could get some mulled wine mulled wine</u>
<u n="565" who="S0517">yes so have you? are you? what? have you heard from your dad?</u>
<u n="566" who="S0558">yes</u>
<u n="567" who="S0517">is he having a lovely time?</u>
<u n="568" who="S0558">he's having a lovely <trunc>ti</trunc> well I say I've heard from him I've heard from him once <vocal desc="cough"/> and then I've had two messages</u>
<u n="569" who="S0517" trans="overlap">when did he? when did he go to?</u>
<u n="570" who="S0558">he went on Wednesday the seventeenth</u>
<u n="571" who="S0517">oh so he's only been gone er coming up two weeks?</u>
<u n="572" who="S0558"><vocal desc="cough"/> coming up two weeks it'll be <trunc>com</trunc> it'll be two weeks next Wednesday won't it?</u>
<u n="573" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right <pause dur="short"/> two weeks <unclear>in</unclear> yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0558">what day are we today?</u>
<u n="575" who="S0517">we're only on Monday so two weeks on Wednesday</u>
<u n="576" who="S0558" trans="overlap">that's two weeks oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm thinking <unclear>on</unclear> Thursday or something <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="577" who="S0517">no no no <vocal desc="laugh"/> we're on <unclear>we're on</unclear> Monday</u>
<u n="578" who="S0558">oh dear erm yeah so he phoned to say the flight had gone well he didn't enjoy it but for no other reason than distance</u>
<u n="579" who="S0517">yeah it's a long flight where did he have to change? Dubai?</u>
<u n="580" who="S0558">well they went to Dubai changed</u>
<u n="581" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="582" who="S0558">and then they went to Kuala Lumpur</u>
<u n="583" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="584" who="S0558">pronounce that right</u>
<u n="585" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="586" who="S0558">erm now I don't know whether that was just for a quick refuel or whether they actually got off and got back on</u>
<u n="587" who="S0517" trans="overlap">got off the plane</u>
<u n="588" who="S0558">I don't know and then landed in Melbourne</u>
<u n="589" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="590" who="S0558">early hours of the morning about two o'clock in the morning</u>
<u n="591" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and was? yeah</u>
<u n="592" who="S0558">so they'd arranged very very close to the airport what they called like a cabin or something and it it's not a hotel as such it's kind of just a room and you</u>
<u n="593" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="594" who="S0558">you have to put a code in to get your key and all that sort of thing</u>
<u n="595" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh okay yeah yeah</u>
<u n="596" who="S0558">that was absolutely brilliant no problems there picked the car up the next day got a better one than they asked for the guy was</u>
<u n="597" who="S0517" trans="overlap">who was he with again? his brother?</u>
<u n="598" who="S0558">uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> from Scotland and uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> from <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="599" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh three of them?</u>
<u n="600" who="S0558">three of them</u>
<u n="601" who="S0517">right oh lovely</u>
<u n="602" who="S0558">uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was the one whose wife also died last year</u>
<u n="603" who="S0517">right yes yeah</u>
<u n="604" who="S0558">and then er uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s local his wife's still alive <vocal desc="cough"/> so erm <pause dur="short"/> then so he phoned to say that and then er they had three hours sleep now I don't know if that was because that he wasn't ready to go to sleep or whatever</u>
<u n="605" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah just</u>
<u n="606" who="S0558">or by the time they'd got through the system the other end</u>
<u n="607" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="608" who="S0558">so they had three hours sleep and then they picked the car up as I say very pleased with that and then drove to <anon type="place"/> to uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> now uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is selling the house in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="609" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="610" who="S0558">they've actually moved to the bush house they're going to live at the bush house and he's gonna sell the <anon type="place"/> <anon type="place"/> one</u>
<u n="611" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="612" who="S0558">whereas when we went out years ago <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> wasn't too keen to go and live up there cos it's more isolated</u>
<u n="613" who="S0517">oh okay</u>
<u n="614" who="S0558">and you have to get in the car to go to the shops whereas <anon type="place"/> she can walk down</u>
<u n="615" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="616" who="S0558">you know? so a few restrictions however she's obviously changed her mind</u>
<u n="617" who="S0517" trans="overlap">she's she's come round</u>
<u n="618" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="619" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="620" who="S0558">so erm dad said when they arrived the photographers were there taking pictures of the house</u>
<u n="621" who="S0517">oh <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="622" who="S0558">so he said I think er he said oh I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was a bit like you know? sort of a bit fraught oh I'm really sorry <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> like and all this and that he said but they were only there ten minutes and then they'd gone</u>
<u n="623" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="624" who="S0558">excelled themselves again as they did for <trunc>h</trunc> for us three beds three beds three bedrooms all made up and ready for them fridge full of food cupboards full of food</u>
<u n="625" who="S0517" trans="overlap">where were where was your? where were they staying? where's your dad staying?</u>
<u n="626" who="S0558"><anon type="place"/> the house at <anon type="place"/> in the house at <anon type="place"/> that they're selling</u>
<u n="627" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh in the house that they're selling? oh okay</u>
<u n="628" who="S0558">yeah so they're stuck in there</u>
<u n="629" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="630" who="S0558">so erm where we stopped at the bush house</u>
<u n="631" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes oh I see</u>
<u n="632" who="S0558">they will go up to the bush house and visit and I said oh look out for the kangaroos and everything it's er</u>
<u n="633" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0558">it's it's equivalent to going up and living in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="635" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="636" who="S0558">that sort of thing you know?</u>
<u n="637" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0558">or you know? for like <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="639" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="640" who="S0558">you know? something like that but erm but so that's the only phone call I've had to speak to him but then aunty <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> phoned me to say they were having problems with the phones or something I don't know she was trying to top it up <unclear/> and they wanted too much information and she couldn't erm anyway I don't know how they've got round it but she sent a <trunc>mess</trunc> she sent a message to me last week to give her a ring and they were going the following day to <anon type="place"/> for three days</u>
<u n="641" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="642" who="S0558">which was last Tuesday to Friday</u>
<u n="643" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="644" who="S0558">and she sent me a text yesterday to say they're going to Sydney for three days this week</u>
<u n="645" who="S0517">oh lovely</u>
<u n="646" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="647" who="S0517">and when does he come back?</u>
<u n="648" who="S0558">mm the ninth</u>
<u n="649" who="S0517">oh that's when my mum goes</u>
<u n="650" who="S0558">oh is that when your mum's going?</u>
<u n="651" who="S0517">mum's going to New Zealand</u>
<u n="652" who="S0558" trans="overlap">what time does she go?</u>
<u n="653" who="S0517">in the evening</u>
<u n="654" who="S0558">what time? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="655" who="S0517">I don't know</u>
<u n="656" who="S0558">isn't that ridiculous like? cos I've gotta pick</u>
<u n="657" who="S0517">about nine o'clock at night I think</u>
<u n="658" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh no I was gonna say I've gotta pick them up at three o'clock in the morning</u>
<u n="659" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh oh have you? oh that's kind of you oh well mother mother's travelling business class again</u>
<u n="660" who="S0558">oh is she?</u>
<u n="661" who="S0517"><unclear/> so they send a car to the house you know?</u>
<u n="662" who="S0558">oh my goodness me</u>
<u n="663" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="664" who="S0558">just tell her when she's leaving shout bye see you in a couple of weeks</u>
<u n="665" who="S0517"><unclear/> yeah yeah</u>
<u n="666" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear/> picking you up</u>
<u n="667" who="S0517">no so no so that's when she goes oh and he'll be back then mm</u>
<u n="668" who="S0558">yeah so he comes back the early hours of the ninth so I'm not working that Wednesday or Thursday I'm working</u>
<u n="669" who="S0517">so oh the early hours of the ninth you're picking him up? oh and that's the night we're at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="670" who="S0558"><unclear/> early hours of Wednesday morning so I'm not working so I can pick them up come home and go to bed have a sleep and then go out in the evening</u>
<u n="671" who="S0517">and go out in the evening</u>
<u n="672" who="S0558"><vocal desc="misc"/> I've got such a busy week next week</u>
<u n="673" who="S0517">have you?</u>
<u n="674" who="S0558">I have</u>
<u n="675" who="S0517">what are you doing?</u>
<u n="676" who="S0558">Monday night it's our works Christmas do <vocal desc="misc"/> oh</u>
<u n="677" who="S0517">oh with <trunc>da</trunc> we</u>
<u n="678" who="S0558">grandad is so funny</u>
<u n="679" who="S0517">is he? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="680" who="S0558">he's grandad now don't call him uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> it's grandad now <vocal desc="laugh"/> I said to him today</u>
<u n="681" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><unclear/>?</u>
<u n="682" who="S0558">no no we're not taking partners I said to him today cos we'd been at the meeting this morning I said erm I said I'll pick you up next Monday <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> for erm for the works do and he went oh no it's alright I'll walk in</u>
<u n="683" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh she's not? where's it at?</u>
<u n="684" who="S0558"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="685" who="S0517">oh nice</u>
<u n="686" who="S0558">he said I'll walk in I said no I'll pick you up he said but you've gotta go all the way round he said <unclear>and it just</unclear> takes ten minutes to walk in I said it's not a problem so erm he said honestly I'll walk in he said but you can give me a lift back and I went well I dunno half a date <unclear/></u>
<u n="687" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="688" who="S0558">I said I've got no er guarantees I'm even going to sit next to you when we're in the place</u>
<u n="689" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="690" who="S0558">so he said well he said erm what was it he said? erm I've got to leave my options open he said you don't know who I might pick up on the way <vocal desc="laugh"/> my ten minute walk oh we was laughing</u>
<u n="691" who="S0517">oh god so that's Monday oh that'll be nice</u>
<u n="692" who="S0558" trans="overlap">so yeah so we've got that Monday at <anon type="place"/> six thirty for seven</u>
<u n="693" who="S0517" trans="overlap">mm how how many of you are there?</u>
<u n="694" who="S0558">oh we're all <trunc>go</trunc> last year last year we had like a lottery do</u>
<u n="695" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="696" who="S0558">and I think the cash collectors had their do and the office had their do</u>
<u n="697" who="S0517">oh but you're all going together?</u>
<u n="698" who="S0558">we're all going together which makes sense doesn't it?</u>
<u n="699" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes oh so there'll be a big crowd</u>
<u n="700" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear/> there's gonna be about twenty of us</u>
<u n="701" who="S0517">oh lovely</u>
<u n="702" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I think</u>
<u n="703" who="S0517">oh that'll be nice</u>
<u n="704" who="S0558">so that's Monday night</u>
<u n="705" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="706" who="S0558">then <trunc>Tue</trunc> it's my Christmas week next week it's all over after next week</u>
<u n="707" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="708" who="S0558">Tuesday night <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s in the choir at the Methodist church <anon type="place"/> choir are performing</u>
<u n="709" who="S0517" trans="overlap">did he join?</u>
<u n="710" who="S0558" trans="overlap">he did</u>
<u n="711" who="S0517">oh good for him</u>
<u n="712" who="S0558">oh he's got to wear a dickie bow</u>
<u n="713" who="S0517">has he?</u>
<u n="714" who="S0558">he has</u>
<u n="715" who="S0517">wow</u>
<u n="716" who="S0558">so I've got that little concert</u>
<u n="717" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="718" who="S0558">apparently it'll be about an hour</u>
<u n="719" who="S0517">Wednesday's <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="720" who="S0558">Wednesday night's <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> thursday night's parents' evening</u>
<u n="721" who="S0517">oh gosh yeah</u>
<u n="722" who="S0558">I know and then Friday night <pause dur="short"/> there's nothing Friday night I don't know why I'm getting overexcited it's only three nights</u>
<u n="723" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><unclear/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="724" who="S0558">I thought it was a whole week <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="725" who="S0517" trans="overlap">week <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s only got one appointment I think for parents' evening so far that I've heard of oh well I haven't heard of any <pause dur="short"/> I don't know whether we got any</u>
<u n="726" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/> there's no point going if he hasn't got you any appointments</u>
<u n="727" who="S0517">and guess er he said guess which one that is I said well PE obviously cos that's the one you're not failing</u>
<u n="728" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/> yes <unclear/> I've remembered Friday night erm up at dad's to see all the <unclear/> chairs and</u>
<u n="729" who="S0517" trans="overlap">oh cos he's back oh yes yeah yeah</u>
<u n="730" who="S0558" trans="overlap">well I thought I'd leave them alone Thursday</u>
<u n="731" who="S0517">oh they'll be jet lagged <unclear>too won't they</unclear>?</u>
<u n="732" who="S0558" trans="overlap">they'll be jet lagged they'll still need a couple of days to chill</u>
<u n="733" who="S0517" trans="overlap">they'll still be jet lagged on Friday but</u>
<u n="734" who="S0558">yeah</u>
<u n="735" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="736" who="S0558">so I thought <trunc>f</trunc> cos then I think uncle <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> might be going back Saturday so I thought Friday night we could all go up there and Saturday night Saturday's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s have you had a text about the open house? cos she told you to keep the date free didn't she?</u>
<u n="737" who="S0517" trans="overlap">no she did she did I'd forgotten about is that the fifth? I can't</u>
<u n="738" who="S0558">no the twelfth</u>
<u n="739" who="S0517">oh the twelfth <pause dur="short"/> oh yeah erm she did but no I haven't had a text</u>
<u n="740" who="S0558">oh</u>
<u n="741" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="742" who="S0558">I'll check that you're meant to</u>
<u n="743" who="S0517">don't worry cos to be honest we're out on the <trunc>Thurs</trunc> we're out on the Friday night as well</u>
<u n="744" who="S0558">oh that's alright</u>
<u n="745" who="S0517">the eleventh</u>
<u n="746" who="S0558">you're alright</u>
<u n="747" who="S0517">and the thirteenth we're busy as well I've gotta take <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> to <anon type="place"/> university first thing in the morning for another tennis course</u>
<u n="748" who="S0558">but it's from three or four o'clock yeah so</u>
<u n="749" who="S0517" trans="overlap">but it's er it's the afternoon she said wasn't it? yes yeah no it would be nice I haven't had a text it would be nice though</u>
<u n="750" who="S0558">oh well we'll be seeing her on the ninth</u>
<u n="751" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="752" who="S0558">so erm <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="753" who="S0517">and also on the sixth I'm going <unclear/> on Sunday you know <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in work? <unclear/> you don't know him I've talked about him</u>
<u n="754" who="S0558" trans="overlap">I don't know him but you've talked about him yeah</u>
<u n="755" who="S0517">he's adopted did you know the adoption went through? he's adopted two little girls he and his wife</u>
<u n="756" who="S0558">ah</u>
<u n="757" who="S0517">oh yes and he's having an er</u>
<u n="758" who="S0558">siblings?</u>
<u n="759" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="760" who="S0558"><vocal desc="gasp"/> ah</u>
<u n="761" who="S0517">I think they're half-siblings I don't think they've got the same dads same mum er two and five</u>
<u n="762" who="S0558">ah ah bless</u>
<u n="763" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so erm he's having an adoption party</u>
<u n="764" who="S0558">oh how lovely</u>
<u n="765" who="S0517">it <trunc>i</trunc> er the I'll show you the invitation actually in the kitchen it's a really lovely invitation really really nicely done</u>
<u n="766" who="S0558" trans="overlap">they made it themselves?</u>
<u n="767" who="S0517">I think so let me just grab it</u>
<u n="768" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh we won't have time to do that after Sunday will we?</u>
<u n="769" who="S0517">no no they only want they only have they've been with them since</u>
<u n="770" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh really?</u>
<u n="771" who="S0517">oh about Easter</u>
<u n="772" who="S0558"><vocal desc="gasp"/></u>
<u n="773" who="S0517">but it's only just legalised <unclear/></u>
<u n="774" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh <pause dur="short"/></u>
<u n="775" who="S0517">yes er the but even though <trunc>th</trunc>they did get the girls they then had to go back to court <unclear/></u>
<u n="776" who="S0558">oh yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="777" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it's alright I'll get them</u>
<u n="778" who="S0558">it's erm</u>
<u n="779" who="S0517">oh if I can get up</u>
<u n="780" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="781" who="S0517">it's <trunc>ta</trunc> it's taken oh the procedure's so long-winded</u>
<u n="782" who="S0558">I know but erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="783" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it it's unbelievable</u>
<u n="784" who="S0558">many years on isn't it? but <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> previously adopted</u>
<u n="785" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yes yeah</u>
<u n="786" who="S0558">I know it's <trunc>n</trunc> <unclear>another</unclear> actually I think there was something on the radio about that a week or so ago about trying to speed up the process yeah</u>
<u n="787" who="S0517" trans="overlap">to <trunc>p</trunc> I heard that trying to make it quicker <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="788" who="S0558">ah</u>
<u n="789" who="S0517">but erm <unclear/></u>
<u n="790" who="S0558">oh right two dogs</u>
<u n="791" who="S0517">oh yeah</u>
<u n="792" who="S0558"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> what a lovely name <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="793" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I know</u>
<u n="794" who="S0558">we <trunc>di</trunc> we didn't we didn't give you the gift of life but life has given us the gift of you</u>
<u n="795" who="S0517">oh isn't that lovely? I just thought ah</u>
<u n="796" who="S0558">that is so lovely</u>
<u n="797" who="S0517">so that's next erm Sunday so they have had the girls living with them oh it was so funny when they first got them because they got them at Easter and so of course the elder one erm was in reception obviously the two year old's preschool so <trunc>th</trunc> she <trunc>th</trunc>they'd been breaking her in er to to the new school and everything where she lived and erm I was in work I mean I'm only in work one day a week but the day I was in <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> was on the phone to his wife and I could er you know there was nobody else in so I couldn't help but just completely listen to the one half of the conversation <vocal desc="laugh"/> and he just went I'm sorry? a what? a summer dress? they've only been there she's only been in school three days what about all the uniform we've bought? <vocal desc="laugh"/> and he put the phone down I went oh yeah did nobody tell you?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="799" who="S0517">soon as Easter's done and dusted they're allowed to wear summer dresses it's the summer uniform <unclear/></u>
<u n="800" who="S0558" trans="overlap">summer dresses</u>
<u n="801" who="S0517">and he went bloody hell she went <vocal desc="laugh"/> it was just so funny</u>
<u n="802" who="S0558" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="803" who="S0517">and he's just like there's so much that erm he's on this learning curve with but anyway I just thought that was a really lovely invitation I know</u>
<u n="804" who="S0558" trans="overlap">that is a lovely lovely invitation</u>
<u n="805" who="S0517">but I don't know what to take as a gift</u>
<u n="806" who="S0558" trans="overlap">er talk about go on</u>
<u n="807" who="S0517">or whether to just put erm cheques cos I'm assuming that he'll've opened them</u>
<u n="808" who="S0558">what about like a savings bond or something? for each of them</u>
<u n="809" who="S0517" trans="overlap">building society account</u>
<u n="810" who="S0558">you know those erm bonds you can get</u>
<u n="811" who="S0517" trans="overlap">the the yes well either that or I was just gonna make cheques out to the girls cos I assume he'll've opened up accounts for them <pause dur="short"/> I don't cos I don't know what to get whether you get presents for the parents presents for the children</u>
<u n="812" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="813" who="S0517"><trunc>presen</trunc> er er</u>
<u n="814" who="S0558">unless you buy a family what about a nice family ticket to the pictures?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0517">oh something like I could do actually</u>
<u n="816" who="S0558">so it's a family it's reinforcing family again isn't it? through the gift</u>
<u n="817" who="S0517" trans="overlap">it <trunc>i</trunc> yes cos when <trunc>th</trunc> when they got them erm at work I think <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> got them like erm an annual pass to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="818" who="S0558">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="819" who="S0517">for the family something I could do something like that actually <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="820" who="S0558">so they have er they're having time out</u>
<u n="821" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="822" who="S0558">as a family</u>
<u n="823" who="S0517" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="824" who="S0558">it's reinforcing family isn't it?</u>
<u n="825" who="S0517">yes yeah so anyway</u>
<u n="826" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear>something nice</unclear></u>
<u n="827" who="S0517">I've got that on Sunday but I'm looking forward to that that should be nice</u>
<u n="828" who="S0558">that'll be lovely are you all going?</u>
<u n="829" who="S0517">er we were all invited but just <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I are going <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'ll be playing football</u>
<u n="830" who="S0558" trans="overlap">mm mm</u>
<u n="831" who="S0517">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> said I don't want to be adopted and I don't want to adopt anyone so why would I go? <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I mean I'm when I wrote back I said thank you very much for the invitation it'll just be <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I <vocal desc="laugh"/> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is playing football and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s just well he's sixteen say no more</u>
<u n="832" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="833" who="S0517">he doesn't want to come <vocal desc="laugh"/> but <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> are going as well</u>
<u n="834" who="S0558">oh that'll be so lovely yeah</u>
<u n="835" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and so are <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="836" who="S0558">oh how lovely</u>
<u n="837" who="S0517" trans="overlap">so yeah so that's nice</u>
<u n="838" who="S0558">I really like the RSVP to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> blah or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> blah or</u>
<u n="839" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="840" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="841" who="S0517">ah</u>
<u n="842" who="S0558">but yeah so I just do think that was real really nice the way they put the little</u>
<u n="843" who="S0517">two little blonde girls yeah</u>
<u n="844" who="S0558">that is so lovely talking about one way <trunc>con</trunc> hear overhearing a conversation I was working at <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="845" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="846" who="S0558">on Friday</u>
<u n="847" who="S0517">mm</u>
<u n="848" who="S0558">and erm this lady had come in and she'd she'd asked me for this thing and and I said oh I said I'm ever so sorry they've sold out I said and I only know that because somebody else has not long asked for them and they've moved the display thing that it was something <unclear/></u>
<u n="849" who="S0517" trans="overlap">and what? she asked you for something in <anon type="place"/>? and you don't work at <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="850" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah she said to me oh do you? oh I get asked oh my goodness</u>
<u n="851" who="S0517" trans="overlap">do you?</u>
<u n="852" who="S0558">I I'm <trunc>pai</trunc> like I'm I'm in Debenhams for example and somebody'll be looking a bit lost and I'll say are you okay? and they'll go oh I've lost my wife or I've lost my husband and I go two options run quick</u>
<u n="853" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="854" who="S0558">or I can help you find them <vocal desc="laugh"/> and then I get people coming and going excuse me love could you tell me where? and I go well I am but I'll try</u>
<u n="855" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="856" who="S0517">I don't actually work for the shop oh right so what did she ask for in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="857" who="S0558" trans="overlap">but so this lady came in something they've advertised twenty-five pounds something and it's obviously one of their specials or something so I said to her oh er erm she came in and she said <trunc>d</trunc> <trunc>s</trunc> do you know where blah? and I said oh I said they've sold out I said and I only know that because on the display <trunc>sta</trunc> oh she said I said erm but look I said you never know they erm <trunc>th</trunc>they might be as we speak fetching some out from the back or perhaps you could order online? and she said <unclear/></u>
<u n="858" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you are helpful <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="859" who="S0558">so she's standing there and then all of a sudden she sees a lady that she knows so it's all like <vocal desc="misc"/> how are you? you know how it is so erm I <trunc>d</trunc> I don't know what they sort of the initial question was or whatever but it went on like this so the lady who's looking to buy something she said yes <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she said well what happened she said I was babysitting for my daughter and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> as you know lives across the road she said it was New Year see and erm she said fortunately for me she said I got up and before the children got up I had a shower got dressed put my makeup on she said so I looked half decent and the other lady's laughing she said and all of a sudden the doorbell rang she said so I opened the door and there was <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> she said so he took one step in she said he put both his hands on the side of my face and he gave me this big <vocal desc="misc"/> kiss</u>
<u n="860" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="861" who="S0558">right on the lips</u>
<u n="862" who="S0517">what? and he's just the man that lives across the road?</u>
<u n="863" who="S0558">from her daughter</u>
<u n="864" who="S0517" trans="overlap">from the daughter</u>
<u n="865" who="S0558">so she said <vocal desc="laugh"/> made me laugh she said gave me this big kiss <vocal desc="misc"/> she said not you know? like you know what I mean? it was just a peck</u>
<u n="866" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="867" who="S0558">the other one's going oh yeah like this you know? so she said well I was a bit taken aback she said I sort of I took a step back and then she said well she said he must feel something she said because he said to me happy New Year <pause dur="short"/> shall we go out for a drink?</u>
<u n="868" who="S0517">oh</u>
<u n="869" who="S0558">she said and I sort of composed myself she said <vocal desc="laugh"/> I was all a bit and I said oh well yes that would be very nice so she said a couple of weeks later we went out for a drink she said and we got back about quarter to eleven and he said to me would you like to come in for a cup of coffee? so she's back to his house opposite the daughter you see</u>
<u n="870" who="S0517" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="871" who="S0558">she's obviously stopping at the daughter's so she said I went in for a cup of coffee she said well she said it was about ten to twelve she said when I you know? scuttled across the road she said</u>
<u n="872" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> feeling like a naughty teenager</u>
<u n="873" who="S0558" trans="overlap">she said and I she said I've opened the door ever so quietly she said and I walked in and my daughter was sitting there on the settee and she said and what time do you call this?</u>
<u n="874" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="875" who="S0558">well I'm standing there listening to this conversation with a big smile on my face thinking</u>
<u n="876" who="S0517" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> laughing</u>
<u n="877" who="S0558">how lovely I hear so many sad stories so she said erm she said yes so she said we've been together since then she said</u>
<u n="878" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">oh</u>
<u n="879" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">and erm she said oh it's all very lovely</u>
<u n="880" who="S0517">how handy that he lives across the road <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="881" who="S0558" trans="overlap">she well she said it's all very lovely she said but she said when I'm at his house they know</u>
<u n="882" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="883" who="S0558">so her friend turned round and said well you're going to have to invite him to yours more often so they don't know that you're together she said I'm going to have to she said because I'll get texts saying mm nice time at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s last night mum?</u>
<u n="884" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="885" who="S0558">and I thought oh how lovely</u>
<u n="886" who="S0517" trans="overlap">ah well she'll have to start getting the bus and not driving or leaving the car <unclear/></u>
<u n="887" who="S0558" trans="overlap">er er yeah yeah or or yeah or getting dropped off by a taxi but she was I would say she was in her early seventies</u>
<u n="888" who="S0517">oh really?</u>
<u n="889" who="S0558">and I thought oh what a lovely story</u>
<u n="890" who="S0517" trans="overlap">ah that's nice yes</u>
<u n="891" who="S0558">he's obviously <trunc>admi</trunc> he's widowed as well</u>
<u n="892" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="893" who="S0558">so he's obviously admired her</u>
<u n="894" who="S0517">yes</u>
<u n="895" who="S0558">from his lounge window when she's to-ing and fro-ing to her daughters <unclear/></u>
<u n="896" who="S0517">ah that is nice</u>
<u n="897" who="S0558">and I thought oh how lovely</u>
<u n="898" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="899" who="UNKMULTI" whoConfidence="low"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="900" who="S0517">oh <trunc>ble</trunc></u>
<u n="901" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low"><unclear>how funny</unclear></u>
<u n="902" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> oh I said I really wanted to turn around and say oh I'm so pleased for you</u>
<u n="903" who="S0517">I'm surprised you didn't <unclear/> you should've done</u>
<u n="904" who="S0558">I know I was trying to control myself</u>
<u n="905" who="S0517">yeah</u>
<u n="906" who="S0558">I said to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> probably if I hadn't been in my greens I probably would've done</u>
<u n="907" who="S0517"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="908" who="S0558">but but</u>
<u n="909" who="S0517" trans="overlap">in my greens</u>
<u n="910" who="S0558">cos I'm in my greens potentially like one of your people was listening in on my conversations <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="911" who="S0517">oh yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> yes yeah that's true actually</u>
<u n="912" who="S0558">so er</u>
<u n="913" who="S0517">that might be frowned upon do you want another coffee <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="914" who="S0558" trans="overlap">yeah oh yes please</u>
<u n="915" who="S0517">do you want? do you want something to eat?</u>
<u n="916" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="917" who="S0517">I feel like you're</u>
<u n="918" who="S0558">no no no I'm gonna have one more biscuit</u>
<u n="919" who="S0517">okay</u>
<u n="920" who="S0558"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="921" who="S0517">right</u>
<u n="922" who="S0558">I'm trying to be good</u>
<u n="923" who="S0517">I'll fetch <unclear/></u>
<u n="924" who="S0558" trans="overlap"><unclear/> two biscuits left do you want me to?</u>
<u n="925" who="S0517">er what?</u>
<u n="926" who="S0558" trans="overlap">come with you and help?</u>
<u n="927" who="S0517">oh shall I pause that?</u>
<u n="928" who="S0558">oh can you do that?</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
