<text id="SRU7">
	<header>
		<rec_length>1:00:29</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-01-27</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>3</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0588 S0589 S0613</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>(ANON’s home):</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Exercising, house prices, cooking</topics>
		<activity>Chat with sister. </activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0588">
				<exactage>49</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>England</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Standard English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>49 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Trascriber</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>6</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0589">
				<exactage>40</exactage>
				<age1994>35_44</age1994>
				<agerange>40_49</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Edinburgh</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Britain</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Standard English</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>London</hab_city>
				<hab_country>UK</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>11 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Administrator</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0613">
				<exactage>54</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Isleworth, Midd'x</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>home counties/RP</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Landry</hab_city>
				<hab_country>France</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>13 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>unspecified</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Writer</occupation>
				<socgrade>B</socgrade>
				<nssec>2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0588">it's like an old an old tape recorder so</u>
<u n="2" who="S0613" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> oh oh that's great isn't it?</u>
<u n="3" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/> you can't get easier than that really</u>
<u n="4" who="S0613" trans="overlap">there's something rather comforting about that isn't it?</u>
<u n="5" who="S0588" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> it is isn't it?</u>
<u n="6" who="S0613" trans="overlap">oh it's going round</u>
<u n="7" who="S0588">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0613" trans="overlap">that means it's yes recording</u>
<u n="9" who="S0588" trans="overlap">press record I'm still in the old-school way of doing things</u>
<u n="10" who="S0613">right so the green light means it's recording?</u>
<u n="11" who="S0588">well it's going round so that always used to mean</u>
<u n="12" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="13" who="S0588">it's recording <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="14" who="S0613">right <vocal desc="laugh"/> yeah or some of them yeah the more sophisticated one you had to get a certain coloured light on as well didn't you?</u>
<u n="15" who="S0588">oh I don't know</u>
<u n="16" who="S0613">yeah</u>
<u n="17" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I can't remember but er</u>
<u n="18" who="S0613" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="19" who="S0588">gosh those were the days everything physical none of this digital crap erm yeah stomach enzymes what were we saying? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="20" who="S0613">no you were you were saying that</u>
<u n="21" who="S0588">oh it's very interesting anyway yeah er that you do have some control over it and I know for fact that well <pause dur="short"/> some control over your body there is some control over</u>
<u n="22" who="S0613">yes <trunc>th</trunc></u>
<u n="23" who="S0588" trans="overlap">your body there there definitely is</u>
<u n="24" who="S0613">in everything that you've read though does your as you get older does your body change?</u>
<u n="25" who="S0588">uhu</u>
<u n="26" who="S0613">because something I've noticed I I've suddenly erm I'm definitely getting middle-aged spread</u>
<u n="27" who="S0588">well there's reasons for that and</u>
<u n="28" who="S0613" trans="overlap">well it's my age I should imagine is one of them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="29" who="S0588">yeah but there's also some control over that as well depending on and I can't remember I've just read the <vocal desc="laugh"/> books on it I can't remember what the thing is that you do but erm that's to do with like sugar levels as well</u>
<u n="30" who="S0613" trans="overlap">what there are certain foods you can eat?</u>
<u n="31" who="S0588">yeah there's all that erm but the worst culprits to simplify it the culprits are sugar alcohol glucose erm probably dairy but I don't think dairy's as bad erm cheese is quite bad but er yeah sugar and alcohol <unclear/></u>
<u n="32" who="S0613" trans="overlap">but that's natural sugars as well you're talking about?</u>
<u n="33" who="S0588">and natural sugars so erm although not nearly as bad but if you were to eat a piece of fruit you've got all the fibre and all the good things as well so that in context is still good</u>
<u n="34" who="S0613" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="35" who="S0588">but if you also mix it with a lunch that has other things that aren't sweet or you can put it in with a savoury thing as well then it doesn't have the bad blood sugar effect</u>
<u n="36" who="S0613" trans="overlap">right</u>
<u n="37" who="S0588">erm but I know for a fact and how I know for a fact that it has a bearing on one's body what one eats is I get these flabby earlobes I've got flabby earlobe syndrome <vocal desc="laugh"/> and erm it gets kind of lumpy under my ears when I have lots of sugar it gets</u>
<u n="38" who="S0613">really?</u>
<u n="39" who="S0588" trans="overlap">really lumpy yes</u>
<u n="40" who="S0613">god I've never heard of that</u>
<u n="41" who="S0588">yeah that's a fatty thing it's a fatty inflammation thing</u>
<u n="42" who="S0613" trans="overlap">well I've got pierced ears though so maybe would</u>
<u n="43" who="S0588">no</u>
<u n="44" who="S0613">the same thing happen?</u>
<u n="45" who="S0588">no you've got I you've got different earlobes to me so probably not</u>
<u n="46" who="S0613" trans="overlap">so I wouldn't tend to get the syndrome anyway even if</u>
<u n="47" who="S0588">no it's not a syndrome</u>
<u n="48" who="S0613" trans="overlap">it it might</u>
<u n="49" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I've just made up the syndrome</u>
<u n="50" who="S0613"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="51" who="S0588">but I just know that I get flabby earlobes and that's to do with sort of inflammation and deposits of crap and <vocal desc="laugh"/> all sorts</u>
<u n="52" who="S0613" trans="overlap">well I tell what I've noticed I've noticed I'm getting a layer of fat on the back of my neck</u>
<u n="53" who="S0588">well yes it crops up in many strange places yeah</u>
<u n="54" who="S0613" trans="overlap">which I never used to have I caught sight of myself in a changing room mirror you know when</u>
<u n="55" who="S0588" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="56" who="S0613" trans="overlap">you can see the back of yourself and I suddenly thought</u>
<u n="57" who="S0588">and suddenly the back of you</u>
<u n="58" who="S0613" trans="overlap">I never used to look like that</u>
<u n="59" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0613">I've just this kind of extra layer of fat round there</u>
<u n="61" who="S0588">no it it comes in really strange places and that's to do with your eating as well because it will kind of store things but if you eat it the right way it won't store things erm</u>
<u n="62" who="S0613">mm</u>
<u n="63" who="S0588" trans="overlap">so there's a very straightforward er scientific thing you can do in around how you eat but the first thing is glucose and sugar and alcohol it really is</u>
<u n="64" who="S0613" trans="overlap">I've always I've always gone before on how I feel rather than how I look</u>
<u n="65" who="S0588">mm</u>
<u n="66" who="S0613">so</u>
<u n="67" who="S0588">looks are quite a good barometer though I find</u>
<u n="68" who="S0613">yeah I mean the fact okay like the an extra layer of fat on the back of my neck er I don't I don't it doesn't I don't feel bad about it other than when I see it</u>
<u n="69" who="S0588" trans="overlap">it doesn't it yeah it yeah</u>
<u n="70" who="S0613" trans="overlap">and then I go oh that's not very nice <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="71" who="S0588">it doesn't hurt I mean getting erm thing these things</u>
<u n="72" who="S0613" trans="overlap">oh batwings</u>
<u n="73" who="S0588">batwings</u>
<u n="74" who="S0613">yes</u>
<u n="75" who="S0588">that doesn't hurt it's not painful but it's just bloody what the fuck?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="77" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="78" who="S0613">oh yeah no it's</u>
<u n="79" who="S0588" trans="overlap">because I didn't no I noticed that in my thirties that everything was going a little bit</u>
<u n="80" who="S0613">going south</u>
<u n="81" who="S0588">well just not as er taut and firm as it was so I started exercising straightaway and it sorted it out the only problem is you do have to work you have to keep working hard at it</u>
<u n="82" who="S0613">yeah</u>
<u n="83" who="S0588">but that's the only way</u>
<u n="84" who="S0613">well have you erm</u>
<u n="85" who="S0588" trans="overlap">to keep it at bay</u>
<u n="86" who="S0613">have you ever read interviews with oh god who's this Gillian Lynne? she's a a choreographer but she was a dancer she's now god in er well into her eighties</u>
<u n="87" who="S0588">uhu</u>
<u n="88" who="S0613">erm and she's still dancing she has this</u>
<u n="89" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="90" who="S0613" trans="overlap">regime she gets up every morning</u>
<u n="91" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="92" who="S0613">and she's had two hip replacement operations as well <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="93" who="S0588">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0613" trans="overlap">but she still does it all</u>
<u n="95" who="S0588">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0613">she's absolutely incredible but she says the thing is it gets harder every day</u>
<u n="97" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="98" who="S0613" trans="overlap">it gets harder so it requires more effort</u>
<u n="99" who="S0588">well your body has changed you I think you have to accept that your body's not the same as it was when you were twenty it starts to change in the thirties but it's radically changed by the time you're reached sort of over fifties it really has so you have to adapt and and change your your whole everything really</u>
<u n="100" who="S0613">but it seems to to maintain <trunc>th</trunc> your the physicality you had when you were younger you have to keep</u>
<u n="101" who="S0588">work harder</u>
<u n="102" who="S0613" trans="overlap">work harder</u>
<u n="103" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="104" who="S0613">and that that just <trunc>ge</trunc> you work harder and harder and harder</u>
<u n="105" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0613">as each</u>
<u n="107" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0613">each year goes by</u>
<u n="109" who="S0588">but</u>
<u n="110" who="S0613" trans="overlap">which is kind of there must come a point where you got I just <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="111" who="S0588">no</u>
<u n="112" who="S0613">I can't</u>
<u n="113" who="S0588">not quite because if you do the right sort of exercise you don't have to exert yourself too much it only takes ten minutes a day to keep it all together really</u>
<u n="114" who="S0613">what are you talking about aerobic exercise or?</u>
<u n="115" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah yeah or weights are really important cos that kind of makes everything come together again <vocal desc="laugh"/> but erm resistance a little <trunc>b</trunc> a little bit of resistance exercise and a tiny bit of aerobic but not whole cos that's actually really ageing if you do the whole really going for it thing or jogging that's really ageing</u>
<u n="116" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yeah cos everything just bounces about and it</u>
<u n="117" who="S0588" trans="overlap">and it's just like yeah</u>
<u n="118" who="S0613" trans="overlap">and you can feel it tugging at your</u>
<u n="119" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah no no don't</u>
<u n="120" who="S0613" trans="overlap">your your everything bouncing and tugging</u>
<u n="121" who="S0588" trans="overlap">don't do it it's</u>
<u n="122" who="S0613">yeah</u>
<u n="123" who="S0588" trans="overlap">just it's the worst</u>
<u n="124" who="S0613">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0588" trans="overlap">it's it has to be gentle and no no big er sort of erm bumps or anything like that</u>
<u n="126" who="S0613" trans="overlap">no jerky yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0588" trans="overlap">no jerky stuff</u>
<u n="128" who="S0613">that's why erm</u>
<u n="129" who="S0588" trans="overlap">just really gentle</u>
<u n="130" who="S0613">that's why I love yoga I absolutely adore yoga</u>
<u n="131" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0613">because also it it makes me feel so because it's all you kind of</u>
<u n="133" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="134" who="S0613">go inside yourself and</u>
<u n="135" who="S0588" trans="overlap">well it opens up all the energy blocked energy things and then everything starts flowing energetically nicely between the body and that's what you ultimately really so that's lovely I don't think though yoga's enough or in itself cos you need just a little bit of sort of resistance and</u>
<u n="136" who="S0613">mm</u>
<u n="137" who="S0588">erm er <pause dur="short"/> aerobic</u>
<u n="138" who="S0613" trans="overlap">to really make make</u>
<u n="139" who="S0588" trans="overlap">a tiny bit</u>
<u n="140" who="S0613">well something that's making the muscles work hard so that they're</u>
<u n="141" who="S0588" trans="overlap">because they're losing something they're <trunc>lo</trunc> literally losing some whatever it is they're losing so they become weaker</u>
<u n="142" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0588">and that is also the reason why people shrink when they get older as well so <trunc>mas</trunc> muscle mass or <trunc>so</trunc> bone something or other</u>
<u n="144" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="145" who="S0588" trans="overlap">density</u>
<u n="146" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="147" who="S0588">goes</u>
<u n="148" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0588">less and it's all to do with the hormones and everything erm so that that's changed fact that won't you can't change the fact that the body has changed but if you erm do certain sorts of exercises you can kind of slow down the process</u>
<u n="150" who="S0613">mm</u>
<u n="151" who="S0588">and feel better really erm so</u>
<u n="152" who="S0613" trans="overlap">is there any more tea in the pot?</u>
<u n="153" who="S0588">yeah and I'll get some milk</u>
<u n="154" who="S0613">I'm gonna put the tea in first I I erm</u>
<u n="155" who="S0588">okay you're a tea first girl</u>
<u n="156" who="S0613" trans="overlap">oh <trunc>t</trunc> yeah cos then you can you can add the milk till it's the right colour</u>
<u n="157" who="S0588">yes true</u>
<u n="158" who="S0613" trans="overlap">if you've already put the milk in there's no going back is there?</u>
<u n="159" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0613">sorry do you want some more? or</u>
<u n="161" who="S0588">yeah I've got plenty</u>
<u n="162" who="S0613" trans="overlap">I'll let you do your own</u>
<u n="163" who="S0588">do you want to do it yourself?</u>
<u n="164" who="S0613">yeah I'll do it myself yes it's</u>
<u n="165" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="166" who="S0613">bit easier</u>
<u n="167" who="S0588">but oh I'm absolutely certain that we have some control over it but yeah simple things er which I haven't done in the last few days like I say cos I need to do a whole new shop for vegetables but er sugar alcohol gluten they're the worst but you don't have to come off them completely but just cut down</u>
<u n="168" who="S0613">mm</u>
<u n="169" who="S0588">right</u>
<u n="170" who="S0613">no I guess I should have one one last bash at erm before it all fully falls apart</u>
<u n="171" who="S0588">I don't think it needs to fall apart</u>
<u n="172" who="S0613">it's quite erm it requires er a lot of erm headspace to concentrate on it you know?</u>
<u n="173" who="S0588">it does what er to concentrate on not falling apart?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0613">yes</u>
<u n="175" who="S0588">yes it does it's a whole area of study <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="176" who="S0613">yeah and there's other things <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="177" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="178" who="S0613" trans="overlap">I I <vocal desc="laugh"/> rather be doing to be</u>
<u n="179" who="S0588">but those other things you need a body for and I think it's important to give it head space cos those other things are dependent on your body</u>
<u n="180" who="S0613">yes oh no that is true and it's all linked isn't it? and with your mind and everything else no you are right really</u>
<u n="181" who="S0588">so the body is ultimate <pause dur="short"/> temple?</u>
<u n="182" who="S0613"><vocal desc="laugh"/> I knew you were going to say that <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's going to be said at some point</u>
<u n="183" who="S0588" trans="overlap">it was going there <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="184" who="S0613"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="185" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="186" who="S0613">my body is a temple</u>
<u n="187" who="S0588" trans="overlap">so it it all comes through your body all the creativity so without that and if you get ill and stuff <pause dur="short"/> but I dunno I think people are rather passive about it I think there is a lot more that you can do I don't think it's as simple as oh I'm ageing that's that</u>
<u n="188" who="S0613" trans="overlap">so therefore it's all going to yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah it's not it there's it's not as straightforward as that</u>
<u n="190" who="S0613">yes I've got a sinking feeling you're probably right and I'm just saying that <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="191" who="S0588">well it's easier to but I mean how great to know that you do have some control over it</u>
<u n="192" who="S0613" trans="overlap">well you have a choice if you if you're</u>
<u n="193" who="S0588">you've got a choice</u>
<u n="194" who="S0613" trans="overlap">if you're prepared to put the time and the energy in</u>
<u n="195" who="S0588">mm</u>
<u n="196" who="S0613" trans="overlap">you you can</u>
<u n="197" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="198" who="S0613">to a certain extent erm</u>
<u n="199" who="S0588">uhu it is to an extent but you can actually feel better <pause dur="short"/> for it you can feel younger and feel better just healthier or whatever it is</u>
<u n="200" who="S0613" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="201" who="S0588">but I'm only doing it because I haven't finished with the music and I I'm such a late starter that by the time I get some money I want to enjoy it <vocal desc="laugh"/> I want to still have a body</u>
<u n="202" who="S0613">yes yeah</u>
<u n="203" who="S0588" trans="overlap">and all that that's</u>
<u n="204" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="205" who="S0588" trans="overlap">the only reason I'm not prepared to just let it all</u>
<u n="206" who="S0613">yeah it's difficult</u>
<u n="207" who="S0588" trans="overlap">go yet</u>
<u n="208" who="S0613">what I'm finding difficult is erm <pause dur="short"/> is cos my work is so sedentary I can't say that word <trunc>sed</trunc><trunc>sede</trunc><trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="209" who="S0588" trans="overlap">well yeah</u>
<u n="210" who="S0613">yeah not</u>
<u n="211" who="S0588" trans="overlap">sitting</u>
<u n="212" who="S0613">not moving around</u>
<u n="213" who="S0588">mm</u>
<u n="214" who="S0613" trans="overlap">erm and if if it's going well the writing's going well I actually hours will go and I'll forget to move <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="215" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="216" who="S0613">whereas erm <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="217" who="S0588">yeah you should move you should</u>
<u n="218" who="S0613">I know</u>
<u n="219" who="S0588" trans="overlap">remember to move</u>
<u n="220" who="S0613">I know</u>
<u n="221" who="S0588" trans="overlap">just a little break and and a home workout that's all it takes</u>
<u n="222" who="S0613">you erm what do you think about this fashion now for er <trunc>t</trunc> for working standing up? you can get special desks can't you that erm?</u>
<u n="223" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I don't know that sounds quite</u>
<u n="224" who="S0613">yeah there are special desks</u>
<u n="225" who="S0588" trans="overlap">interesting</u>
<u n="226" who="S0613">you don't stand the whole time but erm you stand for some of the time and so it's a desk that will convert from a a sit-down desk to a <trunc>s</trunc></u>
<u n="227" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="228" who="S0613">it'll just raise up and you</u>
<u n="229" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah I like the sound of that</u>
<u n="230" who="S0613" trans="overlap">you stand for a bit yeah</u>
<u n="231" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="232" who="S0613">they reckon it's cos we evidently we're not designed to actually erm</u>
<u n="233" who="S0588" trans="overlap">no we're not no</u>
<u n="234" who="S0613">sit down for long periods of time</u>
<u n="235" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="236" who="S0613">our backs aren't designed for it</u>
<u n="237" who="S0588" trans="overlap">oh but I mean</u>
<u n="238" who="S0613" trans="overlap">and our internal organs get all squashed and</u>
<u n="239" who="S0588" trans="overlap">bit yes yeah it's er it's not right we're meant to do different things <pause dur="short"/> you know a bit of variation</u>
<u n="240" who="S0613" trans="overlap">well I suppose we are actually supposed to be erm active aren't we? if we were hunter gatherers we would be active all the time</u>
<u n="241" who="S0588">mm we'd be doing various different things I think er er on a physical level yeah <pause dur="short"/> mm</u>
<u n="242" who="S0613" trans="overlap">so erm maybe I need to need like some pedals under my desk and you could</u>
<u n="243" who="S0588" trans="overlap">how's your erm that hormone thing?</u>
<u n="244" who="S0613">HRT?</u>
<u n="245" who="S0588">yeah you don't have to talk about it if you don't want to <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="246" who="S0613">no no cos I no I mean the it's funny</u>
<u n="247" who="S0588" trans="overlap">it's only going down for posterity</u>
<u n="248" who="S0613" trans="overlap">no I was I was just thinking actually that erm er so I'm on my third month now and it it actually I feel like I've been asleep it's waking me up</u>
<u n="249" who="S0588">oh that's so interesting so you're on actual hormone replacement therapy then?</u>
<u n="250" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="251" who="S0588">the hormone replacement therapy?</u>
<u n="252" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yes very low</u>
<u n="253" who="S0588" trans="overlap">gosh</u>
<u n="254" who="S0613">they'll be the lowest level you can be on cos it's</u>
<u n="255" who="S0588" trans="overlap">because all your symptoms according to the book I've been reading</u>
<u n="256" who="S0613">mm</u>
<u n="257" who="S0588" trans="overlap">have come up in that book</u>
<u n="258" who="S0613">yeah</u>
<u n="259" who="S0588" trans="overlap">and and all the emotional thing as well came up as well</u>
<u n="260" who="S0613" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="261" who="S0588">and I thought god that's just exactly what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was er explaining</u>
<u n="262" who="S0613">well it's gone away</u>
<u n="263" who="S0588" trans="overlap">and er</u>
<u n="264" who="S0613" trans="overlap">now all those symptoms</u>
<u n="265" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="266" who="S0613">I don't the hot flushes anymore I don't have</u>
<u n="267" who="S0588">no</u>
<u n="268" who="S0613" trans="overlap">the horrible <trunc>palpita</trunc>palpitations</u>
<u n="269" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="270" who="S0613">and the kind of panic attacks</u>
<u n="271" who="S0588" trans="overlap">this is the <unclear/> panic er reaction yeah</u>
<u n="272" who="S0613" trans="overlap">I'm not so tired anymore</u>
<u n="273" who="S0588" trans="overlap">that's cortisol something like that</u>
<u n="274" who="S0613">yeah it's cos it's actually was</u>
<u n="275" who="S0588" trans="overlap">the hormones going haywire</u>
<u n="276" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yeah it sends a message to <trunc>s</trunc> to the</u>
<u n="277" who="S0588" trans="overlap">to panic</u>
<u n="278" who="S0613" trans="overlap">pituitary gland</u>
<u n="279" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="280" who="S0613">yeah? which sends messages to your brain</u>
<u n="281" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="282" who="S0613">and it's it produces adrenalin and so it was</u>
<u n="283" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0613" trans="overlap">it was all just going completely</u>
<u n="285" who="S0588">cos the book is saying that you can sort of balance it all out anyway</u>
<u n="286" who="S0613" trans="overlap">with with diet</u>
<u n="287" who="S0588">with diet</u>
<u n="288" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yes people have said that to me</u>
<u n="289" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I mean it's probably the same function that erm you know maybe er a broccoli would do <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="290" who="S0613">yeah</u>
<u n="291" who="S0588" trans="overlap">would do the <vocal desc="laugh"/> however you get there it doesn't really matter but erm yeah</u>
<u n="292" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yeah cos I tried all the er the remedies you can buy yourself</u>
<u n="293" who="S0588">yes yeah</u>
<u n="294" who="S0613" trans="overlap">you know like the evening primrose oil <trunc>co</trunc> wasn't it cohosh?</u>
<u n="295" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I I think that you have to be very extreme about it to do the erm <pause dur="short"/> the vegetable remedies if you're gonna do it you'd have to</u>
<u n="296" who="S0613" trans="overlap">also I should imagine</u>
<u n="297" who="S0588">really do it</u>
<u n="298" who="S0613" trans="overlap">it would take a lot of trial and error cos you'd have to keep trying things wouldn't you to see what made a difference</u>
<u n="299" who="S0588" trans="overlap">well my diet is really extreme when I do the it's like whole thing put it in the bloody Nutribullet <vocal desc="laugh"/> and it's like oh it tastes horrible you know <vocal desc="laugh"/> so I'm quite extreme about it so I and I think that you would need to be quite extreme about it</u>
<u n="300" who="S0613" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="301" who="S0588">no namby-pamby oh it tastes horrible oh</u>
<u n="302" who="S0613">yeah</u>
<u n="303" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I'm not having that no none of that just get it down you sort of thing erm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0613">but no I I feel like I've erm got my sanity back not that I was</u>
<u n="305" who="S0588" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="306" who="S0613" trans="overlap">going completely mad but it's only now I'm kind of I feel like I'm coming out of a fog and I'm going</u>
<u n="307" who="S0588" trans="overlap">well it would make you feel like that</u>
<u n="308" who="S0613" trans="overlap">and</u>
<u n="309" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="310" who="S0613" trans="overlap">and that's also why I'm now looking at myself and going mm my body's changed hasn't it? and I think I wasn't really noticing before</u>
<u n="311" who="S0588" trans="overlap">and the thing you can only now look at yourself and go mm my body's changed sensibly look at yourself and go like that because you've had the</u>
<u n="312" who="S0613">yeah</u>
<u n="313" who="S0588">thing so that's really good</u>
<u n="314" who="S0613">but I think the er what's what I find really interesting is I didn't it's only now that I realised how much it was affecting me</u>
<u n="315" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="316" who="S0613" trans="overlap">the whole menopause</u>
<u n="317" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0613" trans="overlap">thing erm which actually is quite worrying cos you think how many I could have gone on for years because</u>
<u n="319" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="320" who="S0613" trans="overlap">a lot of people er sort of just dismiss it and go</u>
<u n="321" who="S0588">that's the way it's yeah</u>
<u n="322" who="S0613" trans="overlap">it's not you know and and you do you I not not that I was suicidal or anything but I've definitely</u>
<u n="323" who="S0588">well you could get that way</u>
<u n="324" who="S0613" trans="overlap">wasn't wasn't firing on all cylinders</u>
<u n="325" who="S0588">no</u>
<u n="326" who="S0613">and that's a real shame and you wonder how many people erm</u>
<u n="327" who="S0588">just putting up with it and</u>
<u n="328" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yeah they just</u>
<u n="329" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="330" who="S0613">they cos you sort of</u>
<u n="331" who="S0588" trans="overlap">suffering</u>
<u n="332" who="S0613">you don't really become aware because I think it creeps up on you as well</u>
<u n="333" who="S0588">uhu</u>
<u n="334" who="S0613" trans="overlap">and it happens gradually</u>
<u n="335" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="336" who="S0613">er because I as I say this is on my third month and I'm noticing the it wasn't like instant you know within within er two days it's like a felt like a different <trunc>pers</trunc> it's <trunc>b</trunc> that's been gradual as well it's like my body's had to start to build it up</u>
<u n="337" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="338" who="S0613">and adjust to it</u>
<u n="339" who="S0588">mm</u>
<u n="340" who="S0613" trans="overlap">and it's really just been this third month I'm suddenly going yeah this is god this is <vocal desc="laugh"/> making such a difference</u>
<u n="341" who="S0588">what a relief</u>
<u n="342" who="S0613">erm</u>
<u n="343" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="344" who="S0613">yeah so</u>
<u n="345" who="S0588">that's amazing <pause dur="short"/> that it's so physical as well that that always astounds me that the mind is er so physical and then you can create your whole life through the filters of your brain like you say if you go on for years <pause dur="short"/> then you make a life from it</u>
<u n="346" who="S0613">yeah</u>
<u n="347" who="S0588">you're creating your life through those filters</u>
<u n="348" who="S0613" trans="overlap">well you yeah you structure your yeah</u>
<u n="349" who="S0588" trans="overlap">your decisions everything you do</u>
<u n="350" who="S0613">yeah</u>
<u n="351" who="S0588" trans="overlap">you might be feeling unconfident and so don't do the little that would make <trunc>tw</trunc> trigger the other thing</u>
<u n="352" who="S0613">mm</u>
<u n="353" who="S0588" trans="overlap">that it's I mean it's unfair as well it's and and people with depression and mental illness and stuff that <vocal desc="sigh"/> oh god that's so unfair</u>
<u n="354" who="S0613" trans="overlap">I felt I felt quite erm angry about it actually when I realised because I thought this is such a dirty trick</u>
<u n="355" who="S0588">yes it is isn't it?</u>
<u n="356" who="S0613" trans="overlap">and why is it that they do it to women?</u>
<u n="357" who="S0588">yes it is</u>
<u n="358" who="S0613">you know</u>
<u n="359" who="S0588" trans="overlap">well I mean historically it would seem that <pause dur="short"/> yeah</u>
<u n="360" who="S0613" trans="overlap">I say they</u>
<u n="361" who="S0588" trans="overlap"><unclear/> really</u>
<u n="362" who="S0613" trans="overlap">somebody er it's just an accident of nature I suppose</u>
<u n="363" who="S0588" trans="overlap">or god <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="364" who="S0613">yeah but but you know</u>
<u n="365" who="S0588">god's a bastard <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="366" who="S0613">erm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0588">but erm</u>
<u n="368" who="S0613">but you for for a woman particularly if if she's had children you've just you're just getting through all that and</u>
<u n="369" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="370" who="S0613" trans="overlap">and your children are grown up and you think oh I'm getting my life back again and then that happens</u>
<u n="371" who="S0588">well it's no wonder that there's more men who are I know it's changing but it's no wonder it's a man's world really</u>
<u n="372" who="S0613">oh it's so much simpler for men</u>
<u n="373" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="374" who="S0613" trans="overlap">it really is so much simpler</u>
<u n="375" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I mean how can you go through life with all those emotions and sort of?</u>
<u n="376" who="S0613">well all this stuff you have to handle</u>
<u n="377" who="S0588" trans="overlap">it's just stuff</u>
<u n="378" who="S0613">all the time yeah</u>
<u n="379" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="380" who="S0613">it's erm</u>
<u n="381" who="S0588">so it's really unfair yeah erm</u>
<u n="382" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="383" who="S0588">but I then I think I think depression is also really unfair and all that and stuff mental</u>
<u n="384" who="S0613">yes</u>
<u n="385" who="S0588" trans="overlap">shit <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="386" who="S0613">and that can that can affect <trunc>me</trunc>men and women I suppose but it yeah and it's I I it's only actually with the erm the menopause thing that I I think for the first time in my life I appreciated what depression must be like not that I think I was deeply depressed but</u>
<u n="387" who="S0588">no but a sense of it</u>
<u n="388" who="S0613" trans="overlap">but that kind of idea of it being a chemical imbalance in your brain</u>
<u n="389" who="S0588" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="390" who="S0613" trans="overlap">and it actually is out of your control <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="391" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="392" who="S0613" trans="overlap">you kind of go this is crazy why am I</u>
<u n="393" who="S0588" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="394" who="S0613">doing this?</u>
<u n="395" who="S0588" trans="overlap">it's out of your control and yet there's that kind of terrible thing of that fine line of some of it is in your control and er</u>
<u n="396" who="S0613" trans="overlap">but er if you</u>
<u n="397" who="S0588" trans="overlap">but that's also not fair <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="398" who="S0613">yeah but you get the sort of sense of watching yourself</u>
<u n="399" who="S0588">mm</u>
<u n="400" who="S0613">and and I became terribly aware of <trunc>s</trunc> the stuff the what I was doing that that wasn't wasn't healthy or good for for me or those people around me or anything and then and yet still doing it it was almost like this sort of lemming mentality <vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>whi</trunc> was</u>
<u n="401" who="S0588">yes and</u>
<u n="402" who="S0613" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="403" who="S0588">it's extra effort to stop doing it because you can see what you're doing and <pause dur="short"/> it it and but with a little helping hand you can stop doing it <vocal desc="laugh"/> like an antidepressant or whatever it is</u>
<u n="404" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yeah I suppose it's yes you</u>
<u n="405" who="S0588" trans="overlap">but erm</u>
<u n="406" who="S0613" trans="overlap">you break the cycle of then</u>
<u n="407" who="S0588">and then</u>
<u n="408" who="S0613" trans="overlap">then you the yeah the fog <trunc>cl</trunc> lifts a bit</u>
<u n="409" who="S0588">mm</u>
<u n="410" who="S0613" trans="overlap">and you can see things as they really are</u>
<u n="411" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="412" who="S0613" trans="overlap">and then you can take control again but it</u>
<u n="413" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="414" who="S0613" trans="overlap">it's when you're in the middle of the er <pause dur="short"/> yes</u>
<u n="415" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah it is a fog and not seeing the wood for the trees</u>
<u n="416" who="S0613">but erm</u>
<u n="417" who="S0588">but erm interesting because it makes you think about our mother and she she probably menopausal for years and wouldn't even have</u>
<u n="418" who="S0613">no the <trunc>thi</trunc></u>
<u n="419" who="S0588">said a word</u>
<u n="420" who="S0613">also at that time it probably wasn't so</u>
<u n="421" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="422" who="S0613">recognised it was</u>
<u n="423" who="S0588" trans="overlap">so that's <pause dur="short"/> erm has a bearing on things</u>
<u n="424" who="S0613" trans="overlap">I mean it's interesting to well I talk to to female friends about it and some of them are kind of very staunch like no no I'm not going to take er I'm going to do it naturally I'm you know I I can sort this out erm and as you say everyone's different and perhaps some people can and for a long time</u>
<u n="425" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I think so yeah</u>
<u n="426" who="S0613">I I but I almost dismissed it in the same way that other people do it's like well it's <trunc>on</trunc> it's only the menopause</u>
<u n="427" who="S0588">mm</u>
<u n="428" who="S0613">erm <pause dur="short"/> and it's only now <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm not saying I'd recommend <trunc>everyo</trunc> oh go you know you know you just <trunc>y</trunc> just go on it but I I just think I just wonder how many people are not</u>
<u n="429" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="430" who="S0613">really seeing things as clearly as they could because they are right in the middle of it</u>
<u n="431" who="S0588">yeah I mean <vocal desc="laugh"/> <trunc>i</trunc>in a way from my perspective it's always been the case that all those menopausal panic the way you describe it is like my whole life so <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's almost like just a sort of all I'm getting now is the hot sweats and it's all very similar to what I've put up with for my adult life really from the age of seventeen it all went <pause dur="short"/> tits up so erm <pause dur="short"/> er it'll be interesting er I mean it depends how how far it goes and how many physical symptoms you get etcetera and how much in affects you but er yeah</u>
<u n="432" who="S0613">but you say you're you're managing to keep a lot of things under control with your diet?</u>
<u n="433" who="S0588" trans="overlap">oh well I have to er I have to do that and I have to do exercise every day otherwise I get really stiff <pause dur="short"/> er exercise every day</u>
<u n="434" who="S0613" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="435" who="S0588">is good very only short very short exercise er <pause dur="short"/> yeah and diet as well <pause dur="short"/> so <pause dur="short"/> I think so but then I also did that for the depression as well so that was</u>
<u n="436" who="S0613" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="437" who="S0588">it's erm something I'm used to doing is taking steps to oh god okay yeah I'll feel better if I do a workout let's do a workout</u>
<u n="438" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="439" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I'll shift my body and do it and then</u>
<u n="440" who="S0613" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="441" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I do feel better so there's that fine line of <pause dur="short"/> you know there is some control</u>
<u n="442" who="S0589" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="443" who="S0613">yeah hello mm what's the time? oh god it's quarter to I've got to erm</u>
<u n="444" who="S0588">how much did we manage? we've done twenty minutes yes</u>
<u n="445" who="S0613">is that is that useful twenty minutes?</u>
<u n="446" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah that is I can sell that I can sell twenty minutes</u>
<u n="447" who="S0589">home</u>
<u n="448" who="S0588">hello</u>
<u n="449" who="S0589"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s here</u>
<u n="450" who="S0588"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s here</u>
<u n="451" who="S0613">I'm here</u>
<u n="452" who="S0589"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s here</u>
<u n="453" who="S0613">it's not just my coat it's me</u>
<u n="454" who="S0589"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="455" who="S0588">mm what are we going to eat? hello <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="456" who="S0589" trans="overlap">well is is the salmon on have you? so that's</u>
<u n="457" who="S0588" trans="overlap">oh</u>
<u n="458" who="S0589">all cooked now</u>
<u n="459" who="S0588">well we hadn't established that that was what I was going to do</u>
<u n="460" who="S0613" trans="overlap">hello</u>
<u n="461" who="S0589">hi</u>
<u n="462" who="S0613">how are you?</u>
<u n="463" who="S0589">good</u>
<u n="464" who="S0613">mm</u>
<u n="465" who="S0589">are you recording yourself?</u>
<u n="466" who="S0613">yes</u>
<u n="467" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="468" who="S0589">am I being recorded?</u>
<u n="469" who="S0588">you are now</u>
<u n="470" who="S0589">that's not rolling</u>
<u n="471" who="S0588">it is rolling</u>
<u n="472" who="S0589">oh</u>
<u n="473" who="S0613">actually if you want to carry on recording I can I've just got to look at erm an er an attachment someone's sent me so I'll bring my my laptop down here and do it down here</u>
<u n="474" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="475" who="S0613">then erm carry on</u>
<u n="476" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yes that's a good idea</u>
<u n="477" who="S0613">if that's if it's okay</u>
<u n="478" who="S0588" trans="overlap">no that's fine cos that's natural</u>
<u n="479" who="S0589">tired</u>
<u n="480" who="S0588">we could do a macaroni cheese but without bacon</u>
<u n="481" who="S0589">or cheese</u>
<u n="482" who="S0588">we've got a little bit of cheese</u>
<u n="483" who="S0589">not a lot well when what time is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> due?</u>
<u n="484" who="S0588">not till much later</u>
<u n="485" who="S0589">so we don't have to feed him?</u>
<u n="486" who="S0588">no</u>
<u n="487" who="S0589">okay</u>
<u n="488" who="S0588">I'll do like a macaroni</u>
<u n="489" who="S0589" trans="overlap">have you got milk dear?</u>
<u n="490" who="S0588">well <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> brought some milk I could use some of that</u>
<u n="491" who="S0589">we don't have macaroni <unclear/></u>
<u n="492" who="S0588">we've got loads and we've got</u>
<u n="493" who="S0589" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="494" who="S0588" trans="overlap">loads of pasta shells</u>
<u n="495" who="S0589">we'll do that then</u>
<u n="496" who="S0588">okay I'll do that</u>
<u n="497" who="S0589"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="498" who="S0588">erm</u>
<u n="499" who="S0589"><unclear/></u>
<u n="500" who="S0588">after our conversation on gluten and dairy I'm going to do macaroni cheese cos that's what we have <pause dur="short"/> sorry? we are recording</u>
<u n="501" who="S0589">but don't address the</u>
<u n="502" who="S0588" trans="overlap">sorry?</u>
<u n="503" who="S0589">don't address the recorder</u>
<u n="504" who="S0588">no I'm addressing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> not the tape</u>
<u n="505" who="S0589">oh</u>
<u n="506" who="S0613"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="507" who="S0589">sorry darling</u>
<u n="508" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="509" who="S0589">I thought you were being Nabokovian</u>
<u n="510" who="S0588">no</u>
<u n="511" who="S0589">like that <unclear/></u>
<u n="512" who="S0588" trans="overlap">not Nabakovian but I was then cos that's an interesting word</u>
<event desc="sound of computer"/>
<u n="513" who="S0588"><shift new="singing"/> <unclear/> <shift new="normal"/></u>
<u n="514" who="S0589">well do you want a drink <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="515" who="S0613">no I'm I've just had a cup of tea thank you</u>
<u n="516" who="S0589">small glass of beer?</u>
<u n="517" who="S0613">no I'm fine thank you cos we've been talking about <vocal desc="laugh"/> health</u>
<u n="518" who="S0589"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="519" who="S0613"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="520" who="S0588">and on that on that <vocal desc="laugh"/> on that bombshell I'm going to have a glass of wine</u>
<u n="521" who="S0613">yes <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="522" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="523" who="S0613">cos oh I I need a glass of wine now</u>
<u n="524" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="525" who="S0613">that was all a bit yeah</u>
<u n="526" who="S0589">I will get my mufti on darling</u>
<u n="527" who="S0613">no I couldn't quite <unclear/> er alcohol midweek</u>
<u n="528" who="S0589">it is midweek</u>
<u n="529" who="S0588" trans="overlap">sorry?</u>
<u n="530" who="S0613">only drink at weekends</u>
<u n="531" who="S0588">ah er</u>
<u n="532" who="S0613"><pause dur="long"/> your erm roses have lasted well are they the</u>
<u n="533" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I know</u>
<u n="534" who="S0613" trans="overlap"><trunc>sa</trunc> the same ones that were here?</u>
<u n="535" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> it's amazing isn't it? <pause dur="long"/> Tesco's own <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="536" who="S0613">having said that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s bringing wine <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="537" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="538" who="S0613">so that's not very good <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="539" who="S0588">no it's fine <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> doesn't have erm hormonal issues</u>
<u n="540" who="S0613"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="541" who="S0588">can I use some of your butter?</u>
<u n="542" who="S0613"><trunc>c</trunc> oh of course yeah <pause dur="short"/> it's household butter it's not my butter</u>
<u n="543" who="S0588">right <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="544" who="S0589"><vocal desc="misc"/> <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="545" who="S0588">how's <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="546" who="S0613">they're good they're they're having to hold the fort this weekend cos both <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I are away</u>
<u n="547" who="S0588">oh right</u>
<u n="548" who="S0613">so it's just erm <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> is having to pick <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> up from the bus station</u>
<u n="549" who="S0588">wow</u>
<u n="550" who="S0613">and <trunc>c</trunc> and they've got to collect the dogs from the kennels</u>
<u n="551" who="S0588">gosh</u>
<u n="552" who="S0613">I know <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'm a bit erm</u>
<u n="553" who="S0588">that's good</u>
<u n="554" who="S0613">in theory in theory it should be fine but it's the first time we've actually</u>
<u n="555" who="S0588">that's really good</u>
<u n="556" who="S0613">done that so</u>
<u n="557" who="S0588" trans="overlap">though cos they can just start <pause dur="short"/> being adults</u>
<u n="558" who="S0613">yeah I mean they both they both can look after themselves but they've never been in sort of in charge of the house as well</u>
<u n="559" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="560" who="S0613">and the animals and er</u>
<u n="561" who="S0588">that's really useful if you can just</u>
<u n="562" who="S0613">yeah but we had to shut the house up today cos they're not they don't get back from <anon type="place"/> till tomorrow so it was like it's a bit like oh the house is</u>
<u n="563" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="564" who="S0613" trans="overlap">all shut up</u>
<u n="565" who="S0588">gosh it must be such a relief when you get them to that stage like that</u>
<u n="566" who="S0613" trans="overlap">it yeah it is erm</u>
<u n="567" who="S0588">and they're not they haven't proved themselves to be mm <trunc>y</trunc> I don't know kind of murderers or something</u>
<u n="568" who="S0613" trans="overlap">well yeah I mean if you</u>
<u n="569" who="S0588" trans="overlap">and I would always be worried that</u>
<u n="570" who="S0613">yeah if you feel like they've actually made it to adulthood <vocal desc="laugh"/> you <trunc>kn</trunc></u>
<u n="571" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah that's right</u>
<u n="572" who="S0613" trans="overlap">without any major mishaps you think</u>
<u n="573" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="574" who="S0613">but then but then the there's different things to you have to think about because now <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s driving</u>
<u n="575" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="576" who="S0613">and erm</u>
<u n="577" who="S0588">so</u>
<u n="578" who="S0613">we had to go out somewhere the other day and he was driving and and he's picked up so many bad habits already <vocal desc="laugh"/> and I</u>
<u n="579" who="S0588">oh</u>
<u n="580" who="S0613" trans="overlap">I'm thinking god he's gonna have an accident <vocal desc="laugh"/> he's going to <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="581" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yes</u>
<u n="582" who="S0613">so you know then so it's all very well being independent but then there's other things you have to start thinking about</u>
<u n="583" who="S0588" trans="overlap">a whole new set of worries</u>
<u n="584" who="S0613">yeah</u>
<u n="585" who="S0588">well I'm glad I'll never have that</u>
<u n="586" who="S0589">hello</u>
<u n="587" who="S0613">but you're just worried about Mr T instead</u>
<u n="588" who="S0589"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="589" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="590" who="S0613">I think</u>
<u n="591" who="S0588">it's probably not as intense as a human</u>
<u n="592" who="S0613" trans="overlap">well no I think you maybe it because I I remember with our dog <trunc>M</trunc> <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> our first dog before erm</u>
<u n="593" who="S0589" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="594" who="S0613">we had <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> and I remember we had to put <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in the kennels for some reason and I remember being in floods of tears and being convinced that the dog was gonna be really unhappy and</u>
<u n="595" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="596" who="S0613">and everything but I I don't get like that now about the dogs <vocal desc="laugh"/> but it's cos I didn't have anything else to get upset about <pause dur="short"/> so I think you</u>
<u n="597" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="598" who="S0613">kind of er</u>
<u n="599" who="S0588">but at least well I don't know I <trunc>mea</trunc> I think <pause dur="short"/> I can't even imagine what it must be like worrying about children gosh <pause dur="short"/> well we made er we made some friends in the <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="600" who="S0613">oh yeah?</u>
<u n="601" who="S0588">the <anon type="place"/> <pause dur="short"/> we're hoping it's going to take off <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="602" who="S0613">have they have they taken it over full time now?</u>
<u n="603" who="S0588">yes yeah</u>
<u n="604" who="S0589">yeah they've taken over the <pause dur="short"/> leasehold</u>
<u n="605" who="S0588">I suspect that they're going to have children though they're like a couple</u>
<u n="606" who="S0589">they have a <trunc>chil</trunc> oh you mean the people we've met?</u>
<u n="607" who="S0588" trans="overlap">no the people we made friends with</u>
<u n="608" who="S0613" trans="overlap">don't you put that on first after and then start the white sauce?</u>
<u n="609" who="S0588">no you do the white sauce first</u>
<u n="610" who="S0589">no you do not</u>
<u n="611" who="S0588">yes you do</u>
<u n="612" who="S0589">oh strange symmetry to my day I got almost all the way to <anon type="place"/> station realised I wasn't wearing my spectacles and couldn't see anything <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="613" who="S0613"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so</u>
<u n="614" who="S0589">so</u>
<u n="615" who="S0613">didn't you notice when you were walking along?</u>
<u n="616" who="S0589">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> well I use my hearing still or kind of okay to cross roads so I hadn't</u>
<u n="617" who="S0613"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="618" who="S0589">realised that I could barely it was a blur so I I <trunc>tur</trunc> had to turn around and come all the way back er and then <vocal desc="laugh"/> when I left work I had a quick drink with my friend my work colleague cos she's off to Caribbean for a holiday got all the way to <anon type="place"/> and realised I'd left my bag <vocal desc="laugh"/> in the pub</u>
<u n="619" who="S0613">oh no</u>
<u n="620" who="S0589" trans="overlap">so I had to go all the way back to the pub to collect my bag</u>
<u n="621" who="S0613" trans="overlap">oh god</u>
<u n="622" who="S0589">which was still where it was</u>
<u n="623" who="S0613">so you're</u>
<u n="624" who="S0589" trans="overlap">that's a neat symmetry isn't it?</u>
<u n="625" who="S0613">yes top and tailed your day</u>
<u n="626" who="S0589">yeah</u>
<u n="627" who="S0613" trans="overlap">with er forgetfulness</u>
<u n="628" who="S0589" trans="overlap">with with tracking back</u>
<u n="629" who="S0613">yes so erm does this happen often? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="630" who="S0589"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no I don't think it's a sign of Alzheimer's</u>
<u n="631" who="S0613"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="632" who="S0589">I think I have erm cos my friend said she didn't think I'd drunk that much and I hadn't I had like two pints er enough to forget my bag but I think I just had muscle memory of cos it felt</u>
<u n="633" who="S0613">yeah</u>
<u n="634" who="S0589" trans="overlap">when I put my coat on it felt like I had</u>
<u n="635" who="S0613" trans="overlap">mm</u>
<u n="636" who="S0589">and I had my book er which is the only thing in my bag so anyway I didn't feel the strap going across my chest</u>
<u n="637" who="S0613" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="638" who="S0589">in in in the tube and I thought oh hang on oh damn</u>
<u n="639" who="S0613">that's such such a pain isn't it?</u>
<u n="640" who="S0589">mm but I haven't forgotten to wear my spectacles for erm</u>
<u n="641" who="S0613"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="642" who="S0589"><unclear/></u>
<u n="643" who="S0613" trans="overlap">but you cos you wear you wear glasses all the time</u>
<u n="644" who="S0589">yeah</u>
<u n="645" who="S0613">so how can if you?</u>
<u n="646" who="S0589" trans="overlap">in the old days I could if I got as far as I got I'd go oh well I'll get by but now <vocal desc="laugh"/> no just it's not really</u>
<u n="647" who="S0613">no</u>
<u n="648" who="S0589" trans="overlap">I wouldn't be able to I'd be a Mr Magoo</u>
<u n="649" who="S0613">or a magnifying glass</u>
<u n="650" who="S0589" trans="overlap">at work</u>
<u n="651" who="S0613">to read</u>
<u n="652" who="S0589" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="653" who="S0613">things I've I've got to go and make a quick work call</u>
<u n="654" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="655" who="S0613">I will return</u>
<u n="656" who="S0588">okay <pause dur="short"/> how was your day <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>? oh yes you were just saying that you had a forgetful day</u>
<u n="657" who="S0589" trans="overlap">I was just relating it to your sister darling</u>
<u n="658" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="659" who="S0589">it was almost Nabokovian</u>
<u n="660" who="S0588">oh it was Nabokovian was it?</u>
<u n="661" who="S0589">well in a sense because there seemed to be some sort of hidden meaning</u>
<u n="662" who="S0588">what is Nabokovian?</u>
<u n="663" who="S0589">well it's all about things that I read in his biography</u>
<u n="664" who="S0588">are you looking for the er <unclear/>?</u>
<u n="665" who="S0589">I've got these though</u>
<u n="666" who="S0588" trans="overlap">it might be no <pause dur="short"/> I don't think if it's in here <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> in here</u>
<u n="667" who="S0589"><unclear/> it's very sensitive oh <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> said she is happy to be recorded</u>
<u n="668" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="669" who="S0589">so there you go my dear</u>
<u n="670" who="S0588">well I think we should take this opportunity</u>
<u n="671" who="S0589">she's away for the next fortnight in the Caribbean</u>
<u n="672" who="S0588">uhu well we've got people in the house who are quite</u>
<u n="673" who="S0589" trans="overlap">turn that on <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="674" who="S0588">people in the house for</u>
<u n="675" who="S0589">might be too early for that</u>
<u n="676" who="S0588">why? I always do this first</u>
<u n="677" who="S0589">I wouldn't do that until the pasta was virtually almost cooked</u>
<u n="678" who="S0588">no but you've got to heat out the flour</u>
<u n="679" who="S0589">cook out the flour</u>
<u n="680" who="S0588">exactly <pause dur="short"/> is there anything else that can go in it apart from onion?</u>
<u n="681" who="S0589">erm</u>
<u n="682" who="S0588">what about</u>
<u n="683" who="S0589">let me think</u>
<u n="684" who="S0588" trans="overlap">so it's cheese and pasta</u>
<u n="685" who="S0589" trans="overlap">well spinach would be nice wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="686" who="S0588">mm</u>
<u n="687" who="S0589">spinach with cheese is <unclear/></u>
<u n="688" who="S0588">er we've actually got real spinach</u>
<u n="689" who="S0589">erm <unclear/> that's the only option my dear</u>
<u n="690" who="S0588">is that all?</u>
<u n="691" who="S0589">broad beans?</u>
<u n="692" who="S0588">no</u>
<u n="693" who="S0589">spinach <pause dur="long"/> Quorn <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="694" who="S0588">no</u>
<u n="695" who="S0589">Quorn mince</u>
<u n="696" who="S0588">we're lacking the erm bacon really aren't we?</u>
<u n="697" who="S0589">sausages would be alright but I think they're still frozen</u>
<u n="698" who="S0588">with sausages? nothing here what's in the bottom there?</u>
<u n="699" who="S0589" trans="overlap">so my idea of spinach is the best one</u>
<u n="700" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah it is the best one well what do you want shall we put I dunno it would go all greeny wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="701" who="S0589">mm be like the sort of dish we used to have in the old days</u>
<u n="702" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="703" who="S0589">when we were vegetarian</u>
<u n="704" who="S0588">I think it we should have something else apart from this carbohydrate fest</u>
<u n="705" who="S0589">well we're not</u>
<u n="706" who="S0588" trans="overlap">so we're having spinach <pause dur="long"/> if we keep it to one-hour segments <pause dur="short"/> so I'll switch it off after an hour and start another one but we've had a jolly good conversation about</u>
<u n="707" who="S0589">politics</u>
<u n="708" who="S0588">about hormone replacement therapy</u>
<u n="709" who="S0589">oh gosh</u>
<u n="710" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="711" who="S0589">tell me about it</u>
<u n="712" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="713" who="S0613">but not literally</u>
<u n="714" who="S0588">er no but I think that we should have spinach <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> er do you want to grate some cheese for me?</u>
<u n="715" who="S0589">oh well do you want spinach or grated cheese</u>
<u n="716" who="S0588">both darling</u>
<u n="717" who="S0589">well I can't do both can I?</u>
<u n="718" who="S0588">well you can choose to do one and then do the other</u>
<u n="719" who="S0589">no you do everything</u>
<u n="720" who="S0588">okay <trunc>d</trunc> grate me some cheese please the cheese is on the top</u>
<u n="721" who="S0589" trans="overlap">no I just said you do everything no that cheese is supposed to be my lunchtime</u>
<u n="722" who="S0588">oh sorry darling</u>
<u n="723" who="S0589">actually no my idea with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> was that we'd record over a lunch at our</u>
<u n="724" who="S0588">somewhere quiet</u>
<u n="725" who="S0589">well</u>
<u n="726" who="S0588" trans="overlap">ish well not if you're <unclear/></u>
<u n="727" who="S0589" trans="overlap">couldn't couldn't guarantee that city restaurant</u>
<u n="728" who="S0588">yeah I've transcribed</u>
<u n="729" who="S0589">worse</u>
<u n="730" who="S0588" trans="overlap">some horrendous ones <pause dur="short"/> so I really couldn't sleep last night that was</u>
<u n="731" who="S0589">yeah you did sleep quite well actually</u>
<u n="732" who="S0588" trans="overlap">no I didn't and so therefore</u>
<u n="733" who="S0589">I was there too</u>
<u n="734" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I didn't get up till much too late so</u>
<u n="735" who="S0589"><vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="736" who="S0588">I might have to stay up tonight <pause dur="short"/> we've still got the other half of Hinterland to watch which I'm very much enjoying the grimness</u>
<u n="737" who="S0589" trans="overlap">forgot to watch it last night that</u>
<u n="738" who="S0588" trans="overlap">oh darling did you see what I sent you in the email?</u>
<u n="739" who="S0589">no</u>
<u n="740" who="S0588">there's a house that's sold on</u>
<u n="741" who="S0589">oh you're like my mum</u>
<u n="742" who="S0588" trans="overlap">on <anon type="place"/> road</u>
<u n="743" who="S0589"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="744" who="S0588">for four hundred thousand pounds one of the smaller ones</u>
<u n="745" who="S0589">fucking hell you're like my mum</u>
<u n="746" who="S0588">yeah four hundred</u>
<u n="747" who="S0589" trans="overlap">have you rung my mum to say?</u>
<u n="748" who="S0588" trans="overlap">thousand</u>
<u n="749" who="S0589">mind you they have more bedrooms don't they?</u>
<u n="750" who="S0588">what the smaller houses?</u>
<u n="751" who="S0589">well I think so like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s house seemed more not more spacious but more bedroomy</u>
<u n="752" who="S0588">no but it means that this is at least four fifty</u>
<u n="753" who="S0589">the same price what did you say it went for?</u>
<u n="754" who="S0588">the same price? no it's much bigger</u>
<u n="755" who="S0589">mm</u>
<u n="756" who="S0588" trans="overlap">four hundred thousand</u>
<u n="757" who="S0589">no that's my point is that it's not more bedroomy but</u>
<u n="758" who="S0588">I <trunc>dou</trunc> I disagree</u>
<u n="759" who="S0589">I should ring my mum and tell her</u>
<u n="760" who="S0588" trans="overlap">they'll just say that</u>
<u n="761" who="S0589" trans="overlap">which house was it darling?</u>
<u n="762" who="S0588">no they called that five bedrooms</u>
<u n="763" who="S0589">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> they did</u>
<u n="764" who="S0588">so I suggest we wait till we can sell it for about five and six <trunc>thous</trunc></u>
<u n="765" who="S0589">and move to <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="766" who="S0588" trans="overlap">six hundred thousand</u>
<u n="767" who="S0589">where would I work in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="768" who="S0588">and then we buy with the change we buy a a house in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="769" who="S0589"><anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="770" who="S0588">and we pay off the mortgage as well with this one and then we rent out this one</u>
<u n="771" who="S0589">er?</u>
<u n="772" who="S0588">so we keep</u>
<u n="773" who="S0589" trans="overlap">that doesn't work</u>
<u n="774" who="S0588">keep our investment</u>
<u n="775" who="S0589" trans="overlap">cos we no your logic was we've already sold it</u>
<u n="776" who="S0588">oh sorry</u>
<u n="777" who="S0589" trans="overlap">to buy the house in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="778" who="S0588" trans="overlap">oh yes</u>
<u n="779" who="S0589"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="780" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="781" who="S0589">otherwise it's a brilliant idea</u>
<u n="782" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/> apart from that it was slightly flawed <vocal desc="laugh"/> I thought that was rather good <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="783" who="S0589" trans="overlap">yeah <pause dur="short"/> anyway it means we're not in</u>
<u n="784" who="S0588" trans="overlap">oh damn it</u>
<u n="785" who="S0589">not in negative equity so</u>
<u n="786" who="S0588" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="787" who="S0589">it's still good</u>
<u n="788" who="S0588">but I thought I'd like to keep it as a cos it to keep a house in <anon type="place"/> is a very good thing to do</u>
<u n="789" who="S0589">did you see how much of the recycling I managed to put out <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="790" who="S0588">er yeah it's good</u>
<u n="791" who="S0589">that was your job do you remember?</u>
<u n="792" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="793" who="S0589">I thought you probably wouldn't so I did it</u>
<u n="794" who="S0588" trans="overlap">but then I did the whole house today</u>
<u n="795" who="S0589">yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> you do everything</u>
<u n="796" who="S0588">and I oh the sheets are on the line outside</u>
<u n="797" who="S0589">really?</u>
<u n="798" who="S0588" trans="overlap">what shall I do? <pause dur="short"/> yeah I didn't know where else to put them I mean they're nearly dry actually</u>
<u n="799" who="S0589">well bring them in cos there's nothing over the bannisters</u>
<u n="800" who="S0588">okay do it after this cos that as well to try to create the space so I think we've now caught up with our washing</u>
<u n="801" who="S0589">oh that's impressive</u>
<u n="802" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="803" who="S0589">cos normally I do everything I'm not wearing shoes though</u>
<u n="804" who="S0588">do you er put the?</u>
<u n="805" who="S0589" trans="overlap">oh did I get a package?</u>
<u n="806" who="S0588">no</u>
<u n="807" who="S0589"><vocal desc="misc"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> I bought these shoelaces</u>
<u n="808" who="S0588" trans="overlap">we could leave them out there what would happen if we left them out there overnight?</u>
<u n="809" who="S0589">it might rain and that would negate the whole</u>
<u n="810" who="S0588">no but it wouldn't do any harm and they'd be out of the way</u>
<u n="811" who="S0589" trans="overlap">it would do a little bit of harm</u>
<u n="812" who="S0588">and if it doesn't rain</u>
<u n="813" who="S0589">they don't need to be out of the way because the bannister's free for them to go over that</u>
<u n="814" who="S0588" trans="overlap">okay that's still a bit in the way though isn't it?</u>
<u n="815" who="S0589">you go and collect them darling</u>
<u n="816" who="S0588">I'm using up all <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s milk <pause dur="short"/> shall we put some?</u>
<u n="817" who="S0589">yeah</u>
<u n="818" who="S0588">as well <pause dur="long"/> I need to stay here until we've done an hour before I take the washing in <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="819" who="S0589">did you contact our new friends at all?</u>
<u n="820" who="S0588">well you you keep saying that what do you want me to do?</u>
<u n="821" who="S0589">be friendly?</u>
<u n="822" who="S0588">I I have I've done it <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="823" who="S0589">no you just reciprocated the initial</u>
<u n="824" who="S0588">well</u>
<u n="825" who="S0589">friendliness</u>
<u n="826" who="S0588" trans="overlap">well what else can I do?</u>
<u n="827" who="S0589">er</u>
<u n="828" who="S0588" trans="overlap"><trunc>d</trunc> well <trunc>y</trunc>you do it if you want</u>
<u n="829" who="S0589">I'm not going to do it am I? I'm not friendly</u>
<u n="830" who="S0588" trans="overlap">but I I don't know what you want</u>
<u n="831" who="S0589">suggest we meet up</u>
<u n="832" who="S0588">well okay tell me when you want to meet</u>
<u n="833" who="S0589">for a drink or do you want that in there?</u>
<u n="834" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="835" who="S0589">or just bash it <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> er <anon type="place"/> the opening of</u>
<u n="836" who="S0588" trans="overlap">well</u>
<u n="837" who="S0589">the <anon type="place"/> oh <pause dur="short"/> of the <anon type="place"/>  <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="838" who="S0588">okay let's put the pasta on I think</u>
<u n="839" who="S0589">I'm doing this now</u>
<u n="840" who="S0588">how were we gonna do the spinach? put it in here? no that's too watery really we need to cook the spinach as well</u>
<u n="841" who="S0589"><unclear/></u>
<u n="842" who="S0588" trans="overlap">shall we put it actually in a dish when it's all done?</u>
<u n="843" who="S0589">yeah</u>
<u n="844" who="S0588">put it in a big dish then put it in the oven</u>
<u n="845" who="S0589">do the spinach in a separate dish and then drain it</u>
<u n="846" who="S0588">mm</u>
<u n="847" who="S0589">of water <pause dur="short"/> and then it can be introduced perhaps to the cheese sauce</u>
<u n="848" who="S0588">okay could you erm sort out the spinach please?</u>
<u n="849" who="S0589" trans="overlap">oh no cos you said</u>
<u n="850" who="S0588" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="misc"/></u>
<u n="851" who="S0589">that I had</u>
<u n="852" who="S0588" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="853" who="S0589">to do</u>
<u n="854" who="S0588">go on</u>
<u n="855" who="S0589">the cheese</u>
<u n="856" who="S0588" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="857" who="S0589">the cheese</u>
<u n="858" who="S0588">you've done it go on</u>
<u n="859" who="S0589">but then I have ended up doing everything</u>
<u n="860" who="S0588">you haven't</u>
<u n="861" who="S0589"><unclear/></u>
<u n="862" who="S0588">the cheese is okay <unclear/></u>
<u n="863" who="S0589">no I've turned it down it's fine</u>
<u n="864" who="S0588">where's all the salt gone? <pause dur="long"/> okay saucepan?</u>
<u n="865" who="S0589" trans="overlap">probably too much actually</u>
<u n="866" who="S0588">it isn't</u>
<u n="867" who="S0589">no just play it by sight <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="868" who="S0588">but anyway that's good though isn't it? four hundred thousand</u>
<u n="869" who="S0589" trans="overlap">is the kettle on? which house was it? cos my mum ought to know</u>
<u n="870" who="S0588" trans="overlap">well I'll show you <pause dur="short"/> but it hasn't I've not seen we never saw what it it would have been on Rightmove but we never saw what it went for so it's on erm their house prices thing you know where</u>
<u n="871" who="S0589">like Zoopla what went for what?</u>
<u n="872" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah no more like houses in this road went for whatever</u>
<u n="873" who="S0589" trans="overlap">that's what I meant yeah</u>
<u n="874" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="875" who="S0589">in fact I think that's exactly what I said</u>
<u n="876" who="S0588">it's not exactly what you said</u>
<u n="877" who="S0589">well it pretty much is</u>
<u n="878" who="S0588" trans="overlap">you said pretty much that but I was just establishing it <pause dur="short"/> er <pause dur="short"/> four hundred thousand</u>
<u n="879" who="S0589" trans="overlap">is he coming in?</u>
<u n="880" who="S0588">so I think</u>
<u n="881" who="S0589" trans="overlap">not coming in</u>
<u n="882" who="S0588" trans="overlap">ours is worth at least four hundred and fifty thousand</u>
<u n="883" who="S0589">good girl</u>
<u n="884" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="885" who="S0589">funny typing this cos you'll find that I'm often quite right about things and also that you often repeat what I've said moments later as your own idea</u>
<u n="886" who="S0588" trans="overlap">yeah I know that anyway but it's because it is my own idea moments later</u>
<u n="887" who="S0589">mm</u>
<u n="888" who="S0588">so it's got a logic</u>
<u n="889" who="S0589">do you want that in there?</u>
<u n="890" who="S0588">want what in where?</u>
<u n="891" who="S0589">the onion</u>
<u n="892" who="S0588">yeah <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="893" who="S0589">there you go my dear</u>
<u n="894" who="S0588">thank you not too much clattering</u>
<u n="895" who="S0589">flatulence?</u>
<u n="896" who="S0588">not too much clattering</u>
<u n="897" who="S0589">oh <pause dur="short"/> flattering? <pause dur="long"/> did you hear me?</u>
<u n="898" who="S0588" trans="overlap">how's <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>?</u>
<u n="899" who="S0589" trans="overlap">come back in in the morning</u>
<u n="900" who="S0588">no I didn't</u>
<u n="901" who="S0589">you were fast asleep <pause dur="short"/> <unclear/></u>
<u n="902" who="S0588">didn't those flowers do well? I want another set bunch <pause dur="long"/> okay then so here's another scenario in that case cos I did get that wrong rather didn't I?</u>
<u n="903" who="S0589">probably</u>
<u n="904" who="S0588">I said thought we've sold it and then we've rented it out</u>
<u n="905" who="S0589" trans="overlap">and then we've also have the money sold it</u>
<u n="906" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/> and rented it out</u>
<u n="907" who="S0589" trans="overlap">for four hundred half a million</u>
<u n="908" who="S0588" trans="overlap">okay</u>
<u n="909" who="S0589">and still have the money</u>
<u n="910" who="S0588" trans="overlap">so erm</u>
<u n="911" who="S0589">well my scenario which I told <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> about is if I die of stomach cancer rapidly is that you still could be financially able to buy outright dear in <anon type="place"/> or <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="912" who="S0588">well we could buy outright if we sold this place we could buy outright in <anon type="place"/> for three hundred thousand</u>
<u n="913" who="S0589">so now we're discussing options when neither of us actually die?</u>
<u n="914" who="S0588">when neither of us actually die</u>
<u n="915" who="S0589" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="916" who="S0588">so if we were to sell this place we could pay off the mortgage and</u>
<u n="917" who="S0589"><unclear/></u>
<u n="918" who="S0588" trans="overlap">buy a place shh and buy a place in <anon type="place"/> and have no mortgage</u>
<u n="919" who="S0589">I don't know why you're so fond of <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="920" who="S0588">cos it's nice</u>
<u n="921" who="S0589">we've only been there like thrice</u>
<u n="922" who="S0588">well so? and then never been on <anon type="place"/> had I?</u>
<u n="923" who="S0589"><vocal desc="laugh"/> no</u>
<u n="924" who="S0588">erm and then if you inherit <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s flat</u>
<u n="925" who="S0589"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s flat</u>
<u n="926" who="S0588">then we could buy another house in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="927" who="S0589">oh gosh</u>
<u n="928" who="S0588">and rent it out and have an income that way</u>
<u n="929" who="S0589">portfolio</u>
<u n="930" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="931" who="S0589">like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/></u>
<u n="932" who="S0588">no but the thing to do is get you like off from this kind of nine to five working thing cos it's a bit crap so we have to find a way to not have to do that anymore <pause dur="short"/> so we could live somewhere nice and just rent somewhere in <anon type="place"/> as our income and that way we also keep the investment in <anon type="place"/> but that's if <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> moves out of the <anon type="place"/> cos I think he would because he'd have to pay the ground rent because we can't pay the ground rent or the service charge and he'd probably think it's a bit cheaper if I move back to <anon type="place"/> cos he's so insecure</u>
<u n="933" who="S0589">well he'd have almost a million in er</u>
<u n="934" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="935" who="S0589">in fact he'd have a million</u>
<u n="936" who="S0588">yeah so he he could go back to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="937" who="S0589">he'd be a millionaire</u>
<u n="938" who="S0588">yeah he could go anywhere and we could meanwhile sell <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="939" who="S0589">or move there</u>
<u n="940" who="S0588">no we couldn't afford to move there though</u>
<u n="941" who="S0589">oh</u>
<u n="942" who="S0588">can't can't pay the erm although could we? can we pay no <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> wouldn't be allowed there</u>
<u n="943" who="S0589">oh that that's a deal breaker</u>
<u n="944" who="S0588" trans="overlap">that's that a deal breaker</u>
<u n="945" who="S0589">mm poor boy <pause dur="short"/> has he had his supper?</u>
<u n="946" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="947" who="S0589" trans="overlap">yes he has he had his breakfast at three thirty again</u>
<u n="948" who="S0588">oh he's a bit naughty</u>
<u n="949" who="S0589">it's worth having two late midnight snacks</u>
<u n="950" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="951" who="S0589">he does no he wakes me with such a start that</u>
<u n="952" who="S0588">you're so shocked</u>
<u n="953" who="S0589">that I</u>
<u n="954" who="S0588">that you do it</u>
<u n="955" who="S0589">get up</u>
<u n="956" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="957" who="S0589">I mean cos I'm wide awake</u>
<u n="958" who="S0588">he takes you unawares</u>
<u n="959" who="S0589">whereas you probably are able to just roll over and get back to sleep <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="960" who="S0588">right it's time for pasta</u>
<u n="961" who="S0589">yeah well you probably want me to do that as well which would have meant</u>
<u n="962" who="S0588" trans="overlap">oh would you? that would be good</u>
<u n="963" who="S0589">I think I've done the whole meal it's like that</u>
<u n="964" who="S0588" trans="overlap">no we're doing it together</u>
<u n="965" who="S0589">it's like that folk tale with the <unclear/> <pause dur="long"/> where incrementally I've been doing a little bit here and there</u>
<u n="966" who="S0588">there you go</u>
<u n="967" who="S0589">and it turns out that apart from doing the white sauce</u>
<u n="968" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I've done that for you</u>
<u n="969" who="S0589">I've made the entire meal</u>
<u n="970" who="S0588">have you noticed how clean and tidy the house is though?</u>
<u n="971" who="S0589">yes</u>
<u n="972" who="S0588">thank you <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="973" who="S0589">did you boil the kettle?</u>
<u n="974" who="S0588">I thought I did don't know</u>
<u n="975" who="S0589">yeah no you did <pause dur="long"/> put a bit more water in there dear <pause dur="long"/> do you notice any er political bias in the erm stuff you have to transcribe dear?</u>
<u n="976" who="S0588">erm</u>
<u n="977" who="S0589">I would suggest it's slightly more left wing</u>
<u n="978" who="S0588" trans="overlap">I would suggest that people are mainly left wing</u>
<u n="979" who="S0589">yeah</u>
<u n="980" who="S0588">er <trunc>peo</trunc> cos I think people naturally are probably</u>
<u n="981" who="S0589">younger people are and most of the <unclear/></u>
<u n="982" who="S0588" trans="overlap">because that's morally more right <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="983" who="S0589"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="984" who="S0588">just odd that we have not that in a government</u>
<u n="985" who="S0589">it's like the awful business of Cameron saying a bunch of migrants</u>
<u n="986" who="S0588">yeah exactly</u>
<u n="987" who="S0589" trans="overlap">and it's so so clever because he knew it was outrageous</u>
<u n="988" who="S0588">he knew it would appeal?</u>
<u n="989" who="S0589">no it's that he knew it was outrageous so it would be newsworthy but within the actual context it's not as outrageous as it sounds out of context but er crucially out of the entire parliamentary question time er that would be the soundbite</u>
<u n="990" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="991" who="S0589">that's played on the news</u>
<u n="992" who="S0588">and?</u>
<u n="993" who="S0589">so you never have to hear anything about what Jeremy Corbyn has to say</u>
<u n="994" who="S0588">clever</u>
<u n="995" who="S0589" trans="overlap">what you hear is the point</u>
<u n="996" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="997" who="S0589" trans="overlap">he's trying to make which people will then thing is clumsily made I E clumsy not deliberate tripping over his words or whatever but actually all they hear is <trunc>h</trunc> the exact message he wanted everyone to hear</u>
<u n="998" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="999" who="S0589">it's er quite devious but that's what politics is like</u>
<u n="1000" who="S0588">extremely</u>
<u n="1001" who="S0589">and it's where Jeremy Corbyn unfortunately</u>
<u n="1002" who="S0588">is gonna fall down</u>
<u n="1003" who="S0589">falls down</u>
<u n="1004" who="S0588">yes cos he's not</u>
<u n="1005" who="S0589" trans="overlap">as sort of not particularly</u>
<u n="1006" who="S0588" trans="overlap">playing that game</u>
<u n="1007" who="S0589">noted backbencher</u>
<u n="1008" who="S0588">and he cannot play that game because it would be against his whole person to play that game and the whole point of him is to not play that game if you like but it can't work in a playing field where everybody's playing that game</u>
<u n="1009" who="S0589"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1010" who="S0588">shame <pause dur="short"/> because er that is politics <vocal desc="laugh"/> it's er political that's why you say</u>
<u n="1011" who="S0589" trans="overlap">are you doing that pasta dear or the?</u>
<u n="1012" who="S0588">this pasta</u>
<u n="1013" who="S0589">oh</u>
<u n="1014" who="S0588">this is why you say</u>
<u n="1015" who="S0589">don't put it in yet</u>
<u n="1016" who="S0588">when your workplace has become oh it's very political that's what it means <vocal desc="laugh"/> it means it's bitchy and backstabbing and nasty and people telling lies and allsorts that's not what politics should be <pause dur="long"/> well anyway your mum's going to be tremendously excited <pause dur="short"/> that it sold the house sold down our road</u>
<u n="1017" who="S0589">well we ought to contact her</u>
<u n="1018" who="S0588">yeah</u>
<u n="1019" who="S0589">do you know what <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s intentions are?</u>
<u n="1020" who="S0588">towards what?</u>
<u n="1021" who="S0589"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1022" who="S0588"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1023" who="S0589">er when she's here or not here and when <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s arriving</u>
<u n="1024" who="S0588">no I do not know all I know is that <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s</u>
<u n="1025" who="S0589" trans="overlap">are they working that weekend?</u>
<u n="1026" who="S0588">what weekend?</u>
<u n="1027" who="S0589">next weekend not this coming one the one after</u>
<u n="1028" who="S0588">dunno have to ask I don't know all I know is <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s coming tonight <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="1029" who="S0589">hopefully he's bringing me a crate of</u>
<u n="1030" who="S0588">I think he will</u>
<u n="1031" who="S0589">of wine</u>
<u n="1032" who="S0588">I think he will <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1033" who="S0589">you'll have to pay for it dear</u>
<u n="1034" who="S0588">I can't I'm absolutely nothing nothing nothing nothing <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1035" who="S0589" trans="overlap">well after I've done this whole meal</u>
<u n="1036" who="S0588">this is the last of our food <pause dur="short"/> erm this is why I'm having carbohydrates <pause dur="short"/> I've put <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s birthday party in the calendar</u>
<u n="1037" who="S0589">do you think you'll come?</u>
<u n="1038" who="S0588">yes</u>
<u n="1039" who="S0589">oh that'll be fun</u>
<u n="1040" who="S0588">I'm coming and I'm going to help as well</u>
<u n="1041" who="S0589">right yeah <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's non-negotiable</u>
<u n="1042" who="S0588">yeah but I mean I'll go earlier if you want</u>
<u n="1043" who="S0589">well actually I intend to go late <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1044" who="S0588">oh okay</u>
<u n="1045" who="S0589">so I can watch the rugby</u>
<u n="1046" who="S0588">well I'll come and watch the rugby with you then</u>
<u n="1047" who="S0589" trans="overlap">no you can all be there the girls can all go early</u>
<u n="1048" who="S0588">what do you mean go early?</u>
<u n="1049" who="S0589">well like from when it kicks off</u>
<u n="1050" who="S0588">oh</u>
<u n="1051" who="S0589">allowing me to watch the kick-off see that neat little word play?</u>
<u n="1052" who="S0588">okay</u>
<u n="1053" who="S0589">of the rugby</u>
<u n="1054" who="S0588">erm <pause dur="short"/> no but I mean I have to take the er networking opportunity</u>
<u n="1055" who="S0589">is this salted?</u>
<u n="1056" who="S0588">yes you might want to put more in I don't know</u>
<u n="1057" who="S0589" trans="overlap">well there'll be <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> there'll be</u>
<u n="1058" who="S0588">there'll be the mother of the <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="1059" who="S0589"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1060" who="S0588" trans="overlap">there'll be the artist</u>
<u n="1061" who="S0589"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1062" who="S0588">no I'll bring a few copies with me as well</u>
<u n="1063" who="S0589" trans="overlap"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1064" who="S0588">flash that around er <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s quite good at erm publicising things really when he talks</u>
<u n="1065" who="S0589">they own a copy</u>
<u n="1066" who="S0588">yes <pause dur="short"/> er why's that not shall I put this in?</u>
<u n="1067" who="S0589">uhu</u>
<u n="1068" who="S0588">uhu</u>
<u n="1069" who="S0589">wait for it to boil looks nice though is it salted? did I ask that?</u>
<u n="1070" who="S0588">yes you asked that I think it will</u>
<u n="1071" who="S0589" trans="overlap">do you want to taste? yeah I was going to say taste it because spinach needs quite a lot of salt</u>
<u n="1072" who="S0588">mm</u>
<u n="1073" who="S0589">mm</u>
<u n="1074" who="S0588">wow that's beautiful</u>
<u n="1075" who="S0589">mm good girl</u>
<u n="1076" who="S0588">where's all the salt gone?</u>
<u n="1077" who="S0589">finished</u>
<u n="1078" who="S0588">is there no salt then? it's no use using this is there? going to have to <pause dur="long"/> wonderful</u>
<u n="1079" who="S0589">would you like me to measure out the pasta?</u>
<u n="1080" who="S0588">yes please shall we?</u>
<u n="1081" who="S0589" trans="overlap">which dish do you want to serve it in?</u>
<u n="1082" who="S0588">this dish the big one erm this is a bit full <anon type="name" nameType="m"/></u>
<u n="1083" who="S0589">what the other dish?</u>
<u n="1084" who="S0588">yeah and there's three of us and I'm mega-hungry and that's big pasta so they don't actually go very far</u>
<u n="1085" who="S0589">no that's enough it looks well that's that's certainly enough</u>
<u n="1086" who="S0588">well not for me <pause dur="short"/> I want I think we'll all want more than that look if you think about it</u>
<u n="1087" who="S0589" trans="overlap">that's enough</u>
<u n="1088" who="S0588">it's only gonna be that much pasta each</u>
<u n="1089" who="S0589">yeah imagine they double in size</u>
<u n="1090" who="S0588">they don't double in size</u>
<u n="1091" who="S0589">pretty much</u>
<u n="1092" who="S0588">I know this from last time</u>
<u n="1093" who="S0589" trans="overlap"><unclear/></u>
<u n="1094" who="S0588"><anon type="name" nameType="m"/> please</u>
<u n="1095" who="S0589">that's probably enough actually so</u>
<u n="1096" who="S0588">no</u>
<u n="1097" who="S0589" trans="overlap">oh okay</u>
<u n="1098" who="S0588">that is a lot</u>
<u n="1099" who="S0589">it's not</u>
<u n="1100" who="S0588">no less darling</u>
<u n="1101" who="S0589" trans="overlap">just humour me then I'm hungry</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
