<text id="SRWD">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:31:01</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2016-06-08</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2016</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2016_Q2</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0679 S0680</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>ANON’s living room, Leeds </rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Local authority trees outside ANON’s house, Leeds Triathlon and disruption on 12 June, About selling things to a shop in Harehills, Leeds, Other shops in Leeds, Bicycle, Bags for Life carrier bags Local authority recycling and bin issues</topics>
		<activity>Chatting with sister, Wednesday evening</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, complaining, anecdote telling, making arrangements</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T19</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0679">
				<exactage>54</exactage>
				<age1994>45_59</age1994>
				<agerange>50_59</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Kent, Margate</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>None/Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Cambridge</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>31 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired (University manager)</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- level unspecified</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0680">
				<exactage>64</exactage>
				<age1994>60plus</age1994>
				<agerange>60_69</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Margate, Kent</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Mostly Southern</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, West Yorks.</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>42 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>unspecified</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>4_graduate</edqual>
				<occupation>Retired teacher</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>8</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- School</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0679"><anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I didn't hear the end of the story about what's happening outside with your trees getting those lower branches cut off where <trunc>d</trunc> how where did it get left?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0680">well <pause dur="short"/> it started in October last year when pieces of <trunc>s</trunc> well thinnish pieces but pieces of branch kept falling down into the garden</u>
<u n="3" who="S0679">I remember that yes erm</u>
<u n="4" who="S0680">and onto the pavements</u>
<u n="5" who="S0679">mm <unclear>not I saw them happen</unclear></u>
<u n="6" who="S0680">and I rang up about it and was told that erm they don't really do anything unless it's an actual danger of a tree falling on somebody basically</u>
<u n="7" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="8" who="S0680">so erm they said they'd send somebody to look and I think it was probably some months later they turned up and I did <trunc>sp</trunc>speak to a gentleman <pause dur="short"/> and erm he was taking a photo he wasn't actually the man who did the work he was taking a photo of what it was like because I'd explained that while I was having my windows replaced I had a <trunc>f</trunc>fine view of the street outside and just a few minutes prior to school children coming along the road erm there was a sizeable bit of branch came down er so I could actually see because I had an <trunc>un</trunc> er uninterrupted view having no windows erm so er they thought about it and they were going to ring me back but of course they didn't erm because also there's a lot of growth all the way up the tree trunks along this road so when you get to a junction it's very difficult to see without sticking your bonnet right out into the road what is coming up and down at the smaller road junctions so</u>
<u n="9" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes that's so dangerous cos I think that's how <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> had that accident whatever happened we don't know exactly</u>
<u n="10" who="S0680"><unclear>yeah</unclear></u>
<u n="11" who="S0679">because of erm that hedge erm that chap <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s hedge</u>
<u n="12" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="13" who="S0679">sorry I interrupt you you're telling me</u>
<u n="14" who="S0680">no no so erm so anyway in the winter there's also the additional problem that you get all these wispy branches growing out from the trunk which are a bit of hazard to pedestrians</u>
<u n="15" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="16" who="S0680">and erm er children <unclear>and so on</unclear> going up and down especially when it's twilight and you can't really see them very well</u>
<u n="17" who="S0679">oh I'd hate to be <trunc>c</trunc> poked get poked in the eye couldn't you?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0680">yes I mean I I do cut the ones off facing my house but I'm not entirely sure whether I'm supposed to do that</u>
<u n="19" who="S0679">now tell me er is it <trunc>bec</trunc> lime trees?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0680">they are lime trees</u>
<u n="21" who="S0679">is that why they have bits that stick out of the trunk so low?</u>
<u n="22" who="S0680">they seem to grow like that yes because the other erm varieties don't have the same problem but erm it seemed to be originally when this was planted there were there were it was a sort of avenue of lime trees really cos they are quite close together</u>
<u n="23" who="S0679">lime trees are <unclear>a pretty duff</unclear> tree aren't they? all round really because erm</u>
<u n="24" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="25" who="S0679">I mean they may have some nice characteristics but they have these bits that stick out of their trunks and they're not like baby trees it's like the main branches are in the right place and then there are all this nasty sticky stuff off them have they got anything good going for them?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes I <pause dur="short"/> well they're quite a nice bright green in leaf</u>
<u n="27" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="28" who="S0680">but the problem is they also shed a heck of a lot of leaves erm and</u>
<u n="29" who="S0679">there's a lot of tree to shed leaves</u>
<u n="30" who="S0680">and they seem to attract the aphids that erm make the sticky stuff that sticks all over everything</u>
<u n="31" who="S0679">oh right</u>
<u n="32" who="S0680">it's the the erm whatever you call it</u>
<u n="33" who="S0679">greenfly</u>
<u n="34" who="S0680">yes it's er <trunc>s</trunc> that sort of</u>
<u n="35" who="S0679">greenflies</u>
<u n="36" who="S0680">yes it's it's erm something from the greenflies I think rather than it's not the tree itself it's the fact that it's the aphids erm producing something</u>
<u n="37" who="S0679">do you think they drink too drink too much of this and it makes them ill? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="38" who="S0680">I think they go they go too too mad on the on the sap and it just produces all this sticky goo</u>
<u n="39" who="S0679">oh gosh I didn't know <unclear/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0680">erm as in as in aphid throughput as it were erm so I don't know really <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0679">so where's that left us now?</u>
<u n="42" who="S0680">so that's left us now with the fact that when we were walking up the road the other day</u>
<u n="43" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="44" who="S0680">erm we observed <unclear>something</unclear></u>
<u n="45" who="S0679">having</u>
<u n="46" who="S0680">as I er had gone out in the other direction er from the end of the row of erm terraces er I didn't notice until we came back</u>
<u n="47" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="48" who="S0680">from the opposite way on that particular bus that on the other side of the road they have trimmed all the offending bits off right from the traffic lights up to</u>
<u n="49" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="50" who="S0680">just beyond so erm that is why I rang them this morning to ask them if they were coming back the other way</u>
<u n="51" who="S0679">I think I missed a bit of the story you said er did that did you have a man out?</u>
<u n="52" who="S0680">well there was a man who came out to take photos of</u>
<u n="53" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="54" who="S0680">and he said the forestry department would get back in touch with me which they haven't actually done</u>
<u n="55" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="56" who="S0680">so that is why I rang them this morning to ask them if they were coming back</u>
<u n="57" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="58" who="S0680">down the other side as I was the person</u>
<u n="59" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="60" who="S0680">or no doubt one of the people who complained on behalf of our row erm and hadn't heard anything but unfortunately I got a very pleasant gentleman who explained to me that the whole of the forestry department are on a training day</u>
<u n="61" who="S0679">gone to the woods</u>
<u n="62" who="S0680"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so erm whether they've gone for a picnic in the woods I don't know but as it's nice weather they were having a training day which erm seems a bit odd that everybody in forestry is there but er</u>
<u n="63" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="64" who="S0680">this chap did attempt to look up a few things but anyway they're going to ring me back tomorrow</u>
<u n="65" who="S0679">did he find your case number?</u>
<u n="66" who="S0680">he found my case number but he couldn't see into <pause dur="short"/> I don't think it was his usual job cos he said there were some other bits he couldn't get into so possibly he didn't have the right erm</u>
<u n="67" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="68" who="S0680"><unclear>you know</unclear> passwords clearance whatever to to erm use that bit of the system</u>
<u n="69" who="S0679">and I suspect you've been given the code number for fussy woman who we won't do anything about</u>
<u n="70" who="S0680">well I don't know</u>
<u n="71" who="S0679">that would be a good thing wouldn't it? you could give people codes and they you could erm listen to what they say</u>
<u n="72" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="73" who="S0679">and then you think oh that's a really deserving person we should try and help them we'll give them code four or four four O nine or something</u>
<u n="74" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="75" who="S0679">and then oh gosh they're a real nuisance we'll give those six four seven and you'd have a list on your wall</u>
<u n="76" who="S0680">that's right</u>
<u n="77" who="S0679"><unclear/> have you got a code? oh you're <trunc>s</trunc> you're you're the awkward person aren't you?</u>
<u n="78" who="S0680">I believe that happens in some places</u>
<u n="79" who="S0679">really? oh gosh I thought I'd just invented it</u>
<u n="80" who="S0680">no I think</u>
<u n="81" who="S0679">nothing's new in the world <unclear>to be honest</unclear></u>
<u n="82" who="S0680">anyway erm so hopefully somebody will ring up to explain if they're coming back down the other side</u>
<u n="83" who="S0679">but they they won't do that they <trunc>sh</trunc> wouldn't've done that today because they were in the woods having their picnic</u>
<u n="84" who="S0680">yes yes well hopefully they've all had a a meaningful experience on their training day</u>
<u n="85" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="86" who="S0680">and perhaps come back revitalised but erm that's that's it</u>
<u n="87" who="S0679">what time did they start? did he say?</u>
<u n="88" who="S0680">no they didn't say what time they start but presumably not all of them are in the office there must be some out and about <trunc>s</trunc>sawing</u>
<u n="89" who="S0679">some are taking photographs and some might even be cutting pieces off trees <unclear>sort of thing</unclear></u>
<u n="90" who="S0680">well they might be</u>
<u n="91" who="S0679">better if he brought a saw rather than a camera did you say that's not the right piece of equipment?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0680"><unclear/> well he was wearing a suit so I knew he wasn't the</u>
<u n="93" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="94" who="S0680">right man for the job but er and he's the one who gave me the piece of paper with</u>
<u n="95" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="96" who="S0680">and put the <trunc>co</trunc>put the code number on for me</u>
<u n="97" who="S0679">he'd have to wear a hard hat in case the branches fell on his head</u>
<u n="98" who="S0680">well that's true I did offer to show him the offending branch</u>
<u n="99" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="100" who="S0680">cos I had it in the back garden</u>
<u n="101" who="S0679">oh yes</u>
<u n="102" who="S0680">but he didn't seem to be too worried about that but there we are so</u>
<u n="103" who="S0679" trans="overlap">so you wait to hear tomorrow</u>
<u n="104" who="S0680">yes and er when I first rang up they before you sort of try and tell them anything they tell you oh no if it's something to do with blocking your light or various other things we or overhanging your garden blocking your light we can't do anything about that</u>
<u n="105" who="S0679">but if it was somebody else's tree er as a neighbour you would have certain rights shouldn't you? isn't there something about hedges shouldn't be too tall?</u>
<u n="106" who="S0680">hedges are a certain height</u>
<u n="107" who="S0679">so surely a tree should not be that big?</u>
<u n="108" who="S0680">but if it's blocking your light it can't be <pause dur="short"/> well these trees have probably got a preservation order on them or something I wouldn't be a bit surprised but erm that was the thing</u>
<u n="109" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="110" who="S0680">so I mean apart from the fact the tree is now wider than my house and taller than my house</u>
<u n="111" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="112" who="S0680">and the fact that my house is only fifteen feet wide it's only as wide as the lounge</u>
<u n="113" who="S0679">mm mm mm</u>
<u n="114" who="S0680">erm considering it's only that wide I have this tree and I also have a lamp post and a telegraph pole</u>
<u n="115" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="116" who="S0680">admittedly you know they were all there when I moved in</u>
<u n="117" who="S0679">they'd probably take the lamp post away these days and not give you one there</u>
<u n="118" who="S0680">but erm that may happen er but you know there is rather a lot going on in the pavement outside my house</u>
<u n="119" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="120" who="S0680">considering how narrow my house is so er it is a bit tricky cos if you <vocal desc="laugh"/>  as when we arrived in the taxi the other day when the poor man was trying to stop to avoid</u>
<u n="121" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="122" who="S0680">so we could actually open</u>
<u n="123" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="124" who="S0680">both doors of the taxi <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="125" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="126" who="S0680">it is er tricky</u>
<u n="127" who="S0679">mm now is there anything we need to find out? cos tomorrow <unclear/> tomorrow's Thursday isn't it?</u>
<u n="128" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="129" who="S0679">so we've got Thursday and Friday is there anything we need to possibly ask about the triathlon on Sunday isn't it?</u>
<u n="130" who="S0680">well we can we can have a go at the website I have tried</u>
<u n="131" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="132" who="S0680">putting in the thing for the the W W for the <trunc>w</trunc>work website</u>
<u n="133" who="S0679">yes <unclear/></u>
<u n="134" who="S0680">but it's got an interactive map</u>
<u n="135" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="136" who="S0680">but it seems to have a life of its own</u>
<u n="137" who="S0679">would you write that on your things to do? you could put it down at the bottom if it's not the most important thing</u>
<u n="138" who="S0680">so look up triathlon I think I've worked the route out looking at the yellow signs</u>
<u n="139" who="S0679">and we need to estimate the difference <trunc>betw</trunc> different the distance not different and between here and</u>
<u n="140" who="S0680">and the park</u>
<u n="141" who="S0679"><anon type="place"/> so we can go for our very own teddy bears' picnic on your birthday</u>
<u n="142" who="S0680">this is true</u>
<u n="143" who="S0679">as long as we can manage the walking</u>
<u n="144" who="S0680">well the it's difficult this weekend as well because having the roads closed round here because some people are having Queen events er this weekend</u>
<u n="145" who="S0679">yes yes that's Sunday too it's she's decided to have her birthday</u>
<u n="146" who="S0680">because down the road in <anon type="place"/> they're having er street parties</u>
<u n="147" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="148" who="S0680">and things</u>
<u n="149" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="150" who="S0680">now if you're somebody from outside who's going there you know</u>
<u n="151" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="152" who="S0680"><trunc>f</trunc>friends of erm <unclear>I'd</unclear> you're gonna have to <vocal desc="laugh"/> stay the night I would think because you're not going to be able to drive down there</u>
<u n="153" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="154" who="S0680">from one o'clock in the morning</u>
<u n="155" who="S0679">well I think the idea of a street party is you just have the neighbours</u>
<u n="156" who="S0680">I know but you know it's just</u>
<u n="157" who="S0679">which is at least something you can do if you can't go out <unclear/></u>
<u n="158" who="S0680">no but if there's relatives</u>
<u n="159" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="160" who="S0680">you know if somebody's parents are coming</u>
<u n="161" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="162" who="S0680">or children or whatever then erm</u>
<u n="163" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="164" who="S0680">you know they've got to make sure they're in situ cos er</u>
<u n="165" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="166" who="S0680">there's no transport</u>
<u n="167" who="S0679">no quick dash to Waitrose before it starts</u>
<u n="168" who="S0680">no <vocal desc="laugh"/> so er there we are so how far to <anon type="place"/>? well if we drive that way tomorrow I can clock it</u>
<u n="169" who="S0679">mm <pause dur="short"/> now you wanted to look at something in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="170" who="S0680">ah <anon type="place"/> now where was I going in <anon type="place"/>?</u>
<u n="171" who="S0679">it was a shop I don't know why you wanted to look at the shop to see if there was parking outside</u>
<u n="172" who="S0680">ah no I wanted to establish where that shop was</u>
<u n="173" who="S0679">do we know the name of the shop?</u>
<u n="174" who="S0680">it's the one that may potentially well it's a branch of the one that may potentially</u>
<u n="175" who="S0679">do you want to write the name down and I'll look it up?</u>
<u n="176" who="S0680">may potentially be interested in buying <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s vast collection of speakers or at least the big ones that we can't move the trouble is they're they're not people who come and collect well he said he didn't come and collect in town but</u>
<u n="177" who="S0679">okay well <trunc>le</trunc>let's just establish what we can about the shop cos there might be some things we could take there</u>
<u n="178" who="S0680"><unclear>but</unclear> the other man doesn't want them because they're too big for his shop</u>
<u n="179" who="S0679">no <unclear/></u>
<u n="180" who="S0680">but they're very they have a very good tone</u>
<u n="181" who="S0679">okay erm</u>
<u n="182" who="S0680">and I was going to go into <anon type="place"/> the erm</u>
<u n="183" who="S0679">estate agent?</u>
<u n="184" who="S0680">er ironmongers</u>
<u n="185" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="186" who="S0680">next to <anon type="place"/> well it isn't <anon type="place"/> school what was <anon type="place"/> school</u>
<u n="187" who="S0679">what? your school?</u>
<u n="188" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="189" who="S0679">oh yes</u>
<u n="190" who="S0680">erm</u>
<u n="191" who="S0679">ironmongers?</u>
<u n="192" who="S0680"><anon type="place"/> yes</u>
<u n="193" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="194" who="S0680">it's just a few doors along er it's no longer Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> there was a Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/></u>
<u n="195" who="S0679">is that the really small shop with all the <trunc>bo</trunc>all the <trunc>bo</trunc> where you can't can't exactly throw your arms and legs about?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0680">no that's that's in <anon type="place"/> this is an er ironmongers general shop</u>
<u n="197" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="198" who="S0680">locksmith he's the locksmith who</u>
<u n="199" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="200" who="S0680">who looked at <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s door and then er he's no longer Mr <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> who was a</u>
<u n="201" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="202" who="S0680">erm a very <anon type="place"/> gentleman he retired in about nineteen eighty and erm somebody else another man took it over erm and there were various people work there and they're they're very helpful but it is one of these shops you walk in they have had it er slightly modernised but you walk up and down the rows and there's just sort of you know boxes of all sorts of hardware stuff and you can buy lengths of chain and erm you know sort of plugs or bigger</u>
<u n="203" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="204" who="S0680">and all sorts of things and he's he's got very good <unclear>lot of</unclear> locks and so so forth he's the man who came to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s and took the lock away that second lock because they no longer make a lock that would fit in that particular door erm because it's probably the original one so he took it away and replaced some of its insides</u>
<u n="205" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="206" who="S0680">rather than</u>
<u n="207" who="S0679">for a very reasonable price</u>
<u n="208" who="S0680">for a very reasonable price <trunc>n</trunc> so you didn't have to have another lock which would've meant cutting a whole different section out of the door</u>
<u n="209" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="210" who="S0680">and making a mess erm and he was very helpful and he and he also supplied me with erm numerous keys which is what</u>
<u n="211" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="212" who="S0680">I needed just for the you know for the same price as you'd pay for <unclear>bought it with the lock</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="213" who="S0679">yes I checked in Timpson's and they said erm Yale and mortice they cost six or seven pounds each</u>
<u n="214" who="S0680" trans="overlap">a very nice man <pause dur="short"/> no well these in <anon type="place"/> they're they're two pounds</u>
<u n="215" who="S0679">mm I thought I'd pay about two pounds</u>
<u n="216" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="217" who="S0679">so I think I might shop around but I had to get the car key done there</u>
<u n="218" who="S0680">yeah but if you wanted to it probably wouldn't be much use cos you wouldn't try them but erm you I mean you could have a key cut there <trunc>th</trunc>they're usually alright</u>
<u n="219" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> I haven't got any with me so</u>
<u n="220" who="S0680">no but you wouldn't be able to try them very readily cos it's rather a long way to your house but erm they're very good anyway that's that is a proper ironmongers-type shop and there is that one there used to be one in <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="221" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="222" who="S0680">erm run by a very nice Sikh gentleman who died unfortunately</u>
<u n="223" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="224" who="S0680">he was quite old and his wife and his son ran it for a while but his it wasn't really his son's</u>
<u n="225" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="226" who="S0680">kind of job erm but unfortunately they <trunc>ha</trunc> are no longer there erm they did have to close but there is the place in <anon type="place"/> I mentioned erm round the corner from Audio Republic erm hi-fi shop and near what used to be <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s fish and chip shop</u>
<u n="227" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="228" who="S0680">that's now</u>
<u n="229" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="230" who="S0680">been taken over</u>
<u n="231" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="232" who="S0680">erm just on that little corner there is erm an older gentleman who has a shop that is as you say you walk in and he's got a little tiny counter and there's shelves floor to ceiling and you just stand in a little area</u>
<u n="233" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="234" who="S0680">he knows where everything is but you can't actually circulate because it's tiny</u>
<u n="235" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="236" who="S0680">he he just <unclear/> <unclear>you</unclear></u>
<u n="237" who="S0679">what's he what's that one called?</u>
<u n="238" who="S0680">erm now I can't remember that one's name but it's something like two people's names put together or <pause dur="short"/> it's not Bilko <vocal desc="laugh"/> cos that's a different programme altogether but it's</u>
<u n="239" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="240" who="S0680">it's like er</u>
<u n="241" who="S0679">it's er something that sounds like a shop name but it part of it's probably his name</u>
<u n="242" who="S0680">mm mm</u>
<u n="243" who="S0679">because he also has that on some of his little packets of nuts and bolts and things</u>
<u n="244" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="245" who="S0680">okay and I've got that erm dawn to dusk kind of nightlight</u>
<u n="246" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="247" who="S0680">thing there which is erm it's an LED it's not a bulb one</u>
<u n="248" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="249" who="S0680">anymore</u>
<u n="250" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="251" who="S0680">so that er that's a very nice shop to look in</u>
<u n="252" who="S0679">so sorry what was it you wanted to buy in <anon type="place"/>? <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="253" who="S0680">face mask er not a face mask a <trunc>du</trunc> I was considering there was a place to buy a dust mask or dust masks disposable</u>
<u n="254" who="S0679"><unclear/> bought some there have you?</u>
<u n="255" who="S0680"><unclear/> I bought those in Wilkos</u>
<u n="256" who="S0679">but there must have been something else you wanted you just said we could go er sorry I thought you said we could go to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="257" who="S0680">no er I I was thinking of going to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="258" who="S0679">but you don't need to</u>
<u n="259" who="S0680">no <anon type="place"/> or because I <trunc>w</trunc> as I was in town waiting for your delayed train</u>
<u n="260" who="S0679">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="261" who="S0680">erm I er went in there and got some like the ones I had before</u>
<u n="262" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="263" who="S0680">although as I said to you the it was funny because I said to the man I I I was in the hardware section but I said to this chap erm I'm looking for face masks and he kind of looked at me a bit strangely cos I he was in some quandary as to whether I wanted like a face pack or a</u>
<u n="264" who="S0679">mm oh right</u>
<u n="265" who="S0680">a mask to wear in bed</u>
<u n="266" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="267" who="S0680">cos I said I don't want it something to cover my eyes when I'm in bed I said I don't want anything cosmetics</u>
<u n="268" who="S0679">oh yes</u>
<u n="269" who="S0680">being a lady although I don't look that much of the sort of lady who would have <unclear>them</unclear></u>
<u n="270" who="S0679">do you call them face masks?</u>
<u n="271" who="S0680">I don't <unclear/></u>
<u n="272" who="S0679"><unclear/>?</u>
<u n="273" who="S0680">erm they're dust masks</u>
<u n="274" who="S0679">oh right okay</u>
<u n="275" who="S0680">so I said erm</u>
<u n="276" who="S0679"><unclear>so he'd've wanted</unclear> to give you mud a mud pack</u>
<u n="277" who="S0680">yes so he wanted to give me something for a lady really I think</u>
<u n="278" who="S0679"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="279" who="S0680">but he didn't like to say that because it is not politically correct</u>
<u n="280" who="S0679">no</u>
<u n="281" who="S0680">so I <trunc>s</trunc>I sort of said oh I said I want to wear it for sanding down <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="282" who="S0679">mm probably he was erm</u>
<u n="283" who="S0680">chiselling my features yeah</u>
<u n="284" who="S0679"><unclear/> really trying to think how he could say it without <unclear/> <unclear>giving you</unclear> potentially</u>
<u n="285" who="S0680">well that's right so I thought I'd jump we were in that section I said you know cos I said you know for sanding and keeping so you're not breathing in dust particles</u>
<u n="286" who="S0679">mm mm</u>
<u n="287" who="S0680">because I'm I'm <vocal desc="laugh"/> turning out a cellar and he then sort of looked at me even more strangely <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="288" who="S0679">yes well</u>
<u n="289" who="S0680"><trunc>w</trunc>what is this woman doing?</u>
<u n="290" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="291" who="S0680">erm so erm and then he I must've walked passed them but he pointed them out to me I said oh yes I said they're the ones I usually have <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="292" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="293" who="S0680">as if I'm always wearing them <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="294" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="295" who="S0680">er so that was quite funny you can get these strange women in shops</u>
<u n="296" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yeah very strange</u>
<u n="297" who="S0680">so er so that's er</u>
<u n="298" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="299" who="S0680">why I bought them and erm drove to the station with them <vocal desc="yawn"/></u>
<u n="300" who="S0679">talking about the cellar I <trunc>w</trunc> looked I'm tempted to send the photographs from the Carlton bicycle brochure that we you showed me</u>
<u n="301" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="302" who="S0679">to <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> I think he might quite like it</u>
<u n="303" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="304" who="S0679">but I don't like to tempt him with things that he can't have</u>
<u n="305" who="S0680">well he <trunc>ca</trunc> <trunc>w</trunc> he could have it but he can't have it cos we can't get it there</u>
<u n="306" who="S0679">no</u>
<u n="307" who="S0680">unless he's thinking of sponsoring himself to ride it back to <anon type="place"/> <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="308" who="S0679">mm mm mm mm</u>
<u n="309" who="S0680">er or <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="310" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="311" who="S0680">I should say in his case shouldn't I? yes</u>
<u n="312" who="S0679">oh he was also saying something very strange cos he's quite every time he's he tries to give us carrier bags now when we see him</u>
<u n="313" who="S0680">oh right</u>
<u n="314" who="S0679">erm because he doesn't like</u>
<u n="315" who="S0680"><unclear/> bag for life</u>
<u n="316" who="S0679">he doesn't <pause dur="short"/> yes well apparently</u>
<u n="317" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="318" who="S0679">he lives in that you know a flat and</u>
<u n="319" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="320" who="S0679">I think there's six in the block</u>
<u n="321" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="322" who="S0679">and he said you know now you have to pay for carrier bags?</u>
<u n="323" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="324" who="S0679">he said <trunc>hi</trunc>his dustbin erm gets completely stuffed up with bag for life carrier bags that he takes out of the dustbin</u>
<u n="325" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="326" who="S0679">takes back to the shop I think and gets a new one</u>
<u n="327" who="S0680">oh right</u>
<u n="328" who="S0679">because people think it's better value</u>
<u n="329" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="330" who="S0679">to erm presumably</u>
<u n="331" who="S0680">well those are much</u>
<u n="332" who="S0679">buy the thick one rather than the thin one but when they get <trunc>h</trunc></u>
<u n="333" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="334" who="S0679">because the thin one breaks on the way home from the shop and then they just throw them straightaway and they don't even recycle them</u>
<u n="335" who="S0680">no but perhaps they can't</u>
<u n="336" who="S0679"><anon type="place"/>'s gone funny about recycling cos they er they've taken the green bin er well your brown bin my green bin</u>
<u n="337" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="338" who="S0679">er away and maybe they're they're taking the er no I think at the moment you can still do the plastic one</u>
<u n="339" who="S0680">they've taken the recycling bins away?</u>
<u n="340" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="341" who="S0680"><unclear>oh they've</unclear> taken the one that you put er compostables in and garden rubbish so that means people are putting them in the black bins</u>
<u n="342" who="S0679">yes yes</u>
<u n="343" who="S0680">and they'll get charged more for landfill</u>
<u n="344" who="S0679">yes yes</u>
<u n="345" who="S0680">presumably?</u>
<u n="346" who="S0679">yeah <pause dur="short"/> and next year they're going to take away the plastic <trunc>re</trunc> you know the the one you put your paper in and your glass and your plastic er that is the recycling bin do they have different?</u>
<u n="347" who="S0680">well hold on</u>
<u n="348" who="S0679">you can't</u>
<u n="349" who="S0680">I can't have glass</u>
<u n="350" who="S0679">I've got a black bin</u>
<u n="351" who="S0680">yes yeah</u>
<u n="352" who="S0680">that's household general non-recyclable rubbish</u>
<u n="353" who="S0680" trans="overlap"><trunc>h</trunc> yeah <pause dur="short"/> and I guess it gets very</u>
<u n="354" who="S0679">so we're common on black</u>
<u n="355" who="S0680">yes we're common on black</u>
<u n="356" who="S0679">I've got a green bin that I put green things in</u>
<u n="357" who="S0680">garden waste which yours is brown my garden waste is brown</u>
<u n="358" who="S0679">you've got another bin</u>
<u n="359" who="S0680">but it's only selected garden waste specially selected</u>
<u n="360" who="S0679" trans="overlap">yes I know you can only put <pause dur="short"/> windfall apples and not apple peelings</u>
<u n="361" who="S0680">yes <pause dur="short"/> mm <pause dur="short"/> yes <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="362" who="S0679">okay that's the one that they've lost</u>
<u n="363" who="S0680">you can't put any organic</u>
<u n="364" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="365" who="S0680">well any sort of food waste or you can't put any</u>
<u n="366" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="367" who="S0680">any because our system doesn't kind of cook it all up</u>
<u n="368" who="S0679">no no</u>
<u n="369" who="S0680">whereas your system does</u>
<u n="370" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="371" who="S0680">so it the microbes don't get <unclear>deaded</unclear></u>
<u n="372" who="S0679" trans="overlap">except it doesn't in <anon type="place"/> now unless you pay fifty pounds</u>
<u n="373" who="S0680">right</u>
<u n="374" who="S0679">but I don't know how they identify whose bin should be emptied for fifty pounds</u>
<u n="375" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="376" who="S0679">okay</u>
<u n="377" who="S0680">perhaps it has a big pound sign on it in gold</u>
<u n="378" who="S0679">yeah and then we've got the third bin which I is blue for me</u>
<u n="379" who="S0680">or when they lift the lid it goes kerching</u>
<u n="380" who="S0679"><unclear>mm yes</unclear></u>
<u n="381" who="S0680">cos it's making money for the council <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="382" who="S0679">I've got one that's blue</u>
<u n="383" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="384" who="S0679">that I can put plastic erm glass</u>
<u n="385" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="386" who="S0679">and all that sort of stuff and I've got the paper that's the one that has the paper caddy in it</u>
<u n="387" who="S0680">well you've got subdivisions haven't you?</u>
<u n="388" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="389" who="S0680">you've got carrier you've got sub-trays sort of things</u>
<u n="390" who="S0679">I've got paper yes</u>
<u n="391" who="S0680">paper</u>
<u n="392" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="393" who="S0680">trays</u>
<u n="394" who="S0679">except <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> in <anon type="place"/> they just throw it all in one</u>
<u n="395" who="S0680">yes</u>
<u n="396" who="S0679">so all the paper gets all mixed up with the</u>
<u n="397" who="S0680">yes but when it goes for sorting they must be able to segregate that</u>
<u n="398" who="S0679">oh they do sort they do take it out again but it gets a bit spoilt</u>
<u n="399" who="S0680">because my green my green bin</u>
<u n="400" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="401" who="S0680">which is my recycling bin you can put some sorts of paper in it but you just lob it all in together although you probably should take it to an actual specified paper thing at the dump or at the supermarket you know post it in</u>
<u n="402" who="S0679">do you put cardboard in that one?</u>
<u n="403" who="S0680">no er what? I can put it in mine</u>
<u n="404" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="405" who="S0680">yes I can put cardboard in my own personal green bin I can put</u>
<u n="406" who="S0679">and you just put the paper in the whole bin you don't put it separately?</u>
<u n="407" who="S0680">no it all goes in together but I don't put papers in there because when I er because I we have to <trunc>s</trunc> recycle glass ourself ourselves</u>
<u n="408" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="409" who="S0680">we can't put them in the bin I take the glass and the paper together because I can put it in either the tip ones or I can do it up at the shopping centre erm so I don't personally erm put my newspapers in</u>
<u n="410" who="S0679">okay</u>
<u n="411" who="S0680">I do put envelopes and odd bits of</u>
<u n="412" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="413" who="S0680">kitchen erm wrapping off er you know <trunc>f</trunc> suitable paper</u>
<u n="414" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="415" who="S0680">that's been on a food item and we can't put glass in</u>
<u n="416" who="S0679">no</u>
<u n="417" who="S0680">so the problem here is if if you don't live near a glass recycling bin then erm you have great difficulties like <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> next door who hasn't got a car he if he wanted to take glass to recycle he'd have to take it on the bus with him cos there's nowhere within walking distance in this area because the people would probably complain about the noise <vocal desc="laugh"/> erm but erm for example the old lady <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> we know</u>
<u n="418" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="419" who="S0680">in another bit of <anon type="place"/> she hasn't even got a bus available to catch or anything so she just puts all her glass</u>
<u n="420" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="421" who="S0680">in the dustbin unless she</u>
<u n="422" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="423" who="S0680">has given it to me to recycle not that she has that much or she has to give it to the person who gets her shopping to do something with</u>
<u n="424" who="S0679">mm <pause dur="short"/> she's very naughty with things</u>
<u n="425" who="S0680">but</u>
<u n="426" who="S0679">because I saw her in her back garden and she had some litter in her back garden</u>
<u n="427" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="428" who="S0679">and she just poked it through her gate or round her gate into the street</u>
<u n="429" who="S0680">yes because it is not her litter <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="430" who="S0679">which I didn't I didn't think that was quite the public-spirited <trunc>s</trunc> approach</u>
<u n="431" who="S0680">no</u>
<u n="432" who="S0679">erm especially as an agoraphobic who doesn't go in her house went down her garden to her bottom of her</u>
<u n="433" who="S0680">mm</u>
<u n="434" who="S0679">garden</u>
<u n="435" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="436" who="S0679">admittedly not a very big garden to to put her erm to put her er litter out</u>
<u n="437" who="S0680" trans="overlap">well <trunc>sh</trunc>she will go down there <pause dur="short"/> cos she has to put her that's why she her bin's there but erm</u>
<u n="438" who="S0679" trans="overlap">mm <pause dur="short"/> even er more reason why she should put it in her bin but anyway one shouldn't be</u>
<u n="439" who="S0680">mm I don't know</u>
<u n="440" who="S0679">yes but anyway what I was saying is <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> the bin that your green bin my blue bin</u>
<u n="441" who="S0680">yeah</u>
<u n="442" who="S0679">they're going to scrap in <anon type="place"/> next year</u>
<u n="443" who="S0680">recycling?</u>
<u n="444" who="S0679">yeah which is ridiculous</u>
<u n="445" who="S0680">yeah <unclear/></u>
<u n="446" who="S0679">it's absolutely not thought through all the council tax will go up and <unclear/> landfill</u>
<u n="447" who="S0680" trans="overlap">yes <pause dur="short"/> yeah yeah <pause dur="short"/> question</u>
<u n="448" who="S0679">mm yes</u>
<u n="449" who="S0680"><unclear>yeah</unclear> so there we are and of course round not where that lady lives they haven't been told but we were told by the council that if we leave our bin out after the time it's after the day it's been collected so you're supposed to put your bin out before seven in the morning or certainly not till the night before</u>
<u n="450" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="451" who="S0680">if it's then still out after it's been collected and you haven't put it away by you know the next day presumably erm you there is a possibility you will be fined seventy-five pounds per bin</u>
<u n="452" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="453" who="S0680">which is a bit much if it's only certain areas <unclear>are getting</unclear> <unclear/></u>
<u n="454" who="S0679">yes absolutely erm but they haven't they you put your bin out and they haven't emptied it</u>
<u n="455" who="S0680">but then there's the problem with the fact that I put my bin out I do tend to put my bin out slightly earlier than evening because I'm not walking all the way round</u>
<u n="456" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="457" who="S0680">the back of my terrace and round to put my bin out the front where it gets collected in the dark</u>
<u n="458" who="S0679">yes it's hardly a a trivial activity taking your bin out</u>
<u n="459" who="S0680">or in the winter no I mean it is quite a distance</u>
<u n="460" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="461" who="S0680">as there's only one end we can get round the terrace</u>
<u n="462" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="463" who="S0680">erm so there is that and also the fact like today I put it out yesterday afternoon erm late sort of it was out late afternoon ready for the and it's a wide pavement so it's not actually blocking anybody's way</u>
<u n="464" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="465" who="S0680">and erm as we find coming back tonight it just hasn't been emptied</u>
<u n="466" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="467" who="S0680">so are they coming tomorrow?</u>
<u n="468" who="S0679">well they can't fine you by not <unclear>putting</unclear> it in</u>
<u n="469" who="S0680">so I've pulled it into the gateway</u>
<u n="470" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="471" who="S0680">will they consider that sufficiently out on the street? erm and also you're really supposed to push it to the kerb now if on the day</u>
<u n="472" who="S0679"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="473" who="S0680">two of my bins are if on the day when my brown and my green bin are collected on the same day which it should've been this particular week but I didn't put the green one out cos it wasn't full enough erm it means there is a hazard because I've got the as previously mentioned I've got the tree which is an old tree so it's got a good girth on it</u>
<u n="474" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="475" who="S0680">the lamp post admittedly the telegraph pole is further back and then I've got two bins cos you're supposed to put them on the edge of the kerb</u>
<u n="476" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="477" who="S0680">which means there's quite a run of that bit of road</u>
<u n="478" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="479" who="S0680">for anybody parking</u>
<u n="480" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="481" who="S0680">where they won't their passengers would not be able to get out <vocal desc="laugh"/> <vocal desc="cough"/></u>
<u n="482" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="483" who="S0680">so I'm not quite sure where we are on the seventy-five pound argument I don't think anybody's</u>
<u n="484" who="S0679">no</u>
<u n="485" who="S0680">erm taken the council to task on that one if they've been tried to be fined but it is a bit much to fine this area I suppose it's because a lot of houses in this area are big</u>
<u n="486" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="487" who="S0680">detached houses</u>
<u n="488" who="S0679">yeah</u>
<u n="489" who="S0680">and they think <unclear>well</unclear> people won't you know they can afford to do it and they won't make they might kick up a fuss but they'll pay anyway</u>
<u n="490" who="S0679">and if you live in a back-to-back it gets a bit difficult doesn't it? cos you haven't got a</u>
<u n="491" who="S0680">well you have to put it down in er</u>
<u n="492" who="S0679">oh you might if you're a street if you're on a if you're a back-to-back you you <trunc>ha</trunc> do you have a front garden?</u>
<u n="493" who="S0680">some yeah well where we lived at <anon type="place"/> did</u>
<u n="494" who="S0679">yes I was thinking it did</u>
<u n="495" who="S0680">but back-to-backs that are on the street like the ones they've still got in <anon type="place"/> <unclear>six</unclear></u>
<u n="496" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="497" who="S0680">every few houses there's a common yard where the bins tend to go</u>
<u n="498" who="S0679">oh right</u>
<u n="499" who="S0680">but you've got to wheel your bin up or down</u>
<u n="500" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="501" who="S0680">to get it in and also those streets if you think of going down to the main road they're very steep and a lot of people chain their bins to the downpipes or whatever because if you put your bin out</u>
<u n="502" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="503" who="S0680">well it doesn't need to be icy but if you live on a steep hill</u>
<u n="504" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="505" who="S0680">you haven't got a level surface to put your bin have you?</u>
<u n="506" who="S0679">oh I see and they <trunc>s</trunc>they sliddle down the hill</u>
<u n="507" who="S0680">well if that's a possibility because they're really steep roads</u>
<u n="508" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="509" who="S0680">and you haven't really got a flat area cos you've got no garden to pull something in and lean it on the gatepost</u>
<u n="510" who="S0679">so do you have to unchain it every week?</u>
<u n="511" who="S0680">but I have noticed there are some that are chained</u>
<u n="512" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="513" who="S0680">but I don't think I think some of them do keep them chained to their erm thingy-bob but as I say some of the other houses they do have erm</u>
<u n="514" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="515" who="S0680">they do have those little yard areas communal yards that you can keep your bin in</u>
<u n="516" who="S0679">it's not a problem in <anon type="place"/> you know</u>
<u n="517" who="S0680">no no back-to-backs</u>
<u n="518" who="S0679">no no no erm you wouldn't have to chain it for that reason</u>
<u n="519" who="S0680">oh</u>
<u n="520" who="S0679">it wouldn't go down the slope</u>
<u n="521" who="S0680">oh no it'd be flat I see what you mean</u>
<u n="522" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="523" who="S0680">yes yes and probably you don't have to have a problem in <anon type="place"/> either <unclear/></u>
<u n="524" who="S0679">no there's a few areas that are fine although in <anon type="place"/> you might get a bit <unclear>bogged down</unclear></u>
<u n="525" who="S0680">yes so</u>
<u n="526" who="S0679">okay</u>
<u n="527" who="S0680">there we are so we'll see if anybody turns up for my bin tomorrow</u>
<u n="528" who="S0679">yes yes is it full?</u>
<u n="529" who="S0680">I would like that one emptied cos it is the garden bin</u>
<u n="530" who="S0679">mm</u>
<u n="531" who="S0680">so it is full of garden stuff</u>
<u n="532" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="533" who="S0680">and I do need to cut the hedge</u>
<u n="534" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="535" who="S0680">so I'll need another empty bin</u>
<u n="536" who="S0679">yes</u>
<u n="537" who="S0680">okay</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
