<text id="SRZT">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:11:04</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2015-01-14</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2015</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2015_Q1</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0367 S0420</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Ryan's Bar, Edinburgh</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Friends, wider family circle</relationships>
		<topics>Travel, photography, weather conditions</topics>
		<activity>Friends talking about a hobby</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing, explaining, inquiring, anecdote telling</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>n</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T02</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0367">
				<exactage>31</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>Scottish</nat>
				<birthplace>Edinburgh</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Scotland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Scotland</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Scottish</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Edinburgh</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Scotland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>31.5 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>scotland</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>scotland</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>scotland</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Warehouse Regional Trainer</occupation>
				<socgrade>D</socgrade>
				<nssec>7</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0420">
				<exactage>32</exactage>
				<age1994>25_34</age1994>
				<agerange>30_39</agerange>
				<gender>M</gender>
				<nat>Scotish</nat>
				<birthplace>Edinburgh</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>Scotland</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>Scotland</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Edinburgh</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Edinburgh</hab_city>
				<hab_country>Scotland</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>20 years</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>scotland</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>scotland</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>scotland</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>5_postgrad</edqual>
				<occupation>Director of Studies</occupation>
				<socgrade>A</socgrade>
				<nssec>1_2</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0420">so I I didn't know you were going away I <trunc>wha</trunc>what was it for?</u>
<u n="2" who="S0367">well the plan was it was I was meant to go to Glencoe so I'd been checking the weather forecast for the last week the weather was meant to be okay so it was mainly just to <unclear/> get a few pictures taken for the calendar for next year</u>
<u n="3" who="S0420">is this just yourself?</u>
<u n="4" who="S0367">yeah just myself just one day er leave early in the morning come back afternoon time but as the week went on the weather forecast got worse and worse</u>
<u n="5" who="S0420">oh</u>
<u n="6" who="S0367">so yesterday's forecast was to be heavy snow so the trouble is if you go past <unclear>Tyndrum</unclear> you've got the snow gates</u>
<u n="7" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah it can be closed off can't it</u>
<u n="8" who="S0367" trans="overlap">so I could probably get there fine the snowline comes down and I'm stuck up there</u>
<u n="9" who="S0420"><vocal desc="laugh"/> ah well there's worse places to be stuck ain't there?</u>
<u n="10" who="S0367">there is but when you don't plan for it</u>
<u n="11" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="12" who="S0367">erm and especially up there being as remote as it is and the lack of places</u>
<u n="13" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="14" who="S0367">you don't really wanna be left er with nowhere to go so</u>
<u n="15" who="S0420">yeah especially with what you're carrying you've not got a four by four or anything have you?</u>
<u n="16" who="S0367" trans="overlap">no we've not er traction control's about as much as it is thank you cheers so decided</u>
<u n="17" who="UNKFEMALE" whoConfidence="low">are you done with this yeah? shall I take this?</u>
<u n="18" who="S0367">yeah thank you <pause dur="short"/> so change the plans still went up about as far as Tyndrum but safely stayed south of the snow gate so I I could still get stranded by I know that at least the gritters would get as far as the snow gates er should it get any worse so that's what I did went up there yesterday er</u>
<u n="19" who="S0420">what time did you set off?</u>
<u n="20" who="S0367">left just after eight in the morning the snow got</u>
<u n="21" who="S0420" trans="overlap">it was what it was light by then or</u>
<u n="22" who="S0367">no well</u>
<u n="23" who="S0420">or</u>
<u n="24" who="S0367">it was still it was still dark it was meant to be light by the time I got to Stirling but because the the snow was that heavy it was still <unclear/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0420" trans="overlap">was it really heavy grey clouds</u>
<u n="26" who="S0367">grey dark</u>
<u n="27" who="S0420">yeah yeah</u>
<u n="28" who="S0367">er so the snow was really heavy come from about Stirling headed towards Calendar it was getting worse snow was lying on the the road like so the traffic was down to about twenty thirty miles an hour so I ended up taking about two hours just to get up to where I needed to get to so yeah but it was a good day if snow was on or off but I had to abandon <unclear/> eh went up there but it was a single track road left the car in the car park headed off to</u>
<u n="29" who="S0420" trans="overlap">is that the one that the end of Loch Erne? <pause dur="short"/> no</u>
<u n="30" who="S0367" trans="overlap">no er <unclear>Balqhuidder</unclear> before Loch Erne so you take a left and you head up a single track road to <unclear>Balqhuidderkirk</unclear> where Rob Roy's grave is</u>
<u n="31" who="S0420">yeah yeah I've been there yeah</u>
<u n="32" who="S0367">so but at the end of Balquhidder you've got Loch Voil which then leads into another loch at the end of that</u>
<u n="33" who="S0420">ah yeah that's that's the one I was thinking of yeah</u>
<u n="34" who="S0367" trans="overlap"><unclear/> to climb so had a few plans to do er get a few pictures taken along Loch Voil the weather there was worth than it was anywhere else so turned back within about twenty or thirty minutes of being there I had to dig the car out cos the snow was honestly the snow was that bad</u>
<u n="35" who="S0420">jesus</u>
<u n="36" who="S0367">cleared the car got all my stuff off went to set off and had to clear the car again cos it was that heavy</u>
<u n="37" who="S0420" trans="overlap"><vocal desc="laugh"/> so you were like stuck in the snow you had to did you have a shovel or</u>
<u n="38" who="S0367">I had well took a shovel with me just in case I did get stuck so dug the car out made sure the</u>
<u n="39" who="S0420" trans="overlap">you weren't panicking at any point? <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="40" who="S0367">oh no no no no it was a good day out it was fun so had to make sure the road was clear cos no one had been across the road erm and then I set off once the car had been cleared for the second time and headed across to Loch Erne it's only about five miles away but the difference in those five miles had been a bit lower lower down the the weather was different</u>
<u n="41" who="S0420" trans="overlap">the hills can cut off some of the weather as well couldn't they</u>
<u n="42" who="S0367">yeah eh where <trunc>loc</trunc> er Balquhidder is it's right at the end of a valley so it just seemed to be coming straight down the valley and you couldn't even see up the valley you couldn't even see Loch Voil it was that that bad I've got <unclear>pictures</unclear></u>
<u n="43" who="S0420" trans="overlap">did you did you come across anyone else? <vocal desc="laugh"/> or were you the only nutcase out there</u>
<u n="44" who="S0367">I was probably the only nutcase but the other folk I did see were locals and I did get a few kinda strange looks as if they say like what are you doing up here eh by yourself? eh even you're not going to work we were just staying in for the day especially the fact that I had my camera bag and my tripod eh they could obviously see why I was there but I think it still the weather was that bad and a single track road where the gritters don't go I think they were kinda like you'd better get yourself away soon</u>
<u n="45" who="S0420">yeah yeah and so <trunc>d</trunc> I saw one of your photos on Facebook with the er the robin</u>
<u n="46" who="S0367" trans="overlap">the robin</u>
<u n="47" who="S0420">that's beautiful how how did you get so close or was it with the zoom?</u>
<u n="48" who="S0367">er no no it wasn't even a a zoom lens just at the start of Loch <unclear>Luneck</unclear> so it's just north of Calendar there's a wee car park at the start of the loch so I pulled in there eh and no one had been in at all cos there's the ground was freshly covered in snow so I walked straight down to the waterfront and I was setting up my my tripod and a few other things and this robin came and landed on the wall we <unclear/> had my bag so right close by this point I'd had the camera out and it was probably about as close as we are across this table that's how close it was so I kinda stopped stayed still and <unclear>not</unclear> to make any movements in case it did <unclear/> managed to take a couple of pictures and then eventually flew away it was <unclear/></u>
<u n="49" who="S0420">that that one that you posted is that as it was or did have you edited it?</u>
<u n="50" who="S0367">no we have that one actually posted I went after it initially taking the the pictures when it first flew up took other pictures then headed off visited a few other places and about four hours later when I was leaving I nipped back into the same car park</u>
<u n="51" who="S0420">to look for the same robin <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="52" who="S0367">no well not not for the same robin but just to get a couple of other pictures cos although I'd been down there before the way the weather was going the wind was er quite strong it was blowing the clouds so it was changing kinda how looked from when I was there in the morning but at this point there were two or three other folk out with their cameras at the same spot so went down to the same spot again and the robin it actually ended up being</u>
<u n="53" who="S0420" trans="overlap">so he was posing for the photos basically</u>
<u n="54" who="S0367">well it turned out there were actually two robins the the one that came up to me first the second time I was there taking a few pictures and that's the pictures that you saw so there's been the only editing that I've done was just kind of increased exposure just to give it a bit more light with the rest of it it's <trunc>no</trunc>nothing's been done all I've done is</u>
<u n="55" who="S0420" trans="overlap">the the colours are really rich and and and what do <unclear/> fur? er no feathers feathers haven't they yeah</u>
<u n="56" who="S0367">eh so all I did was crop the picture to get it closer eh to the robin and gave it a bit more exposure just to brighten it up but nothing else has been done to the picture but whilst I was there that flew away the robin which I thought was the same one came back so I've taken a couple of other pictures but it was only when I went home and was doing editing that I discovered that the second one is a different one because it was missing</u>
<u n="57" who="S0420" trans="overlap"><unclear/> it was different</u>
<u n="58" who="S0367">no it was missing one or two of its red feathers</u>
<u n="59" who="S0420">ah</u>
<u n="60" who="S0367">so it was like it had either caught it on something or had been attacked</u>
<u n="61" who="S0420">ah okay</u>
<u n="62" who="S0367">so I had kind of like a a grey patch in the middle where red feathers should have been so it so it turned out it was two but there must have either been eh friendly cos they were coming so close to you</u>
<u n="63" who="S0420">so they were used to people being at that so it's a car park so they're used to</u>
<u n="64" who="S0367" trans="overlap">well it's a car park</u>
<u n="65" who="S0420">noise and cars and people and stuff</u>
<u n="66" who="S0367">yeah the only other thing I can think of is with the weather being so bad is maybe the lack of food and maybe <unclear>they</unclear> were just chancers thinking that we'd leave something but</u>
<u n="67" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah <unclear/> maybe sitting on the bonnet of a car engine that's been running for a while <vocal desc="laugh"/> that's nice and toasty on your feet if you're a cold robin oh very good</u>
<u n="68" who="S0367">yeah no that so that I got that at the start and at the end on the way home before heading off so it was a good day</u>
<u n="69" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah and then so what other set of pictures did you get?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0367">well remember we went and walked erm Ben Vorlich</u>
<u n="71" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="72" who="S0367">and we parked at the side of Loch Erne</u>
<u n="73" who="S0420">yeah yeah beside the camp site</u>
<u n="74" who="S0367">beside the campsite now the opposite shore erm you go through Lochearnhead and further along and there's another wee kind of car park so park there so it was overlooking Ben Vorlich climbs so you could see right up the the kind of valley that <unclear>started</unclear> off in so one minute you could see the hill two minutes later it was absolutely covered with a white cloud eh snow</u>
<u n="75" who="S0420">yeah well it changes so fast there I mean we've experienced that as well didn't we?</u>
<u n="76" who="S0367">yeah so I went down to the shoreline on opposite side just set up the camera and just kinda stood there for about half an hour watching the kinda wind change the landscape so I've got a few of those pictures that they're going onto the website today so you'll see them tonight er it's actually surprising although we climbed it and got to the top so that when you see it from the other side of the loch actually how steep and big the hill is</u>
<u n="77" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah I didn't really feel it when we were walking up</u>
<u n="78" who="S0367">no</u>
<u n="79" who="S0420">it was just that last little</u>
<u n="80" who="S0367">the last <unclear/></u>
<u n="81" who="S0420" trans="overlap">twenty metres or fifty metres or something</u>
<u n="82" who="S0367">plus the fact on the day we climbed it's once you got to a certain level they lost sight of everything because of the mist</u>
<u n="83" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="84" who="S0367">so it doesn't give you that</u>
<u n="85" who="S0420" trans="overlap">you don't get the full effect</u>
<u n="86" who="S0367">the full effect but seeing it from a different angle</u>
<u n="87" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="88" who="S0367">full of snow eh it was pretty big pretty impressive so eh we'll still need to go back next year and do the next next one that we managed not to do</u>
<u n="89" who="S0420">well we we need to do the three hills in one day but <vocal desc="laugh"/> in a twenty-four hour period that's that's the ultimate challenge</u>
<u n="90" who="S0367">ah the what was that? is that Snowdonia?</u>
<u n="91" who="S0420">Snowdonia <trunc>Scaf</trunc> is it Scafells Pike or something like that?</u>
<u n="92" who="S0367">oh in the Lake District? no in the Yorkshire Dales?</u>
<u n="93" who="S0420">some or or the Peak <trunc>Di</trunc> I don't know</u>
<u n="94" who="S0367" trans="overlap">Peak District</u>
<u n="95" who="S0420">I don't know and then er</u>
<u n="96" who="S0367" trans="overlap">Ben Nevis</u>
<u n="97" who="S0420">and Ben Nevis in one day but that would be something to document in a like a photography project as well wouldn't it?</u>
<u n="98" who="S0367">thing is you could I think you'd be better starting off at you'd be better starting off at Snowdonia starting off in the morning there cos what I've known some folk <unclear>although</unclear> in saying that it's twenty-four hours you've gotta climb all three</u>
<u n="99" who="S0420" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="100" who="S0367">so you couldn't start on the top camp overnight at the top of Snowdonia</u>
<u n="101" who="S0420" trans="overlap">no no you've gotta climb all three of them in twenty-four hours but erm yeah like you say that would be some photo project like a big you know one of these coffee table books or something</u>
<u n="102" who="S0367">yeah eh especially <vocal desc="laugh"/> I'd hate to imagine all the the rubbish strewn over someone's car in between journeys</u>
<u n="103" who="S0420">I know <unclear>half</unclear> eaten Mars bars and Lucozade <vocal desc="laugh"/> to get</u>
<u n="104" who="S0367"><unclear/> in their pool <vocal desc="laugh"/> but no I think I think be able to do that I dunno when you mentioned it someone started to eh Ben Nevis</u>
<u n="105" who="S0420">yeah</u>
<u n="106" who="S0367">I think you would be better starting the other way start at Snowdonia then do the one in England and with the light in summer</u>
<u n="107" who="S0420">oh yeah</u>
<u n="108" who="S0367">cos you'll then</u>
<u n="109" who="S0420"><unclear/></u>
<u n="110" who="S0367">then do the Ben Nevis</u>
<u n="111" who="S0420">okay</u>
<u n="112" who="S0367">eh</u>
	
	</body>
</text>
