<text id="ST39">
	<header>
		<rec_length>0:11:16</rec_length>
		<rec_date>2014-09-10</rec_date>
		<rec_year>2014</rec_year>
		<rec_period>2014_Q3</rec_period>
		<n_speakers>2</n_speakers>
		<list_speakers>S0202 S0208</list_speakers>
		<rec_loc>Home, Leeds</rec_loc>
		<relationships>Close family, partners, very close friends</relationships>
		<topics>Work, Body Hair, Shaving</topics>
		<activity>General chit chat</activity>
		<conv_type>Discussing</conv_type>
		<conventions>Revised</conventions>
		<in_sample>y</in_sample>
		<transcriber>T10</transcriber>
		<speakerInfo>
			<speaker id="S0202">
				<exactage>23</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Doncaster, Yorkshire</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Yorkshire</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>north</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>yorkshire</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls></fls>
				<in_core>n</in_core>
			</speaker>
			<speaker id="S0208">
				<exactage>19</exactage>
				<age1994>15_24</age1994>
				<agerange>19_29</agerange>
				<gender>F</gender>
				<nat>British</nat>
				<birthplace>Cambridge</birthplace>
				<birthcountry>England</birthcountry>
				<l1>English</l1>
				<lingorig>England</lingorig>
				<dialect_rep>Cambridge</dialect_rep>
				<hab_city>Leeds, Yorkshire</hab_city>
				<hab_country>England</hab_country>
				<hab_dur>2</hab_dur>
				<dialect_l1>uk</dialect_l1>
				<dialect_l2>england</dialect_l2>
				<dialect_l3>south</dialect_l3>
				<dialect_l4>eastern_engl</dialect_l4>
				<edqual>3_sixthform</edqual>
				<occupation>Student</occupation>
				<socgrade>E</socgrade>
				<nssec>uncat</nssec>
				<l2></l2>
				<fls>French -- advanced</fls>
				<in_core>y</in_core>
			</speaker>
		</speakerInfo>
	</header>
	<body>

<u n="1" who="S0208">like just</u>
<u n="2" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="3" who="S0208">and there was another guy that works there <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> he's really nice and <pause dur="long"/> like back when I was doing <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s job and I had to run around and stuff <pause dur="short"/> because I work a little bit faster than <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> I would literally have hours where I would be doing nothing cos I'd have to wait for someone to finish something else for me to do something</u>
<u n="4" who="S0202" trans="overlap">do your part</u>
<u n="5" who="S0208">yeah erm and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> used to clean the terraces so like we'd always take our cigarette break and we'd go into the Wendy house and once he saw me and I was just sitting down on my phone and he was like and I got really panicked cos he opened the door and was like what are you doing? and I was really scared that it was like <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> or <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> or someone like coming to shout at me because I was just sitting there</u>
<u n="6" who="S0202">doing nothing <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="7" who="S0208">but it was him and he was like oh I'm just joking so we used to take this was like two years ago and we used to just sit there for half an hour in the Wendy house just chatting and have a cigarette <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="8" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="9" who="S0208">hide ourselves away</u>
<u n="10" who="S0202">you had nothing better to do <pause dur="long"/> such a nice day I wish them clouds would fuck off</u>
<u n="11" who="S0208">yeah cos it is nice it's just not lounging round the pool kind of nice</u>
<u n="12" who="S0202">no</u>
<u n="13" who="S0208">not really warm enough when you're wet to just lie there <pause dur="short"/> chilling</u>
<u n="14" who="S0202">oh sorry look at my bloody armpits</u>
<u n="15" who="S0208">oh wow</u>
<u n="16" who="S0202">only shaved them other day like <trunc>yes</trunc> the day before</u>
<u n="17" who="S0208">I can tell you were German <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="18" who="S0202">I know it's ridiculous innit? <pause dur="short"/> and my legs look how hairy they are</u>
<u n="19" who="S0208">I know mine as well though</u>
<u n="20" who="S0202">but I like shaved them two days ago</u>
<u n="21" who="S0208">they're slightly finer but you can still tell they're brown</u>
<u n="22" who="S0202">mm <pause dur="long"/> really pisses me off</u>
<u n="23" who="S0208">alright what film do you want to watch?</u>
<u n="24" who="S0202">I don't know <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="25" who="S0208">how about Snow White?</u>
<u n="26" who="S0202">I really fancy watching erm a Disney film <pause dur="short"/> but not Snow White</u>
<u n="27" who="S0208">okay <trunc>li</trunc> well let's go through what we haven't seen I watched Sleeping Beauty the other night when I was baby sitting</u>
<u n="28" who="S0202">we can watch Ariel you were wanting to watch that the other day</u>
<u n="29" who="S0208" trans="overlap">oh yes let's watch The Little Mermaid</u>
<u n="30" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="31" who="S0208">yes yes</u>
<u n="32" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="33" who="S0208">I'm okay with that</u>
<u n="34" who="S0202">so much excitement</u>
<u n="35" who="S0208">I really love I'm not a fan of sequels when it comes to Disney like Cinderella like my mum bless her when I was going through my I want to collect Disney film stage because my dad threw away all my videos when we moved in</u>
<u n="36" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="37" who="S0208">I was so angry cos I still have a working video player</u>
<u n="38" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="39" who="S0208">but he didn't know so he was like oh this is just gonna go to the dump and I was literally like my childhood was in that box</u>
<u n="40" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="41" who="S0208">and erm and so my mum bless her every time she found a Disney DVD or something she'd bring it back for me</u>
<u n="42" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="43" who="S0208" trans="overlap">which was so sweet and she bought Cinderella back one day but because it was French she didn't know that it wasn't the right one and it turned out to be the sequel</u>
<u n="44" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="45" who="S0208">and it's called A Cinderella Story</u>
<u n="46" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="47" who="S0208">but it's actually the next film and it's her when she is already married to the prince and she was moved in and it's like shenanigans with her and the animals and stuff it was shit</u>
<u n="48" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> but</u>
<u n="49" who="S0208">but The Little Mermaid II is fantastic</u>
<u n="50" who="S0202">I've never seen it</u>
<u n="51" who="S0208">so we should watch the first one and then the second one</u>
<u n="52" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="53" who="S0208">it's about her daughter</u>
<u n="54" who="S0202">oh right</u>
<u n="55" who="S0208">but it's it's genuinely really good like er well I used to watch it when I was younger so I don't know if it's still good but <pause dur="short"/> I really liked it</u>
<u n="56" who="S0202">yeah we'll watch that then</u>
<u n="57" who="S0208">it's like a Disney film in itself <pause dur="short"/> so that was good right there we go we've got the next few hours sorted</u>
<u n="58" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/> next few hours of doing absolutely fuck all <vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="59" who="S0208">I am gonna get in touch with <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> later though and erm tell her that I'm <trunc>g</trunc> about to book a train and tell her what time and stuff</u>
<u n="60" who="S0202">yeah oh</u>
<u n="61" who="S0208" trans="overlap">so she can book the same one</u>
<u n="62" who="S0202">are you coming to <anon type="miscPersonalInfo"/>? it's ten pound a ticket and er do you know the one that were <trunc>o</trunc>on last year?</u>
<u n="63" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="64" who="S0202">the final game where everyone just goes and gets pissed?</u>
<u n="65" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="66" who="S0202">do you wanna go to er to it? me and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> are definitely going</u>
<u n="67" who="S0208">sure</u>
<u n="68" who="S0202" trans="overlap">we're buying tickets tonight so I'll buy yours at the same time</u>
<u n="69" who="S0208" trans="overlap">how much is? thanks yeah <trunc>wh</trunc>what date?</u>
<u n="70" who="S0202">I don't know but it's ten pound</u>
<u n="71" who="S0208">okay</u>
<u n="72" who="S0202">it's nothing</u>
<u n="73" who="S0208">we can always sell it on if we can't go</u>
<u n="74" who="S0202">yeah but it was sold out last year that's why I'm buying them early</u>
<u n="75" who="S0208">yeah sure well I'd really like that thank you I'll give you the money back</u>
<u n="76" who="S0202">yeah don't worry about it</u>
<u n="77" who="S0208">let you book it all in one go though cos it's easier and</u>
<u n="78" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="79" who="S0208" trans="overlap">at least you know you've got it</u>
<u n="80" who="S0202">yeah erm</u>
<u n="81" who="S0208">I've given up on getting the Bombay Bicycle Club because erm there's a there was a concert in London and the first time <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> came over she told me about it and her and <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> were going and they she invited me erm it's like in December but it's roughly the time where I went back to <trunc>Englan</trunc> er France last year</u>
<u n="82" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="83" who="S0208">so it was kind of perfect timing cos then I could go from her house to the airport</u>
<u n="84" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="85" who="S0208">so I said yeah I'll get on that <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> a few weeks later when she came back she was like have you bought it yet? and I was like nope</u>
<u n="86" who="UNKMULTI"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="87" who="S0208">and I still haven't and it's definitely gonna be sold out</u>
<u n="88" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="89" who="S0208">erm <pause dur="short"/> but it was only thirty pound which is it <vocal desc="sigh"/> so stupid of me like I always do that and regret it <pause dur="short"/> just from laziness</u>
<u n="90" who="S0202">mm</u>
<u n="91" who="S0208">would have taken me five minutes on the computer and I just didn't do it</u>
<u n="92" who="S0202">oh well they might not have sold out</u>
<u n="93" who="S0208">but hey like it will save a lot of money cos it might just be thirty pound for that but</u>
<u n="94" who="S0202">the drinks inside</u>
<u n="95" who="S0208" trans="overlap">plus drinks</u>
<u n="96" who="S0202" trans="overlap">gigs are fucking so expensive</u>
<u n="97" who="S0208">plus I'd I'd go down for the weekend so that's my train tickets whereas and a train ticket to get from her house to Stansted whereas if I go to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> then I know that I get a free lift so</u>
<u n="98" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="99" who="S0208">I need to ring <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> as well to know if they can pick me up from the airport <pause dur="short"/> erm <pause dur="short"/> I'm sure <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> will be able to if she's not working but <pause dur="short"/> I've sort of booked my flight to Stansted and I've left all my stuff there and I just assumed that they could get me but</u>
<u n="100" who="S0202" trans="overlap">yeah</u>
<u n="101" who="S0208">I need to ask them</u>
<u n="102" who="S0202">they will be able to get you</u>
<u n="103" who="S0208">I'm sure</u>
<u n="104" who="S0202">they'll arrange it <pause dur="short"/> they've got a few weeks' notice anyway so</u>
<u n="105" who="S0208">yeah yeah I'm gonna ring them later but I won't ring during the day cos no one'll be there anyway <pause dur="short"/> so I'll do that this evening and once I've spoken to them I'll book my train ticket so that I know for sure if I need to get <pause dur="short"/> the train from hers to London I'll get on the day that's never expensive</u>
<u n="106" who="S0202">well why doesn't she just like <pause dur="short"/> why don't she just meet you instead of you going down to come back up why don't she come up and then you go from there?</u>
<u n="107" who="S0208">well cos I'm flying into Stansted anyway</u>
<u n="108" who="S0202">I know but you're going to <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s for night aren't you?</u>
<u n="109" who="S0208">yeah but from Stansted it's like a thirty-five forty minute drive</u>
<u n="110" who="S0202">right</u>
<u n="111" who="S0208">so they usually pick me up I stay there for a night and I get to see <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> and see them</u>
<u n="112" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="113" who="S0208">and then from her house station like ten minutes away from hers</u>
<u n="114" who="S0202" trans="overlap">no but that's</u>
<u n="115" who="S0208">and then I go from there</u>
<u n="116" who="S0202">but that's what I mean like why doesn't <anon type="name" nameType="f"/> just meet you</u>
<u n="117" who="S0208" trans="overlap">to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="118" who="S0202">in a train station in <anon type="place"/> or wherever it is?</u>
<u n="119" who="S0208">erm because <pause dur="short"/> it's just more difficult because from <anon type="place"/> it's a direct train to <anon type="place"/></u>
<u n="120" who="S0202">okay</u>
<u n="121" who="S0208">whereas from <anon type="name" nameType="f"/>'s I can't get a direct one I'd have to stop anyway</u>
<u n="122" who="S0202">oh right and change</u>
<u n="123" who="S0208" trans="overlap">so yeah so rather than go to <anon type="place"/> and change for example if I just go to <anon type="place"/> straight away and come up with her</u>
<u n="124" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="125" who="S0208">because she'll have to get two trains whereas in <pause dur="short"/> it would stop at <anon type="place"/> er whereas like I would be going to <anon type="place"/> anyway probably do you see what I mean?</u>
<u n="126" who="S0202">yeah yeah yeah</u>
<u n="127" who="S0208">so it's just much easier for me to be the one that makes that little extra trip rather than her <pause dur="short"/> because her one would be direct anyway</u>
<u n="128" who="S0202">yeah <pause dur="short"/> I've got so much stuff to do when I get home got to go into uni and speak to the careers adviser like get a proper meeting booked cos she only showed me how to use the website when I went in</u>
<u n="129" who="S0208">mm</u>
<u n="130" who="S0202">like I was like this is not helping me like you're not answering any of my questions she was like well you need to book in for a proper appointment then I says well put book me in now are you busy? er no but er no it's like well why can't you book me in now I'm here? like I had to limp all the way round campus cos all the middle of campus had been closed off</u>
<u n="131" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="132" who="S0202">and my crutches I'd like <trunc>l</trunc> and I had to carry all these books it was a nightmare</u>
<u n="133" who="S0208">oh</u>
<u n="134" who="S0202">cos I'd had a meeting booked in with my personal tutor who was fucking shit by the way he does not have a clue about anything like every time I asked him a question he goes onto his computer and looks on the internet it's like I could have fucking done that at home</u>
<u n="135" who="S0208">yeah you need to change personal tutor</u>
<u n="136" who="S0202">like he's really shit he doesn't know anything</u>
<u n="137" who="S0208">I'm gonna give my personal tutor one last chance because he has got a lot of good contacts and bless him he has tried because he sees that I'm interested in the exact same field he is</u>
<u n="138" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="139" who="S0208">but I think cos I was a first year and all of that he pays more attention to</u>
<u n="140" who="S0202">the second years and stuff</u>
<u n="141" who="S0208" trans="overlap">the older people</u>
<u n="142" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="143" who="S0208">so I'm gonna give him more of a chance and actually make more of an effort to make meetings with him cos let's face it it's not it's not his job to chase me</u>
<u n="144" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="145" who="S0208">he's got so many students to care for</u>
<u n="146" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="147" who="S0208">erm and I'm gonna give him one last chance and if that doesn't work out well then I'm gonna go and change to someone else</u>
<u n="148" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="149" who="S0208">but I'm gonna</u>
<u n="150" who="S0202" trans="overlap">well like</u>
<u n="151" who="S0208" trans="overlap">give him a chance</u>
<u n="152" who="S0202" trans="overlap">my <trunc>ex</trunc> my experience of <anon type="place"/> so far has been so shit as a university like <pause dur="short"/> I didn't know that you had until thirtieth of May to change degree discipline no one no one tells you that like you don't have</u>
<u n="153" who="S0208" trans="overlap">no</u>
<u n="154" who="S0202">like and stuff like that I mean</u>
<u n="155" who="S0208">but to honest I think it's the same everywhere cos it's like once you get to university it's like you're an adult you have to do it yourself sort of thing</u>
<u n="156" who="S0202" trans="overlap">you're on your own yeah</u>
<u n="157" who="S0208">it's like we're saying our experience with <anon type="place"/> is shit but had we been somewhere else it would probably be very much the same</u>
<u n="158" who="S0202" trans="overlap">mm but I just expected like better communication</u>
<u n="159" who="S0208">yeah</u>
<u n="160" who="S0202">that's was all like</u>
<u n="161" who="S0208">no yeah I <trunc>a</trunc> I completely agree <pause dur="short"/> not defending it</u>
<u n="162" who="S0202">no</u>
<u n="163" who="S0208">I thought it was pretty shit as well had lots of problems like choosing my modules and stuff</u>
<u n="164" who="S0202">I mean they were really good with you when that happened with your sister though weren't they like</u>
<u n="165" who="S0208">yeah I mean <trunc>a</trunc></u>
<u n="166" who="S0202" trans="overlap">really really good</u>
<u n="167" who="S0208" trans="overlap">amazing and that woman <pause dur="short"/> brilliant <pause dur="short"/> I still haven't sent her the erm <pause dur="short"/> well actually no that's not true my dad wrote a letter so that's <pause dur="short"/> fine cos she wanted a doctor's thing or a note from my parents like just to</u>
<u n="168" who="S0202">yeah verify</u>
<u n="169" who="S0208" trans="overlap">justify it I was like I'm not gonna get a note off off of a doctor like that's impossible</u>
<u n="170" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="171" who="S0208">cos I was only back from <anon type="place"/> then so I was like that's just not not feasible</u>
<u n="172" who="S0202" trans="overlap">it's not gonna happen it's not gonna happen if you did</u>
<u n="173" who="S0208">so she was like oh that's fine then a note from your parents so I got my dad to write one <pause dur="short"/> in block capitals as well so that she could read it <pause dur="short"/> because his writing is atrocious</u>
<u n="174" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="175" who="S0208">it's worse than my mum's my mum</u>
<u n="176" who="S0202" trans="overlap">why didn't you just write it and then get him to sign it?</u>
<u n="177" who="S0208">I could have but kind of looks better</u>
<u n="178" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="179" who="S0208">I could always forge a signature <pause dur="short"/> I do a lot actually my dad's it's really easy to forge</u>
<u n="180" who="S0202">my my mum's is as well</u>
<u n="181" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="182" who="S0202">and <anon type="name" nameType="m"/>'s is his is just <anon type="name" nameType="m"/> <pause dur="short"/> that's it</u>
<u n="183" who="S0208">my one's I know my one's really bad I'm gonna have to change it cos it's just the A and an R</u>
<u n="184" who="S0202">well mine's just a A and a squiggle that's it</u>
<u n="185" who="S0208" trans="overlap">yeah and it's</u>
<u n="186" who="S0202">like anyone could do that</u>
<u n="187" who="S0208">it's like that with an R</u>
<u n="188" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="189" who="S0208">but I I reckon I'm gonna add <anon type="name" nameType="n"/> onto it and it's gonna look a lot like my dad's cos his is so easy he does that with an H and then de de de de de and then a line for the D</u>
<u n="190" who="S0202">yeah</u>
<u n="191" who="S0208">so it's actually just H de de de de de line D</u>
<u n="192" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="193" who="S0208">but my mum's writing genuinely looks like Arabic</u>
<u n="194" who="S0202">really?</u>
<u n="195" who="S0208">have you ever seen it?</u>
<u n="196" who="S0202">no</u>
<u n="197" who="S0208">come to the office my child I shall show you</u>
<u n="198" who="S0202">oh do we have to go right now?</u>
<u n="199" who="S0208">yes</u>
<u n="200" who="S0202">okay</u>
<u n="201" who="S0208">yes we do it's of upmost importance <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="202" who="S0202">I think I saw a note once that <trunc>sh</trunc> that you snapped at you know when she she were telling you about the condom situation</u>
<u n="203" who="S0208"><vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="short"/> her writing though <pause dur="short"/> it does look like Arabic the swirls and the dots and stuff it's ridiculous my dad's like I can't physically even read any of that and this is her when she's writing good I mean</u>
<u n="204" who="S0202">how do you understand any of that? it's so small</u>
<u n="205" who="S0208">I don't <vocal desc="laugh"/> <pause dur="long"/> it's just <pause dur="long"/></u>
<u n="206" who="S0202"><vocal desc="laugh"/></u>
<u n="207" who="S0208" trans="overlap">ridiculous I mean <vocal desc="sigh"/></u>
<u n="208" who="S0202">she's a special woman <pause dur="short"/> again the use of special</u>
<u n="209" who="S0208">you need to use that</u>
<event desc="abrupt end"/>
	
	</body>
</text>
